<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject2621</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Silly cat sits like he's people</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-19 16:11:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I attend the Brisbane, Aus zombie walk every year. My 2013 costume was inspired by recent events in the US</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-06 13:53:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-06 15:05:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>That dry, powdery texture when you get a substance like chalk on your hands. It makes me feel like my skin will shrivel up and fall off. Just thinking about it makes me compelled to reach for some lotion!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-06 15:36:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>"What part of Canada are you from?" I live in Australia and get this questions nearly every time I meet someone new.. except I'm American. I realise Aussie are worried about offending Canadians by calling them American but sometimes the reverse is also true! Replace "Canada/America" with "North America" and the problem goes away.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-06 15:55:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or I can meet you half way and show you last year's American themed costume. http://i.imgur.com/gDpDL9o.jpg?1</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-06 16:09:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm an American but I'll be eligible to take the Aussie citizenship test in a few months (fingers crossed!). I look forward to the day when I can vote against the Australian Liberal Party.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-06 16:25:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Brisbane Zombie Walk raises money for the Australian Brain Foundation, which researches neurological disorders, brain cancer etc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-06 17:25:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a neuroscientist. I'm currently in the Morten electorate but I've moved 7 times in the past 7 years.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-06 18:03:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Zombies are already dead.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-06 18:06:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me last year (also American theme) http://i.imgur.com/gDpDL9o.jpg?1</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-10 17:11:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>It would be a miracle if I could be content with my long term relationships instead of always searching for greener pastures. Nothing in my life is ever good enough.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-10 17:17:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I don't have the aisle seat and have to climb over people to use the bathroom. I have a tiny girl bladder.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-11 07:45:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Midday exercise. I either go for a quick, high intensity run or spend my lunch hour at the gym. The resulting adrenalin rush keeps me energized for the rest of the day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-16 15:58:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've never had a migraine headache.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-17 12:14:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not all symbiotic microbes with the ability to influence the brain on their host are parasitic. There are also examples of commensal and mutualistic organisms (like common gut flora) which do the same. The parasites get a lot of attention because they're freakin' creepy!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-17 22:25:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Never truly being happy or satisfied with what I have. The grass is always greener.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-18 07:00:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh man, I can very much relate to this except my model organism is Drosophila. At least you can squish flies when when they piss you off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-18 12:24:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Berries, oats, honey, and nuts or seeds on top of natural Greek yoghurt. The yoghurt and nuts provide protein while the oats are a source good source of long lasting, slow release energy. The berries and honey are full of good sugars and antioxidants. I also devour raw baby carrots dipped in hummus!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-18 15:33:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I occasionally make my own. It's healthier than store bought hummus.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-18 16:01:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>We already know that many of these parasites alter host behaviour by manipulating neurotransmitters or via manipulation of neural proteins that regulate the brain. In the case of T. gondii, it encodes an enzyme called tyrosine hydroxylase which is the rate limiting enzyme that converts tyrosine to L-Dopa (which later is converted to the very important neurotransmitter Dopamine). Source: Myself - I'm a neurobiologist that specialises in symbionts that manipulate the brain and behaviour of their host.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-19 17:08:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Sacrifice](http://youtube.com/watch?v=x8GTrmXn84c) - Lisa Gerrard  amp; Pieter Bourke After more than a decade it still sends shivers down my spine but I would love to again experience the soul shattering moment of hearing it for the first time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-19 17:18:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>That there is a strong possibility that humans are contributing to climate change which may have irreversible and devastating effects in the near future. You would hope that they would take this information and use it to build a more sustainable society before it gets too far out of hand.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-20 01:41:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I graduated with a degree in Biomedical Science with the intention of going straight into research. I quickly took a position as a manager in a research animal facility in hopes that I'd eventually be able to transfer into a lab. It was a terrible, depressing job and it didn't take me long to realise that anyone who wants to do hardcore research needs graduate qualifications (there is almost no point in going into research without having at least a masters). I started my graduate degree 4 months later.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-20 01:46:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Michigan is gorgeous and a lovely place to grow up. Detroit, a city which only makes up a small area of the state, has a bad reputation but there are parts of it that are quite nice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-20 01:49:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Accept it and focus on the aspects of your marriage that are actually important.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-24 23:48:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wolbachia is rapidly becoming the magic bullet for bio-control.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-25 16:46:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have memorized the majority of the [main metabolic pathways](http://i.imgur.com/hbHh8c9.jpg?1), understand how they interact, and their biological functionS. Although it's been over 4 years since I've started and I'm still learning.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-27 12:23:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>[The Last Unicon!](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Last_Unicorn_%28film%29)! I'm going to a "childhood characters" themed Halloween party tomorrow and I'm dressing as Lady Amalthea, the unicorn's human form. Unfortunately most of the people there are 90's babies and won't get the reference.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-27 16:22:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a research scientist, [this.](http://i.imgur.com/1BepyoE.jpg?1) People assume that any experiment is possible (and will work without problems!) as long as you follow the scientific method exactly how it was taught in 10th grade Biology.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-27 16:29:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone who is super tidy. I'm really messy so I figure we'll just cancel each other out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-27 16:51:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>He'll... But exactly!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-28 07:18:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only if we end up on Hoarders.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-28 22:11:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I live in Brisbane, Australia. WORST drivers in the country. When it rains, even just a little, I seriously fear for my safety.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-31 14:01:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>A fellow accidentally ingested some alpha-L-glucose and discovered that he had no ill effect. Apparently he was ambidextrose.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-05 09:09:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's amazing how much this area of research has exploded over the last few years. The long-held dogma of medical science has been that disease and disorders are determined by the complex interplay between genetics and the surrounding environment. It's now becoming blindly obvious that mutulistic microbial symbionts, which we have evolved with over thousands of years, are a third essential determinant. I'm currently looking at how specific species of gut bacteria influence neurotransmitter biosynthesis and consequently complex behaviours like sleep and attention. It's fascinating.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-05 21:50:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've already mentioned this in a related conversation but this area of science has exploded over the last few years. The long-held dogma of medical science has been that disease and disorders are determined by the complex interplay between genetics and the surrounding environment, however it's now becoming blindly obvious that mutulistic microbial symbionts, which we have evolved with over thousands of years, are a third essential determinant. Currently researchers around the globe are determining this by running complex experiments that involve altering common species of gut bacteria. This can be done by removing the gut microbiome completely, removing specific strains, or adding specific stains. The resulting phenotype alterations are extensive and diverse. Some work has even shown that removing essential gut flora can have large impact on fetal development. We also know that altering these microbes can have a direct influence how genes are activated and expressed. Work like this is highly suggestive that our resident microbes play an essential role in our biology.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-09 07:38:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oats and other similar foods contain a molecule called beta-glucan. Essentially it helps to reduce LDL cholesterol by binding to it in the intestinal tract, forcing the cholesterol to be excreted as waste instead of being absorbed. The exact molecular/biochemical mechanism on how this occurs isn't completely understood.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-18 13:45:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. Remove the brain in PBS under a dissecting microscope.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-18 13:59:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>When you can truly put yourself second in order to make the other person happy. It is a complete removal of selfishness.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-20 21:46:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>This should be a required topic in high school or early undergrad, but unfortunately this is almost never the case. It's shocking how few people are capable of proper critical analysis.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-02 14:30:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a bottle of several thousand dead fruit flies in my fridge because I was too lazy to transfer them from one of my labs to the other (my house in in between).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-03 05:19:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why thank you :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Booty enjoys a good stretch</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-04 15:04:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Australian scientists discover zinc can  #8216;starve #8217; one of the world #8217;s most deadly microbes responsible for serious infectious diseases like pneumonia.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-08 09:57:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A new study published in Nature demonstrates that not all living creatures, including both short and long-lived organisms, experience age related deterioration.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-09 14:32:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dollar Bills Y'all!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-15 10:36:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-15 11:51:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nuit Blanche: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JVuUwvUUPro Brings me close to tears every single time..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>For the first time ever, scientist have synthesized an entire protein hormone in a testube from scratch</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-15 21:28:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Meet Gus! He's a super goofy shelter puppy I'm fostering over the holidays!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-18 06:34:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-18 06:39:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Up until recently this beautiful 9-month-old boy was on death row but QLD Animal Rescue saved him just in time, and now he's living comfortably until he finds a home. He is one of the happiest, cutest dogs I've ever met and I know he'll bring tons of joy to someone someday!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Researchers in Australia believe they have solved the mystery of why zebras evolved with stripes</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-19 05:29:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-22 15:17:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Onomatopoeia. So satisfying to say and the types of words it defines are fantastic. Sizzle... fizz... zip!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-01 07:22:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>At the end of the year I'll submit my thesis and hopefully be granted my PhD. I have no idea how I'll fill the void in 2015 because I wrongly base my happiness on personal achievements.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-01 07:27:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>For some reason I waited 1.5 months after my 21st birthday to have a drink. Interestingly, it took place on a Jamaican party boat during a sunset cruise. I was one of maybe three Americans, the rest were Aussies. Ain't nobody can peer pressure you to drink like an Australian! Needless to say the rum was plentiful and the booty shaking was reckless. Good time though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It's currently 43 #176;C (109 #176;F) in Queensland, Australia. I just witnessed this guy walking down the street</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-04 06:25:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Scientists have found that honeybees use the pattern of polarised light in the sky invisible to humans to direct one another to a honey source.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-06 04:40:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-06 21:48:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>This research determined which neurons were activated during navigation via polarized light.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-12 17:03:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't just memorize the material, really try to understand it and how it relates and integrates with other concepts. You'll be less likely to forget later in the semester or in future courses.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-20 08:18:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>A Silver Mt. Zion - [13 Angels Standing Guard 'Round the Side of Your Bed](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hQZfGa5t4e8)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Not sure if offer of love or act of revenge</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-22 07:06:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-22 13:03:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yup, it's a skink. My kitty was depressed all day because I took it away.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-23 17:53:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Symbiotic microoranisms that have evolved to manipulate their host in order to secure their own propagation and survival. [Example](http://www.newscientist.com/article/dn7927-parasites-brainwash-grasshoppers-into-death-dive.html#.UuFIvBA_7IU)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-23 18:00:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go to your nearest university and start sitting in on lectures. You might come across a topic that peaks you interest, which could eventually, with time, turn into a passion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Daytime sleep can radially alter the expression of genes essential for controlling circadian rhythm (the body's internal clock).</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-24 01:45:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-02 18:50:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Elbow - Starlings.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KGegmMWsgu8) "You are the only thing in any room you're ever in" Brilliant lyrics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Boys are more likely to be diagnosed with neurodevelopmental disorders, such as autism, because girls need more extreme genetic mutations to develop them, according to a study published in the American Journal of Human Genetics.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-27 23:46:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The New York Times reports on Drosophila research which suggests that male fruit flies forced into monogamy for several generations have reduced ability to learn. This indicates that struggling to find a mate may be an evolutionary advantage.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-28 00:05:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>One of the most common bacteria on earth, Wolbachia, which naturally infects roughly 40% of all insect species, has the ability to block transmission of some mosquito borne diseases such as dengue fever.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-03 05:22:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The largest clinical study ever conducted to date of patients with advanced leukaemia found that a staggering 88% achieved full remission after being treated with genetically modified versions of their own immune cells.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-10 02:18:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ima just leave my foots here</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-20 00:14:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-23 16:47:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was born on the day [We Are The World](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=M9BNoNFKCBI) went number one on the charts. Christ I feel old...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>An international study led by The University of Queensland has tracked a potentially devastating multi-drug resistant E. coli strain that is only one gene away from being resistant to almost all antibiotics.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-01 11:21:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-15 14:40:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's handy! Which uni are you at if you don't mind me asking?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-28 11:11:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm saying that the typical standard of teaching in government funded schools, which is almost completely based on test scores, kills passion and eagerness to learn.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-28 11:14:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not quite. I'm about a yearfrom finishing my PhD. A post doctoral fellowship is the next step though I'm playing with the possibility of moving on to science communication, with special interest in improving education.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>For some people, a fear of something can become a hardcore phobia, resulting in crippling anxiety. An international team of researchers may have found a way to silence the gene that feeds this fear.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-29 22:44:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-30 13:04:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Extinction of classical fear conditioning refers to a reduction in conditional responding after the repeated presentation of a conditioned stimulus (e.g. a tone) in the absence of the unconditioned stimulus (e.g. an electric shock) with which it was previously paired (Chang et al., 2009). Source: http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC2756523/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New research suggests that men raised in countries with higher average lifespans and lower child mortality more strongly prefer women with softer features than do men raised in less healthy nations.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-30 23:19:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Researchers discovered that deep sleep heightens the activity of an immune protein, NF #954;B, essential for fighting off viral and bacterial pathogens. This may help to explain why we experience drastically increased sleep when we're sick.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-08 03:43:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>He'll steal your soul with those eyes</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-15 07:53:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Growth hormone, a protein that regulates how tall people grow, could be used in treating diseases including cancer and diabetes.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-20 13:35:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This is my Great Grandpa, Bill while he was stationed in Egypt during WWI.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-01 11:34:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-01 16:36:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>He lived to the ripe old age of 102 which means I had plenty of time to hear his stories. He lead a truly fascinating life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-02 07:29:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not sure exactly, I'll have to ask my Grandma (his youngest daughter). The British Norfolk Regiment was in the Middle East sometime between 1916-1918.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>In 1983 while my parent's were honeymooning in the Bahamas, my Dad met a European guy that looked suspiciously like a hairy Steve Carell. Dad claims he was too drunk to remember what they were pointing at but we can only assume it was magical.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-16 05:28:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-16 15:57:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's still in amazing shape at 55</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-24 23:15:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>You could invest in laser hair removal. I did 6 IPL treatments on my armpits and nether regions, and now both areas are smooth as silk. Sure, it's a bit pricey but it will save you money in the long run, and you'll start seeing major results after only a few treatments.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-27 17:17:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can do micoinjections to administer drugs in Drosophila without any adverse effects. While I've never heard microdialysis in fruit flies, I don't see why you couldn't optimise it for your specific needs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-27 17:31:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>You could argue that Toxoplasma gondii was likely parasitic in cats before it evolved to become mutulistic. One example of this is that it doesn't cause detrimental effects to it's primary host (cats), but it causes many complex behavioural changes to it's secondary host (rodents). It is thought that these changes in behaviour reduce the rodent #8217;s ability to evade predators, and make it easier for felines to find, capture, and eat the infected prey, allowing the parasite to enter the cat and complete its life-cycle. Additionally there is an example of a very common bacteria that infects invertebrates called Wolbachia. Strains vary from parasitic to mutulistic. Some can interchange between parasitism and mutulism depending on environmental conditions. For example, a parasitic strain on Wolbachia called wMelPop reduces it's host lifespan by up to half. However, it's nearly genetically identical counterpart, wMelCS, has no parasitic phenotype and can assist the host by provisioning metabolites and increasing fecundity, ie the amount of offspring. Source - Myself. I'm a specialist in Microbial Symbiont-Host interactions, especially symbionts that affect the nervous system. Reading - http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC1690701/ http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC23488/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Every time I take a bath, my cat waits patiently by the tub so he can watch the water drain.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-28 03:48:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-28 08:38:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's a flame point Siamese. About 8 months old.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-30 15:25:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>[I bet you can't laugh without smiling](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0xLRQohZtuo) So contagious</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It's finally spring in Australia. Little Alfie has been waiting all winter for this!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-02 06:58:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-14 15:56:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I watched Lost in it's entity in one massive binge sitting, that included many sleepless nights. Those mother f'ing cliffhangers lead to a very poor performance in one of my undergrad semesters. Damn that show!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>His favorite pillow is his brother's butt</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-15 13:48:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-16 00:06:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's a 9 month old, red point Siamese. Super naughty and too smart for his own good!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-16 00:12:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here is a wider shot with both of his brothers http://imgur.com/M8ziB0N</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-16 00:18:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>He sure does! It makes sense though because Siamese was used to create the Cornish breed and it appears they have the same color points.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Alfie thinks he's still small enough to sleep on top of the kitty pile</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 09:07:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[TOMT][Short Story] Woman dies in carriage accident and her fianc #233; believes his constant worrying is the cause.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-14 01:29:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I vaguely remember reading a short story in middle school (18 years ago) about a man who frets over his fianc #233;e's death by carriage on her way home. He believes he caused her death though his constant worrying. My cousin is considering it as a horror story for her 8th grade lit class, but neither of us can recall the title. Multiple google searches have't helped. She needs to read it for appropriateness before presenting it to her students. Help would be very appreciated!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-14 09:13:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Want to get the most out of your workout? Have a shot of espresso 30 minutes - 1 hour prior to hitting the gym. You'll have an amazing boost of energy and you'll notice a big increase in stamina. Of course you should continue drinking plenty of H20 during your session. I find that with caffeine in my system, I can extend my overall workout intensity and time significantly. [Peer reviewed research to back this hack ](http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24901809)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-14 09:22:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Equilibrium](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0238380/?ref_=nm_flmg_act_23) It came out in the midst of the Matrix Trilogy hype and was very overshadowed. Frankly I think it's as good (or slightly better) than the first Matrix but barely anyone I know has seen it! Got to love that gun kata!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-14 11:01:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your body is an ecosystem for a whole bunch of beasties that would totally gross you out. In fact 90% of the cells in the human body are non-human microorganisms. We're also populated with larger multi-cellular microorganisms like mites and worms.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-29 10:24:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>[If You are the One](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NXfsSbDSTgc). It's a Chinese dating show that my best friend (Taiwanese) introduced me to. We mock it relentlessly because the girls are insanely shallow and the men are completely ignorant about attracting women. One time a guy came on and tried to impress the girls with his Ventriloquist Dummy. It was beautiful!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-31 15:50:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Look into a disorder called [Trimethylaminuria](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Trimethylaminuria). It's a recessive disorder (though in some cases can be caused non-genetics reasons like liver dysfunction) that is not terribly common but it would describe many of the problems you're having with odour. Essentially it's caused by the dysfunction of a metabolic enzyme leading to the build up of specific molecule, which in turn causes a bad odour in body secretions (sweat, urine etc.). Unfortunately this is not something good hygiene will fix. If you do have TMAU, which I strongly suspect you do, you will likely be referred to a specialist and be placed on a strict diet that eliminates foods that can cause a build up of FMO3 (the molecule responsible for the odour).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Buz isn't allowed outside unsupervised but he managed to escape last night. He came home this morning and hasn't moved for 5 hours. Someone went a little crazy with their new found freedom!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-22 05:42:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-22 06:22:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>He can be super feral and territorial so I don't generally let him out unless I'm also in the yard. I saw a tabby hightail it out of our property when I brought Buz in so clearly he was up to no good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-22 06:28:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>He came in at 7am and he's still in bed at 3:30pm. I should probably poke him or something...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-22 09:08:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>UPDATE: It's been exactly 11 hours since Buz dragged his sorry ass to bed and he's still completely comatose. He did get up for about five minutes to hoover down his dinner, which gave me just enough time to change the sheets, but he immediatly went back bed. His little brother, Alfie, has joined him. http://imgur.com/vm9cBpK</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Clinical Scientists discover that experimental drug "alisertib" completely rids mice of cancers to the cervix, skin, head, and neck caused by the human papillomavirus (HPV).</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-19 01:00:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My cat can be a feral jerk</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-22 04:42:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>High quality kitty pile up in here!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-03 13:02:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-22 15:43:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>90% of the cells/DNA in your body are made up of non-human organisms.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Brotherly love</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-07 08:43:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-09 09:04:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ask a woman who already has children with her for help. A female's empathy for children doesn't normally stop at her own.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-09 01:31:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't understand why she is waiting. The Cheerios should be readily available for that face.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Alfie wants to show you his stuff.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-23 06:34:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-22 16:19:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bacteria in fly brains makes them do weird things. Lets put it in mosquitoes and see if we can stop them from killing millions of people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-06 13:37:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Professor Scott O'Neill](http://www.npr.org/2012/06/08/154528752/eliminate-dengue-team-has-a-deep-lab-bench) and his team are on the brink of eliminating mosquito borne disease after more than 15 years of painstaking research. His work funded by the Bill  amp; Melinda Gates Foundation's Global Health Program, has lead to unbelievable successful control of mosquito borne viruses, like Dengue, by introducing a bacteria to mosquitoes that stops them passing on the virus to humans. The bacteria, known as Wolbachia, has a powerful ability to invade natural populations of insects and alter their reproduction and lifespan. [Learn more about this breakthough research here](http://www.eliminatedengue.com/program)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-27 12:04:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Thanksgiving Dinner" So basically the greatest night of my life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Antibiotic apocalypse: Gene discovered among bacteria in China is resistant to all known antibiotics</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-20 04:31:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My Grandpa taking my Grandma for a ride on his horse while they were still dating (1950's)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-29 08:34:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-30 07:10:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Michigan, actually</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-30 07:14:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty much this. My Grandpa was a farrier and trained racehorses. My Grandma helped with the horses but was primarily a stay at home Mom to her 5 kids. My Mom said they were poor but very well loved.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-30 07:16:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I showed this post to my Grandma and she said: "We were cool all right! On our wedding day we trained horses then got into our suits, went to the church, got married with a few friends and family, all in a few hours. Then we headed up north for a 3 day honeymoon...total cost of maybe fifty dollars"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-30 07:41:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lots of people in America ride English. I certainly did.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Proper sleep is critical for focus and attention while we're awake because it helps us block out competing stimuli.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-31 02:10:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-05 09:39:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>This may have nothing to do with her intelligence. Has she ever been evaluated for an attention disorder? I ask because it sounds like she exhibits a lot of classic symptoms of ADD or ADHD. I would recommend that you gently discuss the possibility of seeing a specialist for evaluation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Zika virus: Australian dengue researchers may have solution</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-05 10:41:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-05 12:49:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wolbachia infects  gt;40% of all invertebrate species, however it is highly unlikely to infect species that do not naturally harbor the bacteria. This is because Wolbachia is vertically transmitted, passed from a female to it's offspring. Female to offspring Wolbachia transfer uses an almost identical mechanism as mitochondria. In fact, it took the research group in the article nearly 10 years to infect one female mosquito, which are not naturally infected with Wolbachia. This was only able to occur by transinfecting the bacteria from a naturally infected host (fruit flies) by micro-injection. Once the female was infected, all of her offspring was infected, and the bacteria could rapidly spread through lab stocks. Additionally, because of the mechanism Wolbachia uses to spread (Cytoplasmic Incompatibility) if actually offers a fitness advantage for the mosquito to be infected, thus quickly overtaking the uninfected population under the right conditions. Watch this [youtube video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1ErcwogWbIA) made by the research group cited in the article to better understand Wolbachia and its utilization as a control agent.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-20 07:17:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your husband should be evaluated for an autoimmune disorder. His headaches and additional health issues point towards something more system wide like lupus or MS. Specifically, there are several autoimmune disorders that attack the vascular system and this can lead to chronic headaches, along with other health issues. Also, diabetes is also worth testing for us untreated diabetes can also destroy the vascular system and lead so similar symptoms. His sugar consumption would make this significantly worse.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-13 01:05:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh come on, doing a master's degree isn't that life consuming. I did a PhD in a difficult STEM field and managed (along with the large majority of others doing grad degrees) to maintain their relationships and a work/life balance. Some of them even had time to get married and have babies It sounds like you're using your degree an excuse to check out of your relationship. Do the girl a favor while she's still young and break up with her so she can find and have a normal relationship.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-30 08:25:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Acute behavioural changes like this are not normal and can be a sign that something is malfunctioning in the brain. It may not be a major problem but it's something that does have the potential to get worse if ignored. These behaviours may indeed stem from stress and exhaustion but it's important to rule out other problems. PM me if you would like to discuss this further.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The pathogenicity of a strain of Wolbachia, one of the most common bacteria on the planet, is regulated by the environmental temperature at which the host resides.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-25 12:34:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-03 03:54:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>High fang to face ratio.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-29 13:04:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Under the sea, wish I could be.... A MERMAID ZOMBIE http://imgur.com/a/6krQO</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Scientist identify remarkably diverse mitochondrial mutations in individuals with autism spectrum disorder (ASD)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-30 04:27:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-02 05:41:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Narcolepsy without cataplexy or sleep apnea would be my guess. Go to the doctor and rule out other conditions first and then consider a sleep study.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-12 15:42:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm actually a neuroscientist that is specifically researching sleep. From your description it sounds like your boyfriend has classic symptoms of a hypersomnia disorder such as narcolepsy without catalepsy. He's probably not experiencing enough of one of his essential sleep stages (slow wave sleep or REM sleep) during his normal night time hours and needs to compensate with naps. My money is on hypersomnia. Also, it sounds like he is easily aroused and even being disturbed once during the night is enough to cause an increased sleep need. Get his to a specialist. If he doesn't go, you have every right to be frustrated. I personally have narcolepsy without cataplexy (too much REM and not enough slow wave sleep) and I have to take a 1 hour nap on my lunch break and another when I get home.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Alfie is patiently waiting for Santa Cat to bring him a brand new bottle cap</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-06 05:06:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-23 00:46:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>If my boss gave me a VS gift card, I'd be immediately uncomfortable and start questioning our professional relationship. What on earth were you thinking?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Scientist may have finally discovered the root cause of severe premenstrual syndrome (PMDD) at the molecular level</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-07 16:45:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-08 05:34:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>No it's not my paper, but as a uterus holder I found it to be quite promising.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>LOST CAT - Balmoral / Bulimba</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-11 06:05:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am offering a reward for his safe return. LOST approximately 9PM on 10/01/201 near Sixth Ave. in Balmoral Male, desexed, Dark Brown, Green/Yellow eyes, Oriental Cat. He is skinny and small in size. Meaty escaped and is not used to being outside. He is extremely timid and may not come to you. He is an older cat so I'm very concerned about him in this heat! If you have seen him, please contact me immediately. See photos: http://imgur.com/a/SdVe6</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-11 07:38:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! I'm really worried. Hopefully he's just on an amazing adventure</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-11 08:46:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for the tip. I am willing to try anything!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>UPDATE: LOST CAT - Balmoral / Bulimba</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-17 02:04:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Last week I posted about my [missing cat](https://www.reddit.com/r/brisbane/comments/5na94e/lost_cat_balmoral_bulimba/) A few people PM'd me asking for an update. I am extremely happy to say that we found him on Sunday! For 5 straight days we looked everywhere within a 2 suburb radius. I even took two days off of work and walked all over Balmoral in the blazing heat. We knocked on doors and hung up posters with no luck. We ended up contacting a feral cat trapper to ask if they had any advice and they suggested we set up a live animal trap in our yard with some stinky food to lure him back. So we drove to the North side and hired a live animal trap, and baited it with tuna. Well it worked like a charm because we caught him 9 hours after setting up the trap! It turns out the little jerk wasn't far at all and was probably having the time of his life. Meaty is currently resting in the aircon at home. We will be keeping an eye on him for a while and have ordered him a special GPS chip for his collar, in case he pulls this stunt again. I'd like to thank everyone for their concern and suggestions! If anyone else loses a cat I would highly recommend setting up a trap as soon as possible!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-17 05:29:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>They aren't cheap but considering we spent over $100 on posters, the cage hire, and petrol, it's probably worth it in the long run. Plus if your cat gets picked up by council, you have to pay a fee to get them out of jail. This is the tracker I bought: http://www.gpspetcollar.com.au/ I specifically ordered this one: http://www.gpspetcollar.com.au/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-17 05:30:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yup. He's the loudest, chattiest cat too. We thought for sure we would hear him if we were close. Turns out he wasn't terribly interested in being found.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-17 05:30:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here is the track I ended up buying. Some use GPS while others use radio frequency http://www.gpspetcollar.com.au/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-17 05:31:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really appreciate the concern! I have learned this past week how kind and helpful people are when it comes to animals.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-17 06:40:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Absolutely! http://www.gumtree.com.au/s-ad/lutwyche/pet-products/hire-rental-large-humane-animal-trap/1133818334 This one is in Lutwyche but if you search for "animal trap" in Brisbane on gumtree, heaps of places hire them out for weeks or months. What you need to do is set it up somewhere outside of your house that is accessible and also under shelter (like a bush or tree). Place stinky food and a little water at the very back. We used tuna. Drizzle some juice from the tuna can around the trap to lure the cat in. Make sure you remove any food already outside to the cat is more likely to enter the trap. Check the trap twice a day (once in the morning, once late afternoon. Don't hang around the trap too much or you might scare the cat away). It's extremely likely that the cat will only investigate at night so don't assume you'll catch him during the day. Our cat was trapped at 1AM on Sunday morning. Good luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Natural selection may be causing a decline in gene variants that predispose people to attain higher levels of education</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 14:17:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My cat's sleep face is truly majestic</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-22 08:47:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I thought the point of working from home was to get away from your boss</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 06:08:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-05 07:37:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you haven't already, list the cat on the following FB groups: https://www.facebook.com/Queenslandlostpets/ You can also list the cat as found via the RSPCA lost and found database https://www.rspcaqld.org.au/What-we-do/Find%20lost%20animals/Register%20a%20Found%20Pet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-10 07:43:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of my girlfriend's is an infectious disease researcher for QLD health. She does a lot of testing and statistics tracking on local STI rates. She tells us all the time how Gonorrhea and Chlamydia rates are absolutely skyrocketing, getting worse every year, because people are using condoms less than they were 10 years ago (probably because people are less concerned with HIV infection). Not surprising, the highest rates are around the three big universities in Brisbane. One University in particular has one of the highest gonorrhea rates in the country. Wrap it up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-10 08:51:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's irrelevant because all three have some of the highest rates in the country. One is just slightly higher.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-15 10:45:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a USA/Aussie dual citizen. I did my undergrad in the U.S., my PhD in Australia, and have worked and lectured at both Griffith and UQ. Frankly I think both Universities are more or less the same (I can't speak for QUT but I'm sure it's comparable), especially if it's for undergraduate education. I find it laughable when undergraduates at UQ or QUT make fun of Griffith because nobody outside of QLD gives a shit about any of these Universities. But I digress... For graduate school, it depends more on your specialty. Go to the university with the highest rated graduate program in your field. For research, it completely depends on your supervisor, the University doesn't really matter in this case. The only thing that matters for research is publication output. Nobody cares where you did your PhD when you have a Nature paper.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New evidence supports the dopamine ontogeny hypothesis, in which dysregulation of dopamine during fetal brain development may be responsible for Schizophrenia</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-15 15:58:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-05 12:18:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>My Mexican friend said that La Cantina Mexicana in Bulimba is pretty good, though I haven't personally been there. Obviously nothing here is going to be super authentic. I'm a yank and I too miss authentic Mexican.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-07 06:06:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Has she actually been diagnosed with CF or does she just claim to have it? As a neuroscientist, it really annoys me when people claim to have a chronic, life-long disease in order to excuse normal, or slightly above average, levels of fatigue. CF is thought to be a disorder of the mitochondria (the molecules in our cells that pump out energy for the body) and also causes inflammation to the brain and spinal cord. People with CF literally feel mentally and physically lifeless all day, every day. You know when you're really sick with an infection like the flu, how you can't get out of bed or even perform the most mundane task without feeling exhaustion? That's what it is like to have CF. I just find it hard to believe someone with CF is capable of working in a fast-paced environment like a bar. It sounds more typical of a shift work sleep disorder (google it for more info). Most people with CF can't even leave their homes. Sure, she may be fatigued after a long day's work, but until she has an actual diagnosis, I wouldn't let her get away with using it as an excuse. It does sound like you both have very different needs and you should consider what that means for you in the long term.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-07 07:39:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's fair and I completely understand why you would be exhausted. I would be too! Just be careful about equating your normal tiredness from being overworked and over-stressed with a disease like CFS.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-07 07:45:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>As I said in another comment, it's totally fair that you're exhausted from working that much. I can completely empathize with that. However most people with active CFS can barely work at all. I'm looking at this from a purely medical/scientific perspective. I totally recommend seeing someone if you think you're still suffering though. Good luck. P.S. I was with a guy who didn't work when I was in my early 20's. That relationship ended after 5 years. I should have left sooner.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-07 09:12:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have a bias because you have CFS yourself but the vast majority of people who were diagnosed in the early years of CSF awareness actually have something else. It's not my opinion, it's the opinion of the current, up-to-date scientific research. CSF used to be a blanket statement for a lot of conditions that were not well understood. An updated diagnosis with a rheumatology specialist is important.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-10 20:42:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Neuroscientist here. You need to see another neurologist and get a second opinion. It sounds like you have a form of agnosia. Perhaps integrative agnosia but there are multiple forms. Get it checked. Specifically bring up agnosia.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-30 05:26:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Non-essential staff were also sent home with pay.  lt;3 thanks UQ</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 04:51:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>This sounds like classic addict behavior. Ask him to take a drug test. If he refuses, you should assume or at least be extremely concerned that this is the problem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Wishful thinking</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-11 15:00:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-16 17:07:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is an inflammatory response not an infection.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-17 01:47:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Feeling a little crap for 1-2 days vs. pneumonia and potential death? Sounds reasonable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-25 16:35:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>This sounds like early stages of dementia. His age and sudden personality change are two big red flags. Please consider talking him for an evaluation if possible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-28 07:54:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>You should post this in the Brisbane Lost and Found Pets group. There are a lot of missing birds: https://www.facebook.com/groups/231647446910269/ Also the QLD lost pets register https://www.facebook.com/Queenslandlostpets/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Pair of young kittens stolen from a Brisbane home</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-29 14:41:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Do you recognize this man? Attempted abduction of two girls in Newport</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 05:38:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-17 15:54:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>You should consider setting up your own trap near your house. You can rent them on gumtree. http://www.gumtree.com.au/s-ad/lutwyche/pet-products/hire-rental-large-humane-animal-trap/1133818334 What you need to do is set it up somewhere outside of your house that is accessible and also under shelter (like a bush or tree). Place stinky food and a little water at the very back. We used tuna to bait our cat when he went missing. Drizzle some juice from the tuna can around the trap to lure the cat in. Make sure you remove any food already outside to the cat is more likely to enter the trap. Check the trap twice a day (once in the morning, once late afternoon. Don't hang around the trap too much or you might scare the cat away). It's extremely likely that the cat will only investigate at night so don't assume you'll catch him during the day. Our cat was trapped at 2AM on Sunday morning. You can read this guide for more information: http://www.missingpetpartnership.org/recovery-tips/trapping-lost-pets/ Good luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-26 08:48:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also, humane animal traps are one the most successful way to catch a cat since they are almost always hiding near their house, and usually only move around at night. http://www.missingpetpartnership.org/recovery-tips/trapping-lost-pets/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 09:22:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm so sorry for your loss :( Two years ago I went through something very similar where I had to put my young cat down because he was born with a birth defect that damaged one of his kidneys. The other kidney had to work extra hard to compensate and he went into renal failure when he was 6 years old. I was devastated and my heart was broken. After a week of grieving, I saw some photos of adoptable cats that were on death row and decided the best way to honor my deceased cat's memory was to give another kitty the chance at life. I ended up adopting two and while I still think about my first cat all the time, it brings me peace and happiness to know that I am giving a wonderful life to my two little fur buddies. Everyone grieves differently but I hope my story gives you something to consider!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-19 14:13:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>You should consider setting up your own trap near your house. You can rent them on gumtree. http://www.gumtree.com.au/s-ad/lutwyche/pet-products/hire-rental-large-humane-animal-trap/1133818334 What you need to do is set it up somewhere outside of your house that is accessible and also under shelter (like a bush or tree). Place stinky food and a little water at the very back. We used tuna to bait our cat when he went missing. Drizzle some juice from the tuna can around the trap to lure the cat in. Make sure you remove any food already outside to the cat is more likely to enter the trap. Check the trap twice a day (once in the morning, once late afternoon. Don't hang around the trap too much or you might scare the cat away). It's extremely likely that the cat will only investigate at night so don't assume you'll catch him during the day. Our cat was trapped at 2AM on Sunday morning. You can read this guide for more information: http://www.missingpetpartnership.org/recovery-tips/trapping-lost-pets/ Good luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-26 10:27:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I completely agree with this. Herve Ledger knockoffs are everywhere, especially on Ebay, and labels inside are extremely close to the real deal. You need to own up and give her the full amount.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-03 13:22:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Totally agree. I study their role in sleep and it's huge. Don't be hating on glia, ya'll</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-19 11:42:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a yank and I work at UQ. If you really need to be close to coffee shops and bars, but also be within walking/biking distance to UQ, than West End is going to be your best option. Plus it's basically hipster central in Brisbane. The only issue is that it can be pretty pricey unless you're willing to live in a share house. Taringa, Toowong, Milton and Paddington are also good options.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-14 12:30:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Look into monofeme. Alternatively, get the copper IUD. It's hormone free and of of the most effective, although your initial price to get it is about $300. However, they can last 5-10 years so you'll make your money back</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>'There was a screw-up': UBC researchers pull paper linking vaccine component to autism</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 04:04:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>UBC researchers pull paper linking vaccine component to autism after data alleged to be manipulated</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 04:07:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 05:59:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because there are several forms of mercury. Mercury is a naturally occurring element found in the earth #8217;s crust, air, soil, and water. Two types of mercury to which people may be exposed  #8212; methylmercury and ethylmercury  #8212; are very different. Methylmercury is the type of mercury found in certain kinds of fish. At high exposure levels methylmercury can be toxic to people. In the United States, federal guidelines keep as much methylmercury as possible out of the environment and food, but over a lifetime, everyone is exposed to some methylmercury. Thimerosal, the type in vaccines, contains ethylmercury, which is cleared from the human body more quickly than methylmercury, and is therefore less likely to cause any harm.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 06:47:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you stick this bacteria in this mosquito, it can't infect you with Dengue Virus or Zika anymore. Also the bacteria changes insect behavior in a lot of weird ways.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Betsy had a rough start to life but she's a princess now.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 00:02:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 01:31:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>She's such a smart, sweet, relaxed little girl. She nearly died from Parvo and I think she's thankful to be alive and pays it forward with love.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New research shows that fruit flies experience different sleep stages, suggesting that dynamic sleep co-evolved with the evolution of the brain</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 00:55:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-16 09:11:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Try Paddington/Bardon/Ashgrove area. You can find houses for rent here with decent yards for around $500-600/week. Most houses with yards in family areas like this allow pets. I am renting a 2 bedroom house in Paddington and we have two cats and a Belgium Malinois.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 10:04:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will play devil's advocate due to your Mother's age. Has your Mother been exhibiting other odd behavioural changes? The reason I ask is because signs of Dementia normal occur after age 65 so your Mother is the right age.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 09:53:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably not long. There are tons of share houses always looking for new people to fill rooms.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 12:57:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, it's just over 80k. Considering how much education is required plus the extreme hours postdocs typically work, it isn't that great.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 01:54:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Parvo is basically doggy Ebola. Scary stuff! My rescue had parvo before we adopted her and spent 3 months in the hospital where she nearly died. She's now 9 months but she'll never reach her full growth potential because she was so malnourished due to the disease attacking her digestive tract. She'll also likely be on a special diet for most of her life. Parvo is almost always fatal. Get your pets vaccinated, people!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 07:49:22</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I want to sit in an ivory tower and write papers/engage in discussion for a living. In real life this translates to sitting at a shared desk with 5 other researchers, writing about a super specific topic that your boss predetermines for you, that maybe a handful of people will ever read. The first thing you need to do before going down this long, difficult path is come to terms with the fact that you may never be able to study topics that truly interest you. You'll research what you have to in order to increase your chances of getting future funding. In this current climate, you take whatever jobs you can get.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 07:25:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>You should consider setting up your own trap near your house. You can rent them on gumtree. http://www.gumtree.com.au/s-ad/lutwyche/pet-products/hire-rental-large-humane-animal-trap/1133818334 What you need to do is set it up somewhere outside of your house that is accessible and also under shelter (like a bush or tree). Place stinky food and a little water at the very back. We used tuna to bait our cat when he went missing. Drizzle some juice from the tuna can around the trap to lure the cat in. Make sure you remove any food already outside to the cat is more likely to enter the trap. Check the trap twice a day (once in the morning, once late afternoon. Don't hang around the trap too much or you might scare the cat away). It's extremely likely that the cat will only investigate at night so don't assume you'll catch him during the day. Our cat was trapped at 2AM on Sunday morning. You can read this guide for more information: http://www.missingpetpartnership.org/recovery-tips/trapping-lost-pets/ Good luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 00:56:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Try Ouma's Pantry in Milton. I go there all the time for biltong and the prices are pretty reasonable. https://oumaspantry083.wixsite.com/oumaspantry</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 08:10:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really like Il Posto in Paddington. They really take pride in the quality of their food and it shows!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I will protect you from the scary bathtub, Mom.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 09:53:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My girl thinks she has to protect me from the scary bathtub.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 11:57:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 21:33:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh wow they look so similar! Is yours a Belgium malinois?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 21:34:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>She's not scared but she really dislikes them. Has no problems with the rain or the b each. She tries to lick me the entire time and gets especially nervous if I put my head under water.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 02:30:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 02:42:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>The biggest current problem is constantly exposing ourselves to too much artificial light. We evolved to rise and fall with the sun but it's almost impossible to do this when looking a bright phone or computer screen. It inhibits our normal biological clock so we don't feel tired when we should, i.e. night. At least 1 hour, (I always go for 2) prior to going to sleep, shut everything down, reduce the light in your house (try a low-intensity light-bulb) and do something relaxing like reading. This will allow your brain to naturally transition into sleep. Also, don't go to bed hungry because hungry will actually make our brains actively stay awake. And if you have sleep issues, see a doctor! A lot of sleep-deprived people have an underlining medical issue they aren't aware of.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 02:55:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Consider getting a light-box and do 20 minutes of light therapy when you wake. This could be done while you're eating or getting ready in the bathroom. The natural UV light will trick your brain into believing it's normal day-time hours and it will produce the molecules necessary for staying awake. People also use these for seasonal depression and jetlag http://sleephub.com.au/light-therapy/ Conversely, try to make your room at light-tight as possible. Make sure you're in your dark room at least 1-2 hours before going to bed WITHOUT electronic devices to trick your brain into making sleep promoting molecules.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 03:06:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have never heard of the banana thing before so I can't comment. As far as food, you need to go to bed without being hungry. You don't need to be overly full, just not hungry. From an evolutionary standpoint, this makes sense because your brain will inhibit your sleep so you can find food and survive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 04:34:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>A lot of people are long sleepers and just need 1-2 hours more than the generally population. On the other hand most people don't know that you can stay asleep and still get poor quality sleep because one of their sleep stages in dysfunctional. Let's say for instance you get a lot of REM sleep but not much slow wave sleep. Even though you might be seeping 9-10 hours, if you don't get enough slow wave sleep you're still going to feel un-refreshed the next morning. This is also why most people don't feel 100% when they take sleeping pills because they generally induce a deep, slow wave sleep and you miss out on all your essential light and REM sleep. And of course there are also problems like sleep apnoea which most people are completely aware of until they see a sleep specialist.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 09:21:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was in high school during the early day of internet 2.0, including the popular days of message board. My nickname has been Bean since I was a baby so that's what I uses as my username to talk about anime and science, and other nerdy stuff. Changing my username would be like destroying a little part of my very being.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 09:21:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you very much! Your support is appreciated!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 09:22:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I find that sleep is one of those research areas that can be easily transition to because you can study it from so many different angles. It's never to late!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 11:41:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. Worse, even if you sleep well with a partner. Sleeping alone is always optimal. 2. The mattress doesn't matter as long as you find it comfortable and it doesn't restrict your breathing. Generally people can adjust to any mattress as long as it's comfortable. I personally like memory foam mattresses but that's just a personal preference. 3. As long as you are getting enough sleep for your personal genetic needs it doesn't matter when you sleep. You can listen to your body's normal rhythm and wake up when it feels natural to do so as long as it isn't affecting other aspects of your life. 4. This is controversial but it shouldn't matter. Your brain knows exactly how much sleep it requires and will push you to get that sleep until the sleep deprivation debt is paid off. So if you can achieve all the sleep your brain requires in several broken bouts than you should be fine. 5. I think the absolute main sign (besides the obvious of simply feeling tired) is that your ability to pay attention is affected. Sleep and attention are very connected. For instance, if you spend all day cramming for an examine your brain will require more sleep than usual. If you don't get enough sleep, your ability to pay attention, stay focused, and learn will be extremely impacted. I wish I had a sensory deprivation cocoon but I've not come across one!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 05:20:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>You should consider setting up your own trap near your house. You can rent them on gumtree. http://www.gumtree.com.au/s-ad/lutwyche/pet-products/hire-rental-large-humane-animal-trap/1133818334 What you need to do is set it up somewhere outside of your house that is accessible and also under shelter (like a bush or tree). Place stinky food and a little water at the very back. We used tuna to bait our cat when he went missing. Drizzle some juice from the tuna can around the trap to lure the cat in. Make sure you remove any food already outside to the cat is more likely to enter the trap. Check the trap twice a day (once in the morning, once late afternoon. Don't hang around the trap too much or you might scare the cat away). It's extremely likely that the cat will only investigate at night so don't assume you'll catch him during the day. Our cat was trapped at 2AM on Sunday morning. You can read this guide for more information: http://www.missingpetpartnership.org/recovery-tips/trapping-lost-pets/ Good luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 02:27:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Try A Mini Rescue https://www.facebook.com/aminirescue/ And Brisbane Valley Cat Rescue https://www.facebook.com/Brisbane-Valley-Cat-Rescue-39456639193/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 05:47:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>My roommate puts his entire mouth in my mouth while I'm sleeping.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does autism arise because the brain is continually surprised?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 01:43:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 06:37:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is the most Barnaby looking pup I have ever seen. Barny for short.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 04:25:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used to have Turkeys. That's most certainly a female. Males are aggressive as hell.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 06:52:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think my Mal is broken because she's super chill even to the point of being lazy. She even lays down to eat her food. She did have a very unique start to life so that could potentially be responsible for her laid back behavior. If we ever get another Mal, I have to go into it assuming it will be nothing like our current pup.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 11:18:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>She was abandoned at about 3 months by her first owners and was found sick on the street with parvo virus. A rescue group paid for her treatment but she nearly died. She was in the hospital for two months. She basically had little to no contact with other dogs but was constantly surrounded by people. We adopted her at 6 months and now she's completely healthy. Her ears will never stand up because she was so malnourished during her major growth period, but we adore her regardless. She's completely docile and cuddly, but still smart as a typical Mal. She loves nothing more than to just chill with us while we read or watch TV. We do the typical activities that most dogs would require, but she simply doesn't have the explosive energy that is typical for a Mal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 11:23:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know! She has such a beautiful soul, I don't know how someone could dump her. She's still whip smart though. The speed at which she learns commands always amazes me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My great-grandfather, Archie, with his ice cream truck.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 09:33:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My great-grandfather, Archie, looking like an absolute boss in front of his ice cream truck. 1950s</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 09:37:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 15:21:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>We adopted a pure Mal (DNA tested and confirmed) that was found on the street with a deadly case of parvo. She had a really rough start and we had no idea where she was from, but she is an angel baby from heaven. She is the sweetest dog on earth. There is always a risk when taking in a dog with an unknown history but more often than not, they are wonderful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 13:21:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>$10 says you have a redundant colon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 16:23:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why not do something simple like examining how certain strains affect the host animal's behavior?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Classic double turnover</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 13:50:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 09:41:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Neuroscientist here. This honestly sounds like a mild form of Touretts. These aren't just bad habits - they are a extreme compulsion to complete a physical action caused by the dysfunction in certain areas of your brain. Touretts has a strong genetic component and is strongly related to OCD. It's not just something you can train yourself to stop doing without a medical professional! See a doctor!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 12:04:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a Dr. of neuroscience that specializes in sleep. Your husband has sleep apnea. Seeing as how he's nearly 40, he's probably already done considerable permanent damage. There is a reasonable chance he will develop dementia if complications from the SA don't kill him first. There is still time to reverse some of this damage but it needs to be done ASAP. It's time for you to have a come to Jesus talk.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 07:26:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not necessarily. My dog looks exactly like this, floppy ears and all, and DNA test revealed she's a GSD x Belgium Malinois. Her thin face suggests she's a Mal cross.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 07:32:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh wow, my off the street rescue looked almost exactly like yours when she was a puppy! We DNA tested and found out she's a German Shepherd x Belgium Malinois cross. Betsy as a puppy: https://imgur.com/a/4aeo1ki Betsy Now: https://imgur.com/a/6aYePZR</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 13:41:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi, fellow early 30's yank here (although I've lived in Brisbane for over 11 years). Shoot me a message if you want to hang.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 02:43:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I moved here from a state in the US that can get down to -30 in the winter and the summers always hovered around the mid 20's. When I moved to Brisbane it took me over 3 years to adjust to the climate. You will sweat more than you realised was possible. My recommendation is make sure you move somewhere with aircon. Carry an insulated bottle of ice water with you whenever you go out. Always wear sunscreen because your skin will take years to adjust to the sun. Keep extra shirts you can change into at work and keep deodorant handy. The good news is that you will adjust eventually. I used to be ghost white, my skin was practically see through and I always burned, never tanned. I'm still pretty white but I achieve a mild tan in the summer and my natural base colour is slightly darker than it used to be. The summer heat also doesn't bother me that much anymore except when I'm sleeping, but that's when having aircon comes in handy. The downside is that anything below 20C feels cold, which is a real bummer since I was so used to extreme cold before. Good luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 06:27:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Scientist don't get paid enough to be evil.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>