<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject5256</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>PC Wont Power Up</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 16:09:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>So it started last night when I went to bed I turned my pc off and I noticed it didnt turn off immediately. The screen turned off but the PC was still on for about 30 minutes. And now today when I came home from school my PC wont turn on at all. I would really appericiate some help, thanks in advance!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 16:46:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Didnt work do you have another possible solution?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 16:59:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Didnt work either, anythyng else that might work?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 17:03:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dont have one is there any other way to check?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 17:12:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Already did do you know any other solutions?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Help with magnetic questions</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 19:28:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>After Miller walked for one hour, the compass needle was positioned vertically with the north end downward. Miller was at the Northpole. I wanna know if this is true or false and if so why.? Would appericiate quick answers, thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What should I listen to next?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-13 20:34:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey I'm looking for some good bootlegs to listen to! I've heard all of their official released concerts such as Budapest and Wembley '86, Montreal '81, Live Killers '79 and so on but now I wanna listen to some bootlegs too, what concerts should I listen to?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 07:22:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks so much! This will keep me busy for a while :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 22:53:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would be great! Please do!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 13:13:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>this meme was shit overuaed and old format -rep</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Favorite Tour? - Poll on strawpoll.com</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-25 17:55:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Don't think It's gonna work, should I try again..?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 21:29:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok so I'm 15 years old and I've been thinking of starting this for real but I don't really think It's gonna work. It's great to jerk off and I feel good doing it. I actually went two weeks without jerking off and I feel any difference except I was had like a boner 24/7. Should I try again though? What are your guys thoughts. I don't really think It's gonna be any difference like the last time but I might try again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 21:49:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very rarely, I'm mostly on instagram. Why?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 22:11:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wouldn't really say I'm addicted to fapping. Some weeks I fap maybe like once a day so 7 times a week, some weeks less, some a bit more. But I'd really say average is 4-5 a week. and I don't have any problems because of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 22:12:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did it because of a joke really during November there's this thing called "No Nut November" and I tried that for two weeks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 22:13:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jazz in Japan by faaar, It's just terrible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Vampire lord - is it too late?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 00:17:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey /r/ skyrim! I'm collecting all the achivements in Skyrim and now I wanna get the "Vampire Mastered" the problem is that I chose the Dawnguards and I've cured Serana is there some kind of way I can still become a vampire lord? Via commands maybe? Just so I can get my achivement. I would be very thankful for quick answers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 01:07:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I use console commands will I still be able to get the achivement?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Become Vampire Lord via console commands.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 02:22:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was wondering if I would be able to become a Vampire Lord via console commands so I can get the Vampire Mastered achivement. I sided with the Dawnguard and have already cured Serana. Ty for answers!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 02:31:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just got a idea that might work, I reload my save before I cured her, make myself a vampire there and get the achivement. I mean that should work right?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 02:37:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright so I've reloaded my old save and im a vampire now. When I get the achivement ima the save i used before.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 01:41:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. Liar 2. The Night Comes Down 3. Keep Yourself Alive</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 11:15:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah ur right. But then ppl would have just taken hor space anyways. It was a shitty poll</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 15:16:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same I think its a great album</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 01:20:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>How am I doing something wrong?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 01:23:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah you're probs right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 02:46:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree with you a littlw bit. I become tired too but only for like 1 min then i get a boost of positivty and energy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 04:30:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pmo ing?? What's that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 04:34:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh i see. Maybe you're right, maybe i should give it at least one month. Im not sure if theres gonna be any difference but ill try it out. Ill make an update post in one month</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 04:36:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>How long will it take for me to really feel any difference?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 04:40:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright ill do it for 1 month and ill then make a update post</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 01:47:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>oh ok. ty.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 07:26:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Queen II, A Night At The Opera, News of The World, The Game, The Works, The Miracle, and Innuendo Queen II: Father To Son A Night At The Opera: Sweet Lady News of The World: Sleeping on The Sidewalk The Game: Save Me The Works: Radio Gaga The Miracle: Was It All Worth It Innuendo: I Can't Live With You</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 19:33:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I chose that list because it contains my favorite albums. I like alot of the albums from the other list too but I dislike Jazz and Hot Space, and A Kind Of Magic has some great stuff but also some really weak material. This list had my top 3 albums, 1:Innuendo 2: A Night At The Opera 3. News Of The World I also picked Sweet Lady over Bohemian Rhapsody cause It's just my favorite ATM and a great rocker. It's been my favorite for quite some time now. Bohemian Rhapsody is a great song but I think It's pretty overplayed and I've heard it so many times that I've gotten pretty tired of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How do I get a album cover next to my name?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 19:37:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi! I was wondering how you could get that album cover next to your name, I have noticed some users have it and I'd like one too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 08:48:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Favorite Live Album? - Poll on strawpoll.com</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 18:30:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 16:16:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>A really tough one between It's Late and Spread Your Wings but Spread Your Wings wins by an inch IMO</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What year was this video recorded? 1986?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 17:58:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I found this channel "Bulat Araslanov" he got some pretty nice videos. Alot of rushes of their music videos, you should check out his Queen and Freddie videos. Anyways, found this video on his channel and I've never seen it before, What year was it recorded 1986? https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=68XfzyqwB9g EDIT: I think It's from 1982 actually.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 15:55:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agree, Innuendo is my favorite too!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What are the top 3 greatest inventions the last 40 years?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 14:00:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 14:11:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't have any homework about this subject, just curious what people think.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lost Legacy Bug- Help please :(</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 15:06:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm playing Lost Legacy and I'm currently in Vahloks Tomb and I've gotten the two halves of the Amethyst Claw and now there's a magic bridge When I cross It's supposed to reappear and that guy should cross it. But the bridge just dissapears and he cant cross and the door wont open. I've tried reloading several times but still the same result.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 08:15:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>All of it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 15:59:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cause it sucks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 20:53:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alrwady fixed it. Ty for the comment though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 20:03:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>You And I, how can you not smile when you hear that beautiful song?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 20:06:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 20:06:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Start with Queen I and then listen to all of their albums in order.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 20:09:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I saw these guys here in Sweden, the singer is great! His name is Johan Boding btw. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vDPCG88x9oE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What's your favourite Somebody to Love performance?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 20:11:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven't heard that many but my current favourite is Stockholm 1978.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 11:47:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a great version! My favourite Queen cover</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Men of reddit, what advice would you give a 15 year old guy?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 22:25:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just some advice about anything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>HyperX Cloud II Red Mic Not Working</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 14:09:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi I got a Hyperx Cloud II Red today and I got a problem, my mic is not working. Any solutions? It dosent work when I use the single 3.5mm either. The audio is working fine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-28 12:21:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Vila i fred v #229;ran k #228;ra Ingvar!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Anyone else here that likes Party/Khashoggi's Ship?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-28 14:52:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anyone else like them? Everyone I talk to seem to dislike them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-28 14:53:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Innuendoooo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 16:12:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>You really think so? I can understand why some people really dislike Party, It's not for everyone but Khashoggi's Ship is such a great and energetic song</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Have you ever been to a Queen concert? If so when and where? How was it?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 17:08:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please share.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 20:32:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 15:47:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Made in Heaven should be higher and Jazz lower</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What's your favourite show from every year?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 16:12:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you could pick one favourite show from every year, (From 1973-1986) What shows would you pick?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Easiest and most difficult Queen song to sing?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 13:18:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's the most difficult and the easiest Queen song to sing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Freddie Mercury with his moustache and his mother 1947</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 18:49:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It's a Hard Life Remastered Video</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 15:29:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 22:29:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>How did you feel when you were my age? Did you feel the same?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 22:30:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I guess but It feels like I just wished I wanted to cause It sort of feels like I'm missing out on alot of fun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 22:34:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think I am honestly, It looks like alot of fun. Even though they aren't as serious or last as long as adult relationships.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 22:41:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not sure I remember lol, I think I teleported using console commands.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 22:44:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Miracle? Pretty sure they would have preformed that one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 23:03:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know. Someone who I can have fun with and someone I really like being around.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 23:22:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>How did you feel being in a relationship?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 23:50:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can try asking out some intresting guys.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Are carpeted floor usual in the US if so why?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 22:52:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I often see carpeted floors in American movies and series, is this actually common and if so, why?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 11:13:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's ugly though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 11:15:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can just use some nice slippers instead of carpeted floors. Just as comftarable + much more nice looking floor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 11:22:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wood floors are much more nice looking. You can have wood floors and use some comftarable slippers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 15:06:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its not the same but Its just as comfortable IMO.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 15:13:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're not weird, I know alot of people who like doing it, including myself. But I love walking around in slippers too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Do dwarves have smaller penises than most other people?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 20:52:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do they have smaller penises?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A guy I know uploaded this to Facebook.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 17:08:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 21:57:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's an awesome song! One of my favourites from Innuendo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Anybody know when this was recorded? Was it after Mother Love?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 21:58:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New image from Bohemian Rhapsody</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 21:39:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 21:42:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Another one. https://www.facebook.com/Queen/photos/a.141525617361.111618.17337462361/10155603169942362/?type=3 amp;theater EDIT: And another one https://www.facebook.com/Queen/photos/a.141525617361.111618.17337462361/10155603174512362/?type=3 amp;theater</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When does a small/medium populated city become a big one?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 17:41:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>When do you think a small or medium populated city become a big city? 100 000+ people would be my guess.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 17:59:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's CT and NH?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Did you ever call your teacher by their first name in High School? If so what was the reaction?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 18:28:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here in Sweden we call all of our teachers by their first names but I've heard that you don't, if you ever did what was the reaction?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 18:48:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why do you think It would have been seen as impolite?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What's the most usual transportation to school?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 20:11:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is it the bus? And Is it normal for kids to walk/bicycle to school?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 20:21:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>So bikes are not common? Why not?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Rog, Brian And Fred recording Killer Queen Footage? (Check comments)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 16:19:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 16:20:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is from a Swedish TV program, at around 4:00 I think you can see Roger Fred and Brian recording Killer Queen in the studio anyone seen anymore of that footage?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 00:12:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I might be able to translate this, since I'm Swedish.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 00:18:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UjaA_LW9OVM This is a much better video of it, and it has some info in the description aswell!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 15:32:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is amazing! Would be awesome if you could do the same with Somebody to Love!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 18:18:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's great, thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 19:40:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>This looks great honestly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 15:58:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great job!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Queen Wembley '86 35mm film bits</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 14:58:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 15:01:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm positive we will see him in drag, since the IWTBF video is so iconic and popular.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How much tax do you pay?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 18:15:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>How much tax do you pay procent wise? 25%..?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Queen - Live in New York 1976 8mm HD</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 22:02:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 08:54:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hungarian Rhapsody is much better!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Queen Wallpapers</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 11:34:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Share your Queen wallpapers here!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Queen - Killer Queen (HD re-broadcast)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 12:54:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 22:21:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please never post something like this again, this was awful</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 10:20:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mysigt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 10:22:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jag h #228;lsar dig, v #228;naste land upp #229; jord</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Good shows with good audio quality</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 20:14:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>What are some good Queen shows with good audio quality?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 20:48:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Keep Yourself Alive and Liar Outtakes</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 21:52:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 13:22:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lmfao</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 14:40:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would be nice if he kept that hair and grew a beard like he did in 1989-1990.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Breakthru (3sat HD broadcast)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 22:13:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 11:16:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow this is great! Good job!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>hmmm</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 21:00:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 18:00:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Freddies haircut was so bad in the early 80's</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 10:50:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Miracle or Innuendo!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 15:12:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's Freddie's solo version https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vNhhAEupU4g, It's a little bit calmer but the most calm version I could find was the song but with just piano and vocals. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n7HqZXI_bYI</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 23:44:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit, is it just me pr does that look like a traditional manchu haircut?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 22:43:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>What did that SelfishCunt4 say? It won't show</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 17:55:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anyone got an idea when this picture was taken?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What instruments did the boys play?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 23:08:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any idea what instruments the boys played? (Except their "main" instrument) I know Freddie could play some chords on the guitar, but what about the other guys?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 00:48:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could someone please send me the picture of the cat?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 12:31:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes it is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cursed cat sock</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 18:29:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>cursed_sampsons.family</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 21:25:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How was Michael Jackson in debt?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 00:40:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was said that Michael Jackson was deep in debt at the time of his death in 2009, how did this happen? I mean earlier in his life he was probably worth around 1 billion, which he has said himself. So how did he get into debt?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What concerts are most likely to be released?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 21:20:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>What concerts do you think are most likely to be released in the future? I'm very certain they will release Hammersmith '79, maybe Earls Court '77 not as likely though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 23:12:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow! Very very impressive!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 22:54:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really like his clean shaven area 1987-1988!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 14:44:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>What language do you speak most fluently?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>N #229;gon annan som l #228;ngtar till vintern?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 13:52:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jag l #228;ngtar till vintern s #229; j #228;vla mycket, klarar inte av den h #228;r v #228;rmen.  #196;r det n #229;gon annan som k #228;nner detsamma?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What are some normal dishes that you eat during a normal work-week?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 14:26:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>What do you usually eat during a normal week?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 14:28:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>H #229;ller med att Sommaren och Vintern  #228;r bra p #229; olika s #228;tt men den h #228;r v #228;rmen  #228;r helt enkelt f #246;r mycket f #246;r mig, det skulle vara perfekt om det var cirka 20 grader!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 14:41:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love it, one of the best songs on Innuendo!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 17:38:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aaa, man kan ju halsa 2 liter p #229; nolltid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 00:45:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's terrifying.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What's your Queen feel good song?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 08:44:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mine is probably Misfire. What's yours?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>OK this is epic..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 10:23:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Best concert during Bad, Dangerous and HIStory tours?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 16:10:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>What were the best concerts during the Bad, Dangerous and HIStory tours? And I'm talking about performance, not quality.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How many cups of coffee do you drink everyday?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 16:29:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>How many cups of coffee do you usually drink?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How many cups of coffee do you drink each day?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 16:30:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>How many cups of coffee do you usually drink?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How has Reddit changed your view on Europeans?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 13:16:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>A similar question was asked on AskEurope about Americans, so I was just curious on what you think?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 10:49:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you have the same opinion of European redditors and European IRL?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 11:59:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's just waiting for you to take it back or prank it or something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>