<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject5938</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 11:28:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>ZMI is semi afk and when you hit lvl 77 you can go do bloods which is super afk. I don't get the hate towards runecrafting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 11:48:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I look at runecrafting this way; it gives a feeling of satisfaction looking at your stats and see that your rc lvl is +80 when the skill itself is time consuming and slow and that people think you're some kind of a maniac if you have high rc lvl.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 20:18:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you tell me how many hours have you played? I have 1864 total lvl if i remember correctly and 1100h. Just curious about your numbers and i know that the hours doesnt really mean anything because of various things like afk etc but im just curious :D oh and i dont have any 99 unfortunately.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 14:28:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>New overhead prayer and the armour is good too in my opinion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 08:53:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah one of my friend gave up after dying several times to jad and he's +90 in all combat stats. I got mine at second try with +80 stats because i hard panicked at my first try and kept it cool at the second try. That's the best tip propably, try to keep your cool and you don't screw up with clicks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 12:06:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>It has begun, the facebookians arrived.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 06:29:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>So you're 30 yo today? Nice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 09:42:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>LOL just joking =)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 00:23:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's funny that so many people whines (and now i mean REALLY whines) about stuff you do in runescape yet they still play it. If you don't enjoy most of the things you can do why even bother playing the game?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 00:34:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Copystrike incoming</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 22:04:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh man, this is why im sometimes afraid of playing OSRS. I have email for only runescape and every other little thing that can save my account from getting hacked or anything like that but still i've heard stories about guys getting hacked when it seems almost inpossible. And the worst part is that if you do get hacked everything can be and almost certainly will be lost and thousands of hours wasted.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 01:17:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was a hardcore nerd back in the days so it didn't come as a surprise to my friends or anyone who knew me that i played runescape. Nowadays their like "oh you're still playing that?" and im happy to say that i am and the game is still very much alive and kicking.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 01:22:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's wrong with the 10:01 if the content is good? So many people complain about this and i don't get it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 01:32:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes it does but why wouldn't you make longer videos (even if it's just couple seconds) if that equals more money? If you're at work and get an opportunity to make more money with ease you would do that i'm pretty sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 19:21:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Money and community i think. Faux have pretty nice community.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 00:40:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 00:55:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's going to be a sad day if they add MTX to osrs. They should know that MTX is going to destroy their game but hey it' jagex after all so anything can really happen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 23:33:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Torille</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 16:08:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>And no need for house tabs. Put law, dust and chaos to your pouch and you have crumble undead and home tele avaible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 01:24:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>That dudes story is really sad af. Glad that he's doing ok today.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 01:03:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I live in turku hmmmmmmmm</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 16:24:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lmao this is propably their first time doing anything related to fighting with fists what the heck did you expect lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>