<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject6644</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why does the Paulician Patriarch continuously bully the Byzantine Emperor? (HIP)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-28 19:50:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>So, this is the first game I'm playing with HIP on, started as a count in Byzantium made it to duke level. I'm trying to play as a loyalist vassal, but i noticed that we are in war with the Paulician Patriarch for the second time in a row... But the guy has no land, no army, nothing. He declares war in conquest for a holy land and then does nothing. My liege in the meantime keeps a standing army on the Eastern border of the Empire, but since there is no one to fight they are just hanging around. We are winning the war very slowly due to ticking war score, but it puts an unnecessary strain on the Empire and it's really annoying. My liege doesn't want to declare war either as it seems, while this war is ongoing... Anyone ever seen something like this? Is it because of HIP? (I haven't played in Byzantium before.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This should not be possible</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-20 19:39:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Meh... I changed my mind.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-31 20:32:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>M'lord, the council is most discontent.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-04 18:00:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The famous Siege of Rome</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-04 18:41:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Home, sweet home!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-18 20:48:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I always knew the Spanish flag needed more colors.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-12 20:25:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ahh, the famous mills of [RootGetName]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-18 16:40:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Found someone's archery range</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 22:23:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Make it happen! (x-post from r/titanfall)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-23 01:53:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Looks like Gravity Star is now OTK</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 23:34:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Quick flank route on Crash Site</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 03:37:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Don't be this guy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 19:00:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Instant karma</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-06 22:30:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Found this window of opportunity</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-24 17:56:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>EPG best gun (:</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-25 20:25:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>See, gravity sucks</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-25 21:32:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Titanfall 2] Gravity sucks</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-25 21:33:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>8v8 on Complex be like...:</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-04 22:36:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Spectating a ninja in live fire</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-13 00:48:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Showcasing the new pilot ordnance: the holonade</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-25 21:26:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Elegant way to counter rodeo with Ronin</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-25 21:52:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-06 03:09:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah, it's on ps4.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-06 18:24:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe you would have had to stand up onto the ledge of that window to return it...?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-06 20:06:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Depends on your region, in EU or NA the player count is fine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-06 21:38:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do you slide hop otherwise..?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-06 22:33:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I see people crouching, I assume they are new to the game tbh, you shouldn't tbag them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-06 22:35:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do you have so little time in air? :? The floor is lava, you need to improve on that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-06 22:37:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>The pictures are from titanfall 1.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-06 22:46:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Choose a loadout and stick with it. Set your sensitivity to an appropriate level, fitting with your play style. (Lower is preferred for AR's or smg's, higher for mostly everything else. This is my opinion at least. I like to play with higher than most people tbh.) Learn the movement system. It will take time to have all that in muscle memory along with the aiming, you will slide hop around without thinking about it in a couple hundred hours. ;) Then you will be able to assess situations and play accordingly more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-06 22:52:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most people here are playing on pc according to the straw poll we had earlier.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-06 22:59:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>No problem. It's not bad per se, but rather useless. The game has such an awesome movement system, you can dodge bullets easier running and slide hopping around than sitting in a corner. Even when I'm amping a hard point fe, I like to move around constantly, looking for enemies. If you are sitting in a corner you are going to get picked up by a pulse blade or something and die easier than if you were to move around. This is especially true for pc, where you don't even get the aim assist, therefore camping is basically useless, unless you are trying to take out a titan from your hideout. But you don't need crouching for that either, it's more useful to move around...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-06 23:02:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Meh, I just don't really have the time to bag. Have to hop away, that will teach them more than t-bagging.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-06 23:04:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reach lvl 50 and start buying before regeneration... Although, if I were you I would buy low profile.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-06 23:30:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Idk, my time is naturally at around 40% in air. Do you slide hop?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-07 00:23:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can still play around avoiding line of sight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-07 02:22:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>So next time play your match instead of leaving.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-07 11:57:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Here](https://youtu.be/ntWSepVH3YM)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-07 12:24:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Idk, but I played quite some ctf, pvp and LTS matches on it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-07 18:20:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>You didn't know that it's a figure of speech? If you say that something is unbearable, most of the time is not meant literally. There's nothing magical about this notion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-07 20:05:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why is it such a revelation then that "unbearable" pain is not in fact unbearable?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-08 02:28:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I played on it a couple times in various modes. Ctf, LTS, pvp, amped hardpoint iirc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-09 12:41:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>R #225;n #233;z #233;sre ezeknek a k #233;rd #233;seknek nincs sok  #233;rtelme, mivel a v #225;laszok csak a sz #233;ls #337;s #233;geket fedik le.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-10 04:21:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Join the rddt network.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-10 19:25:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you ads, it's a pinpoint accurate hitscan weapon and can kill in one hit if amped or by hitting a head shot. Thank God it has terrible sights.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-10 19:28:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>He is clearly on pc if he has a problem with kraber players.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-10 19:31:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>To counter kraber quick scopers you need to move fast and use your double jumps wisely. Same goes for every projectile weapon, though you will still get shot sometimes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-10 19:46:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>The game is trying to force you to slide hop.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-10 19:51:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Idk, i play it a lot. On pc. I can remember playing in every mode I have enabled on the map recently. Even had a free for all on it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-11 04:08:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>It does have it, except if it's amped.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-11 11:40:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe you need to aim in front of him. I heard the Volt and the rest of the smg's are projectile now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-11 11:54:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Should have it already, filthy casual.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-11 11:59:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>You already can't contest or amp a hp in phase iirc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-11 15:49:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm just joking.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-12 04:10:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can change network, that will change the happy hour.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-12 07:55:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it's good and very much needed, so you get punished for mistakes while running with the flag. You can cancel it btw by jumping backwards and then use the double jump to get up onto whatever you were climbing afaik.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-12 11:38:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's only important in LTS tbh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-12 11:43:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>How can you play an fps as a pc player on console? (Genuine question.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-12 14:49:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. Btw you can probably play online with every dlc enabled through steam if you find someone who has them and would play with you. You don't need to download the dlc's for this. At least this is true for eu4 and ck2.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-12 18:46:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just imagine how slow I could turn with a controller and honestly probably couldn't bear it. Sure, it goes both ways, but it still requires a different play style completely. Each to their own, I understand, but changing from mouse to controller seems awkward.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-14 22:11:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm skeptical about the second case, sometimes shots or explosions just don't register. Today I had a lot of grenades that went off but randomly didn't deal damage. The servers seem to be terrible periodically, I guess it's that time again. Melee is worse than it was 2 days ago again. I very rarely see cheaters btw.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-15 01:13:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>You get the same xp for every mode, except the double xp mode. That's always the "featured" one. For weapon xp, it's pvp; for titans it's lts. Load outs are similar because phase shift is op, but weapons vary in my experience. Ofc smg's are more popular, but every weapon is viable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-15 02:03:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only part of the sp, but there will be mp trial weekends later again. Probably about 2 months from now next time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-15 10:17:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>It would turn into pre buff spitfire.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tf2 jousting</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-15 11:54:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-15 11:55:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ctf Nitro is awesome.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-15 18:32:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>In EU I can find matches in reasonable time any time of any day basically. Am usually searching for a wide variety of modes and managed to find even free for all a couple times. Every mode is played.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-15 20:38:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ctf nitro only has the lf maps, drydock and forward base kodai plus the new map. Also played a lot of other modes, even free for all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-15 22:10:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only played ctf nitro lately, it's one of the maps of the mode, this much I know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-16 08:29:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, but some people don't bother to toggle "run" and don't know how to move while shooting otherwise.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-16 12:40:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>No.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-16 18:53:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't play Attrition much lately, but iirc they changed it so you can do it...? Or it was just an example of bad netcode when this happened to me a couple times in a game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-16 19:40:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>From what I heard the game is fairly slower on console and the meta is different. They use more assault rifles and a-walls and whatnot, while on pc the meta is more smg's. Also feel like the grandiers and sniper rifles see more use on pc, as you can make swingshots easier.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-16 20:27:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Play something other than Attrition...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-16 20:28:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, it was. I don't think there is any left not found.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-16 20:55:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would say that if you are not in the EU or in the US, then you would generally have problem finding matches outside of peak hours. Except if you are willing to play on far away servers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-16 21:22:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are no such things as records in titanfall 2 imo, except speedruns and gauntlet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-16 21:27:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>And the record is 5. :D Nah.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-16 22:00:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>He literally said that amped dmr is op. That includes dmr with a-wall.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-16 22:04:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've seen ppl spawn kill noobs with 100+ kills at the end. Really no need to keep track these since there is no matchmaking. He doesn't play competitively either btw.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-16 22:10:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>True, it's small and got smaller over time, but there were some organised matches, even tournaments. Private match "beta" and the insufficient spectator mode is really not encouraging the competitive scene.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-17 08:29:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, it's basically the spec mode you can see in live fire matches. It's only annoying because you can't see flags tbh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-17 08:35:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>PC population is pretty good in EU, kinda OK in the US and that's about it. You can change servers around though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-17 08:36:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>PC population is pretty good in EU, kinda OK in the US and that's about it. Other regions are under populated. You can change servers around though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-17 09:26:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is no mid on Meadows, you either spawn camp or play the objective.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-17 17:17:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Doesn't really matter, it's still basically spawn killing on Meadows...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-17 17:27:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's useful if you find an amped one. It's name is written in yellow in that case when you stand above it. Also good to get an smg as a secondary to your kraber.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-17 17:28:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Once I picked up an l-star with 2k kills and fast reload attached...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-17 19:01:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Idk why were people complaining about a-walls then, if no one used them anyway... xD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-17 20:30:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's like that since the game came out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-17 20:35:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you check integrity? Haven't heard of this issue so far.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-17 22:27:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>He turns sideways, but after the cut he's facing the ship again. :?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-17 23:20:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>The game is pretty casual already though...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-17 23:26:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>G23 is pretty good for the kraber, gj! I'm just nearing g10. Also have the epg at around g15 or so. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-17 23:31:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd run my fingers around those curves!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 06:28:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's a tooltip about it and a lot of people do it too. I don't think this is the reason ppl call you names.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 06:28:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kraber</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 06:39:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Idk, on pc a lot of ppl hop around.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 06:41:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Check benchy on yt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 12:39:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>You actually shot someone at the end!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 12:40:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd ask for real content instead tbh,this would be pretty useless.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 12:58:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't find it useful. People were asking for random executions, we got it. I couldn't care less... But I think we should stop asking for useless "improvements" because they still take time from devs and a whole bunch of these still take as much effort as bigger projects that are actually beneficial to everyone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 14:33:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>She should get it, it's a cool game. This is a shit post though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 19:13:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>What do you mean? Isn't glitch a remake as well? (Idc, haven't played the first titanfall.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 19:16:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This one?](https://www.reddit.com/r/titanfall/comments/5q5y6k/gravity_star_saved_me/) Yeah, it's cool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 19:43:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, i've seen some [tif 1 footage](https://youtu.be/APVMlaMJO3s) that was something similar, but apparently that's wargames...?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-19 00:54:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not in Attrition. Play something else.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-19 01:07:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>They said that there's a bug concerning that map in that mode since the last update so they took it out of rotation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-19 01:47:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>It has never been good on pc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-19 01:52:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>It looks like the wingman to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-19 09:31:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you damage it? Sentries have self-preservation coded into them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-19 09:34:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can join the rddt network too and ask around there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-19 09:39:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>This way you can still melee it safely. Or use anti titan weapons or the mastiff or anything that can one shot it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-20 18:18:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe play something other than Attrition. I played free for all and ctf just yesterday on dry dock.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-20 22:35:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>It should be nerfed anyway, just too strong on pc already.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-20 22:51:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are supposed to prove that you are good by actually playing well. You don't have to win for this. The people who go nuts ingame are the losers in my eyes, not the ones who actually lose. Try to help the newbies and do your best with what you are given.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-21 01:21:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't even remember to 2 of these from the game...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-21 16:17:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>The upcoming map looks really nice. Tbh I'm fine with anything that is not made with the layout of crash site and complex.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-21 22:37:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>What did they take out of rotation for what?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-21 22:38:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Never had problem in pvp on colony with the spawns. Although I usually spawn in that mode on that map like 5 times at most... But still. Edit: Nvm, saw your comment about the G2, you are on console.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-22 19:45:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>[You can](https://www.reddit.com/r/titanfall/comments/65icwu/tf2_jousting/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-22 20:09:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know, this happens sometimes when the servers are lame. Nades don't register.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-22 20:20:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Colony as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-23 01:02:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then again, it is perfectly fine on PC. You guys should ask for less aim assist imo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-23 01:13:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Depends on the platform and region, PC in EU and NA is good. You can also change servers to find games faster, but your ping would be higher obviously.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-23 01:17:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>So you are in Canada? Afaik the game has good population in NA on both platforms. (Population is better on PS, but the game is better on PC imo.) Not sure how the servers are located there though, I'm in EU.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-23 01:26:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was the other one that came after him, as he has the indicator about one being activated when he starts moving out after he shot it. (Even OP has the indicator at the start of the video.) They can't move after being activated.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-23 01:29:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, then, there it is. I think the player base is fine there except in like Australia. Xbox One Playerbase: Weekend: 21,657 Saturday(April 1) 9:00 PM EST Weekday: 9,373 Players online at Tuesday (April 18th ) 9 PM EST</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-23 01:34:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Ikr](http://i.imgur.com/0Mvpk0M.png)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-23 19:47:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's not true people running with gun runner look ridiculous and make me smile all the time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-24 08:20:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also you have to fire from the hip and tap it that way. So it's probably a pc thing again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-24 08:31:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's an excel sheet somewhere with all the weapon stats. Google will find it for you if you want it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-24 12:03:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>It removes bullet drop though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-24 12:08:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can see the target flying through the screen. It's a little misleading though as it looks like OP flicked his aim when he made the shot so it's hard to tell where was his crosshair when he actually made the shot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-24 16:20:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, 2k. Tomorrow is dlc day so it's gone get bumped up for some time. They release a dlc at the end of every month.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-24 17:17:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Amped kraber doesn't have bullet drop.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 10:25:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ask for less aim assist, there are no campers on pc, except the occasional dmr scumbags, but they are very rare.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 11:31:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This guy](https://gfycat.com/WelllitLividDragon). Pretty entertaining.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 11:42:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not in nitro ctf.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 11:37:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>He saw it. I x-posted that gif to r/gaming, so I know. He commented late, so his comment was pretty much lost though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 11:44:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>The verticality of maps and gameplay takes time to get used to. Also the movement system that's part of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 11:46:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is prerelease and on console. It might be a glitch, but not hacking for sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 11:49:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is precisely why I don't go outside, because I've seen a car accident once in a gif on reddit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 14:20:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Here](https://www.reddit.com/r/titanfall/comments/5pki3m/if_you_say_so/dcshlqb). He also commented on the x-post, but there are too many comments there...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 22:13:18</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;camper locations. What game are you even playing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 10:11:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seems small for ffa, but could be good nonetheless.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 11:34:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like glitch could be a permanent live fire map. Grabbing the flag actually makes sense there. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 11:41:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe just nerf it on pc. No one uses a-wall here anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 11:51:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>The particle walks are pretty strong against salvo. Even Legion's gun shield can eat it, but probably only if he's using the bulwark perk and if tone is using the reinforced wall. You have to shoot your rockets around it (like up to the sky and then back).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 15:18:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh. If it wasn't like [this](https://youtu.be/9dPwwy40uOg?t=9m52s) then yeah, it's a glitch. I rarely play tone, so idk.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 15:29:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a reference. A cruel one at that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 22:10:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Should have told your teammate that he's writing in the team chat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 22:11:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was really possible before the buff though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 22:15:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't do it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 22:50:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't worry, it happens all the time. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-28 21:57:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, k #243;kuszkocka too. Also, every second shit iirc. (Like if you write "shit shit" only one of them is censored.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>