<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject6173</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Not sure if this is rosacea. I've googled many different things and thought it was acne. It's been in the same place for months now and all signs  amp; symptoms lead to rosacea. I've tried many different treatments and might have to go to a dermatologist but any thoughts?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 03:15:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 13:14:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>It does and it flares after hot showers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 13:24:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry, I've tried different products/ treatments and eliminating certain foods. I haven't been to a derm yet and none of the products are prescription strength and that could factor into why they haven't worked. I'm using a topical cream now that is sold over the counter for rosacea but no results yet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 13:34:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>We're they able to diagnose what it was in one visit? I'm going to be paying out of pocket so I'd hope it's doable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 13:45:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>AK is a half day park, given you get fastpass for Pandora, if not, get there early in the morning so you can go right in. You should be done with the major rides and sightseeing by early afternoon. HS can be an all day park, especially with kids, if you include all the shops and shows. You can also take the boat from HS to Epcot, free of charge, to see the fireworks there in order to maximize your time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 22:53:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's called Prosacea, not expecting it to do much but any improvement is helpful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 20:42:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>The cutest</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 03:30:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would switch! I stayed at CBR recently and although some rooms aren't close to the main area, the resort is one of the most scenic and the grounds make the walk enjoyable and tranquil. The palm trees and the view of the water on your walk to the dining area are wonderful. I disagree on the bus service. There are multiple bus stops because it is such a large resort, which I found helpful and easier to just get on no matter where we were. The room I stayed in was renovated and wasn't a pirate room, I think most rooms are renovated there so that shouldn't be a problem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>2 week update using Prosacea</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 04:18:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 18:40:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>No! It's not bad at all</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 14:06:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Was this captured on your phone?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This is Oreo and he's the greeter at our menswear store!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 13:29:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>