<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject1064</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>First time at RTX</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-09 20:05:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I'm thinking about going to RTX London this year as I live in England so London is really convenient for me but it is my first time going to any convention and I'll be going alone. I'm not a super sociable person either. Any first convention tips or tricks I should know? How busy does it get as I sometimes struggle with crowds? Is it worth trying to get VIP tickets? Thank You!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-19 21:17:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>That I have depression and Anxiety. I only had to face this when I was put on antidepressants.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-23 02:20:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, I'm probably not one to talk about the social aspect since I'm the one who posted this in the first place but in terms of age I get why that would seem weird. Hell, when I go I'll only be 16! But I don't feel like age will be an issue. Rooster teeth creates content that can be enjoyed by all ages so you going enforces that! Besides, I very much doubt that you'll be the only older attendee there... I'm pretty sure that there are loads of other people wondering the same thing so I think you shouldn't worry about it (she says being a massive hypocrite with an anxiety disorder) and enjoy yourself! I'm pretty sure I'm going to go despite my worries! : )</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Musical help!!!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-05 17:31:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm currently trying to write my very first musical and I've got the story and characters as well as the lyrics to one song. I'm 15 and live in a rural town in England. I don't have and don't know how to find any actors, choreographers, musicians as I can't write sheet music very well or a location to put it on once I've actually written it! Also if anyone has any tips on writing songs and scripts that would be very much appreciated. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-05 19:43:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much! This is awesome advice and I'll be sure to message you when I need more help! Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-05 20:46:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you very much, luckily I have a few friends that share the similar ideas as me for this piece so hopefully I can go to them for support and a second opinion!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-06 20:50:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for your advice, the idea of once I have a complete draft I can enter it into festivals is amazing! I didn't really think of doing anything like that but it would be so good to see what can be kept and what can go! I hope you keep writing as well! I'm a bit overloaded at the moment as I have exams but writing is really relaxing for me so I'll make sure I keep it up! Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-06 20:51:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ooh I'll look into that! It sounds pretty good especially since finding new melodies for songs is pretty difficult! Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-06 20:55:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>This looks pretty useful so thank you! I'll be sure to watch a lot of musicals especially since they make up most of my life!  #128523; Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm scared</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-04 01:02:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Although I live in a rural area of southern England I'm really scared about the recent terror alerts and attacks. I'm only about an hours train ride from London and I have family in the surrounding area. All this news scares me and I don't know what to do about it. I'm 16 so I can't vote or anything if there were some sort of referendum on the topic. I don't want to be afraid because that's what terrorists want but I don't know how else to react. I'm seeing so many people responding this with hate such as "ban the burka" or "close all mosques" and I hate that. I refuse to fight fear with hate but I don't know how to feel. Any help would be much appreciated. X</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Birthday painting for my mother</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 18:45:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's my mums birthday in October and she is absolutely in love with a painting by Jo Quigley that is in the window of a shop in our village; however, it is  #163;349 which we can't afford but I want to save up and get it for her birthday. I worked it out and if I'm really good at not spending money and I have a job by July then I will have enough money in 3 months time. The issue is that I don't have the money now so I can't have the shop keep hold of it for me as I asked and they said I'd have to pay. If you have any tips on how I might be able to get money quicker or ensure that they can keep hold of it for me ( I was thinking of giving them a deposit but they didn't know if they could do that) then I would really like to hear them! I am 16 years old but currently don't have a job despite having been applying for a few months now but I should have one by July otherwise I won't have enough money. Thank you! Chloe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 22:52:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unfortunately not, the only job I could do would be babysitting but my mother says she doesn't want me doing that. I'm looking into retail and care assistant roles near me but have been turned down for a few months now. I'm volunteering at a charity shop to get experience so hopefully that will help,</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 02:21:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am 16 and identify as female but I wear a binder because it makes me feel more comfortable in my body as someone who is very boyish. I have B cup breasts and recently bought my first binder from the internet for a very low price so it's probably not the best quality but I'm saving up to get a proper one by beginning of 2018 hopefully. My problem is though that despite already having the worlds smallest boobs I feel like my binder is too loose and doesn't flatten them to the level that I want them to. Is there anyway to DIY tighten a binder bearing in mind that it is a clasp type one on my side and is very breathable currently to the point that I wonder if it's actually doing anything. Thank you and sorry if this is an off topic question, I'm new here! Chloe x</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"I'm..." pen on lined paper I've never been an artist (not a good one anyway!) but I wanted to throw this out there as a 5 minute doodle after hearing my grandmother (who taught me that it's okay not to be okay sometimes) is in hospital again.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-19 23:01:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"I'm..." pen on lined paper I'm not much of an artist (not a good one anyway, might be why this drawing was removed by r/art) but I wanted to throw out this 5 min drawing that I did just now after I was told that my grandmother (who told me it's okay to not be okay) is in hospital.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-19 23:11:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Please help</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-20 23:15:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello, I am 16 and currently work in a canteen like restaurant in which I serve hot food on hot plates next to and using a very hot pizza fire without proper arm protection (fair to say, not good) I feel that my current work is damaging my already weak mental state as I take antidepressants but because I can't seem to get the job right and I keep messing up its making me miserable. I spoke with my mother about the situation and she said that my generation were "snowflakes" and that no one likes there job so I need to "deal with it". I also spoke to my college career advisors who said that the environment could damage my mental wellbeing and strongly suggested I seek other employment. I don't know what to do. I'm miserable and self harming again and most days I'm wishing I was dead but I'm getting conflicting messages. No one at my job finds it fun even the managers don't like it there and I would talk to them but they are terrifying. I was taken into the back office yesterday and shouted at because I wasn't wearing my name badge because I forgot it at home despite my apologies. If anyone has any advice I would love to hear it because I'm feeling trapped right now. Thank you, Chloe x</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Advice needed</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 16:15:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello, I am 16 and currently work in a canteen like restaurant in which I serve hot food on hot plates next to and using a very hot pizza fire without proper arm protection (fair to say, not good) I feel that my current work is damaging my already weak mental state as I take antidepressants but because I can't seem to get the job right and I keep messing up its making me miserable. I spoke with my mother about the situation and she said that my generation were "snowflakes" and that no one likes there job so I need to "deal with it". I also spoke to my college career advisors who said that the environment could damage my mental wellbeing and strongly suggested I seek other employment. I don't know what to do. I'm miserable and self harming again and most days I'm wishing I was dead but I'm getting conflicting messages. No one at my job finds it fun even the managers don't like it there and I would talk to them but they are terrifying. I was taken into the back office yesterday and shouted at because I wasn't wearing my name badge because I forgot it at home despite my apologies. If anyone has any advice I would love to hear it because I'm feeling trapped right now. Thank you, Chloe x</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 20:43:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, I'm going to try job searching again, I wish I could just leave but I don't want to disappoint my mum. Thank you for the advice x</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 08:32:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you, good to know that other people have trouble as well and it's not just me. x</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Best route?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 19:40:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is the best route in terms of which order to go through the girls? Personally I did Sayori, Yuri then Monika and missed Natsuki which made me sad. I'm watching a let's play where they start with Yuri so what will happen? Which order did you play?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 21:58:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's pretty interesting actually! Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 21:39:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hell yeah you pass, great job dude!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 00:31:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>First of all please speak to your doctor or a trusted adult about this, especially if it becomes concerning. Secondly, be careful about watching tv shows or reading books in which characters experience mental illness as it is incredibly influential on people's behaviour. I am in no way saying that you have been influenced but it may be that this show has increased this issue for you to a more noticeable standard. I am not a medical professional and I really think it would be good for you to seek advice from them but this does sound like a form of multiple personality from my limited reading on the subject, especially in the form of them having somewhat of their own life. In short please speak to a trained medical professional! That will be the best thing for you to determine whether this is a medical matter or if it will go away in time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 21:56:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I absolutely would! Where did you hear this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 22:26:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Worthing, down south but not that bad :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 01:19:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>My comforter. A blanket I've had since I was born. It's always kind of embarrassing since I often struggle to sleep without knowing it's near me and I'm 16. It has helped when I needed it though when I have late night crying fits it's always there to help even though I've ripped holes in it and thrown it it's always there for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 01:28:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>My first thought was Alfie</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>After over a month of waiting (as I had to get a different size than I thought due to my weirdly proportioned shoulders) I FINALLY GOT A PROPER BINDER!!!!! I have managed to get stuck in it several times but I am so happy!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 19:01:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 19:31:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 19:33:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's so nice! Gc2b is great but I spent way too much money on it  #128523;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 17:37:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, I got number 4!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 17:37:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! I'm really happy  #128522;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 17:42:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not great. Still alive but self harming again after a clean streak of about a month. Started CBT and have been on 100mg of Sertraline (despite only being 16) for a while but still not great.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 01:07:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please know that I'm trying my best to reach the standards you set for me but that I won't always BE the best. Context: I got an E in my psych test and considering that I've only been learning psychology for 6 months I was pretty happy, only 5 marks of a D which is a pass in my school. My mum got pissed at me saying I wasn't trying hard enough and need to study more (I already study 5 hours per subject every week at least) far to say I won't be sharing my results with her anymore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 02:31:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>If she is being physically hurt and scared for her life then call the police immediately. I have a friend who was in an abusive household and the high expectations of perfection sound very similar. If she is not being physically hurt but is still scare then I highly recommend talking to someone. You say you are 14 (I apologise is I got that wrong) so speak to a trusted adult. Your parents or teachers, at my school we had specific staff for emotional wellbeing and they greatly helped. As parents it's their responsibility to raise their children in a safe environment and if that isn't being upheld then it's an issue. It's very likely that if you talk to someone then she will be recommended therapy which is a good thing. Please be there to support her through all this and get her help!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>An example of my handwriting, advice very much appreciated especially on how to keep handwriting consistent</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 00:35:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 13:25:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Woah, thanks! That's really helpful!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Depresseddreamer's circle</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 02:39:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 02:43:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>My key is: Thisisstrange I don't mind who joins I'm just doing this because it looked interesting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 01:13:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have super specific dairy allergies where I cannot eat certain things such as cheeses and yoghurts but other things like chocolate are fine so people normally think I #8217;m lying (I #8217;m not. I have an epi-pen for a reason) anyway my stepdad thought I was just a liar so when making mashed potato he put cheese in the mix so I wouldn #8217;t know and he could prove me wrong. Needless to say I had an allergic reaction causing major swelling and had to go to hospital. Not fun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Help please</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 00:49:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, so I got tickets today for me, my friend and my mum to go see a k-pop group my friend and I really like (BTS) my mums coming for back up as I have social anxiety I #8217;m still getting over so concerts are an idea that super freak me out but I know I can do. But, the concert is in London, at the O2 and will be packed, basically all the tickets are sold out and since the Manchester attack my anxiety has gotten worse about crowded places. I know security will be prepared but the thought terrifies me. Is there anything I can do? Any advice would be really helpful  #128531; Thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Please help I #8217;m so damn lost</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 14:03:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s like a techno dance song from this year that my little brother really wants to know. It came out around the time of Havana but all he knows it The it goes do do do do dodo do do do do I #8217;m so sorry it #8217;s so vague but I #8217;m losing my mind trying to find it  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 21:20:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope, thanks anyway</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 03:19:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, this is weird. I #8217;ve been cutting on and off for a while and don #8217;t intend to tell anyone but does anyone else ever feel like they can #8217;t even cut properly? I feel like when I think of cutting I think of scars from deep cuts but mine a just scratches on my stomach. I don #8217;t know, I feel crazy for thinking that I can #8217;t even self harm properly. I think it #8217;s mostly because what I do, my small scratches with a razor that heal in a few weeks, isn #8217;t taken seriously compared to people who have scars for a long time and cut deeper. I don #8217;t know, just wanted to rant I guess.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>