<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject9917</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-27 21:23:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am not really sure exactly what causes but I have a few ideas like issues with friends, parents constantly lecturing me for everything, parents telling me how I have no friends (and other things) always being alone, horrible social anxiety, etc.. Edit: also having 5 hours of homework every night doesn't help</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-27 22:41:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know if I would be able to get to one, but if I could I don't know if I even would. When it comes to being social I am a total mess. I always result to the shortest possible things I can say, never ask questions, avoid saying anything, and I have even had stomach pains/nausea. Then there is stuff like issues with friends, people generally ignoring me, overwhelming amounts of homework (3 hours is very little and 5 hours is the expected amount per night), parents having 0 respect for me as a person, parents telling me stuff like how I have no friends, etc..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-27 22:48:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>The issues are all my fault. It is stuff like me being the "place holder" for another friend, being forgotten, heavily outspoken, and things like that. And it isn't just my friends, really everyone does this to me or treats me even worse. So I just stick with this since it isn't as bad. I've considered joining clubs many times but I don't know if I ever could. Besides being too nervous to, I already have too much homework and have no hobbies/interests/skills. Basically all I do is homework, video games, and Reddit. Going to public gives me nausea, stomach aches, and are just generally really stressful. And the reason they say that is because I never join clubs or do anything and they always yell at me for it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-28 01:01:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have tried many things but something always stops me from pursuing it further. I once played pool a lot, thought I got pretty good, first time my brother plays and he was already better. That happens all the time and so I just gave up. The one thing I seem to actually be good at doing is researching suicide methods. Not the best skill but it should come in handy pretty soon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-28 02:56:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>With who I am intrinsically I don't think I would be able to live on this world. I don't work very fast, I am very reclusive, there is nothing exceptional about me, I just have a long list of undesirable things. And I'm sorry for continuing to waste your time, I don't know why I am bothering you with all this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-29 02:25:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bojack Horseman portrays it really well if your interested.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-29 03:42:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>That movie looks pretty good, I will have to watch it at some point. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-30 13:09:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was just the simplest and most recent example of things like this. A few weeks ago there was a small party (it was only like ten people). At some point I realized I wasn't really contributing to the conversation so I moved to the side, my place was immediately replaced and I was forgotten.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-01 05:35:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>The issue is I won't really be heard no matter what. My voice is really quiet and no matter how hard I try it stays the same volume unless I am shouting (which I would assume isn't very loud either but hate doing it none the less). If there is a decent amount of noise going on there have been times where I can't even hear myself talk.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-03 03:30:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry I didn't respond earlier. I really hate being alone and wish I could be with my friends more. But I don't think anyone ever realizes that because I am always so quiet, which again I hate. I haven't talked to any professionals either, just two of my friends (one who doesn't talk to me anymore and the other doesn't want to talk about all this).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-03 15:32:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't do anything so there is nothing to invite them to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-04 04:14:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I remember posting here a while ago and the only response was:  gt; don't  gt; [helpline number]</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-04 04:37:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was nice to know I wasn't worth the effort to write a complete sentence or even capitalize it for that matter.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-14 04:42:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is nice to finally have a supportive response from someone rather than the usual ones that make me feel even worse. One of the many things I worry about is that I am wrong about all this. I have just convinced myself this is how I feel due to some subconscious reason. Maybe I want to have close friends/a support group, maybe I just want attention (probably not, hate being the center of attention), I am not really sure. Then there are also the things that point to it on the subconscious level. Like I have always had long hair, I would always get along better with girls than guys, just a lot of little things. I spent some time browsing /r/asktransgender/top and was fascinated by it. It was very interesting but then I felt guilty since I couldn't relate to most of the posts. I will probably look at the chat room at some point but they often give me anxiety so I am not really sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-15 04:54:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't stop questioning the legitimacy of my feelings. I say I want to, but there is still the thought that I am just saying that for whatever reason. Like it's not real and I a making it all up, I don't know what to do about it. And I'm sorry for wasting you time with this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-16 05:12:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry I have been taking so long to respond, it is difficult for me to do it during the day. I don't know how I can get to a therapist though. Telling my parents isn't something I am too keen on doing and going myself isn't an option. And the more I think about it, the more right it sounds but I have no idea where to go from here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-16 05:38:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>One thing that has been causing me stress lately is that I don't know how it is supposed to feel. What if I am misinterpreting things and I'm not trans? I don't identify as female but I feel like I would be more comfortable if I was, but then I could be totally wrong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-18 04:36:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think I realize now that I have always felt this way but would suppress it. I remember from way back having a dress, thinking of myself as a princess, and even being Hermione (from Harry Potter) for Halloween one year. After that I began denying those feelings (I am assuming that was the case) and pretended they never happened.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-18 05:23:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>The issue is I am not really sure what I can do here. I don't know how I can try any of the things you suggested and I am not sure how I can get therapy for it. Then there is the issue of depression and some form of anxiety to make everything more difficult.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-18 22:41:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know, this whole thing is making me very stressed and nervous. Every solution that I can think of only causes more problems and it seems that killing myself is my only option.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-19 00:44:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have considered it many times but I am always too nervous. And when I get too nervous I get in a panic which makes more problems which make me panic more. What else can I do?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-19 03:47:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know that I really should get help for it but I doubt it would be worth it. It really solve the problems I am facing and only removes my escape option.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-19 04:24:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I meant to say that it wouldn't solve my problems. But I doubt things can or would get better. I don't have any hobbies, good skills, interests, nothing. Getting help won't change any of that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-19 05:04:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess that I will try it at some point in the near future, what should I expect/need to know?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 00:05:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry I haven't gotten around to responding until now. I don't know if I will actually seek help, it doesn't sound like a good idea anymore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-15 03:36:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>It made me actually feel like I wasn't alone for a while. It was really pathetic but I felt like I always had friends with me and that I wasn't alone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-15 04:15:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have tried similar things and every time it leads to a half hour lecture about how I am disrespectful or they guilt me out of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I am so pathetic attempting suicide for attention seems like something I might do</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-17 23:31:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>A few months ago I thought someone doing that was ridiculous and misguided, that they were crazy and selfish. The worst part is all of those adjectives describe me. I am just so sick of being invisible to everyone and ignored. I have been with my friends where they don't even acknowledge my existence and it isn't uncommon, this happens all the time with everyone. Why is it so hard to have one person actually realize that I have emotions and care about them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-18 20:37:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>This stuff pisses me off so much. I spend 6 hours in school everyday, that's not that terrible, just so I can do 5-7 hours of homework *every* night. That is about 12 hours of work non-stop 5 days a week and I don't even get paid for it. Slap on everything else I have to do and it becomes unbearable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm stuck in limbo</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-27 04:26:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>For a while I was just biding my time until I would kill myself. I had everything planned and I thought I was ready. Then everything changed. My English teacher gave a very passionate speech about suicide for 30 minutes of the 40 minute class and it just fucked up everything. I cant do it anymore, I never really thought of the amount of people I would hurt. Part of the reason I planned to do this was so I would stop hurting others, I do it unintentionally and I never forgive myself. This morning I started playing the game Life is Strange (a choice-based story game) which has been incredible and I played it for almost 7 hours today. Playing it makes me feel like I actually have good friends who care about me and that I don't screw up every social situation, that I am not such a failure. But as soon as I leave the fantasy world I just realize that I have none of that. This puts me in the limbo, I need to kill myself to fix everything but I just can't.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>All I want is a best friend</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-28 03:36:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even something that simple is too much to ask for. I just want someone who I can do stuff with, trust, hang out with, stupid stuff like that. All I have are a handful of friends to whom I am a mere after-thought. Then came the game Life is Strange. It made me feel like I had a close friend while I played it. It's really pathetic but I even became upset when certain things happened (trying to be spoiler-free). It allowed me to live my fantasy for some time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I don't even enjoy video games, I just use them as a distraction since I am not good at anything else</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-28 13:33:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-29 01:30:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was really great when I was still playing it, finally beating that boss you had been stuck on for such a long time (looking at you NG+ O amp;S).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-29 01:39:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't play most multiplayer games because of that exact reason. In single player I have no one to compare myself to so in my eyes I am the best.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm not going to make it through high school</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-01 00:36:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't need comments like "your so young", "high school is so short", etc.. It doesn't help, makes me feel worse, and I really don't care. Right now I am in high school and right now I am miserable and suicidal. I'm not anti-social, in fact I would love to be talking to everyone, but I can't. If I don't expect something in a conversation I panic, and when that happens I have even lost the ability to talk. Whenever there is a conversation that I hold up in I always say what I am thinking in the shortest manner possible. Sometimes when people do things such as thank me I pretend not to here then to avoid speaking. Everything thing I say is an arduous task. When it comes to clubs and sports I do none. Which makes sense when I am too scared to say simple things such as "thank you" and "your welcome", but I absolutely despise myself for it. I never do anything besides school, I just stay home all the time. Which is a product of the fear of speaking and a horrible fear of public places. In school I do have friends, which is nice, but out I have none. Even in school I am never someone people look at and think "I want to talk to them", I am always the person people go to when there is absolutely no other option. And when anyone else they know comes along I am immediately abandoned. It isn't a matter of bad friends either, everyone does it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I can't deal with high school</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-01 02:18:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't need comments like "your so young", "high school is so short", etc.. It doesn't help, makes me feel worse, and I really don't care. Right now I am in high school and right now I am miserable and suicidal. I'm not anti-social, in fact I would love to be talking to everyone, but I can't. If I don't expect something in a conversation I panic, and when that happens I have even lost the ability to talk. Whenever there is a conversation that I hold up in I always say what I am thinking in the shortest manner possible. Sometimes when people do things such as thank me I pretend not to here then to avoid speaking. Everything thing I say is an arduous task. When it comes to clubs and sports I do none. Which makes sense when I am too scared to say simple things such as "thank you" and "your welcome", but I absolutely despise myself for it. I never do anything besides school, I just stay home all the time. Which is a product of the fear of speaking and a horrible fear of public places. In school I do have friends, which is nice, but out I have none. Even in school I am never someone people look at and think "I want to talk to them", I am always the person people go to when there is absolutely no other option. And when anyone else they know comes along I am immediately abandoned. It isn't a matter of bad friends either, everyone does it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-01 03:20:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had two friends at one point who I were comfortable talking about this with, they quickly abandoned me so I don't really want to deal with that again. And not really, going out and doing stuff like that is the thing that makes me panic and I feel awful whenever I ask stuff like that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-01 04:59:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only people that I am comfortable saying anything to are my friends, parents, and brother. I don't really feel confident saying anything to my friends, my relationship with my parents is kind of bumpy, and my brother can't keep anything to himself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-01 20:39:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>They would probably be ok with it but I don't think I would be able to anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-02 01:58:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I explained it on the OP.  gt; I'm not anti-social, in fact I would love to be talking to everyone, but I can't. If I don't expect something in a conversation I panic, and when that happens I have even lost the ability to talk. Whenever there is a conversation that I hold up in I always say what I am thinking in the shortest manner possible. Sometimes when people do things such as thank me I pretend not to here then to avoid speaking. Everything thing I say is an arduous task.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm really nervous that I'm trans</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-07 03:30:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let me start by saying that I am by no means transphobic or anything of the sort. (Little thing that may help is that my birth sex is male and I have always felt more comfortable with girls and women.) Back before Kindergarten I distinctly remember having thought of myself as a girl and doing/liking things that girls do. That kept up until some point in the 1st grade where I realized that wasn't normal and I stopped doing it. Skip a few years to 3rd grade where I grew out my hair to about my shoulders and didn't cut it much until halfway through 5th grade. Skip to 10th grade (now) where I finally realized that being trans is a possibility. I have been thinking about this a lot for the past few weeks and I am really unsure what I am going to do. Say I am, that brings up a lot of things I really don't want to deal with such as issues with the high school, losing all my friends, how my parents would react (they are both *extremely* judgmental), and stuff like that. I am not too familiar with the process but I am already really self conscious about my looks (such as only wearing solid-colored shirts so people won't judge me for that) and I want to draw any attention to myself. Sorry for the long post, I could probably write a lot more but that would just be more of a turn-off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-07 03:51:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>With a choice like that I would almost undoubtedly take the switch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-13 13:56:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not religious either but maybe it could be seen as a form of self-discovery?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-13 19:07:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sorry I wasn't really thinking when I said that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How can I tell this isn't "just a phase"?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-22 03:05:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Little background: 15 and male by birth. When I was young (before school) I thought of myself as a girl and some other things, once school started that went away after kindergarten. Had mostly girls as friends for a year or two after that, then about halfway through middle school had mostly girls as friends again. All through this time I didn't really question. Probably had a lot more info than I needed but I wanted to be sure I was through. I haven't been thinking about his possibility for very long (month or two). One thing that has been bothering me during this time is what I assume is dysphoria (trapped, unease, etc.) but that might just be a product what I assume is depression (including all the fun things such as hopelessness, loneliness, worthlessness, suicidal thoughts, and everything in that realm). One response I expect to get is to talk to my parents, but I don't really know if that's a good idea. They are constantly gossiping about everything going on in my family, seem transphobic, how accepting they are is a little iffy, and they aren't always the best people. But I don't really know. I'm just looking for some advice, but it might not matter very soon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-25 02:47:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was using Alien Blue so I thought I was on /r/asktransgender, good thing it was on an actual sub related to what I was posting about for once.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[15, MTF] Need some help</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-25 02:48:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, So I haven't said anything to my parents or anyone at all and have kept this to myself for about 2 months. Obviously the first step would be come out to my parents and get to therapy but I don't know what to do then. Transitioning during high school sounds like a horrible idea as I already have anxiety and announcing it to the whole class sounds like a nightmare let alone the staff. I could say nothing but that would cause it's own problems. There are a few more things I'm concerned about but I don't wan to make this post too long.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-25 03:08:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>The other things are stuff like how my parents will react, how my (honestly very few) friends will react, if this is really a good idea, etc.. Something I had forgot to mention in the OP was that when I was about much younger that would definitely act as "signs", such as thinking of myself as a girl (openly to my parents). That is only one of the more prominent examples so I doubt it being a phase would be much of an issue. One thing I really don't want to do is draw attention to myself. I already have such low self esteem that I don't want to wear shirts that have anything on them due to fear of bullying. So doing something as drastic as a dress doesn't really sound too appealing, but neither does simply announcing it so I don't really know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-25 03:11:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't really know how severe it is since I haven't found any solid basis of what to judge it off of. Generally there is a feeling of being trapped and things just seem off. Occasionally something triggers it to become bad but for the most part it doesn't seem that bad. But that might just be because it is covered by (what I assume is) depression. The rest sounds good and thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-25 18:42:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>For the most part it's bodily, I feel trapped and just generally off. Male pronouns don't bother me but occasionally people accidentally refer to me as female and it just feels right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 03:09:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Inside Out As pathetic as it sounds it actually made me feel less alone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What does it feel like to have friends that care about you?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 03:14:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have always had shitty friends who didn't really care about me, so what is it like? Is it as great as I imagine it to be?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>School starts again tomorrow</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 04:51:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>And I am really nervous because of that. When in school I am stuck in a perpetual state of panic, depression, and loneliness. So many things can trigger the suicidal thoughts it is like navigating a mine field. Then I finally get home just to have several hours of homework just to repeat it again. I can't wait until I can finally muster the energy to finally kill myself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I am afraid to talk</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-05 04:53:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>To put things into context I am in high school. Sometimes I have small panic attacks (I don't what else to call it) during certain social situations. What happens is sweat starts pouring down my neck, I can't speak, I become extremely nervous, and generally get panicky. It almost always happens when presenting something but will occasionally happen when simply talking I don't know what else to do but avoid talking.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-06 03:55:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry for the late reply. I have said anything to anyone because, well, I'm too nervous too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Everyone is all for helping the depressed and suicidal</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-07 04:56:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Until they realize it takes more than a 5 minute talk to fix everything, then it's fuck you you're on your own.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The stress and fatigue from keeping it inside for so long is unbearable</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-13 00:29:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Little context, I'm in high school. And please don't give me the old "it sucks for everyone", "it gets better", or the "you're so young though!" So for a little under a year I have had almost constant suicidal thoughts plaguing my mind. Recently they are no longer thoughts and are creeping into the realms of planning. For instance last night I had the constant urge to, right at that moment, go and kill myself on the spot. I was able to eventually relax myself and get to sleep before I could do anything. This was the first time it has ever been this bad, and I thought I almost couldn't do it, but I do this almost every night. Fight the thoughts until I sleep. Then there is the stress of school added on and it comes out to be one big mess. I have tried talking to two of my close friends (who thankfully) abandoned me and didn't say anything to anyone. In the end I regret it both times so I am very reluctant to try again. I don't think I will be able to take this for much longer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-13 01:12:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>In general I don't really trust anyone anymore so I don't know who to go to. Depression, anxiety, loneliness, failing constantly, many screw ups, lack of social skills, lack of interests, being afraid of public places, stress and things of that sort just kind of congregated to put me where I am now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-13 02:00:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>The other day I spent several hours trying to come up with a reason as to why I shouldn't. The entire time I couldn't come up with anything, only reasons I should. This world has no use for someone like me. So I ask, is there really a reason I should seek help?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-13 03:36:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sorry for poking wholes in this but it's the best way I can think to reply. Basically if I wasn't depressed I would be nothing. For my entire life I pretended to be someone else, a more interesting person. Eventually it washed away my true personality and left me with a one dimensional image everyone saw me with. It's too late to go back. But depression is something, it adds a dimension to my void of personality. I too am terrified of everything and it prevents me from doing anything. I want to seek help but am too afraid, yet I am also afraid of what will happen if I don't. In this situation not seeking help takes less effort so I just go with that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-14 04:31:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>One issue I have is my fear of speaking to anyone that I am not very comfortable with. It's to the point of being too afraid to say simple things like "thank you", "your welcome", etc.. So meeting anyone new is an absolute ordeal that takes forever and everyone moves on long before I can get to showing my pseudo-personality. All this then branches into other issues like not being able to speak in front of a group without panicking and other such issues. On an unrelated note I couldn't handle an assignment for my Latin class that is near identical to a test I have tomorrow so failing both of those will be great. And because of the Latin assignment I didn't do any of my other homework! Which includes studying for two other tests. So I failed all those.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-15 17:42:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>The teacher is really horrible and everyone hates her. She will fail you if she doesn't like you, get pissed if you don't understand something, squees the weights of assignments to effect grades, etc.. Besides I'm too scared to ask for any kind of help so I would probably be too scared.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Depression is my personality</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-15 17:58:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I constantly think to myself just how easy it would be to do</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-20 00:55:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just end all of my problems in an instant. Never have to worry again. Never have to suffer again. Is there any legitimate reason to keep going?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>High school is making me suicidal</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-21 05:04:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is a constant stream of work, there is no break, it never ends. When one teacher doesn't give homework that doesn't mean there isn't work from them, they expect you to constantly study every night especially when the don't assign anything. Well it's kind of difficult to work that in when there are hours of worked piled on from all the other classes. Then there is the issue that I can't focus on most things for more than 20 minutes. I have so much trouble simply sitting down and getting things done. And I know that the grades don't really matter but I still can't not do them. I feel so incredibly guilty for not doing something and seeing my grades constantly dropping is so crushing. There isn't much of an issue of not having friends (of course not a lot), there is however the issue of not having any meaningful friends. I am the filler friend, when I'm there people will talk to me and when I'm not no one cares. I'm the first to be left behind and the last to be remembered. I'm always the after thought. And the only reason anyone even talks to me is because I have been able to create a fairly likable persona. The title may not fit perfectly and it may be a little weird but that's because I edited it quite a bit. And I don't really know why since no one will read it or care anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I am terrified to go to school</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-24 04:41:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>The constant stress, the constant work, the constant loneliness, I just can't take it anymore. Saturday is the only day that I can fully relax, every other day is just the same nightmare again and again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I love sleep yet I still hate it</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-01 05:05:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sleeping is the only time I can relax and not worry about anything, but I know that sleep brings on the next day faster. With a new day it means that I have to leave the comfort and safety of my bed then the house.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[15, MTF] Not really sure what to do</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-03 04:42:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thankfully I don't seem to have any real dysphoria, just the desire to be a girl. So that's great but I don't really know where to go from here. Obviously one of the first steps would be coming out to my parents but of course that can't be easy. To start there is my general relationship with them, it isn't bad but kind of distant I guess. I try to keep most things about myself a secret and always use a facade. Then there is also that I am the youngest and most "normal" child (my two older siblings have mental issues) so they never spoke to me about a lot of things such as sex. Also, they are not accepting people at all. They believe people who are depressed and/or those that go to therapy are crazy, people who talk about emotions are crazy, stuff like that. However I don't know how they feel about trans folk, I know they hate Caitlyn Jenner but that might just be because they find her to be a shitty person. The issue is I am fairly sure that I am depressed, have some kind of anxiety disorder, and need multiple types of therapy. So yeah, I don't really know what I should do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-03 05:10:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>The thing is, I am not really sure how they would react they might flip out or be really accepting. The only way I could see any doctor or therapist would be through them and talking to someone at school doesn't sound good either due to social anxiety.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-03 15:36:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't really go anywhere since I live in the middle of no where. And I am pretty sure there isn't any other way I can get help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-11 04:29:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Many times a day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Sort of long] Pretty much everything there is about me</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-15 04:10:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Background: I am a 15 year old closeted transgirl (MTF) in high school. My parents aren't very accepting and are very republican who I don't ever talk to about anything meaningful. In school I don't have any meaningful friends, just people I would hang out with and talk to in school. I haven't been diagnosed with anything but I would imagine I have severe depression, severe social anxiety, anxiety, and a small chance at minor OCD (doubt that last one very much) and the cherry on top is suicidal thoughts day-in-day-out. In school we just began reading Catcher in the Rye, already I know it is a bad idea for me to read. With how the book is written I project myself into Holden and whenever something like this happens it always makes me very suicidal. Knowing I couldn't ever have a life half as normal as his completely screws up my head. Now I know his life is a mess but he is actually able to talk to people in a normal conversation and not flounder, panic, and hate myself after. This post probably won't have a logical progression, since I will write stuff as it comes to me. I always have these absolutely ridiculous recurring fantasies about normal things like having friends that don't treat me like shit. That is another thing, most of my friends have treated me like shit, but that is unrelated. One of the more outrageous ones is having a (mildly) successful YouTube channel. And it isn't because I want money, fame, or anything else, I just want to be part of a community and bring other people happiness. But of course I am too young, unoriginal, unambitious, and anxiety-ridden to do it. This really bothers me but I will try to write it out anyway. About a year ago I tried to talk to two of my closest friends about some of these issues. It started out great with them being really supportive, a week or two later one of them grew increasingly distant from me until they eventually abandoned me entirely. The other friend held through for a while longer but eventually started giving hints that they didn't want to deal with me anymore. Through the power of denial I was able to ignore all those signs and come up with fictitious excuses as to why they were ignoring me, avoiding me, and all sorts of obvious things. The workload from school is completely overwhelming to me and I often can't deal with it. When things overwhelm me I begin to panic and it makes the situation far more difficult than it should be. Not to mention I tend to do work slower so what would only be about an hour or two of work becomes a 5 hour ordeal. If you somehow made it this far thank you for actually caring enough to read about my shitty excuse for a life. I really don't know what I should do from here other than the obvious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-15 06:07:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have heard it an unbelievable amount of times, but the issue is this is all I have none, how can I expect things to change? It doesn't seem to be an issue with the people either, it is my fault. And say that I do make it through then what? Not to sound edgy but the whole idea of going to college, getting a job, getting married, and having kids just so they can repeat the cycle isn't something I want.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[TW] Coping with a certain dysphoria</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-27 04:40:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>How am I supposed to deal with not being a "real girl". Now I am pre-everything and so deep into the closet I'm in Narnia (close enough, right?) so I don't know if all of this goes away or something of the sort. When it comes down to it no amount of hormones, make up, or anything really will cover that I am a trans girl. I can't ever be cis no matter how much I want to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-28 21:22:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably not the kind of answer you are looking for but Bullet by Hollywood Undead. Just everything about it is too relatable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I can't decide what I want from myself</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-02 01:25:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>At some points I have horrible dysphoria and all I want is to transition, then at other times I am blatantly opposed to doing it since I'm happy with who I am. I am so confused and I don't know what I should do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Young trans teen looking for some help/guidance</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-03 02:28:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Little background: MTF in high school Simply put I have a fair bit of suicidal thoughts, by a fair bit I mean always on my mind, even just at the back. Now I know I should get help but I would need my parents help and that probably wouldn't work out. I am not very close to them at all and they legitimately know nothing about me (not "they don't understand me"). I don't even know if there is anything about me, my personality is too shallow and I never do anything. As a result I have no real friends, sure I have friends but only in school. People only want to talk to me when I'm around. I got off track and at this point I should probably post this in a different sub but whatever, back to trans stuff. The first issue is, once again, is my parents. They are both very republican and are not very accepting or open minded. One thing I have seen is that they think stuff like depression is on the same level as schizophrenia in terms of mental illnesses. Now I'm guessing I'm depressed since everything points to it but I am not really sure. Dysphoria wise it comes and goes, sometimes I can't understand why I would ever be trans others it's the only thing I can think about. I don't know where I should go from here. I feel trapped by my body, mind, home, life, and school and I am actually becoming claustrophobic from it, if that doesn't sound too crazy. If you made it here and do decide to reply please bear with me, for these kinds of posts I often get overwhelmed by the replies and take forever to reply. Sorry for generally annoying throughout the post.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-03 03:19:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>16, but when I get scatter brained posts like these happen. Something I forgot to say in the OP is that (again, no diagnosis going off assumptions) that I have social anxiety and some other form of more general anxiety. And so saying anything to anyone that I am not comfortable talking to takes a lot of effort. I also don't think I can trust any of them. Also, I know that I am being difficult and I am really sorry for that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-03 03:45:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really am not sure how they would react beyond their political views because of other reasons. One thing they have made very clear is that they think talking about emotions or feelings is bad. And thus I have kept everything bottled up for at the very least 10 years which is about 2/3 of my life. Now I don't want you to get the wrong idea, I love them and they never said any of these things to me explicitly and I don't want that to change.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The idea that not everyone seriously contemplates suicide frequently is so strange to me</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-03 04:47:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-03 23:08:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>At this rate I doubt I will even make it to 18, but whatever. When I was much younger (3 or 4 maybe) I remember some very obvious signs I was trans (down to calling myself a girl almost constantly). At some point I completely repressed all that until recently and I assume that my parents assumed it was just kids being kids. My parents divorced at some point and so my dad might not even have known about any of that, I'm not really sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-05 00:04:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sorry, it's been on my mind everyday for almost a year and I can't stop thinking about it. When I say this I'm not trying to be rude, but why would anyone ever love me? I can't even manage to have close friends, I did once and I quickly fucked that up. This is probably said by everyone, but I don't want to be trans. I just want to be a cis girl. I know it isn't possible and I will always be stuck as trans. And for grades I'm not smart enough and often can't handle the work from school. I am failing two classes and hardly pass the rest. I just don't know what else I can do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-07 05:02:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was just reading your post, and I can't contribute a ton but none the less there is something I wanted to say. Life is Strange had a similar effect and if I transition I might just have to go with the name Chloe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How should I go about coming out to my parents and where should I go from there?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-07 05:26:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>15, MTF What comes after coming out to them? Where do I go from there?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I feel claustrophobic from life</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-10 00:54:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Something to add is that I am in high school. Basically I am stuck between home and school, there is no where else for me to go. Everyday it is exactly the same. I don't think I would even be able to kill myself due to the fear of living and going to a mental hospital. Those places seems like everything that makes me stressed and nervous packed into one place I have no freedom in making every ting worse. I don't know what I should do anymore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-10 01:17:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, that is part of why I can't go anywhere.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-10 01:56:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am too athletically inept for sports, I am not religious, and no club in school sounds like a good idea. Even if I went to one who would even want to talk to me?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-10 02:14:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is true too and I doubt I could handle any kind of job interview much less manage to keep the job for long. But maybe a mental hospital wouldn't be that bad, I have never been in one so I don't really know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-10 03:20:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Another thing I have realized is that this sub might not actually be the best place for help. I once accidentally posted to an unrelated subreddit and it got a lot more attention and support than any other post I have made here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-10 03:36:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is true but it was interesting to see it garner so much attention. I guess I had gotten so used to it I assumed everyone dealt with it/no one cared.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Has anyone tried the Crisis Text Line before?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-10 04:19:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am thinking about trying it at some point but it is making me stressed and I need some help with it. Stuff like what should I expect, what do I need to do, how can I not disappoint/waste the time of the person on the other end, etc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How can I know that everything I have been feeling isn't fake/a phase?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-13 19:26:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Little background: I'm a teen in high school, think I'm trans and have had frequent suicidal thoughts for around a year. Basically I don't know what to do anymore. I got to thinking about how I am always hearing about how all of these things turned out to be phases in teenage years and how everyone has suicidal thoughts at this age, but how do I know I am not one of those people? That I just made this all up and everything I have been feeling for the past year has been fake?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-13 20:34:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for the help. But I don't know where I am supposed to go from here. I don't have anyone close to me, even my immediate family. I learned pretty quickly that people don't like who I am so I just decided to always act as a different person, at this point I am getting really tired of doing it and I can't stop myself it has become a default thing I do. On top of that I am terrified to talk to most people so getting professional help would be incredibly difficult and I just feel trapped.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I don't even know why I do anything anymore</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-17 00:59:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have begun to question every action that I make. I realized that everyday I do the exact same thing, act the exact same way, say the exact same things, go to the exact same places, etc.. Nothing changes and I don't think I can live like this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I feel like I may just be lying to myself about this whole thing</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-17 04:04:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>If it means anything I am a teen in high school. So basically something that I have noticed about myself is that I am very flexible and conforming, not just stuff like changing my schedule but I will change my entire personality for different people and situations. I find it easier than displaying actual emotion, but that is beside the point. The point I was trying to make is that stuff influences how I act really easily and I often (accidentally) convince myself things or read something and take it to heart. Here is an example, I like a movie then read about how everyone hated it and the ratings were horrible. Now I won't like the movie nearly as much or at all. One more thing before I can actually get into the trans stuff, I am probably depressed but haven't been diagnosed, just going off everything I have read and felt for a while. So what if I just fabricated this whole idea of being trans because I am not happy? I don't really know, I am just a bit confused right now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I don't really feel like the opposite gender</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-22 01:54:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>For reference I am MTF, pre everything. So I keep hearing about how people don't feel like their gender and feel like the opposite. I don't have that, I feel like a boy but I think I would be happier as a girl. That just doesn't seem right to me and I don't know what to do. Another thing is that I often convince myself of things without realizing it, what if I convinced myself that I am trans and would be happier because I would be a girl because I am not happy with my life now? What if all of this is just me lying to myself and I am just a disgrace to the trans community? What if everything I think of myself is just a lie and I am actually happy with my life and everything else?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-30 03:55:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Completely immaculate, boring lamps, boring desk, boring chair $20 from a thrift store, no decorations, etc.. Even though I spend all my time in it I just don't care what it looks like.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I am completely worn out and I don't know what I am supposed to do anymore</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-31 01:37:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>To put things into perspective I am only 16, so I may not be very worldly, but I think I have a decent understanding of things around me. Now I don't expect any kind of respect from anyone, that is just how life is, but please don't condescend me I am sick of it. Where I currently am I am stuck completely, I can't move. There are only two places that I ever am and those are home and school. I don't have any friends that would want me around after school and I live out in the middle of no where so I can't just go do something. On top of that everyday plays out exactly the same, wake up early, be stressed throughout school, get home, stress over homework, probably not do any of it, then stress about how I didn't do it the next day, go to sleep and repeat it every single day. Being unable to hold a conversation doesn't help either (think Tomoko from Watamote if you have seen it), I just freeze up and can't do it. And why even bother with it all? I know all of my "dreams" are just delusions and I will be stuck working something meaningless. Then there is suicide. It is constantly weighing on me, day to day, hour to hour, minute to minute. I can't say anything about it to anyone, I will just end up in a psychiatric ward and that seems even worse than where I am now. I know the typical response would be to speak to an adult but how am I supposed to do that? I don't know what my parents would do and I don't trust any of my teachers, and I can't even approach any of them about anything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-31 03:33:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>The issue is I don't enjoy the procrastinating but can't actually sit down and do my homework. I try to for maybe 10 minutes then give up and try later. And often times it is an obscene amount of time for no pay off (5 points for a 3 hour assignment, for reference a quiz would be 50). When I don't do it I just waste the time on Reddit, and I don't even know why I do that. Regarding all my dreams basically a few of the ones that have stuck around are being something note worthy since I am completely invisible to everyone but my family (who sometimes don't notice me anyway). One that is stuck with me for 5 years or so, as stupid as it is, is YouTube. I don't even know if I want to do YouTube in particular anymore, just entertainment, but that is unobtainable because of terrible social anxiety and I am not creative or unique. And I don't know about talking to anyone, I am overly paranoid about opening up to anyone and have just lied about everything for as long as I can remember, I am just not the person people think I am (on the inside that is). Kind of unrelated but everything I do I only do because I feel like I have to. The only reason I go to any classes is because I am supposed to, the only reason I go home everyday is because I am supposed to, I want to try what I want but I know I would be too terrified to actually do it. It sounds like you were in a rough spot yourself, I hope things are better now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-31 20:24:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I often try it but I just can't do it, I don't really know how to describe it but I just end up looking at it and not doing anything. Basically for YouTube I expect the very most I could get would only be 1,000 if I was very lucky, I would expect more like 100 though. That is assuming I even do it though, and I would still have to deal with the anxiety and it probably would never work out. The issue with not changing what I have already been doing is I don't have anything else to do. It just comes back to what I said earlier, I am stuck. Everything I do isn't from my own decisions, I am forced into everything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Every path leads to suicide</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-21 04:55:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know what I can do, every road, every option, everything I do just loops back around to suicide. I am so tired of it and I don't know what else to do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I can't deal with high school</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-27 04:37:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't do presentations, I just can't. My most recent one ended with my entire body shaking violently while I attempted to figure out how to form words properly out of fear. That wasn't even for a full minute, just a quick here is the project, this is what I did, and done. Now I have another presentation coming up, this one is 5 minutes long, I haven't started the preparations, have barely started the project, and all needs to be done by Friday. If I somehow manage to finish all of it the actual presenting will be horrible. I don't think I have ever managed a 5 minute presentation and it is making me really stressed. Then another similar project was assigned today, a debate project. Not only is it the hardest assignment in the hardest class I have ever taken, but I have to work with a partner that I was able to choose. For the sign up I didn't sign up with anyone and I will just wait and see who I end up with. That is making me incredibly stressed. I don't know who I am going to be with and once I fail the project I am also failing my partner. And failing the project would be in front of the entire class which is already stressful in the first place. Then there is another project due in about two weeks (thank God it isn't a presentation again) but again it is a group assignment that I haven't started. I will surely fail it and let down both of my group members and I can't deal with that. I don't know what I am supposed to do, I am getting completely overwhelmed and am feeling suicidal over all this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-27 04:54:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>What am I supposed to say? "Hi, I'm too scared to present so I won't,"? That would never work and if they said anything like I still had to I would just go with it despite everything. And simply avoiding one doesn't solve any of the other issues.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I don't have control over my own life</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-02 04:27:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know what I have been doing, I just go through the motions everyday without thought. Any kind of decision is always decided for me and I don't know what I can do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-09 02:57:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is true and I am not holding it against them but it made me realize that I don't want to be trans and there is nothing I can do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-09 03:15:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I guess I could put it like this, being trans put me in a place where the only solution is death. Don't transition and I am miserable until I die, or do transition get ostracized by everyone and die miserably.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-09 03:22:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't really feel comfortable talking about it and saying something to them would make them suspicious of me being trans.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I just can't do it</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-09 04:26:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't be trans, I am too weak for it. There is no way that I could transition, it would lead to an overwhelming amount of stress that would eventually lead to suicide. So the alternative is not to transition which I can't do because of dysphoria leading to suicide. I just don't know what I can do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I give up and wish I could just be done</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-11 23:58:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am sick of this and just want to kill myself but know I can't. My emotions are so volatile there is no way I will feel like this when I actually get a chance. I am just so sick of it, I can never rely on how I will feel about anything and it is horrible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-12 17:07:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the big issue with this subreddit, only the front page posts get any attention and at that they get a lot of attention.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[TW] I can't ever be who I want to</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-03 05:55:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know what to do, this is just wrong. I just want to be a girl but I will just turn out to be a monster, and even then it will only be on appearance. Physically I am stuck as male, I can't change that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I need help/guidance</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-30 10:32:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am not sure how important the background is so I will try to make it brief and concise. In high school, male at birth, nearly everything in this post is entirely kept to myself, my parents are very Republican and generally not very accepting, despite that they are kind and supportive, I don't really have any real friends. The first part isn't really trans related but bare with me here. I have an issue that I supposed would be best described as very drastic moods. When I say drastic I mean to use it in the most extreme extent I can, often going from happy and normal to the brink of suicide. Seemingly nothing changes and it just kind of happens, I don't even know if it is sudden since I can't recall it changing but it feels like it takes a while. Really confusing and I'm sorry. Along with this accompanies similar thoughts regarding transitioning. Sometimes I am fine with how I am, sometimes I think it would be nice to transition, sometimes the dysphoria is absolutely horrible. It is all really weird and confusing and I have no idea what is going on. Sorry for the long post but I don't really know how to abridge it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>High school and just general trans issues</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-06 05:44:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I'm a junior in high school and I feel like this is the year that I need to start transitioning or this will be it, so I guess I should get to it. * My parents. I expect them to be pretty accepting (here is to hoping) my big issue right now is how to come out though. I am thinking I will write a letter but I have no idea what it should say. * My friends. Not like there are many to begin with amiright? I don't know what to do here really. For the most part I am the unnoticeable one in the group that gets forgotten and so people don't really talk to me that often so I don't really have any friends that I am that close to. I still feel like I should talk to maybe 1 or 2 of them but should I do that before or after coming out to my parents? * School. This is where things get fun! Should I just keep to myself and not say anything? Start wearing baggier clothing so if I start developing breasts no one will notice? I don't really have much social dysphoria, just physical so I would probably be fine there. * Gym. At my school changing is mandatory for gym. Would I be better off talking to the school before hand and trying to work something out there? Changing in the boy's locker room doesn't seem like a good idea and neither does changing in the girl's. * Doubts. I feel as though if I do transition (which I hopefully will) I will just look like some half boy half girl amalgam forever. What if I somehow look worse that I already do (if that is even possible)? I don't really know what to do, this whole idea is terrifying to me which means I will probably never actually go through with it. I will just be stuck like this forever and hate myself for it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How do I know this is right for me?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-17 06:03:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have been thinking about being trans so much lately (completely closeted) that I began to question if it is really who I am. What if I have just been subconsciously leading myself on because I want to feel like I am part of something and actually have something interesting about myself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-18 06:15:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought I was done with it already though, I had finally settled on accepting it but here we are again. I was probably wrong the first time anyway so that doesn't really help answer anything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[MTF] What if I have been misinterpreting the signs?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-19 04:32:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel as though I may be trans, but what if I have been misinterpreting all the signs and it is something completely different? I don't really have much dysphoria, I just think that my current body is kind of disgusting but who wouldn't? I can't really expect it to get better. I don't really know what it means to be a women, so how could I know if that is what I want? There isn't anything interesting about me so what if I am making this up to try to fix that? Make there be something notable about me?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-19 04:53:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do think I would rather be a women, but I have this issue where I just can't picture myself in the future.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-20 06:33:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>The issue is I feel as though once I come out there is no going back and I don't really have any way to really experiment without coming out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Reddit is transphobic, nothing new</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-04 04:24:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was just browsing Reddit as normal and I stumble upon a comic about trans-issues that seemed to be written by someone who was trans (99% sure they are) and it seemed a little transphobic (probably just me). A little confused I went to check the comments and quickly learned my lesson. There was one comment with at least a few hundred up votes (score hidden but it was at the top) about some guy that they used to date. About half way through the comment I realize they aren't talking about FTM and my heart dropped. In the entire post he referred to her as her once, to call her delusional for wanting kids. Then to top it all off, he called every trans person crazy. I don't know what to say, he's probably right about me. I'm just crazy, delusional, and not really a girl, just telling myself what I want to hear to keep myself happy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dysphoric because of changing in school</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-05 05:09:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm probably overreacting to this whole situation but I'm going to need to start changing for school and the entire situation is making me really stressed, nervous, and dysphoric. Basically the year is split into two halves (semester 1  amp; 2) and in the second half would he when I had to start changing. That would have been fine because I plan to be out and have that all settled before then. Until I learned I needed to start changing in a few days. I wasn't prepared in the slightest and I don't know what to do. I think I'm going to have to just deal with it but I don't know if I can, I can't imagine needing to change in the wrong locker room, and everyday for that matter! I'm just really stressed out and I don't know what to do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[MTF] I'm sorry for posting another one of these, but am I really trans?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-07 00:52:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know this gets posted all the time but I feel like my case is a little different (at least I haven't seen it posted here before). Now, I am really ugly and I know that, this is where the issue comes in. I see women and find them beautiful (and attractive) and so what if the reason I feel trans is because I want to look like them (beautiful and attractive)?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-07 01:12:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really don't know, sometimes yes and sometimes I don't think it would make any difference.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What are your thoughts on otherkin/2+ genders?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-14 01:54:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Personally I'm very torn on the issue, on one hand I am all for people presenting themselves however they are happy but on the other I feel as though it can hurt the credibility of transfolk. Edit: just wanted to clarify I don't mean gender fluid</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-14 04:01:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't mean to lump gender fluid in with otherkin at all (in fact I thought about clarifying as such in the post), I think I just worded the title incredibly poorly. I'm really sorry for the misunderstanding!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-14 04:05:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Apparently I worded the title terribly, I wasn't referencing gender fluid at all and I'm really sorry for the misunderstanding. Now what I meant about otherkin was that some people identify as book characters, which are probably trolls, but at what point is the line drawn?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-14 18:22:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had meant 3+, not sure why I said 2.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Help dealing with my own transphobia?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-15 01:57:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>So for whatever reason I can't help but view MTF (which also happens to be what I am) as "bad" or "wrong" until they are at least semi-passable. On the flip-side I have absolutely no issue with FTM. What can I do to get over this? One last thing, I already feel really shitty about this so please don't make me feel worse about it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-15 02:23:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>The issue is though that it extends beyond myself and I start looking at other people in the same way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-15 03:35:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is your problem? Did you cherry pick my post just so you could write an angry comment? Did you miss the part where I said that I'm MTF myself? I came here for help in overcoming this, not to be crucified for trying to fix an issue with myself. Did you also miss the part about how I already feel really shifty about this too? I even specifically asked people not to act like this, do you just find joy in causing others misery?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-15 03:40:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I just wanted to apologize, I thought I understood it, didn't, and I screwed up. So I'm sorry again, I need to understand topics better before I start talking about them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-15 04:01:35</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I laid out a rational argument for why it's ok to treat transfolk as their preferred gender even if they don't pass with not one personal attack or character judgement. But why? I didn't ever mention not treating not them as their preferred gender.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-15 04:08:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think I actually figured it out, I have trouble separating the ideas of men in dresses and MTF as two different things. I know they aren't but subconsciously I just can't stop associating the two.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-15 05:54:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Basically just getting "information" from the wrong people and taking it as fact.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-16 01:34:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>That makes sense, but what can I do about it? I just can't get that idea out of my head.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Confusion with non-binary</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-01 01:37:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Disclaimer: I don't really know much about non-binary at all, so if I say something wrong or offensive I apologize in advance! That isn't the intent and is a result of me being misinformed. So I'm trying to fix that. TL;DR I'm an uneducated fool who needs enlightenment. From what I understand a someone who identifies as non-binary is someone who doesn't identify as male or female. Genderfluid: From what I understand this is someone who kind of changes what they identify as frequently (ish?). Is this even non-binary? Was I even remotely close on my guessed definition? How does this even work (wrong words but not sure how else to put it) and what does it feel like, assuming I have the right general idea on it. Otherkin: First I'm not even sure if that's the right word or something made up in mockery. Anyway, I've never really gotten a solid answer on what this is and how it works and frankly I'm really confused. I've heard it's a joke, I've heard it's made up, I've heard it's real, I've heard all of these from this very sub so I don't know what's true at all. So what exactly is it? Is it when someone identifies as something else (fuck, this sounds horribly wrong and I'm afraid I'm going to offend someone)? Like I've heard of people identifying as/with animals and things of that sort but what does that exactly entail? The whole thing is really confusing and I don't really know anything about it. Fictionkin(?): This one is even more out there, from what I understand it's when people closely identify with a fictional character? This just, I'm not even really sure what to say. If someone could give me an explanation on this that'd be great. Agender: Not identifying as M or F and just kind of being, right? Is this non-binary or something else? Or am I horribly wrong again? Anything I missed: I'm not sure if I missed anything but if I did please let me know about it, thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What if I'm wrong about this?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-19 04:36:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>MTF, teen I came out to my mom two weeks ago (ish) and she took it really well and has been very supportive. I started counseling, have a date for my consultation for HRR, etc.. Then there are a ton of issues along with it. Due to shitty scheduling I need to come out to some school staff this week to handle the whole changing room issue, which is kind of scary but what choice do I have? Then I need to come out to my dad, who I really doubt will take it well, soon because of more shitty scheduling! Everything is piling up all at once and really quickly right after coming out. Now I'm worried I might be wrong about all this. I don't want to go back on it once everyone knows because that would be horrible, everyone would constantly be reminding me of it and how it was a mistake and I'm terrified. Help?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[TW][MTF] I feel sick to the stomach</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-23 05:33:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let me start by apologizing for this post, it's probably the wrong sub but I don't really know where else to post it. I'm feeling depressed, crushed, and defeated and I don't know where else to turn. I'm terrified of the idea of coming out at high school. I need to come out, at least for next year, as I'm starting HRT within a few months and I can't hide it for an entire year. And with that I know there will be a lot of bullying. In one class there's already a group of students who often make transphobic jokes even when they don't know someone will be offended by them, they certainly aren't the kind of people that will stop if they found out they did. A lot of people already treat me like shit now and I'm too much of a coward to stand up to them so I can't do it now. I don't even have very many friends either (like one, maybe two) so I can't always turn to them for support. A while ago I came out to an online friend who was also friends with my best friend. That worked out fine until a few days later when they went and said a ton of really nasty shit about it for a really long time to my best friend. I tried really hard to forget what they said because it made me really depressed for several days. One thing however that I can't stop repeating in my head again and again is chicks with dicks. I hate it so fucking much and I can't stop repeating it. I feel like a joke. A shitty thing to be made fun of without any real value. The worst part is I know there isn't a chance I could ever kill myself. I'm too afraid of the physical pain and too afraid of ever hurting another person. I hate how I'm too much of a coward to do anything about anything. I let people hurt me all the time and never speak up for myself and the same is true when something happens to other people I care about. I'm too much of a coward to help anyone even myself. Sorry again for posting this here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How am I supposed to deal with the wait?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-10 04:25:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just went in for my consultation for hormones and blockers with an endocrinologist the other day and my mom had commented to me afterwards that I didn't seem very excited about it. All I learned was how long I really had to wait for hormones to even be an option. A month for blood work, another month or two for the results, another month for blockers, few more months for the actual hormones, then a few more months before I actually see any results. How am I supposed to deal with that? I was hoping to get hormones started early spring but not being to even start until mid-late summer? I don't know what to do... I just can't get excited for it anymore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Questioning asexual, need help</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-12 07:11:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I know that I'm trans (MTF) so that's a thing but now I've started questioning asexuality (again). Let me explain the situation. I feel like I'm attracted to women however most of the time I find myself longing to look like them so maybe I'm misinterpreting attraction with envy. I also occasionally watch porn but it's always either softcore or BDSM (not really interested in the sex aspect of it though). I've also never had a crush or really been attracted to anyone in particular. What do you think?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-12 15:25:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thing is I'm not on anything yet and I still feel like this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My best friend was incredibly manipulative and I'm finally realizing it</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-16 05:07:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>This has been really frustrating and an overall painful experience for me. I've never had very close friends, hell maybe I haven't even had friends all along. I have always felt like people would only talk to me when I was conveniently there. Until I met her and everything changed. She was so kind and honestly seemed like she wanted to talk to me, we talked for hours about nothing and I really enjoyed it. She had just ended a friendship with someone else, they argued between themselves a lot and it generally seemed like a bad situation (first warning sign). For the first few months we really hit it off and I would do anything for her which she obviously knew and would later abuse. The next warning sign was when she would pretend to "break up" with me saying how she couldn't be my friend anymore because of reason XYZ. Upon hearing that I would rush to her side (not literally) and support her until she eventually came back around and was my friend again (conveniently 2 days every time). I put so much effort into it and it was exhausting, stressful, depressing, and scary all at the same time. She knew that and lo and behold she would do it time and time again. The most obvious warning was when she lied to me saying she had a crush on me and how she wanted to date me, but what can I say? Denial is a powerful thing. Anyway, she wanted to date and I didn't but she acted very depressed and said stuff like now no one wanted to date her etc. etc. and I eventually folded hating seeing her like that. Second I said I would she bounced back and was all fine. I was so resistant to it she eventually gave up and we broke up a week or two later but stayed friends. Around this time she started getting really nasty and irritable, she would get mad at me for everything. She would yell at me for this or that, tell me I couldn't be depressed because she had it so much worse, etc.. Prom was coming up and she didn't have a date so naturally she turned to me to keep her company. I didn't want to go so I said no. She responded by being upset, to livid, to ignoring me in all of 5 minutes. That was when I finally started getting suspicious. Later down the line she began complaining about how I didn't talk to her as much and how we never did anything together. I told her how she has been so nasty to me recently why would I want to? Hoping to reel me back in she told me we couldn't be friends anymore. I responded with an "ok" got up and walked off (in the most literal way, we were sitting next to each other when it happened). Since then I've seen her talking to someone new again, being all friendly and happy. It's a cycle with her, I can tell exactly how it will happen. Be nice, test the waters for manipulation, go full control freak. I glossed over a lot of details, some other things she did were tell me I shouldn't talk to this friend because they said nasty stuff about me (when asked what she found excuses not to tell), telling me what my emotions were, telling me how I should respond to things, the standard stuff. I talked to another friend about her and he confirmed everything from the outside, she was crazy but didn't say anything to me because I wouldn't listen. I just feel so shitty about the whole situation. I took all of her bait and just fell for it. I should have known that nobody would actually want to be my friend but yet I wouldn't believe it. I tried so hard to be the perfect friend but it was all for nothing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The blatant transphobia on Reddit is really frustrating</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-07 06:39:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Earlier I stumbled into an AskReddit thread (not going to say which but you can probably guess) which was my obvious first mistake. After reading a bit I found a comment saying how trans people are have a mental illness, well yeah gender dysphoria is what I *thought*, but I was so off from what they *meant*. They meant that the process of transitioning was a (paraphrasing) "miracle of modern medicine that allowed people to live out outlandish fantasies and should not be allowed". The worst part was the absurd support it got, lots of upvotes, lots of comments reciprocating and few people challenging it. I tried challenging it and all I saw was more hate. The worst part about this whole situation isn't the confirmation that some people would hate me before knowing me just because of this, but it gets me down the path of questioning if transitioning will really make me a girl, etc..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Had my first awful experience in public today!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-09 06:38:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Little background here, I'm MTF and I've known I was trans for maybe a year or two and there was a little before that where I was questioning. Well once I figured it out I kept it to myself and didn't really say anything. Since then I've come out to some friends and they've all be really really supportive and don't bat an eye and they are all wonderful. Now to the story. Me and my SO decided to go into a store so I could try on a dress or two, so we walk in browse a bit and pick a nice dress for me to try on. So we start making our way towards the dressing room, I should have stopped myself when I saw the dressing room was split into a "men's" section and a "women's" section. Situated between the two was a desk with a women sitting behind it (she was in her 40s or 50s?), basically you had to get a card from her to access the dressing rooms. So my SO gets the card and we start walking towards the women's dressing room. The women behind the counter immediately stops us, looks me dead in the eye and just says "no, you can't go back there." I felt my stomach drop, I had been completely invalidated, and from there I turned around, walked out, and I'm never going near that store again. So anyway, how was your day :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I [17F] miss being with my abusive ex-best friend [17F], not sure what to do</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 05:10:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a bit reluctant to make this post as I am expecting to be chastised for my age and the such but please hear me out. What happened is a really long story so I'm going to skip around a lot and only hit the main points. Everything happened over the course of around 6-7 months. I've always been a really shy person so I'd have trouble making friends with people, at some point I met someone wonderful. She and I hit it enough immediately, we got along great and they were really nice. Fast forward a bit and they were constantly berating me for little things and I felt like every conversation was a land mine. She worked to isolate me from what little friends I did have so when she later pretended to cut me off I would panic afraid to lose my only friend, she proceeded to do this several times. After we had been friends for a few months she pressured me into a relationship (for reference yes, I am in fact gay), I had never had romantic feelings for her and never have I however conceded and accepted it despite much resistance from my part. We broke up very quickly due to my continued resistance to it but we remained friends. She continued treating me like shit and was at this point not bothering to hide it with niceties, she was blatantly cruel all the time. After some time she attempted to pretend cut me off again however this time I never went back. Fast forward another 6 months or so. I've moved on and managed to make some great friends who are all very friendly people. The aforementioned person is out of the picture. However now I'm beginning to miss her. With my newer friends, since they are always so nice, I'm afraid of what bad they are capable of. With the person from before I knew what she would do and say and looking back it was comforting in a way. Help please. TLDR; had an abusive bf who isolated me and manipulated me, moved on, miss being friends with them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm addicted to abuse</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 16:47:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Physical, emotional, verbal, it doesn't matter, I can't get enough of it. I've never been physically abused myself but media allows me to experience it vicariously. It's awful. I know it is. I don't know what to do about it though. When I'm in a relationship (friendship, dating, etc.) if they're abusive in some way it makes me feel more comfortable like they won't just abandon me. I'm ace so it's not even in a sexual way, it hurts me but the pain of it is good, it's something to fall back on like I can know the worst a person can do. I keep track of a list of people in my head who I know have the capacity to be emotionally and verbally abusive just in case I need someone to fall back on. I know it's bad but what am I to do?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Internalized transphobia and hating oneself for being trans</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 05:06:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>For reference I'm MTF. My friends see me as though I'm cis and treat me as though I'm "one of the girls" but I feel out of place and like I'm lying. I'm not a girl I'm just a guy that *wishes* I was a girl, constantly pretending and acting like it. How can I get over my own internalized transphobia?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I guess that connections and friends are just impossible for me</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 05:48:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never really had any close friends. Or friends. The closest I had were people that would talk to me if I was there, they would never reach out to me or anything. Then I met this person and they quickly became my best friend (not hard when there's literally no competition). A few months down the lane I drifted off cause they started being very nasty to me more often than not. Looking back they were abusive. Now I've met this other person, again became my best friend and were wonderful. We started dating after we realized we had mutual feelings for one another. I love this person. I really do. They're so incredible and everything. But I think they're just taking advantage of me. Sometimes no just isn't an answer when it should be, asking if I can buy them XYZ as a gift then getting overly upset if I say no until I concede. Not once but multiple times, almost every time we would go out. I just don't know anymore. I'll probably stay with them ignoring all this since I can't stand being alone, I'd probably die alone. I just don't know what I'm supposed to do. I've pondered the fact that there has to be something wrong with me. I'm the only common thread among all my failed attempts at connections. I just don't know what it is and nobody will help me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I really want to do this but I'm terrified of the pain</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 16:32:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>How bad is it? There's a lot of reasons that I feel like I need to do this but that's not the point. I've been terrified of knives my entire life so I need some kind of reference.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>