<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject3737</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Got this message on FB...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-08-22 07:15:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mega Man X Short film.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-21 09:58:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-23 19:55:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rubber!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A horror film that I want to see.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-08 05:03:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Chasing Love (2013 - Arkansas - USA)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-15 20:39:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-16 00:15:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, Toad Suck Park in Conway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This guy doesn't get the credit he deserves.(Bradley Hathaway)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-31 05:23:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I need a good Flying Type for Pokemon Black</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-01 19:39:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty self explanatory. I need a Pokemon that can use fly so I don't have to withdraw and deposit my tranquill, I don't like tranqill every time I want to go a long distance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Study War No More (2013-Arkansas-USA) 4:19</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-13 11:03:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-03 17:41:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Needs banana.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-04 07:29:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Darn you and your beating me to the post.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lovely Wii Fit Trainer - Dem Games</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-04 07:31:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-11 05:54:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm always looking for teammates ID: Jakeswaff</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-13 03:05:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you want to send me the videos I could do it for you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-10 17:20:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Deathbed by Relient K. Gets me every time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-11 20:43:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dokapon Kingdom, Its Mario party meets pokemon. Very unknown, but everyone I play it with loves it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-13 01:43:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I got it before it got too expensive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Since SEGA doesn't want to release the 2nd one in the west I want a HD version, with online.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-28 07:55:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>As Dreamers Do- A Walt Disney Biopic Staring Olan Rogers</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-31 04:39:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Most Amazing Mother Son Wedding Dance EVER!!!!!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-07 17:56:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-11 08:46:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's not back I'm going in after him!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-11 09:16:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>TIL What a AGS-101 is and that I have one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Really great video tutorial on how to play online on th e wii</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-14 07:10:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Talking to my Mom on the phone about school and life in general and she tells me not to get overwhelmed.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-20 22:18:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lets not forget what comes out today!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-20 23:20:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-20 23:47:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah that's what I've gathered too but its just alpha so hopefully we see some pretty sweet updates.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-28 17:49:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Japanese teachers hate him!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I want a sequel of this game! One of my childhood favorites.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-06 20:55:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-08 16:27:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>That sexy bastard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 05:10:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I bet those prostitutes made a fuck ton of money.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 19:19:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone wants the D.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-21 11:09:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great now I'm crying in the middle on the library at 5 in the morning.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-21 11:43:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here have some extra nope!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I get chills when Superman shows up!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-21 11:47:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-23 08:24:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yo dog I heard you liked ties</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>He's havin' a good time</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-18 19:53:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>El Muppet Song</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-07 18:47:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ant good free DVD authoring software?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-09 00:38:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been using, well trying to use, Encore but have run in to too many issues. Is there any free software that you would recommend?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Richard Donner wanted to make a Batman film starting Mel Gibson</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-16 09:16:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Donkey Konga Documentary</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-23 21:26:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sleepover Prank</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-08 06:10:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-09 21:17:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>More like the world's biggest nope swing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-23 04:23:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kids these days.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Missed opportunity?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-29 03:41:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I realize now that I Should have taken a picture but about a week ago I happened across a NES with cables, 2 controllers, and a handful of games, none notable except super mario bros. all for $100. Did I pass a decent opportunity or make a good choice?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-29 14:16:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the feedback everyone. I haven't really kept up with NES value. I really wanted it but cringed at the price.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-09 05:04:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is so good. That is all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-20 04:12:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm currently a senior at the University of Central Arkansas studying Digital Filmmaking. I have really enjoyed my time here and I would love answer any questions you may have. I do think that I have learned things much faster and more in depth than if I didn't go to school. Although I don't think I've learned anything that I couldn't have learned outside of school. It's really nice to meet people and have friends who are interested in film as much as you and as well educated. I've seen a lot more classic films that otherwise I probably wouldn't have been exposed to, and I have really enjoyed them. At this point I'm just trying to reach the character limit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Settle It In Smash (Original Rap) Ft. Garrett Williamson</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-04 01:15:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Settle It In Smash (Original Rap) Ft. Garrett Williamson</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-04 01:15:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New Zelda footage and news on a new Starfox!!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-06 06:25:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New footage and new Starfox confirmed!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-06 06:27:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-02 03:12:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have found that using strong tea in the base helps to give a stronger buzz. That is how my old roommate and I had to get a buzz. He had a really strong Korean tea we brewed specifically for hookah.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-02 04:41:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't remember the flavor seeing as it was nearly three years back but I know the tea was super strong to begin with and my roommate brewed it extra strong on top of that, way too strong to drink. It definitely helped though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Now I See (X-post r/religion)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-06 16:34:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My VFX reel, any constructive criticism welcome. (I'm new at this)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-12 07:06:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-19 06:06:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am praying for you as I type this. I am going through/have been through a very similar situation. I am 21 and would have been married for 2 years on the 19th. I can identify with you so much. Okay here's the backstory. Back in 2010 I started at a new school for my senior year and almost immediately fell for a girl. Sadly she did not share the feelings. After pursuing her for about a year and a half. She finally agreed to date me. We fell in love fast and after a few months I knew I wanted to spend my life with her, and she reciprocated the feelings. After seeking counsel with our parents, I proposed and we set out on the road of getting married. Fast Forward to early of last year, my wife begins talking about divorce and wanting "freedom" and "independence". Later that year in May she went to volunteer all week at a Film Festival. She did so against my wishes seeing as we were planning a big trip the week after. Tensions were high between the two of us the whole week. God ended up providing us with the money to still go the trip and so we went. Later that year, last August, she came to me and told me she was unhappy, I told her I understood because we had been going through a rough time lately. She proceeded to tell me very seriously that she wanted a divorce. Told her that we biblically could not do that and she then told me that while at the festival, nearly three months back, she had brought a man back to her hotel room one night, after we had a fight over the phone. This absolutely devastated me. I completely know of the numbness that you mentioned. Jump to today, we are no longer together. Now I say all this purely so that you can know: you are not alone, I empathize for you deeply, I pray for the best and for healing. If you ever need to talk to someone you think can understand your pain, PM me. I want to help if I can. Love and peace, A brother in Christ.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Texting on a tablet</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-23 04:49:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>What are the best texting apps for tablets? I'm using MightyText right now but I'm not liking it too much seeing as not all my contacts are importing from phone. My tablet is WiFi only and my phone is a lg g2, if that helps at all. Thanks ahead of time for the help!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-23 04:51:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really like google play music. Its easy to use and you can upload music off your desktop, so downloading is easy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-30 19:36:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>This sounds almost like a first world problem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-03 04:47:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Although it sounds like a cool tool I don't think I can imagine a automated editing software editing anything that requires an artistic or emotional touch. I feel it could be useful for something along the lines of editing a sport or a concert, but not a narrative.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-10 06:44:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Praying for you and for God's guidance. He can give you much better advice than anyone else. Remember you can't change how much God loves you, he loves you just as much now as he ever has. Love, a Brother in Christ.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-09 06:07:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't offer much council but I will pray for you and the situation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-11 06:58:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Westbury Park Apartments allows pets. It's a decent place too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Got licensed today</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-19 17:48:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-20 01:57:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got it at a local game store.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-24 16:20:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well if you think about the soteriology of judeo-christian religions all sin is punishable by death. Hence why a sacrifice is necessary to be cleansed of sin. Specifically an innocent sacrifice such as a lamb which was only temporary or Jesus, the perfect son of God, which cleansed sin once and for all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-30 04:36:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I use a pc but I can say that using a hub does cause problems occasionally, definitely effects the data transfer speed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why A Director Shouldn #8217;t Edit Their Own Movie</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-04 04:56:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-23 00:25:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can add me at : jakeswafford. Ive been playing a lot lately.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 04:01:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>These look great! They are getting me hyped already! I don't know a whole lot about 3D animation but I'm pretty good with after effects and an experienced film editor. PSO is one of my favorite games and I'd love to help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-16 19:52:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Monterey jack</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-23 11:01:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Superman is the sixth. The seventh is unknown, but my guess is Hal Jordan.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I(24/m) recently started texting with a girl(22/f) out of state. I'm not good at texting.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-15 04:23:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I met this girl at my best friends wedding this weekend. We were both part of the wedding party and the bride has thought we would be a couple for 3 1/2 years, she's been trying to set us up. We finally met and she's great, we hit it off pretty well and I asked her, via text, if she would want to keep in contact and she seemed enthusiastic about it. Also I got confirmation from the bride she was into me. We've been texting a little since she left town, but I'm not great via text, we mainly talked about her new job. When is a good time to bring up phone calls? What are good things to ask via text? How can I stay interesting?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-22 06:58:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could I please have a link?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[VIDEO} GO TAKE IT</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 06:29:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Justice League as an 80s TV show</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 06:54:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A Rock (OC)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 22:26:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 03:48:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well thanks, I'll relay the compliment next time I see him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 08:42:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good thing you put that asterisk there, I almost read a bad word.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Work Design of Dark Souls - Game Maker's Toolkit</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 06:33:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 18:03:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>You trusted me and I failed you...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Best Jordan Peterson Impression</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 13:00:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Jordan Peterson on Burger King</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 13:12:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Crazy Lightning Build</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 08:09:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 08:55:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah he does! I love seeing what he comes up with.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>