<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject3283</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>To-do list and note app rolled into one?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-04 17:50:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have been a Toodledo user for years, but I am currently experiencing some pain points with Toodledo and am looking to see if there is anything that is doing it better. I have tried a few different apps, but nothing that meets my needs yet. My two biggest struggle with Toodledo right now are their notes feature and their app. I absolutely love the Toodledo has a notes section connected with their app, but it is extremely basic and doesn't offer a lot of the functionality I want. (ie Id loke to be able to do picture notes or have more ways to organize them.) As for the app, Toodledo's app is just a pain sometimes, and I want some that's a little more user friendly. Most of the great to-do list apps I tried have nice apps, but absolutely no notes section (I do not mean notes connected with the task, but sperate notes used for reference.) I like having my notes and tasks all under one roof, but haven't found any apps that do them both well (I'm not even looking for perfection or Evernote quality notes, just better than Toodledo's). Do you all know if there any good systems that have both notes and tasks rolled into one? My only big requirement (besides doing tasks and notes passingly well) is that it must work on Android. Thanks for your help, r/productivity!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-05 00:50:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its just a preference. I like to have everything in one place rather than two separate ones. It's one less program I have to jump to and one less place for me to look.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My first octopus!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-14 14:19:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-14 14:23:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>The album also has a gif of him moving around! He is in a 75 gallon tank and I believe he is an abdopus abaculus (although I'm not sure yet). He is showing some aggression in the gif (that white stripe) but he is still getting acclimated to his new home! If you all have any other questions, I'd be happy to try and and answer them!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-14 16:27:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm in the US. As I said, this is most likely an abdopus abaculus, and they get to be about the size of an orange (give or take.) You're thinking of a Giant Pacific Octopus, which this is certainly not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-14 18:51:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep, he's already eating. Right now I feed him only live food. (Currently it's grass shrimp from the local bait shop, but I have access to crabs and clams in the future.) Hunting also keeps him occupied. As he gets acclaimed, I plan to give him more toys and what not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-14 18:53:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>All the other inhabitants were put in there to be food at some point. I'm ready for it. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-14 21:43:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>This made me laugh so hard! That blue pipe is just the hiding place he was shipped with. It literally nothing but a 6in piece of blue PVC pipe open on both ends. :-) I really appreciate your confidence in me, though! I like to think I know what I'm doing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-15 02:51:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.tonmo.com/threads/cuttlefish-availablity.6279 The last post is someone offering some cuddle fish in SD in 2016. Difficult, but not impossible. What would be almost impossible is getting your hands on are some blue-rings. I'm not even sure how you would get those or why you would want them!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-15 02:52:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! It took A LOT of planning, research, set up, and waiting. Definitely possible, but you have to be committed! :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-16 11:38:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel kind of wired that I looked at this and thought, "I know that filtration!" And then remembered I saw it on here. (You're privious post) I guess I'm remberimg filtration by sight now. :-) Awesome tank!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-20 12:09:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, no body writes in ASL symbols (there are systems, but none that are widely adopted). You're right in your thinking. If someone has the English skills to read the fingerspelling on the paper, they are able to read the English words just fine. It is nice for someone who lacks the English skills to read that would still see the letters in ASL (even if they can't completely figure it out) and would understand they could have it signed. However, as another user said, there's also other ways to accomplish this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-21 01:09:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>As someone who works with the Deaf in a church setting, just relax! The Deaf people in my church are super friendly and patient! Also, be willing to take a risk, introduce yourself and interact with the Deaf. A lot of people I see learning ASL are too intimidated to go out on a limb. Don't be. 99% of Deaf people like the fact that people are learning their language and are happy to interact and help, but they aren't always up for breaking the ice. I hope you have a great time! :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-22 03:28:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Best: Meeting all kind of different people. Getting to be in all kinds of interesting situations and learn a lot of new things (example, I got to interpret a year long culinary class once. I learned so much!) Oh, and anytime there's an assignment with free food! :-) Worst: It's hard sometimes not being a participant (I say this as someone who prides myself on my ability to stay neutral). Sometimes, I just want to interject, especially when I see someone getting taken advantage of or wronged. Also, interpreting is not always fast paced (I work in educational interpreting), and that slowness really wares on me sometimes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-24 22:38:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>All of the Deaf-Blind people I know use ASL. You have to make some adjustments (ie, signing NOT rather than shaking your head), but, in my experience, it is certainly not another language all together. I have no idea where your friends got that idea. If possible, find some Deaf-Blind people in your area and just talk to them. Experience it for yourself. If there are any groups who work with the blind, they might be able to point you in the right direction as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-26 23:33:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's crazy. I've never heard of a Deaf event with a profesancy requirement. It can't be stated enough, you need to find a way to get out there and use what you know with real signers in the real world. You will never reach your full potential without signing with the Deaf. As for the word order (OSV), you are on the right track. As for the Object, Subject, and Verb, ASL tends to be more flexible than some teachers let on. LifePrint has a good write up here[](http://www.lifeprint.com/asl101/pages-layout/syntax.htm) Best of luck to you! My advise is go for it and start immersing yourself in the Deaf community NOW. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 21:38:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>ASL (American Sign Language) will do this thing where you point four of your fingers foward horizontally and wiggle them. It looks like [this](https://www.signingsavvy.com/sign/SPELL/4561/1) without moving your hand to the side. Also, some people just finger spell "Um", "Uh", "So", or whatever their filler word of choice is. Edit: format</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 13:11:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's why you shouldn't make whales mad!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-01 15:14:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>They did, but not always how we would think. ASL is strongly derived from French Sign Language (plus Martha Vineyards Sign Language, Plains Indian Sign Language, home signs, and I am sure others). I don't know the history of BSL (although now I'm curious), but it's also probably not so cut and dry either.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-01 20:14:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Use ASL. Go to some local Deaf events if you can over the summer. The more you produce and see ASL in conversations, the better feel you will get for the grammar, the better you will automatically recognize signs, and the less you will forget. There's no real replacement for using ASL with fluent signers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-02 17:43:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I understand that. I was just curious about the history of BSL itself. It seems like an interesting topic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-06 12:28:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not that I am aware of. The only other things it might be is if the Deaf use HELP to mean aid in that context or possibly even CARE. I have never seen it used like that, but I don't go around talking to people about first aid. :-) I would say you are always safe fingerspelling it, but I wouldn't #8203; say someone is "wrong" if they signed it differently.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-07 17:25:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Get a five or ten gallon aquarium kit from Walmart (you won't beat their prices for a tank and filter). Then, go to a decent pet store, with a better selection than Walmart, and buy whatever decorations you like. After that, buy a Betta fish! You're now a fish keeper! :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-09 01:32:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a rule, long and/or bright nails are considering distracting. So are pieces flashy or large jewlry. Not all jewlry is a no-go (I always wear my wedding ring), you just have to use your judgement. As for tattoos and scars. They can be distracting. If you do not have any hand or forearm tattoos, I would advise against it. For me, it's a matter of doing my job to the best of my ability, and keeping my arms tattoo-free is part of that. If you already have them, nobody will ask you to remove them, though. Scars can also be distracting, but you don't have much of a choice there. Most Deaf clients and employers will be very forgiving in that regard. I don't know your gender, but as a male interpreter, I also want to add that facial hair that covers or obscures the lips is also not appropriate for interpreters.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My octopus swimming and messing with a shrimp</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 20:59:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 21:41:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got him (I'm not sure it's male, but I still call it a him) about a month ago. I am not sure how old he is. Most likely he is around a year old, but I have no way to be sure of that. He hasn't been as difficult as I expected to keep. The biggest thing (as always) is keeping up with water changes. I was worried about feeding, but he loves bait shrimp, which are easy to get where I live. :-) I have the lid secured with the child-proof latches used on refrigerators and a few pavers to weigh it down. The overflow is secured with nylon screen (the same kind you used for a porch). Yes, screen is aquarium safe. He is pretty clever! Most of what I have seen intelligence wise is in his hunting. He will hide behind a rock and creep his tentacles around to surprise unsuspecting shrimp. His camoflaoge game is also impeccable. He not only makes himself the exact same color as the rocks, but has even started adding random darker spots to look like the holes in the rocks. It's impressive. He can be sitting on top of a rock and I can still miss him!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 21:43:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not as bad as I expected, but still more work than normal. I have to be very consistent with my water changes and so far he only eats live food.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 21:45:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>75 gallon</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 22:22:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Expensive depending on your perspective. He cost me about $60. If you're coming from fresh water, it feels like a lot, but I've seen frags go for prices that blow my mind.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 22:30:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>No problem! I'm happy to answer! - About $60 - 75 gallons - I have a sump with a protein skimmer. - I believe an abdopus, but I am not certain what kind it is beyond that. It was sold as just a "Long Armed Octopus"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-11 01:23:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its pretty amazing that's all he cost seeing as he's wild caught and shipped half way across the world!! He'll grow to where his mantle ("head") is about the size of a small orange. This tank is plenty of space for him for the rest of his life. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-11 12:47:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>About 7. I've noticed him eating about one a day. I buy them by the dozen (the smallest quantity sold by my local bait shop), so each load lasts me about a week and a half. I usually re stock when he gets down to a couple left. He seems to be able to regulate his eating and I haven't seen any downsides to having all those shrimp in there at once. They also make a pretty interesting clean up crew that keeps the sand airated (they bury themselves randomly during the day.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-11 12:51:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like the other person said, don't start with an octopus, but don't be afraid to work up to it. He really wasn't hard to get. I went to my local fish store and ordered him. He did take a while to come in (about 4 months), but that's because their supplier did not have them in stock. My experience is it's just a waiting game... Like everything in this hobby. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-11 14:37:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Ask and ye shall receive](https://streamable.com/i1is9) Not as good quality, but still cool. I'll post another album another time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-11 14:38:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Ask and ye shall receive](https://streamable.com/i1is9) Not as good quality, but still cool. I'll post another album another time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-13 11:35:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can only give you an idea for where I work. I work for the public schools in Florida (not an agency, I'm a staff interpreter) and this is not including the summer (so think of this as a 10-month salary). An interpreter in the public schools here earns anywhere from. 23,000-33,000 annually not including benefits. Sorry I can't give you an idea for freelance interpreting, it's been a while since I've done that full time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-16 03:04:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Overhead is worse for your shoulders and rotator cuffs. Stick with eye level!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-30 01:51:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is right. I believe it originally had some connection to using a TTY as well. I also see it used for "message" (ie Text, Facebook, etc) sometimes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hitchhiker? Not sure what this is.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 13:27:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 13:34:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>First and foremost, sorry for the worst quality photo in the history of Reddit. :-) These little things are hard to take a picture of with a cell phone. I started noticing these a week or two ago. Its a 75gal salt tank and Google hasn't helped much. They appear as little flakes in the morning and are gone after my light has been on about an hour. At first, I thought my Octopus went crazy on the shrimp in the tank (they are there for food). However, they are consistently there every morning now. Upon closer inspection, I THINK it's some kind of hitchhiker. They are small, maybe an 1/8 in at the most. They are round with a small hole in the middle. On one side, they have a clear bulbus bubble. They drift around in my water column and slowly disappear after about an hour. I have no idea where they go. They sort of look like mini jellyfish or some kind of polyp. They appear to be filer feeders (if they are some sort of creature). They also don't seem to bother anything in the tank. This is all more out of curiosity than anything else. Thanks for your help!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hitchhiker help</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 17:50:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 17:50:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>First and foremost, sorry for the worst quality photo in the history of Reddit. :-) These little things are hard to take a picture of with a cell phone. I started noticing these a week or two ago. Its a 75gal salt tank and Google hasn't helped much. They appear as little flakes in the morning and are gone after my light has been on about an hour. At first, I thought my Octopus went crazy on the shrimp in the tank (they are there for food). However, they are consistently there every morning now. Upon closer inspection, I THINK it's some kind of hitchhiker. They are small, maybe an 1/8 in at the most. They are round with a small hole in the middle. On one side, they have a clear bulbus bubble. They drift around in my water column and slowly disappear after about an hour. I have no idea where they go. They sort of look like mini jellyfish or some kind of polyp. They appear to be filer feeders (if they are some sort of creature). They also don't seem to bother anything in the tank. This is all more out of curiosity than anything else. Thanks for your help!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-06 10:43:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't think of it as a Word-to-Sign equivalent. "Need" and "should" are similar concepts with the main difference being the strength of the word. In ASL, there is one sign for that concept and you show the strength of it by the force you use during the sign. What that means is that "need" will use that sign more forcefully than "should." Also, if you really care about using a particular English word, you can always mouth "need" or "should" (This is not usually considered proper ASL, but sometimes useful). Now, to actually answer your question... If you want to make a request politely, I recommend signing "please". :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 11:23:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>It depends on you. If you go all in and immerse yourself in the Deaf Community, you could be able take a food order or hold a basic conversation in about a a year or a year and a half. That's a little optimistic, though. You wouldn't reach fluancy in that time frame. I'm basing this off my own experience. I immersed myself in the Deaf community and was able to start holding down a conversation in that time frame. To be clear, for that time frame, you're looking at immersion in the community. Meet some Deaf people. Become real friends (not just the kind who wants to learn ASL from them) and do things with them. Go out to eat, go camping, attend church, whatever you would do with friends! A class at your local Deaf Services is a great place to start, but won't get you there that quickly. I can't give you a time frame for the taking-classes route, as that wasn't my experience. Perhaps someone else can help with that. As a final note, don't expect fluancy in a year and a half. Expect to be able to hold a conversation without feeling like a TOTAL dummy. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-09 00:54:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bay Street Seafood! Hands down my favorite!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-11 13:18:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Such little love for Florida on here. I absolutely love it in Florida. It does get hot, but you get used to it, and you never have to deal with snow. We have amazing beaches, and there's also no state income tax! Lots of bugs, though. You just learn to live with those; it's not that bad. Job market can be tough, but if you are not tied to a location, you can line up a job and let that decide where you move.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This is in my garage</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 22:45:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 22:59:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Follow up question. What exactly is the transformer? I'm familiar with the things on power poles, but why is there one for a door bell or alarm? Edit: Solved! Thanks everyone!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 13:27:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tiger Bay State Forest. It's between Daytona Beach and DeLand on 92. There are a few small lakes scattered around there. The South side of it has better fishing than the North.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-17 22:28:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>It does, thank you! I just don't understand why they don't make those products to work with the voltage that I already have. I'm sure it's not that simple, just interesting! :-) thanks again!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-19 20:47:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not exactly. Sign Languages are not based of spoken languages. They are independent from the spoken language around them. There is no true sign language for any language. While there are what we call manually coded forms of a langue (like Signed English) these are not considered languages. A true sign language in its own right. Practically, this means BSL (British Sign Language) is not English done on the hands. It is its own separate and unique language with its own syntax, idoms, Grammer, and quirks. In fact, it is unintelligible to an American Sign Language users despite America and Britain sharing the same spoken language (English). So for your original question, there's no Esperanto Sign Language because Esperanto is its own language. To answer the spirit of your question, as far as I know, there is no manually coded system for Esperanto (ie no agreed upon manual alphabet or signs to represent words). Gestuno, also called International Signs, is the closest thing to Esperanto in the Manual Languages sphere. It is used most often in international conferences on issues related to interpreting and Deafness. TL;DR No. True Sign Languages are independent of spoken languages. Gestuno comes the closest to an international signed auxiliary language. Source: I am an ASL interpreter and I love languages.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-19 21:18:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Arguably more roots. English and French are different language families where as ASL is a direct descendant of French Sign Language (amongst others, but that's for another post). Not much. I can pick out some signs, but I cannot understand a whole message in French Sign Language.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My Octopus has become a lot friendlier! He even lets me pet him!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 01:30:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My Octopus lets me pet him!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 01:34:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 01:36:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope! He's been a good boy. However, my tank is pretty well Octo-proofed, just in case. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 01:56:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I bought him from an aquarium store!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 02:16:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I sure will :-(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 02:17:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Naw, he likes all the free food and no predators. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 02:24:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>They are more difficult than a lot of animals people keep. They like their water very consistent and clean. Additionally, they have some species specific needs. For example, mine only eats live food and I also have some toys in his tank.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 02:43:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure can!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 03:33:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>His mantle was a little smaller than my fist.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 03:36:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>He only eats live food. Here's a video of him hunting, though! https://streamable.com/i1is9</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 03:44:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can do that: http://imgur.com/a/VPfhA</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 03:46:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep. He doesn't over-eat. Unless it's crabs in there. In which case he eats all of them in the span of a couple hours. Learned this the hard way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 10:54:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>75 gallons. He eats mostly bait shrimp and, as a treat, toddler crabs. He only eats live food. I tried frozen food, but he just swims around with it and then leaves it in his tank.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 10:55:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's do-able. You just need to get past the high demands and short lifespan. TONMO.com has some amazing information!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 10:57:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>They are 2 inch fiddler crabs, he has nothing to worry about from them! :-) he just likes the taste.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 10:58:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I buy them. I live in Florida, so bait stores with shrimp and crab are everywhere.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 10:59:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep! With the lid shut, they just got the lid, but they have jumped out of an open lid before. Also, transportation is tricky. Yesterday, three jumped out while driving them home!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 11:00:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right now, a floating block of Legos as well as shells and small rocks. He likes the shells the most. They are all inside his den.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 11:01:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>They are not. They really don't like friends at all. Even in the wild, they only mate once and that's it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 11:03:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>RIP</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 11:06:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought it was less. I could be wrong, though. I haven't researched them as in depth because there's no way I could meet their care requirements. [They can be "friendly" though](http://m.imgur.com/1NkBk1h?r)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 11:15:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Native Americans did just that. They developed what we call Plains Indian Sign Language for trade amongst tribes who spoke different languages. I hadn't thought of it that way for us, though. I like it! Personally I would give both a shot. Esperanto does, however, have the advantage of having a written form. Signed Languages don't lend themselves to writing. :-(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 12:51:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sadly, yes :-( that's just not captivity though. That's their natural lifespan in the wild as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 12:52:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>TONMO.com has tons of resources if you're interested!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 17:48:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>For me, nylon screen around the Overflow and a lid that is secured with child safety locks that you would use on a refrigerator. Different people do it different ways. Tonmo.com has a lot of info on it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 21:07:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Live food is the main way. Along with floating toys and interaction with him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 00:03:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope. He has never inked despite my three year old charging the tank multiple times. Not all the water, you just need to do a water change and try to suck up as much as you can. The protein skimmer will get the rest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>You all seemed to like my octopus! Here he is catching multiple shrimp and changing colors.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 02:02:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>You all seemed to liked me petting my pet octopus. Here's his more murdurus side!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 02:05:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My pet octopus hunting is  #128293;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 02:11:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 10:11:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a challenge. The most important things are making sure you are diligent in your regular tank maintenance (water changes, cleaning, etc), making the tank escape proof, and providing enrichment (for mine, that's live food and some toys). It's not easy, but it's addictive!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 10:15:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Plenty of space for them to patrol. Locks and lids so they stay put, and (often) they won't take frozen food (my won't eat it). Also, depending on the species and your location and heater or chiller might be required. They are also unforgiving on poor water quality. But it's really not bad if you stay on top of your maintenance and live in an area where live food is easily accessible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 10:22:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not horrible to take care of it. The hardest part was setting up the tank and octo-proofing it. I have child locks and lids weighted with brocks to keep him in. They are fairly unforgiving on water quality, so you have to be diligent maintenance wise and they sometimes they will refuse any food that's not moving. Oh, and they only live about 2 years. But, it's pretty amazing to have a pet in a tank so alien and so intelligent! He recognizes different people on my family (he doesn't like my wife), likes to redecorate his tank (he has lined up every shell in my tank in his son), and even likes to interact with people if he's in the mood (he also lets me pet him). One of the best resources for this is tonmo.com of you want to learn more!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 10:34:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't know tunicates were a thing, thanks for that! I know, it's mind blowing!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 10:51:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now I really want to post this there! :-D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How do marine invertebrates, like octopuses, show up in the fossil record if they don't have bones? Wouldn't they simply decompose and leave no evolutionary record?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 11:04:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 16:05:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>75 gallons</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 16:10:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've lost count. I didn't really set it up all at once, I did it overtime. I can answer any prices about specific equipment if you have any though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 16:53:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>He has some Legos to play with. I'm planning to put some shrimp or crab in a container soon and seeing how he does with it. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 18:26:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think 2k would be a solid estimate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 18:28:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>In that case, I would guess about 2,000. That was starting from scratch. Hope that helps :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 18:29:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's in a 75 gallon tank. He should be around full grown. If you have other questions, feel free to ask!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 20:01:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>They float and he usually just grabs them and lets them go. He doesn't build anything with them, unfortunately.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-29 02:10:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here: http://imgur.com/a/VPfhA</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL the domestic pig is one of the most numerous large mammals on Earth. There are an estimated one billion alive at any given time.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-29 02:14:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-29 02:14:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>With around 1 billion individuals alive at any time, the #160;domesticated #160;pig is one of the most numerous large mammals on the planet. gt;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-29 10:54:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I special ordered it from a local aquarium store. Almost any locally owned fish store should be able to get them in. I don't know about the big guys, though (PetSmart, PetCo, etc). There are different species, but it can be difficult to know which you're getting. They can often be mis identified or labeled under very vague names. For example, many are sold as a "Common Octopus." However, there really isn't one octopus that is widely considered THE common one. It depends where you live. This article from TONMO explains that point t better than I can [here](https://www.tonmo.com/pages/octopus-pet-checklist/). They also have a lot of good information all over their site! Mine is from the Abdopus family.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I need some inspiration/advice on what to do with this island in my front yard. More info in comments.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 03:28:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 03:41:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have this strange little island in my front yard bordered by walkways on all sides and I'm not sure what to do with it. I've thought about going with a meadow like look and seeded it with flowers, but I'm not too sure I like how that look is turning out, especially with the palm tree (I inherited the tree from the previous owner). I need some inspiration. I'm not sure what would look good there. I've considered a small tree, like a yellow trumpet tree, on the side closest to the door, but that's just an idea (if it's a bad idea, please let me know). I'm not married to anything there (including the border), so I'm willing to get rid of or keep whatever will look best. The island is on the west side of my house. My budget isn't huge, but I'm willing to do whatever I need to make it look nice. I also like in zone 9a. What would look nice in that area?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 10:48:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>In Florida. I know. I've driven around my neighborhood, but no one really had an island that's like this one for me to glean some inspiration.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 16:33:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Central Florida, and costal. Thanks for the tips!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 16:38:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you mean making the ground even/level with the walk way?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 16:38:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! This is really helpful! Edit: How many trees/shrubs work in there? Is it big enough for two (it's about 8-10 feet) or is it best to stick with one?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>An app that lets me annotate text on screen</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 20:28:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am looking for an app that lets me annotate whatever is on my screen. I teach, and I often use a Chromecast to display PowerPoints and pictures. I would like to be able to display text, photos (maybe even video, if I'm dreaming) and annotate it on the screen. It can even be one that simply allows me to annotate something on my phone and then I can just cast my whole screen. Is there an app that can do something like this? Thanks for the help!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 21:45:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well if that's not weird, I don't know what is!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-05 23:32:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>The public schools are the biggest employer in the area. Start there. Also, a lot of new retail jobs are being added with the new Outlet Mall and One Daytona (new shopping center across from the race track). Is there a particular field or skill you have in mind? It can be tricky to find good work here, but not impossible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-06 00:14:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's definitely work in Special Ed here. I don't know a lot about admin work, so maybe someone else could chime in. If you have other questions about spefic fields, I'll be happy to answer anything I can!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Here's some more of my octopus! Some of his food didn't want to be eaten today</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-06 01:33:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Fiddler crab vs. octopus</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-06 01:33:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-06 01:56:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not this kind of octopus. The minimum for him would be a 55 and he's in a 75. He also looks a little larger because his arms are just so long, but his overall size is relatively small compared to his arms.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-06 02:03:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some are good in a 55! If you get a dwarf (also called a pygmy) octopus you can use a 30 gallon! TONMO.com has way more info than I can share here. If you're interested, check them out!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-06 02:11:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep :-(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-06 02:36:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is, but it helps knowing that is just their natural lives. It's short for us, but a lifetime for them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A fiddler crab fighting off an octopus!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-06 03:15:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-06 10:43:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most likely [Abdopus Aculeatus](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Abdopus_aculeatus). Most definitely from the Abdopus genus, but the exact species can be tricky to nail down.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I need help with this possition. More info in comments.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-06 12:03:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-06 12:09:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am a low-mid 1400 player on LiChess. Not amazing, but I could be worse. I enjoy playing the Vienna Game and more specifically the Vienna Gambit. However, twice I've come up against this Bishop to e7 (threatening/following up with Bishop to h4) and both times have been crushed by it. I've used LiChess' analyzer, but I'm having a hard time picking out a coherent strategy against it from the moves it comes up with. I've tried capturing with the knight (that ended poorly) and blocking with the h pawn (Wich kept me alive longer, but I don't think I followed through well). Any advice? What's a good line in this situation?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A new opening?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-26 18:03:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm in a little bit of a slump, and I've found nothing helps me out of a slump like learning a new opening. However, i can't decide what to learn. I:-( I really enjoy "fun" openings. My current go to is the Vienna Gambit. I'm not TOO concerned about soundness, I just like to have fun games with sharp lines. Any recommendations for something that's just fun to play? If it matters, I'm a high 1300s on LiChess. When I'm not in a slump, I run in the mid 1400s.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-26 18:53:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do as a matter of fact! It was one of the first real openings I learned. I still use it from time to time. It just got a little stale and I wanted some variation. Thanks for the recommendation, though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 10:40:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>ASL.ms is a nice tool to practice. Still not as good as the real deal, but it will help. A little pro-tip I teach my students with fingerspelling. Don't focus on the individual bletters, but focus on "reading" the fingerspelling. Almost like you would while reading a book. Sound out the words (in your head) and you should catch more than if you're mentality spelling them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 10:41:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm also trying to gauge what I can do if I decide that interpreting isn't the best option for me full time. I just kind of put my interpreting on hold (I still could do it, but no longer full time) for a job teaching High School ASL. If you're not keen on interpreting, why not teaching? I absolutely love it. It's fulfilling, fast paced, and I get to introduce people to the Deaf World. Also, if you do stay with interpreting, consider k-12 Interpreting as a viable option. I did it for years and it was a great fit. Steady hours with benefits and annual raises. When I eneded I was earning about $20/hr with a guaranteed 35 hrs/wk for 10 months (I started with a QA 2 in FL and when that ended I got an EIPA 3.4). And they withheld taxes (I always stunk at the self employed tax thing). Not to mention, working with kids is a special kind of rewarding. (that's all my opinion, though!) Edits: 1. Formatting 2. Some encouragement! I realized I forgot to actually encourage you in my post. We all hit times when we question if we should continue what we are doing, even if we love it. Don't make a decision you could regret later based on a potentially passing feeling. Stick with it and it will pay off, but also understand in might not end up like you expected. (Source: my major is totally unrelated to my field, still no regrets).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Movies and TV show episodes including ASL.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-31 11:31:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello everyone! I'm a new highschool ASL teacher. I want to start building my school's collection of ASL related moves and TV shows and I would like some recommendations. I have some on my list already. There are the documentaries: -Through Deaf Eyes -The sound and the furry -The follow up to the sound and the furry I am also looking for ones that are more fun and less educational. I already am getting: -Switched at birth (first season for now) -Mr. Holland's Opus -Star Trek TNG episode with the Deaf Actor (I believe it's called Louder than a Whisper) Do you all have other recommendations? It is high school, so I have extra paperwork if it is rated pg-13, so I'd rather it be PG or something equivalent. Thank you everyone! Edit: I forgot to add, I do have access to Netflix and Amazon prime, but if I can find the DVD, that would be preferable. The internet at work is not 100% reliable and the school gives us money for this kind of thing anyways.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 10:53:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oops, I do mean that. You're right</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 10:54:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm looking for any and all ideas!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 12:42:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>How did you assure it was safe for the tank? Will any brick work for an aquarium?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-05 10:48:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is the context of the helicopter video? Did he fly away and never come back?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How do you all feel about pet Octopi?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-05 22:30:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-08 03:30:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Typically, they close the bridges going to the beach side. I haven't heard that they will do that this time around, but that would be my guess.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-11 11:24:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also no power.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-11 12:00:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright, professional interpreter (mostly educational) turned ASL teacher here. Everything I say here is related to Florida unless otherwise specified. I also do not have a degree in ASL (unrelated bachelors as well) so you definitely can become an interpreter without going back for a degree. The biggest challenge is mastering the language. I'll explain certification it a moment. As for the language, classes are VERY helpful (this is from the guy who didn't take them), but the most important thing you can do is immerse yourself in the Deaf World. That can be Deaf friends, a Deaf church, Deaf events, but you have to build those relationships and use the language to reach your full potential. Taking a college class or two would be helpful. Also, keep in mind that Deaf Service Cemters (they go by different names depending where you are) and churches will often offer free or cheap classes. Take advantage of whatever you can. As you get a little bit of the language under your belt and become ready to LEARN interpreting (note, I did not say ready TO interpret. You can start learning to interpret before you're ready for that step), a mentor will be invaluable. Make friends with an experienced interpreter and buy them lots of lunches or something. They can help you learn interpreting without a full college Interpreter Training Program (ITP). If you work in the school district already, find out if you have a lead interpreter for your district and reach out to them to see if they have any resources. Where I am, the lead interpreter would often work with other school emplees who wanted to become interpreters. You're results may vary, though. One last note on learning the language. It will take longer than you feel it should. Don't get discouraged. It's almost impossible to put a number on how long it should take. If it were easy and quick, we wouldn't have a shortage of interpreters right now. Although it might be difficult, it is worth it! It has opened a whole new world of people and oppurtunities for me and I wouldn't trade my experience for anything. Now on to certification! There are currently a few "national" tests depending on where you live. There are also state tests, but I do not know if Nevada has one or not. You would have to ask someone local. Now for the national tests. You have the BEI, NIC, and EIPA (for all the professional Interpreters, I know the EIPA isn't considered on par with the BEI and NIC, but it is widely accepted in k-12 schools across the country, so I'm including it.) I'll look at each one. Sorry for the lack of formatting... I'm on mobile. You can Google these for more information. BEI- We don't have this in FL, and I'm not sure if they use it in Vegas. Some states prefer this one, others don't. It is less accepted than the NIC (for now). I don't have experience with this one, so I cannot say much about it. If it's preferred in your state, go for this one. NIC- this is offered by RID (Regestry of Interpreters for the Deaf). It is currently the most widly accepted national certification. It's also very difficult. It has around a 30% PASS rate last I heard. Also, it's pass or fail. No middle ground. As of now, you are required to have a bachelor degree for this certification, but it can be in anything, not necessarily interpreting. EIPA- this stands for Educational Interpreter Placement Assessment. If you want to do educational interpreting, this is a great starting point. It is NOT pass/fail. You get a level (0.0-5.0) and amazing feedback. The EIPA focuses more on signing for children and is generally not valid for what we call community interpreting (doctors appointments, job interviews, and the like) If you are interested in educational interpreting, aim for an EIPA as your first test. If you would rather do more community work, see if Nevada has a state credential. All of this is also affected by local and state laws, so some of this might not be valid for your state. If anyone who has experience with the interpreting field in Nevada wants to correct me, feel free! I think I covered everything. If there is anything else you're wondering about, feel free to ask!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My octopus passed today, but she left me these!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 00:22:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 00:28:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Those are a batch of eggs. She laid them a couple of weeks ago. If you don't know, octopi stop eating after they lay eggs (some think it's an adaptation so they don't eat their young). The moms devote the rest of their lives to caring for the eggs. They are fertile (you can see little eyes inside). Unfortunately, my octopus was a small-egged species, which means there's almost nil chance of these surviving to adulthood in a home aquarium (even labs have had very limited success with these kinds of eggs). Still, I thought it was interesting and figured I would share with you all! Here she is in her living glory: https://streamable.com/y6gbb https://streamable.com/pv8ql RIP Kevin (I didn't know she was a female when I got her).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 00:29:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>You commented before I finished my comment! Sorry about that! They are eggs!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 00:30:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>They do, I have my nozzle aimed near it. She was part of the Abdopus genus. Not sure of the species. Edit: thanks for the condolences!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 00:37:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>When a mommy octopus and a daddy octopus love each other very much... :-) In all seriousness, it is fascinating! They mate once at some point during their lives (not always when the females are ready to lay eggs) and the female holds the genetic material until it's egg time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 01:34:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most likely no. It is a small-egged species. There have been no successful hatchlings growing to maturity in a home aquarium that I can find. Who knows, though, maybe I'll be the first! :-) If they live, I'd probably sell all but one and keep that one!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 13:12:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm going to see what happens, but I'm not holding my breath. If I can get any pictures I certainly will! You never know!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 13:16:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had her around 4 months. This kind lives about 2 years-ish. However, she was wild caught, so apparently she was around a year and a half old. It's a risk you know you're taking when you buy a wild caught octopus. Still, totally worth it! On my phone, but that's the only one I put online. It turned out the best from the ones I took that day. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 13:17:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 16:54:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Caught.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 16:55:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep, one of the nozzles from my return pump are blowing into the cave.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 21:02:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>From what I understand, nobody has figured out the "secret sauce" of conditions to raise them. Some labs have had limited success with live crab zoa and fresh ocean water pumped through the tank, but you can't just go down to your LFS and pick that up and I'm too far from the ocean to run piping. :-/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 02:54:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I brush it off. People say lots of stuff, but that doesn't mean I have to care. When people knowingly say stuff like that for political gain, I think it's just a symptom of a larger problem. I'm not exactly sure what that problem is, but my gut says that the problem is that there are people who can believe that. They (the people who espouse that stuff) are a symptom, not the root problem. As a side note, I believe the people who actually believe that the hurricane was a hoax are very, very few.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 02:54:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Try the website of the local newspaper for the area you want to visit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 03:37:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is a long line of cars stuck in the road. Source: ASL Teacher</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 13:06:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>The captions on the YouTube video are accurate to his signs. One issue, though, some of the captions take the craziest possible meaning for his signs and use that. For example, when it says "monster" he's clearly hesitating between signs, but he still signs monster.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I drew with this possition today (I was black). I feel there was a way to mate, but I just can't see it. Can you all see something I'm missing? (This position was white to move)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 13:56:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-22 12:20:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>That doesn't sound normal at all. Honestly, it's very inappropriate and unprofessional on the VP's part. My thoughts (as a fellow first year teacher) is that you need to demand respect from the VP in front of your students. It could get risky (job wise), but if you don't the VP will keep walking all over you and it will make your life miserable. I would go over the VP's head and bring your issue to your principal. Focus on this situation in particular. Keep it specific to the disrespect shown in this instance. Don't focus on other intangible or minor issues. If you're not a union member and you can be, join it yesterday. A union rep can be a great friend to have in a situation like this. Oh, and document everything! Good luck! Make sure you report back! Edit: one more thing I should add. If/when you talk to the principal, keep your requests concrete. If you go in and just complain, the principal will just say, "so what do you want me to do?" Have an answer to this. At a minimum, I would request a new evaluator.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-23 12:00:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Career suicide is a little harsh, but, depending on your principal, it could result in you getting canned. I'm not denying that. What do you think a better response would be?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-28 10:50:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Beaches. Florida has amazing beaches everywhere. Also, the state park system has some other neat gems. If you go the opposite way from Tampa towards DeLand you can find Blue Springs State Park and DeLeon Springs state park. Both beautiful. If you can make it to St. Augustine (it will be around 3 hrs from Orlando) the downtown area is very unique. Also, if you're in Orlando, you're not fat from Ocala state Forest. There's also a lot of natural beauty there. I'm sure Orlando has a lot of great areas, too. I hope someone local to there can chime in and help. Is there any kind of place you had in mind?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hobbyists of Reddit, what unexpected ways has your hobby become useful outside of your hobby?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-30 19:25:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is this coral? I bought it off the discount rack at my LFS. The guy said it will survive a low light tank (and it's even grown some)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-03 23:38:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 02:27:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is there something wrong with it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 11:47:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your options are Bright House and ATT. Neither of which is great. I'm on ATT now, but I switch every few years for the promo rate. Both of them have internet only plans.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is this coral? I know the little wine is Xenia, but what's the bigger one? Another find off my LFS discount rack which I was told is fairly hardy.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 12:29:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 17:59:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>My bad! You're right. Old habits. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 20:58:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not concerned about it taking over. My tank is NOT a coral tank (low lights and low nutrients) so I'm not sure they will thrive. I am just curious if it's possible to raise them in a tank like mine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 10:47:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can think of five reasons they're still around. 1. Some people DO like Subway. I like Subway over Firehouse. 2. They also have a better selection than Publix. 3. You are right about the cost to quality ratio thing, but sometimes it's nice to just have something cheaper. Subway is cheaper than Publix. 4. They are everywhere. I have 2 or 3 WaWas in my town. I don't even know how many Subways I have here. I feel like there's one around every corner. 5. They are faster. Say you forgot to order online and it's lunch time. You really don't want to wait in line at Publix during lunch. It's awful! That's all my two cents. I do prefer Publix over Subway, but Subway does have its redeeming qualities!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 12:18:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's way more of a variety of subs at Subway. Everything from chicken bacon ranch melts to salads, to avacado guacamole subs. They just have more options than Publix subs. I'm coming from the perspective of having young kids. Sometimes, you just don't have the money for a full on Publix sub. Also, Publix doesn't have kids subs last I checked. Subway does. I don't think I've ever paid $9. I tend to pay around 7.50 tops and you can get a similar length sub for less from Subway fairly easily depending what you get. Oh, some subways also to a $3-$4 lunch combo. That's hard to beat. The chicken tinder subs aren't usually 5.99 (for a whole) that's just the sale price. I don't know about your area, but here there are tons of Subways around every corner. I'm not saying your wrong about Publix having a better product. I love them! I just think those are the things keeping Subway in the game here. Edit: format</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 18:30:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>The rule of thumb in Florida is that there's probably a gator in every body of water. That being said, unless they are accustomed to people feeding them or you are near their nest, an adult human has almost nothing to worry about from an alligator. Some bodies of water are not safe due to pollution or flesh eating bacteria (sadly, that's not a joke), but plenty of people still enjoy the lakes, especially the ones in central Florida, year round.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What kind of tree to these leafs belong to? I'm in central/Eastern FL.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 23:22:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-13 10:10:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>It does! Thanks for the help!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Beginner questions. Mostly mulch related.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-13 10:23:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have been struggling to find some of these answers online. I'm afraid I'm not asking Google the right questions so I'm hoping you all can help. From what I understand, mulch works best when it's about 3" deep, correct? I don't intend to use the tarp/weed blocker material (it's for a little planter/island in my yard, if you're really curious, it's in my post history, but i dont think it really matters for this question). I know with mulch around trees, you need to keep it away from the root ball/trunk, is there a way to keep it from leveling out like sand would? Is that a maintenance thing or does it not happen with mulch? In that same vein, do I need to do the same with flowers (keeping it away from the base) if I have a 3" mulch bed? Final question about the same feature but not mulch. I always loved boulders or large rocks in landscaping. What is a reasonable price for one of those? Are there any unforseen issues or frustrations I should know about if I want to get one? Thank you all so much for your help!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-13 11:41:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the reply! I thought the mulch had to be away from the root ball or it could cause decay and rot at the base of the tree. Is that not the case? Or, would you just plant it so that the root ball is a little above the mulch (if that makes sense)?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I HAD a little bristle worm in my tank. Then I thought it died... I was wrong it only grew bigger!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 10:34:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 10:35:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not really looking for any advice. It doesn't seem to hurt anything. It's just amazing to me how big it has gotten! As far as I know, it's the only one in my tank.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 10:52:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>You don't NEED a degree to work, but you need one of you want to take this career as far as you can. Interpreting is mostly about credentials. If you have one of those it's very unlikely you will be competing for jobs; there is plenty of work out there for qualified interpeters. It doesn't even have to be a NIC credential. Depending on your state, you can work with a state QA (if available), an EIPA, or a BEI (If your state uses that). You can Google all of those for more info. However, a BA will open up many more opportunities, including the ability to get the most widly accepted (and best compensated) certification in Interpreting, the NIC from RID. Also, if you might want to teach, a minimum of a bachelors will be required for high schools and many colleges (even community colleges) like to see master's degrees. Tldr a bachelor's will let you go way further in this career than only an associate's.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>LiChess says Be2 is the proper move for white in this situation, but I don't see it. Why wouldn't the pawn capture on c6 and white be up in material?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 11:46:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 11:49:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>The crazy thing is, I didn't do that. I seeded a lot of dead rock with a couple pieces of live rock and I still get this thing. Not that I'm complaining, I think it's amazing the stuff we share our planet with.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I found this while analyzing one of my games. I'm glad my opponent missed it. Black to play and win.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 03:33:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 00:49:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think we need to know more about your friend. Does he need therapy or just a friend? Are there counsolors at the school? That would be a good place to start. Besides that, I don't know of anything close and free in that area. Depending on his religious bent, churches can be a great help for things like that. They often offer free counseling and can provide a place to meet friends and just to get away from school. PM me if you want any info on churches in that area. If you give us some more info, we might be able to help a little more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-01 09:47:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've lived all over Florida, so maybe I can help some. I have no experience with where tech jobs are in Florida. I only know two people who work in tech. One from home and one at a hospital. Neither one is dependent on a location. So for that part, I can't help at all. Pretty much anywhere in Florida will have the same weather. Up north will get a little cooler, but not too bad. Housing is more tricky. I can only speak for my area (east coast), but prices have gone up here lately. Ok, for some concrete recommendations, look into any Tampa Suburbs (Clearwater, Riverview, and others). You're close to Tampa for work but in a smaller area. If that's too big, Sarasota, Daytona, or Ft. Myers might do it. Jacksonville is a large city, but it is so spread out many places feel less populated. If you narrow down things a little I might be able to help some more. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 09:23:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's what I thought.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 09:36:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>ASL sentence structure is looser than English structure. I wouldn't call the order "improper" at all. Life Print has a great write up ASL sentence structure here: http://www.lifeprint.com/asl101/pages-layout/grammar.htm Also, there are ways to sign more casually, but, in my experience, those tend to deal with production of the signs, not sentence structure. The signer might not bring a sign up to their forehead or wont make all the movements properly. A fluent signer can get away with this but any good teacher will correct it as sloppy while you're building the foundation for ASL. Finally, both sentences are fine in ASL. There are even more ways to sign it, too. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 10:50:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>To answer the question in your post, it can be. North Florida gets cold fronts sooner, but all in all, Florida is just hot. :-) Ormond by the Sea is a neat little town in Volusia County. Flagler Beach is kind of quaint. I can't recommend the keys enogh. I love it down there. I'm sure there are other small towns dotting the coast. What exactly are you looking for? Any reason you don't want the gulf coast?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 11:46:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Keys are awesome. If you want a small beach town feel, don't stay in Key West bit check out Marathon or some of the smaller islands. However, Key West is still awesome and I love to visit there! I hate to be that guy, but just to temper your expectations, hurricanes are a thing wherever you live in Florida. I've lived on both coasts and have been hit in both places. It's just part of the deal here. That being said, the Atlantic is still awesome. Better surfing on that side! :-) I hope you enjoy your time in Florida! Make sure you get a Publix sub while you're here!! :-D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What are you favorite sound openings?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 11:58:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I am in a slump (like right now) learning a new opening is something that always helps to refocus my mind, break the rut, and pull out of it. However, I also struggle with too many options, so I want to look for recommendations. I posted before asking for crazy and fun openings to help me out of my last one and it worked! I have noticed that solid, possitional play is a weakness of mine. I tend towards gambits almost every game. This time I want to ask what your favorite solid, boring openings are? I should add, I do already know and have played the London System countless times. I'm looking for something more fresh (to me). Any solid openings you all love to play?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 18:49:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>My school is trying to move to all PBL. It seems really promising, but I feel like it works better for some subjects rather than others.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 10:20:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>St. Augustine is one of my favorite cities in Florida! I wouldn't call it as a small place (the places I named off are really little beach towns) but there is tons to do there! The down town is a blast to walk around in and there's a lot of tours, state parks, restraunts, and sights to check out. I highly recommend! :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 03:03:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dankon! Mi komprenis malmulte, tamen estas bona por mi! :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I just got a new Octopus! Meet Pete! (More info in comments)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 10:36:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 10:39:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is my new Octopus following the death of Kevin. This is Pete!! He was sold to me as a Common Octopus (O. Vulgaris) and of that ID is correct, he is a baby! He is living in my 75 gal aquarium and is still adjusting. This morning was the first time I cought him out and was able to get him on vodeo. I must have spooked him because his response was to pretend to be algae. :-D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My new octopus pretending to be algae!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 10:41:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My new baby Octopus got scared this morning, so he pretend to be a piece of algae!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 10:43:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 23:47:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I special ordered him from my LFS :-) they are awesome!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 23:48:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep! My tank is locked down tight!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 23:49:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's tough. The last one I got was full grown when I got her, and she passed after 4 months. That was kind of rough, but it's also neat to get to see them round out what is for them, a full life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 03:18:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>No she won't, who would take care of the Octopus if she did? ;-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 10:25:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have all my desks in a giant semi-circle. However, I teach American Sign Language, so I have to keep good sightlines for everyone to the front of the room.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 21:38:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>What was the purpose of the brow plate? He is already wearing a large helmet. What extra protection did it provide? Great colorization, by the way!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL of the tongue-eating louse. A parasite which detaches a fish's tongue and becomes a new, functional tongue. This is the only parisite known to replace a host organ.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 13:22:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 13:24:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>C. exigua #160;extracts blood through the claws on its front,[clarification needed] #160;causing the tongue to #160;atrophy #160;from lack of blood. The parasite then replaces the fish's tongue by attaching its own body to the muscles of the tongue stub. gt;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL of the tongue-eating louse. A parasite with detaches a fish's tongue and becomes a new, functional tongue. This is the only parasite known to replace a host organ.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 13:34:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 13:34:39</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; C. exigua #160;extracts blood through the claws on its front,[clarification needed] #160;causing the tongue to #160;atrophy #160;from lack of blood. The parasite then replaces the fish's tongue by attaching its own body to the muscles of the tongue stub.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 15:28:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would recommend r/Orlando for your question. You will get better answers there!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Variation of the sign "Early"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 10:36:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was having a discussion with a colleague yesterday regarding the sign EARLY. I could have sworn I have seen it coming toward the signer (as a variation) but she never had. I went to look it up, and can only find EARLY being signed going away from the signer. Am I misremembering the variation? Has anyone else seen EARLY signed coming toward the signer? EDIT: thanks to some of the comments on here, I know this is a signed used for early in some places. I had a conversation with a different colleague today who thought nothing of this variation for early. His words were a very casual "I've seen it both ways." Now, I'm more curious to figure out where this sign is used and if it is possibly an older sign for early. :-) Fun stuff!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 10:47:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is an old post, but I just came across it and I wanted to take a stab at it. First, it is alway commendable to study and learn a language. I learned a little bit of LSP (Peruvian Sign Language) for a trip to Lima a few years ago. Honestly, I forgot most of it because I don't use it. If you don't have an outlet to use that language, you will always be limited in your fluancy. That being said, the exact opposite is true if you do or will have an outlet for it. With an outlet to use it, sky's the limit! I would start with ASL. It is one of the most widly used sign languages. Many (but not all) countries who don't even use ASL borrow heavly from it due to the fact that many of the first Deaf Schools were established by Americans.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 17:54:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>The one I'm referring to looks like the first variation you mentioned, but the dominant hand moves towards the body rather than away.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 17:57:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm just glad to know I'm not crazy! :-) Would you mind sharing in what region you learned ASL? I learned in Florida and I'm wondering if it's a regional variation or if something else is going on with it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 17:58:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the input and your region. I'm really interested in what is going on with this sign.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 18:00:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>The variation I'm referring to is signed like "take advantage" with the non dominant hand face down. A lot of my formative signing years was spent around older Deaf people, so that's an interesting observation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 21:14:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, it's not fingerspelt. It looks just like the standard sign for early but moving towards, not away, from the body. Apparently, I'm not the only one to have seen it, now I'm just trying to see if it's an older sign or just a regional one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 21:15:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm trying to place what region it belongs to as well. Just because it's not signed here doesn't mean I haven't picked it up elsewhere. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 21:23:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could be an issue with getting signs crossed. I've seen it happen to fluent signers whj know multiple signed languages. Either way, probably still with while if you enjoy it. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ASL Art Idea</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 21:29:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I teach in a public school. The art club is doing an awesome fundraiser where we can commission a piece of art. I want something for my classroom, but am having a problem coming up with a good idea. I want something lighthearted and related to ASL. I like the idea of two hands signing something on the canvas (of you do an image search for ASL art there are some neat examples), but I can't decide what sign for them to be doing. Right now, my leading idea is "Bacon" (I'm not a very creative person) but I thought I might ask the internet and see if you all could help me come up with better ideas! What is something light hearted but still related to ASL I could do for a custom painting?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 23:51:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>As an instructor, I teach it as a matter of preference, but I always use the ckeched E in my finger spelling.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I've never seen a $600 clown fish before. Saw one today at my LFS! I thought you all might appreciate it!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 00:12:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 11:47:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think I know the sign you're referring to. That's a regional sign for early. I think it's regional to Canada, but didn't quote me on that. This sign looks exactly like the typical sign for early except in movement. Rather than the hand moving away from the signer, it moves towards the signer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 22:27:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I-4 East to I-95 South should avoid all tolls. You might add some time to your trip, though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 12:26:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Best thing you can do is get involved in your local Deaf Community. Use the language as much as you can and it will pay off in spades later on! As to certifications, they tend to be valid across state lines unless it is a test for your particular state. Usually a NIC (requires a bachelor's) is good almost anywhere. An EIPA is also good for Educational interpreting just about anywhere and does not require a 4 year degree. The BEI is valid in some states. What state do you plan to live in? That will influence the route you take! Alternatively, you could just move to Florida. All you need to do is walk up to a news conference and you can become an interpreter. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Local students get credit for keeping Daytona Barnes  amp; Noble open</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 03:43:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 10:52:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I teach ASL. I don't really have a short, pithy thing like that which would translate well. I was more looking for a semi-random sign that would look well in a painting. I found one, though. I've decided to go with Octopus. I keep them as a hobby (you can see some in my post history). Thanks for the idea, still!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I love playing people like this! Had a great game this morning with a good sport! The game continued 16. ... Re6 17. Ng5 Qxh2+ 18. Kf1 Qxf2#</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 11:39:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 13:15:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good call, I missed that line. I'm also pretty sure there was a better move on his part than Ng5, but I'm not sure what exactly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 16:05:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why don't you play at 5am?! I'm just an early riser and I enjoy an early morning game. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 04:36:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I totally agree! Also, a lot of people never take into account the number of resources that went into translating the KJV. King James had literally the entire riches in England (and the political motivation) to hire all of the best scholars of that time. Even taking into account they didn't have access to newer discoveries like we do today, the actual translation work itself is top notch. These people were experts in their respective languages and they had teams of these people translating, retranslating, and editing those translations the Bible. The KJV was not some monk working alone, but the King of England poring resources into a massive translation work that hasn't been seen to that scale since. Read whatever Bible you want, but it bothers me to see people be so dismissive without backing up their claims.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 12:18:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>They did fix the mistranslations. The KJV was updated several times since its first printing. Can you cite any blatant mistranslations? Newer documents does not make them better. There's a whole process of textual criticism that went into any text that was used. Regarding the Old Testament, newer manuscripts have just proved how exact the Jews were with their copying (original manuscripts have all been lost to time). With the New Testament, it's a little more difficult, but everything they had, even when the Greek Text for the KJV was put together, was taken into account at that time. However, they have more now, and that should make a difference, right? The variation between manuscripts is tiny. Most variations are synonyms replacing one another. A few are verses that are or are not there (this is where textual criticism comes in). None of these changes affect any doctrinal aspects of the Bible. I'm not criticising the newer translations, they can be great. I also don't want to write the KJV off because of its age, either. It still has some great qualities that have kept it around for so long.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 12:28:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thou/Thee/Thy is singular. You/Ye/Your is plural. Singular and plural pronouns are definitely a thing in Greek and I'm pretty sure they are in Hebrew and Aramaic as well. I would also disagree that there is political influence in the KJV. King James was very hands off in the translation work. The translators themselves were experts in their fields. I just can't make that leap. Not saying there's not other great translations out there, I just don't see the political bias.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 13:11:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a teacher in this area! (I won't say where for privacy concerns, but I can help!) First year teachers make about $38,000 a year. I don't know your experience, but that would obviously matter. Benefits aren't awful, but if you want the family insurance plan it's insanely expensive and unaffordable. I am the only one on my insurance and I don't pay anything for it. As an FYI here, you can earn more if you teach in Flagler County (about 30 mins north) but theres more work around here for teachers because of that. I teach High School, for reference. Nothing more has been expected of me outside the usual paperwork and classes that you get anywhere. I haven't even been asked to coach or sponsor a club yet. That could vary by administration. The students all depend on the area. Port Orange is more wealthy and has more involved parents. Other schools, especially the title 1 schools, tend to have poorer students and all the issues that come with that. Not saying that you shouldn't teach at a title 1 school, I have and love it. But I can't really generalize about the students. I can't really say specifically for each school. We get a stipend fro. The county every year for supplies (still waiting on this year's). My school has been awesome about getting me books and whatever else I need, and I am not even a core teacher. We follow the same standards for the state. For me, my curriculum map is more of a guideline, but you might have an EOC (End of Course) Exam which would mean a more detailed Curriculum. I can't speak to any of that for Math, but I know they involve World Language teachers in making the coroculum I use. There's too much testing, but I think that's a Florida thing. There's EOCs and DIAs (District Something Assessment) AST well as PERT (some college entrance test) and I'm sure I'm missing others. It bites, but it is that it is. Please feel free to ask more. I enjoy teaching in the area and do recommend it. If you have more questions, fire away. If you want to talk specifically about schools, send me a message! Edit: just realized I missed your question about the union. We have a fairly strong union. Sometimes too strong for my taste, but I'm still a member.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 13:51:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I respectfully disagree. In more contemporary English, I believe you are right, but with the KJV, it's specifically is singular and plural. I took two years of Biblical Greek in college. Our second year was exclusively practicing translating Bible passages. We were specifically trained to follow this convention. Additionally, every passage I translated and later checked against the KJV follows this convention. Here's some Wikipedia articles: Ye: https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ye_(pronoun) Thou: https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Thou Here's an informative discussion on a fundamentalist forum: http://av1611.com/forums/showthread.php?t=1025</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 14:29:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did. It can be used like that, but in Biblical Translation, Ye and You differ in tense:  #160;If ye abide in me, and my words abide in you, ye shall ask what ye will, and it shall be done unto you. John 15:7 For ye have the poor with you always, and whensoever ye will ye may do them good: but me ye have not always. Mark 14:7 Ye have not chosen me, but I have chosen you, and ordained you, that ye should go and bring forth fruit, and that your fruit should remain: that whatsoever ye shall ask of the Father in my name, he may give it you. John 15:16</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 15:54:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>As far as I know, and I encourage you to follow up with the department of education on this, It is mandatory, but you have a year to take tests and three years to take any required classes. Once you get the job, there are a lot of help and resources to get you through the tests. Also, if you have a master's in math, this area has a lot of colleges. Daytona State College, Bethune Cookman University, Embry Riddle (might require more than a master's to teach math there) and I believe UCF or USF has a small satalite campus here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 16:29:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's all classroom management. It's up too the teacher how much talking they allow to happen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 22:07:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>You would be paid more right off the bat with a Master's. Also, if you have teaching experience, you will earn more. My figures are for a brand new, inexperienced teacher with a bachelor's. You will make less here than any large city, but it is much cheeper to live here. If you're careful with your expenses (read:don't waste money or have mountains of debt), it's entirely possible to live off a teacher's salary here. It helps that there is no state tax in Florida, so you do get to keep more of your money. :-) FCAT is not tecnically a thing anymore. It's called the FSA now, but it's the same thing with a different name.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 22:11:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was my first thought. This is one of the stupidest things I have seen in a long time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 02:40:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Deltona is the same county, so all the information should carry over. :-) If you're not tied to Daytona Beach (I love it here) another poster commented about towns in the area. Daytona Beach is small compared to the surrounding area. New Symerna Beach and Edgewater both have that small town feel with a lot to do in the area. Port Orange is nice as well. South Daytona and Holly Hill are cheap and Ormond Beach is up scale. All that is in a 15-20 minute drive. Its a great area! :-) The Deltona side of Volusia County (there's a state park that divides the county) has its own personality and is neat as well! It's worth checking out! I will also say that there are houses in my neighborhood a little bigger than that for around $130,000-$150,000.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 10:48:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I'm going to use this when I teach about Helen Keller in my ASL classes!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 00:01:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>You'll have better luck in r/Orlando and r/Miami for your specific questions. More locals on those subs! Good luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 13:51:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would talk to the apartment manager first and see if they won't mind letting you do it for a quick job like that. They are people too and get that you might need to work on your car. Most of the time, leases have that stipulation so their parking lot doesn't look like a salvage yard. If it's a quick thing and you know what you're doing, check with them first, they might not care or might ask that you have it done by the end of the day. That's been my experience. If they are strict about that, try the back corner of a Walmart parking lot or ask the parts store where you buy your parts if they would let you do it there out of the way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 12:38:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>You could. My advice, in that case, is be quick, clean, and do it during non-working hours. Also, I doubt they will evict you over that if you are an otherwise good tennant. Good luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 14:51:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>In this area, I see CRITICISE with an R handshape with the agent marker.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 10:12:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're willing to fork out the money, there's some nice text books out there. "Master ASL!" And "Signing Naturally" are the two biggest. "A Basic Course in American Sign Language" is also ok, but a little dated but cheaper and still a solid choice. If you want to go really dated (and cheap) "The Joy of Signing" has been used for around a century (maybe two) to teach ASL. There's also lots of nice ASL dictonaries to look into. I'm not as familiar with those, but I'm sure you can find them on Amazon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 00:44:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's quite a range! Thats a little out of my purview. I am partial to places I lived (Myacka State Park, Tamoka SP, Blue Springs SP, Tiger Bay St Forest, and many more) , but I've never camped them. There's a fairly strong Florida presence on r/camping. If you ask there I bet you will get some great responses. Also Google Florida state parks, there are several to pick from. No promises on the experience you will have it each one though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 11:56:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very much so. The pulsing is a warning. Kind of like "Don't mess with me, I will fight." Edit: Source: I keep Octopi as pets. My first one would do this all the time when she was upset.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 11:58:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's actually doing it. They are called Papillae.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 12:06:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Proper names are usually fingerspelt. That's not always done by fluent signers, and I'm sure for some better known movies it's not the case, but it's never wrong to fingerspell proper names.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 14:46:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the funniest thing I've read in a long time!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 01:15:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://imgur.com/0WXhKBF I like to keep my system as lean as possible</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 23:55:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I was figuring the buckets were bolted to the table or something. It took me too long to see what the fish was all about.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I found this neat move analyzing the game behind a tactics puzzle. The puzzle was good, but I thought this move was brilliant! White to move!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 13:21:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 13:43:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're right, but I didn't know it had a name! I'm learning all kind of stuff this morning!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-22 02:36:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>The puzzle was actually the next move (Nxe5) and how to proceed from there. It was a fun puzzle, I hadn't seen it before.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Not the biggest milestone, bit it's still mine. I finally hit 1500 for blitz on LiChess! I'm just very excited and wanted to share!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 22:20:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 22:54:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most of the year is quiet, but there's bursts of big events (races, concerts, bike week etc) and many small local events. We always find great family events to bring our kids to. There's lots to do outdoors here. There's a state forest just outside or town and a few springs about 30 minutes away. There's also a lot of entertainment and small concerts that go on. Once, my wife and I stumbled on a Styx cover band playing a concert down by the beach. It was a blast! I love finding things like that. I'd have to know more than service industry to give you a fair assessment of the job market for you. It can be difficult here, but they just recently built and outlet mall and more shopping centers and restraunts are opening as well. If you're in the right buisness, there's work to be had. I never had trouble finding work here, but I am (and was, recently did a little career change) in a field that is usually in high demand. Housing is expensive right now. I have no evidence for this, but it feels like a bubble how fast prices are rising. Of course, it could be all the new construction, only time will tell. I just looked up my old Apartment complex and they are renting for $765 a month for a one bedroom. That place doesn't include cable, internet or many bells and whistles, so you're probably looking at $800/mo average depending where you go. That's compared to $600/mo when I moved here five years ago. All and all, I love it here! If you have any more specific questions, I'm happy to help. Feel free to message me, too, if you're more comfortable with that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 01:03:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rapid- 1476 Clasical- 1537(?) I only have one clasical game on record since they split off rapid. It's just a little too long for me with young kids. I usually play 5+3. Sometimes I play a 5+0 or 3+0 if I want to mix it up or know I don't have much time, but 5+3 is definitely my favorite.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 01:05:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 01:05:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 01:19:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Congrats!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 10:20:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish I could say I read tons of books and play 50 puzzles a day. However, most of it was learning how to not make mistakes. Not doing stupid stuff like playing when I'm tired or getting sucked in to endless rematches because I "almost" had them. Also, learning to slow down and really look at my moves. I do some tactics puzzles and watch some YouTube videos of grandmaster games as well. I also try to take time after every game and analize what went wrong/right. I especially do this against stronger players. I do my best to play people several hundred points higher than me periodically as a measurement for how I'm doing. It's not a vary disciplined regimen, but it's fun and keeps it mixed up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-28 12:44:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ha ha, I was on a hot streak and started over doing it. I wasn't paying attention, making dumb moves and hanging pieces all over the place. I took a break from playing for a couple days and played some different openings to mix up the possitions and that did the trick. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-28 14:36:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like a dwarf Octopus (aka a Merc). Neat find!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>To get someone to buy an underage local beer.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 22:58:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 19:47:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was posted the last time this image was uploaded. http://reddit.com/r/ColorizedHistory/comments/186ljt/unemployed_lumber_worker_ca_1939/c8c6f6g Still an awesome picture.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 19:55:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never realized that was the header for the sub (I always use Bacon Reader). It's tasteless. That header should change and I'd love to see some new mods (I would even throw my name in the rink for it). Thats beside the point, though. That header is just wrong. :-/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 20:12:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fellow Octopus keeper here! What kind is it? What's your tank set up? Coolest animal I've ever kept! Also, for those wondering why anyone would do this, in my experience, the Octopus gets a pretty good life in a tank. Constant supply of food (live in my case) and no predators. Most Octopi in the wild end up as dinner before they die of old age.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 23:55:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey if you're cool, it's all good! :-) That does suck. I can't imagine how much work you put into it not to even get a mention! :-/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 23:57:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awesome! Still neat to see one looking pretty well kept!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 23:59:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have my backing! Who do we even make a case to? I don't know if there's much we can do besides start a different sub. :-/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My latest pet Octo, Pete</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 02:25:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Were Tiberius and Gaius Gracchus' reforms akin to the Homestead Act in the US?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 12:51:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Currently I am listening to "SPQR" and I am at the part when the author looks at Tiberius and Gaius Gracchus and their proposed land reforms to give captured land to the poor. Is this analogous to what the US did with the Homestead Act? I'm seeing some parallels but I am wondering if I am correct in thinking this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 13:25:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had one once who was the coolest. He had a Dwarf Gourami as a tank mate (20 gal. In hindsight probably not the BEST tankmates, but it worked) and a lot of smaller tetras/guppies etc. The ram kept to himself, but the Gourami was a jerk and would chance and harrass other fish. I never saw him bite the smaller fish, he would just chase them. One day, I saw him swim up and, unprovoked, bite the ram right in the side. That ram turned right around and bit him right back and didn't want to let go at all. I like to think my Dwarf Gourami learned a valuable lesson that day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Looking for a logo for my SubReddit: r/OctopusPics</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 00:58:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.reddit.com/r/octopuspics/ Edit: just saw I need a description. Something related to octopuses. Outside of that, as long as it's sfw, I'm happy. Whoever designs this is probably far more creative than me! :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Petting my old pet Octopus</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 01:01:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>r/OctopusPics ... a place to enjoy pictures and videos of everyone's favorite, slightly strange, and hyper-intelligent cephalopods!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 01:43:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm a new sub at a relatively new sub... r/OctopusPics just a place to enjoy pictures and videos of everyone's favorite cephalopods!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 02:00:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I just became a mod for a year old sub that had one post... r/OctopusPics a sub to share and enjoy cephalopods of all kinds!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 02:10:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Not the kind of octopus you ever want to hold... Or touch... Or see without a huge glass screen protecting you!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 10:25:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 10:27:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>From Wikipedia: "The blue-ringed octopus, despite its small size, carries enough venom to kill twenty-six adult humans within minutes. Their bites are tiny and often painless, with many victims not realizing they have been #160;envenomated #160;until #160;respiratory depression #160;and #160;paralysis #160;start to set in.[8] #160;No blue-ringed octopus #160;antivenom #160;is available.[9]" Source: https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Blue-ringed_octopus From what I remember about this photo, the holder was terminally ill and wanted to cross stuff off his bucket list. Still...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 10:28:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good bot!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 10:30:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! That octopus (Kevin) has since passed, but she (I didn't realize it was a female until she laid eggs) was pretty amazing!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 10:52:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cross posting to r/OctopusPics we love this stuff over there, too!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cross-post to r/art a beautifully done squid!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 10:53:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A blanket octopus! This post also has an interesting TIL about the sizes of the males vs females I never knew. (X post r/Cephalopods)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 20:59:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 22:16:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you sure this wasn't shot in color? I need to see the original for proof! :-) Fantastic job!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A new(ish) Octopus themed sub I thought you all might find interesting! Just a place to enjoy pictures and videos of cephalopods of all kinds! Introducing r/OctopusPics!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 22:22:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I just started modding a new(ish) sub you all might like dedicated to pictures and videos of our favorite cephalopod (and others)! Come on and check out r/OctopusPics!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 22:37:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm rebooting an old sub focused on pictures and videos of our favorite cephalopods (and the other ones, too)! I think you all might like it! Introducing r/OctopusPics!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 22:47:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>(x-post from r/scuba) Pelagic octopus on a black water night dive :)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 00:55:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 01:21:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>From what I remember, it was a terminally ill patient. I don't know if that makes it any better, but I could see why someone would want to if they were going to die anyways.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 02:20:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fellow Florida first year teacher, but with more experience in the system as support staff. When it comes to certifications, I've heard, from my admins, it's out of the principal's hands. Even if they're saying that, you still ought to cover yourself and figure out that certification if you want to continue to teach TV production. The only hope I can imagine you have without it is to teach out of area (I'm having to do that now while I do classes for my endorsement). I know that sounds bleak, but don't just go off what your admin says. There are laws that supercede their authority. Admins say all that stuff now, and then it's "oh, you have 2 weeks to pass this test." Always remember, it's your job on the line, not theirs. Edit: a word</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 02:31:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>A lot of deep sea animals are. It's still amazing to see a picture!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A baby Octopus!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 10:28:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 10:36:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I don't understand this analysis. LiChess says it's better for white to play rook takes knight. However, it also has white losing their queen a couple moves later in that line. What's so wrong with king takes bishop?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 12:15:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 17:47:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not stupid at all. Honestly, I'm not sure of all the science behind it. I just know that, as long as they remain wet, they can survive out of water.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>An octopus crawling around on land!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 17:52:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 17:54:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics for more like this!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>(x post r/aww) octopus and human interaction. He's a brave little guy!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 17:59:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>An octopus uses shells to defend itself from a predator!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 22:23:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 01:06:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>When you stop to think about it, what a crazy pair of people to even meet, let alone develop a friendship!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Octopus in an aquarium acting like a pice of algae.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 01:44:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It never ceases to amaze me how quickly and adeptly an octopus can change color and texture!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 10:18:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 10:29:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some students call me Mr. First Name. I was support staff (ASL interpeter) the last 2 year at this school. I went by Mr. First Name with students during that time to differentiate myself from a teacher (if students see you as a teacher, they will interact differently with the Deaf student). Now I'm a teacher, some students haven't been able to break the habit, so I let it slide as long as they stay respectful. I still always say something if the drop the "Mr," though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Octopi dont have any bones (except their beaks) so they can fit through some incredibly small openings!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 22:49:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 23:53:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looking at my school, my big question is how would it be enforced? Students can just lie and say they don't have one. Or carry an old decoy phone (they do this already so their real phone doesn't get confiscated). What about students who leave early for OJT or dual enrollment classes? What about students who legitimately need their phones for family matter (rare, but does happen). Phones irk me as much as the next teacher. I just have a lot of questions about how a system like this would be implemented.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 01:21:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed! Just amazing the way they move!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 10:39:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love it! Thank you so much! I do have one request. For me, the ones with text are showing as black on a black background. Can we either change the background or the text color? Also, and this is just ignorance, why the 3 different sizes? Is there a reason I would use the small one over the bigger one? Thank you again!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>These guys are so smart!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 10:43:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 10:51:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good bot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 17:57:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Perfect! Thank you for the explanation!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Octopus in a home aquarium catching multiple shrimp and swimming away with her prey!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 21:44:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>(x post r/OctopusPics) An octopus in a home aquarium catching multiple shrimp and swimming away with its prey!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 21:49:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>An octopus hatching!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 23:25:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 10:43:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know! Itsnt that the craziest thing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 14:09:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I doubted you when I read the title, but that was really nice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>(x post r/Octopus) The underside of a tentacle!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 14:23:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 15:42:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just want to put out there that if you like this you might like r/OctopusPics!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A dumbo octopus.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 15:44:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 15:45:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>The thing that gets me about these guys it's just how strange and alien they look. Even though we share planet with them, they look like they could be from somewhere else.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 18:35:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>As an octopus keeper myself, I'm just blown away it's napping outside its den! My first thought was that something was wrong, but it still has way too much control over it's skin to be ill. Neat video!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Not sure if it's "dreaming" like the video says, but still an awesome video!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 18:35:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 19:55:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do! And it's pretty fun! They're so intelligent and so strange all at the same time. It's neat to have an animal in an aquarium that can interact with you. My first one would grab my hand and let me pet her if she was in a good mood. My current (second) one isn't as interactive. It is a different species and more aloof than my first one. It has its down sides, too. The biggest is that their lives are so short. Dwarf octopi live about 8 months and medium sized octopi (think head the size of your fist) live only about 2 years. Couple that with the fact that almost all octopi for sale are wild-caught, and you have a recipe for having a very interesting pet that you won't have very long. I had been keeping aquariums for years and had always been interested in octopi. When I bought a home, I finally got an aquarium big enough to house one (mine is 75 gallon). It was just a natural fit!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 11:35:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I recently switched to Todoist and I spent a lot of time shopping to-do list apps. There's not really anything "better" for me, but there are some that do things differently. Toodledo is nice! I used it for years before todoist. The reasons I switched were that Todoist has a much better mobile interface and file/photo attachments. However, Toodledo is much more customizable (seriously, there are so many fields you can turn on and off) and has a simple notes and list functions semi-integrated into their list (I wish Todoist had this). When I was shopping, any.do was also VERY interesting to me. In the end, I went with Todoist. The biggest reasons I went with Todoist over any.do were filtering and the recommendation of a trusted friend. I didn't notice anything any.do did BETTER, but it does almost everything Todoist does and it also has a very clean UI. If you're looking for a change, I would start with Toodledo and any.do. Their both solid to do lists. I hope this helps!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 15:01:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here's an article about the video: http://abcnews.go.com/Technology/wireStory/virginia-aquarium-captures-video-octopus-born-52970390 By the way, if you're into this, you might be into r/OctopusPics!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 16:44:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for that clarification!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 17:56:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're not alone! You know there's a lot of subs out there for this stuff! r/Octopus r/OctopusPics r/cephalopods r/octopi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>An octopus on top of an eel!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 18:03:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 11:21:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/ofcoursethatsathing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 11:22:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm glad I'm not alone in that!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>(x post r/gifs) Ninja Octopus uses ink to make a decoy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 11:28:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 12:46:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you have to make it happen now!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 13:39:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I see the old one far more than the new one. Could be regional, but I'm not sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 14:26:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even a day without subs can be a real pain for administrators! Good for you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Amazing octopus camoflaoge!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 02:16:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Video of octopi in the wild!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 22:55:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 00:17:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cool concept! Seems like it will be a neat series of videos!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>An octopus showing off its color changing abilities!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 18:02:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-14 22:41:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A baby octopus!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-14 22:43:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A "walking" octopus (with a bonus sea urchin)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 02:27:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 02:27:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 02:29:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is it really? Had me fooled!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I think most of us would agree with this guy?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 10:01:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 10:36:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know it's totally different being a military interpeter, but I can't help but to think, as a sign language interpeter, how strange it would be to shoot someone you're interpreting for. Edit: I know it's not the same thing. It just had a connection to my life I found interesting. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 12:11:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>It must feel so crazy to have a big one like that grab your hand! I wonder where this was and what the backstory is!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just some more Giant Pacific Octopus for your enjoyment!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 12:43:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 12:43:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 14:31:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>A nick name is 100% fine. If your name is Robert and you decide to go by Bob with the Deaf, that's no problem. It's not totally uncommon for new signers to do just that. If your name is Methuselah, and that's what you go by to everyone, but you decide to just call yourself Met out of uncomfortableness/laziness, then that's different. However, if it's a real nick name people use, I wouldn't worry about it. If you want a sign name, using your full name will facilitate that quicker. The Deaf will get tired of fingerspelling it sooner than a shorter name. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The colors on this octopus are pretty amazing!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 20:13:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-20 10:21:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just want to leave these here for people who might not know about them but love this stuff: rOctopus r/OctopusPics r/Octopi r/ Cephalopods</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A baby dumbo octopus!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-20 10:23:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Here's some extinct and some living octopi!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 01:14:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 01:14:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love this video!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 02:45:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fair point! The color change is pretty sweet. It amazes me how soon after hatching they know how to control their coloration!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>(x post r/OctopusPics) Here's some living and extinct octopi!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 16:56:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I got a new pic of my octopus this morning!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 16:59:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It's been a while since I've shared my octopus! I got a neat video this morning of him digging a new den! More pictures in comments!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 21:47:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 21:50:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here's a link to an album with some more pictures of him from this morning: https://m.imgur.com/gallery/T0QwX He lives in a 75 gallon tank. He's alone except for some feeder shrimp (for food) and a large worm. He's a small octopus. His mantle (head) is only a few inches long.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 22:11:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got him in November, so about 3 months!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 22:21:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>This one I think knows me, but he's not very interactive. He's just shy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Here's a video of the same octopus from earlier digging a new den!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 22:25:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 22:29:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>My set up really isn't that crazy. It's pretty doable for most hobbyists. It's just a standard 75 gallon, with some added security. If you get a dwarf octopus (which this one might be, still not sure if it's a dwarf or baby) you can house it in a 30 gallon!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 23:41:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I special ordered it from my LFS. This one cost me $60. It depends where they are sourced from and the species.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 23:43:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>For a dwarf octopus that's true. For the medium sized octos (which I've kept in the past), they live around 2 years. A Giant Pacific Octopus can live up to 5 years. Still tragically short!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>(x post r/OctopusPics) An octopus in a home aquarium.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-22 01:15:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-22 01:36:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>He hasn't, but I am prepared for the possibility. I have standard glass lids. On the back I have pavers to weigh them down. On the frot and back I have child locks for a refrigerator to secure the lid. I also have nylon porch screen around the overflow.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-22 02:05:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've never had an issue with them shedding suckers! They definitely shed them, but it never clogged anything up. Maybe because I have an overflow rather than an intake? Not sure, but that's very interesting!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-22 10:13:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm beginning to think it's octopus digueti, but still no positive ID.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-22 10:16:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've found nothing beats live food! Shrimp are plentiful and cheap here. He eats salt water ghost shrimp. For larger octos, I get bait shrimp. I also have A LOT of shells. He likes to move them around and put the. In his den.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>An octopus using it's camoflaoge to scare away fish!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-22 20:54:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hand feeding a nautilus!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 22:46:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Doesn't seem to be hurting anything, but what is this hitchhiker? Looks like a plant?!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 23:16:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 23:40:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any particular kind?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>(x-post r/octopus) I won't be as colorful as the original title, but still a very unique hunting tactic used by this octopus.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 10:38:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How about an octopus taking some pictures for a change? :-)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 02:07:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 02:17:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I comurrently own one. It's 100% legal all over the US. It's really neat to have such an intelligent aquatic pet. It does kind of stinks they only live 8mos to 2yrs. I special ordered mine from my local aquarium store. :-) TONMO.com has tons of great resources!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 02:23:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you like octopi, you might want to check out r/Octopus r/OctopusPics r/octopi and r/Cephalopods there's a lot more of these guys there!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 02:24:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you like octopi, you might want to check out r/Octopus r/OctopusPics r/octopi and r/Cephalopods there's a lot more of these guys there!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 02:25:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you like octopi, you might want to check out r/Octopus r/OctopusPics r/octopi and r/Cephalopods there's a lot more of these guys there!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How about some love for a pulsing cuttlefish?!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 21:44:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 21:48:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Get an assassin snail. Then you have an awesome predatory snail! :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 23:48:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a flamboyant cuttlefish. According to Wikipedia, they grow to about a 3 inch mantle length (that's not including arms). Cuttlefish in general can vary greatly in size and, again according to Wikipedia, average 6-10 inches with the largest known species running up to 20 inches!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 00:23:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm jealous! I don't remember how much mine were, but not a dollar!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 10:44:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree. I hate how "assault weapon" is thrown around like some sort of boogie man. It's hard for me to get behind something that's so vague.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 23:11:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Laws need well defined guidelines. Knee jerk reactions that forego clearly defining what is banned and what is not will do absolutely nothing. Take this rifle: https://goo.gl/images/8AesRK Now compare to this one: https://goo.gl/images/r0qciu Which is the assult weapon? They clearly have two different purposes and one clearly looks like an assault weapon. However, they are the same kind of gun! They just have different bodies and are capable of the same damage. You ban "assault weapons" and don't clarify what you mean, people will just get the first one and do the same damage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>One of the things I love about octopi is just how alien they are!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 00:51:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A very, very playful octopus!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 02:45:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 02:47:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're into octopus pics, you might also want to check out r/OctopusPics r/octopus and r/octopi!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 03:04:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/SeeYaLaterLosers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>See ya later, deer</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 03:05:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>r/SeeYaLaterLosers a new subreddit for people and and animals who know how to make an exit!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 03:07:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A new sub for awesome exits I'm starting up... r/SeeYaLaterLosers</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 03:08:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Watch all the way until the end!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 11:41:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Piggy back ride? Piggy shell ride? Not sure what to call this!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 22:59:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 02:06:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Who let the dog out?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 02:17:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hammer Time!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 02:20:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm just going to slide right out of here.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 02:21:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>See ya!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 02:23:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 15:29:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm just going to put this over here...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 19:03:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 19:28:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm going to leave these here for my fellow Octopus lovers: r/Octopus r/OctopusPics r/Octopi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 19:29:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm going to leave these here for my fellow Octopus lovers: r/Octopus r/OctopusPics r/Octopi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 19:29:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm going to leave these here for my fellow Octopus lovers: r/Octopus r/OctopusPics r/Octopi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 22:36:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Makes sense to me! :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 00:22:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I might go with $5. I just feel like $10 is a little much when it's really not about the money, but the gesture.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 02:12:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm going to leave these here for my fellow Octopus lovers: r/Octopus r/OctopusPics r/Octopi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 10:19:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm going to leave these here for my fellow Octopus lovers: r/Octopus r/OctopusPics r/Octopi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>There's some footage of wild blue rings in this article! It's worth a look!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 10:24:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 18:11:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Honestly not sure if they're fighting or mating...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 21:55:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 01:45:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 02:55:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/SeeYaLaterLosers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 02:55:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/SeeYaLaterLosers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'll just slide right out of here...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 02:56:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 11:58:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>So true! Went to a deaf chat at the mall with my kids yesterday and had to leave "early" so they could go to bed. Still there over an hour! :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 12:05:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shouldn't that be on the bride and groom, not the officiant? When I got married, that was on us to procure an interpreter.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 12:25:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love this! It's probably already there, but it remains me of the sub r/likeus Edit: Just checked and I didn't find it! Karma is all yours if you want it. :-) Edit 2: a word</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 14:10:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reddit is a strange place. If that doesn't fit their sub, I don't know what does!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 15:47:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's crazy! How is that NOT what they're looking for? Looks like I was wrong about the karma thing. Sorry :-/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 19:53:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/SeeYaLaterLosers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 19:59:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>My fault. Thank you so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 20:00:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just saw this comment now! You have a similar looking pigmy? I'm trying to narrow down the species. Do you know what species you have?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 20:04:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>It sends a message. Im not sure about this one. It could be a warning, flirting, hunting, or whatever else it's going through its mind. As for how, they have special cells in their skin which change color. They are in control of their skin (which is pretty cool).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>That camoflaoge!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 21:28:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 01:22:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/SeeYaLaterLosers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>(x-post r/OctopusPics) octopus camoflaoge is one of the most amazing things to see in action!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 03:26:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 03:52:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, I know one coral I never want to own!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Nothing to see here... Just an octopus out for a jog!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 23:08:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 10:39:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's awesome! I love this video!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 10:43:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I see where you're coming from, but, as a parent of two, sometimes the ends justify the means :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The mimic octopus being awesome!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 21:41:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 23:15:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Depends on the languages. ASL and British Sign Language are totally unintelligible. They even use different alphabets. However Peruvian Sign Language and ASL have a decent amount of crossover and a fluent ASL user can get by with Peruvian Deaf people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 01:43:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not uncommon. I've heard from an interpreter friend who worked in Texas that the schools for the Deaf in her area used SEE in elementary school and switched to ASL in middle and high school. I haven't had much first hand experience with SEE (besides interpeting English classes), so I don't want to pass judgement too quickly. She said the students had fairly impressive reading skills, for what it's worth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 10:47:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or it supposes not everyone can be trusted and we live in a world where a career can be ruined with one false accusation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>No bones=No problems</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 00:09:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 03:05:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Until this year I was the non-teaching spouse (now I teach). I loved hearing how things were going with my wife and listening about how things went with her. I don't know if this is a general issue with teachers and non-teaching people. I think your guess at the beginning that this is more of a relationship issue is spot on. On that front, I'm not sure I have enough information to really advise what to do. Typically, I'd say tell this (what you told us) to your spouse. Clearly communicate your needs and try to find the breakdown. Use things like "I want to talk to you, not *child's name* right now." Dont assume he knows unless you tell him, he doesn't read minds and he's probably not doing it out of spite. You might have already done all that, I'm not sure. It's just my basic advice. :-) That being said, I think it's important to make sure it isn't consuming your personal life. Have some interests that are not school related. Binge watch Netflix together, take the kid on a walk together, or find a hobby you both enjoy. Also, cultivate your own non-academic interests. Have something you care about not related to school you can talk about. I hope this helps!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Even if you know it's there, it's hard to spot!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 22:51:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 10:17:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Scientists have theorized that octopus/cephalopod eyes evolved apart from our eyes. They work totally differently than ours and still achieve the same purpose!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 00:35:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 00:37:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 00:37:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 23:28:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just a great little picture of an octopus!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 23:29:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 23:34:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/SeeYaLaterLosers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Get me out! There's a human in here!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 23:36:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 23:37:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/SeeYaLaterLosers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 11:37:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>First, there's not one way. All the answers I've seen here are good. Secondly, I would also add this one: https://www.signingsavvy.com/sign/A%20LOT/2905/1 Edit: a word</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 11:41:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>About a year with a lot of practice. At 4 days, if you remember all the letters, you're doing well! :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 12:06:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>That video is even cooler than the photo! Was it in a tank or were you able to get that close to a wild one?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 14:33:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's sad to think how close this was to the end of the war. :-/ Then, couple that with the fact it was a sniper shot and he probably never saw it coming. War is tragic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Some more original video of my pet, Pete!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 21:39:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 21:42:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 21:43:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 21:43:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 21:43:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 22:33:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/SeeYaLaterLosers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>r/OctopusPics is now using Naut! Super easy to figure out and it looks great!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 23:31:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 01:26:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ha ha, I guess I did! I never realized the spelling was so similar between octopus and octopics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>One down and he's gone!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 01:48:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Deaf grandmother teaching her grand baby sign language</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 01:59:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 02:16:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mostly she's signing "grandma" and telling the baby it's funny. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 02:24:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree except at the end she grabs the baby's hand and has it sign "grandma." This is a common technique to teach babies to sign.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 02:25:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know ASL! :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 03:12:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Will do! :-) He loves the internet love!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 03:24:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>American Sign Language...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 11:07:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, hearing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 11:09:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Websites are fine, but I recommend getting connected to your local Deaf Community. Go make some friends and you will learn so much faster!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 11:14:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 12:06:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like how their largest argument against it was for TV programing. With the rise of Netflix and cord cutting, this will be less and less of an issue.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 12:33:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love how baby octopuses look! Amazingly awesome picture!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 12:50:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honest question, why do you think squid eggs? I'm fairly familiar with baby octopuses, but I'm curious what the visable difference is between baby octos and squids.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 12:52:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honest question, not trying to say you're wrong, why do you think squid eggs? I'm familiar with octopus eggs, and those look like them to me, but I have no personal experience with squid eggs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 19:22:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>That makes a lot of sense! Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 21:05:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm so excited to see our sub on here! Thank you so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 21:08:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was wondering where all these new subscribers came from! Thanks to our awesome readers! :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 00:56:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Try r/OctopusPics r/Octopus or r/cephalopods. They might be able to help!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 09:30:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I made Deaf friends in college. I haven't done a lot of formal training, but j really immersed myself in the Deaf world. It's the best way to learn. It's free, and you make some great friends!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 09:35:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>ASL is its own language. SEE is based off English. Even other English speaking countries have their own sign languages. For example, ASL and British Sign Language are totally different languages. I cannot understand a BSL signer and I know ASL. Not always, but by and large, each COUNTRY has their own sign language, even ones with the same spoken language.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A squid taking on an owl fish much larger than itself!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 09:48:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 12:26:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Something I'm not seeing mentioned is that those hours are not sustainable long term. If 7am to 6pm is regular for you, you need to take time for yourself. Of you don't, you will burn yourself out. Some things won't get done, but sometimes you need to learn to say, "I'll get to it tomorrow" and just leave. Of course, teaching isn't for everyone, but the right thing to do is finish out the year before you make that decision. Also, some organizational/productivity changes can help you get the most out of limited time. I'm a big fan of the book "Getting Things Done." I hope it helps!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 12:30:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 16:00:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is r/OctopusPics material!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 16:13:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>For my fellow cephalopod lovers: r/OctopusPics, r/Octopus, and r/Cephalopods</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 22:39:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't think of another animal without thumbs that would be able to do this!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How do you feel about "Article Wednesdays"?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 23:04:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do you feel about "Article Wednesdays"? ---- We all love the pictures and gifs of Cephalopods, but we were thinking it might be fun to learn a little while we watch. We are considering doing "Article Wednesdays" for sharing cephalopod related articles. Why Wednesday? It's between Tuesday and Thursday. It's really an arbitrary choice. We also want it to be one day because our main mission is the "pics" in r/OctopusPics. However, we are REALLY interested in your thoughts. We (u/Rex_Digsdale and I) can come up with ideas all day long, but this sub exists for you and we care what you think. Would you like "Article Wednesdays" to become a regular feature here? If you have other ideas or comments, let us know in the comment section! This poll will only be open for a few days, so vote now! ---- |Vote Button| Poll Options|Current Vote Count| |:-----------:|:------------:|:------------| |**[Vote](http://redditpoll.com/vote/6OJLI70V)**|Yes, I want Article Wednesdays!|**2** Votes |**[Vote](http://redditpoll.com/vote/2lZoijA0)**|No, I don't want Article Wednesdays!|**0** Votes |**[Vote](http://redditpoll.com/vote/8XvpfnVz)**|I don't care either way.|**0** Votes ---- **Instructions:** * Click Vote to Register Your Vote. ---- **Note:** Vote Count in this post will be updated real time with new data. ---- Make Your Own Poll Here **[redditpoll.com](http://redditpoll.com)**. ---- See live vote count **[here](http://redditpoll.com/poll/how-do-you-feel-about-article-wednesdays)**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 11:06:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Start going to Deaf events. Meet Deaf people. That's about it. It's fine if you can't sign, but I highly recommend learning your ABC's and some survival signs before you go. Otherwise you will have a rough time communicating with the Deaf.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 11:14:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>For fluancy, I learned by immersing myself in the Deaf Community. I never went to college for ASL and never had a high school or college level ASL class. I had some somaller community classes, but that's it. What I did was made friends with Deaf people (real friends, not just I-want-to-know-ASL friends) and spent time trying (and failing) to communicate with them. It took me 3 years to really feel comfortable with ASL and a couple more to really call myself fluent. It's not easy, but possible. Classes are certainly helpful! I'm of the opinion anything helps and don't get too concerned if it's a Deaf or Hearing teacher as long as they make you use ASL. Sometimes, a Deaf teacher isn't a viable option; you just have to work with what's available. Certification is a different beast. Signing and Interpreting (I assume you mean interpreter certification) are related, but different skills. I was lucky and made the transition easily, but not everyone does. There are lots of good signers who are mediocre interpreters. There's a few main certification tests right now, the NIC, EIPA, and BEI (the last one depends on your location). Right now, focus on learning the language. Get your skills up before you worry about certification.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 13:52:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>You should totally share this to r/OctopusPics! We love this kind of stuff over there!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 17:45:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven't been following the news lately. Has there been something going on with the homeless population?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Philip's Hue)Google Home issue</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 00:48:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got a new hue light (my 5th) and installed it. Everything works normally except, when I tell Google to turn it on or off I get the following error: "I'm sorry there was an error and I'm unable to control your home device." The strange thing is, it still works! It still turns on and off, but I get that error message as well. Not sure what to do about it. Has anyone had this issue? Any known fixes?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The octopus in my aquarium. I love watching him move around the water!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 01:28:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I love the purple and yellow coloration on this one!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 01:48:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 01:52:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure is! They only other things in there are shrimp (which he eats) and a very large bristle worm. Thank you! :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 02:05:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're in luck, I happen to be a mod at r/OctopusPics! You should check us out. ;-) Also, here are a few other videos from this octopus and my last one: https://streamable.com/f9b1j https://streamable.com/yvsya https://streamable.com/y6gbb https://streamable.com/pv8ql I hope you enjoy!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 02:27:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Still working out the ID, but my working theory is that it is a grown dwarf octopus, specifically Octopus Digueti. I know it's not a new baby because I got him when he was much smaller, but there's a slim chamce it still could be a young larger species.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 02:38:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got him in November. I special ordered him from my LFS. It usually takes a couple months to get one in when I order them. It had always been a dream of mine to have one. Last year I took the plunge! It's not easy, but 100% possible to keep them TONMO.com has some amazing resources about keeping cepholopds (octopus and cuttlefish) in home aquariums.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 02:43:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://imgur.com/lbdh3g2 This is it right now. The tank itself isn't very exciting when the octopus is hiding. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 11:28:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awesome! Very short lives. A dwarf lives around 8 months and a medium sized octopus lives around 2 years. They are also all wild caught, so you don't know how old they are when you get them. That is the toughest part of keeping one, in my opinion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 11:30:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Check out TONMO! They even have articles on there about setting up dwarf cuttlefish breeding tanks. It's really amazing stuff!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 11:30:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>75 gallons</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 11:36:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have weights (pavers) behind the lights. I also have latches used to child proof refrigerators on the top. Here's a better picture of my lid. https://imgur.com/1Ulyqmf</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 11:40:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>The other poster is correct. My lid is latched on and weighted down pretty well: https://imgur.com/C3CwxLk Also, it's a drilled tank with nylon screen (porch screen) covering the overflow. Also, if your wondering, nylon screen (anything you buy today is nylon, but old screen has metal in it, and that's not good) is 100% aquarium safe. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 11:41:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! You might also like a video of me petting my old octopus! She was a lot like a dog. :-) https://streamable.com/pv8ql</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 11:47:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Was it a Merc? Sorry for you loss :-/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 11:56:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just stumbled on this and I love what you're doing! I'm a mod at r/OctopusPics and I already got you on the side bar. If you want to cross post some content (it just has to be a picture) to our sub for some exposure, feel free! I'm also a fellow octopus keeper and I'm looking forward to what this sub becomes! I'm glad I could be your 161st subscriber. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 12:16:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the most adorable thing I've ever seen! Thank you so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 13:08:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Depends 100% on the species. Dwarfs are nocturnal. They aren't the best for that unless you're a night owl or early riser. I highly recommend one from the Abdopus genus. They are often sold under the name "Long armed octopus." They come out during the day (mostly mornings and evenings) and are fairly common in the hobby. I have also heard good things about Bimacs (I forgot the scientific name, sorry). I have never kept one and, as I understand, they are hard to find outside of the west coast of the US (I could be wrong there). I always feed live shrimp, so usually when the octopus is not out, I still have some shrimp zipping around, which is nice. The tank can look empty sometimes, though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 14:48:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its not strange. I have Legos in the tank, but they are usually ignored. I have found the octopuses are more interested in shells and hunting than in on toys. That's not true of every octopus, though, they all have their own personality.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 16:32:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just googled it, those are pretty awesome! I'll have to look into them! Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 16:36:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not as difficult as people make it sound. A lot of experienced keepers talk like that to scare away people who aren't really dedicated and won't put in the effort to care for it. The biggest thing is having no gaps and a lid it can't lift. Most octopuses, if they have steady food, clean water, and aren't bored, won't bother with escaping.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 17:56:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've seen worse</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I love how they move around!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 18:22:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>These two toddlers having a chat in American Sign Language are adorable!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 22:57:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 23:36:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>They are. He was wild caught as a baby. He's also a dwarf, so he won't get much bigger than that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 11:11:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe he's an Octopus Digueti. Especially in this video, the resemblance is uncanny.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 11:36:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 15:18:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks so much! If anyone is wondering, we are all about pictures of octopuses! :-) We hope you enjoy it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 17:54:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Obviously, you have to do whatever your professor says for the particular class. In the real world, ASL has a looser sentence structure than English. It doesn't alway have to follow the exact same structure everytime. In my experience, signers use this quality of ASL emphasize part of their statement. To answer your question, any of these ways are, in my opinion, acceptable ways to sign that concept.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A free swimming octopus</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 19:06:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 19:58:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>The interpeter should interpret it as is. It would be unethical to not faithfully interpet the source message. If the teacher does not intend to show a video with mature themes, the teacher shouldn't show a video with mature themes. That's on the teacher.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 20:48:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love seeing the way people dressed back then. I find it fascinating that people used to wear their watch in their vest! Great job, by the way!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 02:21:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am assuming you're in the US. If you're not, ignore this. :-) First off, it looks like you would meet the educational requirements for most states. Secondly, your ability to find work really will depend on your state. States that are short on teachers (like Florida) will be far easier to find work in. If you're willing to work at a title one school (low income families), your also have a better shot at getting work. I would think you have a good shot. With some administrators, your age might be an issue (yes, that's illegal, but it happens). However, don't let that hold you back. If you want some more specific advice, your state would be extremely helpful as education systems vary greatly from state to state. Good luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 03:08:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unfortunately, I don't know anything about that market. I hope some people in that state chime in!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Requesting a Snoo for my new sup r/SeeYaLaterLosers</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 03:15:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I posted this a few weeks ago, but I was looking at my post today and realized I wasn't clear on what I wanted, so I wanted to clarify what I'm looking for. This sub was inspired by the gif of the guy wind surfing out of his window. So possibly a Snoo with wind boarding or making some other kind of dramatic exit (that's what the sub is all about). Thank you for your help and sorry for my lack of description earlier. We are at r/SeeYaLaterLosers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Too cool to pay</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 03:22:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 09:25:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did not know that! TIL! Thank you so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Her really wanted out of there!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 09:42:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 21:16:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks awesome!! I love the idea of a crowd of snoos! Also, and this is a personal thing of mine, and we change the middle finger to something like a thumbs up? I'm just not a fan of that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The eyes! So much going on there.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 01:23:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 09:20:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's it right there! Thank you so much! You did a fantastic job!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 09:33:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Every job I've ever interviewed for, that wasn't freelance, has done this (in my industry then, freelance salary was very negotiable). I'm surprised more organizations don't! It's always made the interview go so smoothly when salary was put in the open.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 09:35:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow. Probably wouldn't have been the best thing to say, but I'd be tempted to come back with "are you sure you don't want to negotiate on pay? It makes you look cheap."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 10:50:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Should be fine without fish. Mine lasted that long with fish after a hurricane. You can buy battery powered air pumps if you're still concerned.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 00:04:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 00:04:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Octopus changing color with slow motion!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 00:06:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 11:50:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know! I'm the kind of person who gets annoyed with too much slow-mo, but it works so well with the footage here!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 12:05:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would love to have a Kroger here!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 12:14:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think this is the "last year" thing OP is referencing: http://www.news-journalonline.com/news/20180313/last-daytona-bike-week-on-beach-street-for-itinerant-vendors</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Footage squid in Japan. A guy gets in the water and swims around with it!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 22:48:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 21:49:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 21:49:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 21:50:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 21:50:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A pulsing octopus. I love how they can manipulate their skin! This one has some more slow-motion video as well.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 21:56:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 20:35:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's so small! I love it!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 20:36:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics! You should totally share this with us!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 20:42:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 20:48:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/SeeYaLaterLosers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 22:58:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>They see me rollin'...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 02:02:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>r/SeeYaLaterLosers - a place for gifs and other images of people and animals making awesome exits!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 02:10:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Making an exit... Underwater!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 09:40:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 09:44:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 09:44:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 09:45:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 09:45:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 09:47:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope OP did! It's such a strange feeling to touch one!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 22:55:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oops! I didn't realize I didn't have 25 posts! Can this stay up, or do I need to wait?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 22:56:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure! I'll add you here in a moment!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Garbage surfing!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 01:14:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A new octopus any the New England Aquarium exploring its exhibit! (Video in FB post)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 09:30:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>r/OctopusPics - a place to enjoy images and videos of all kinds of cepholopds!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 09:37:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>r/SeeYaLaterLosers - a subreddit for people and animals making awesome exits!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 09:47:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 21:02:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>You should totally share this in r/OctopusPics! We love this stuff over there!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 21:13:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Will do! Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>(x-post r/awesomenature) An octopus cleaning itself!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 21:15:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 21:16:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wanted to include a link in the comments to r/awesomenature. It's a small sub, but it's pretty neat!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A blue-hued octopus!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 00:28:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 01:53:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 10:37:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is that some sort of VR thing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Up, up, and away!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 10:43:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 10:46:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>My bachelor's isn't in education or the field I teach. At least in Florida, the only difference is j have to take education classes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 10:51:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>My subs aren't very big, but I recently went to r/needamod and recruited a small team. That might help take a load off you. With 15k subscribers, you could probably be picky when looking for a mod as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Octopus Cyanea</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 22:20:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 22:28:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 22:28:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just a great picture of an octopus!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 00:04:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 17:58:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Swipper no swiping?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm just going to ride this dog out of here</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 23:18:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 10:41:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you like this kind of stuff, also check out r/OctopusPics!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 10:41:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 10:42:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics and r/Octopus if you are into these 8 legged guys!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 10:48:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I divide it into areas of my life and, if one sub asspect has a lot of parts (eg bills) or needs to be shared with someone (like my wife), I make it a sub project. For me, this is what that looks like (I hope it helps): https://imgur.com/vYimCPo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 11:02:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for the idea! I did bring it up in a mod discussion, and we will see! Thank you for being a reader! I want to encourage other members of the community to constructively comment on this idea in these comments. That will give us some more feedback to work with!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Some research into how octopuses fight one another! It's fascinating research!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 02:25:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 22:59:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you like octopi, I can't recommend r/OctopusPics enough!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I love the red in this one!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 00:20:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Octopi like to make exits, too!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 00:22:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 00:24:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some of you all might not know, but I'm also a mod at r/OctopusPics AND r/Octopus (I got a thing for cepholopds) and I came across this beauty while looking at some content for those subs! :-) I love when worlds collide!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 01:01:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know. I don't like semantic arguments, so sometimes I like to do go against conventions. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 02:11:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think that was a different user. I don't know what you're referring to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 10:28:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do we know he didn't have trumpet fanfare? Looks like I need to find the source now! :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My octopus people need me!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 10:32:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 10:33:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>x-post from r/SeeYaLaterLosers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>An octopus running along the sea floor!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 03:05:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sometimes, great exits involve sneaking away...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 03:06:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 19:28:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 19:28:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 19:29:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 19:29:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 21:47:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 23:32:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can someone please explain the "meme potential" thing to me? Maybe with some examples? I'm having a hard time grasping a vission for what that could look like. Edit: I stickied this for visibility. I'll undo it when I get an answer. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 02:15:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was the gif that inspired this sub!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>An octopus in a heard of crabs. It's like an all you can eat buffet!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 02:18:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Swim, swim, swim and... See ya later!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 02:43:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 02:43:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cross post from r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 17:36:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Indeed it is!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 17:42:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dwarfs are less than half that! If you're interested in octopuses you should check out r/OctopusPics and r/Octopus!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 22:39:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Crosspost from r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This purple octopus is adorable!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 01:32:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 01:33:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cross post from r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 02:22:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks purple to me!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Up and up and up! In honor of gaining almost 3k subscribers yesterday and planning to hit 10k subscribers today!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 10:31:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 10:41:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>For the sake of accuracy it was 2,989 subscribers YESTERDAY! It was literally 2 days ago we had a post celebrating 5k subscribers! TWO DAYS! Oh, and this sub has only been around 1 month! I never imagined how fast this would take off! I want to thank each and every reader of this sub! You all are fantastic! Also, a public shout out to our mod team! This place wouldn't be what it is without each of you, u/xxxANIMExxx, u/Parallax, and u/SuperPeak. Enjoy the gif! :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 21:48:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seconded!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>We're taking off! Officially at 10k subs!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 00:23:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What kind of tree is this? Found in central Florida and I see them everywhere in land scaping.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 03:13:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 10:21:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 10:22:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now I know! Thanks! :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sub banned unexpectedly</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 10:47:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a mod (and founder) of a growing and thriving subreddit. I wake up this morning, and all the sudden it's banned due to "being used for spam." We've been operating within the reddit rules and I don't believe this is justified. Is there a way to contact reddit admins about this? At a minimum, I'd like more of an explanation. Thanks for your help! Edit: I should add that it was banned without any kind of warning and without giving us (the mods) a chance to get whatever happened under control. Edit 2: for people saying me posting the name r/OctopusPics on octopus pictures is spamming. I think it's debatable, but my bad if it's not. However, it still has no bearing on the sub r/SeeYaLaterLosers. Also, I fixed a word.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 11:01:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/SeeYaLaterLosers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 11:21:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gifs and videos of people making cool exits. Kinda like r/mypeopleneedme.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 15:14:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>For r/OctopusPics EVERY post was related to my sub. Usually pictures or videos of Octopuses. I wasn't aware this was inappropriate. I see it happen all the time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 15:22:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's why I posted here... How?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 18:01:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had no idea that was happening. Why do they ban the whole community, then, rather than coming to the other mods? That seems like a huge over reaction.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 18:13:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>How exactly do I do that? That's what I want to do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I think it's trying to look like a lion fish!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 15:49:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 23:49:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't. I go days between listening to music for enjoyment. Even then, it's background music. I enjoy audio books more than music. Also, as someone who knows American Sign Language, I know tons of Deaf people that couldn't care less about music. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 02:07:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a good guess, too!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 02:11:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope! It's fun to speculate, though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 11:32:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Moving to a new city was one of the best things I've ever done. It made me learn how to depend on myself. I feel bad for people who don't get the same experience. It takes a lot of work and long hours, but I'm 5 years post-move now and it's so worth it. For what you want to do, anywhere in Florida will work. Just make sure you'll be able to find work and rent isn't crazy expensive. If you already have a roommate lined up, rent should be pretty easy to figure out. I hope that helps!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 12:27:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought mimic, but I'm honestly not 100% sure either.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 11:38:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know some of the details, but not all. Could you elaborate why?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why was r/SeeYaLaterLosers banned temporarily?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 21:54:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you didn't notice, we disappeared for a few days! I want to be as transparent as possible for this! One of our mods (ex mod) was spamming our subreddit name on unrelated threads. Apparently, it was an alt for a notorious spammer (RazAli, for those who are in the know). He's done these things before on much larger subs than ours. However, at the end of the day, we were tricked and his accounts were deleted. The admins saw fit to just shut down the whole sub. The other mods and I got in touch with the admins and today we got the sub back online! We don't approve of the methods of our former mod. The other mods and I believe in running an ethical and fun subreddit. We're excited to move past this and to keep enjoying this great community! I'm happy to answer any questions you may have and we're sorry for the time you went without us! :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This octopus burrows into the sand for protection!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 22:17:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 22:22:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sorry to hear that! :-( hopefully the mod-removal will help! If you ever notice any issues, please feel free to report anything that doesn't fit this sub!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 22:22:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm just going to jump off this bridge! See ya!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 22:25:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 01:57:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ha ha! That gif feels so appropriate! (Btw, that should totally be its own post!)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 10:37:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is going to sound cheesy, but as someone who is married to a woman I love more than anyone, I truly warms my heart to hear you all were bonding over this sub. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 12:02:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe they have a free trial. That or a no questions asked refund in a specific time (I believe it's 30 days).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 18:04:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Isn't patrino 'mother'?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 19:49:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Disclaimer: I'm a first year teacher. I'm still figuring this out as well. I feel like people are over estimating how much they work or I'm doing something horribly wrong. I start school around 7:00-7:15 and never stay past 4:00. I don't work at home in the evenings (if I don't make time for my family, what's the point?) And I rarely do school work on the weekends. I also don't teach English (I'm a word language teacher) so I have more flexibility with what assignments I give. I usually opt for fewer large assignments and this seems to work well for me. My point is, to an extent, your schedule is what you make it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 20:08:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I probably spend less than average because I do a lot of performance evaluations. Some of those take place during school hours, so I have that going for me. However, some of the numbers just seem insanely high to me. Like I said, I'm a first year teacher, so I'm happy to admit I'm doing something wrong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 00:38:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I rented in Indigo Plantation on Williamson. Bare bones but nice area.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 16:44:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Try this one: http://www.indigoplantationapartments.com/listings.php?comm_id=5</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 16:48:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Strange! Works for me! Here's their contact information from that site: Connect With Us Address:100 Powell Blvd. Daytona Beach, FL 32114 Office Hours:Monday thru Friday 10am  #8211; 5:30pm Saturday 10am  #8211; 3pm Sunday CLOSED Last tour 30 minutes before closing time Phone:(386) 274-2926 Fax:(386) 274-2931 Maintenance Phone:(386) 274-2926 Email:indigoleasing@broadmg.com</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-12 20:52:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>My first octopus was one of these! They are my favorite! They make great pets, too, as far as octopuses go!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 01:38:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is she part of a public aquarium?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Requesting r/kidjokes sole mod seems inactive.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 10:50:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 00:23:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OctopusPics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 00:24:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>You should share this on r/OctopusPics and r/Octopus for some extra karma!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just like this octopus, we are getting bigger! 2,000 subscribers as of today! Thank you all so much! :-)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 00:28:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>(x post from r/aquariums) there was a video of a cuttlefish at Disney on there this morning!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 13:29:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The first part of the second guy! He totally just leaves them hanging!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 14:32:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 10:50:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>We are teaching both our kids ASL. For teaching them, look into Signing Time. You can pay $9 a month for their streaming service and you have access to Baby Signing Time as well. It's a great product and has help my kids (especially my oldest) learn ASL. I believe Baby Einsteins has a similar product with Marliee Matlin, but my kids just aren't as into that one. If your kids are watching stuff like that, your husband will be picking it up as well. It will only take you so far, but it will give you a surprising solid foundation. I hope it helps!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A Deaf friend of mine posted this on Facebook...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 02:49:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 02:51:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Indigo Plantation on Williamson was good to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A pet octopus hunting a fish!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 22:11:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 22:11:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>For the record, this one is not mine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 23:42:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it is. When I keep octopuses, I keep them in a 75 gallon tank. I don't think that tank is anywhere near that. However, the bigger issue to me is the lack of hiding places. That tank MIGHT work if there were ample hiding places, but I'm not seeing that in this tank. However, I am going to hope this is a display tank at an aquarium store or a viewing tank at a research facility. I have no evidence for that, but it makes me feel better. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 02:33:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's interesting. I always thought that applied more to hiding spaces. Mine always squeeze into impossibly small areas. I'm not saying they're wrong (maybe I am, I just love discussing this stuff), but I'd be interested to know their meaning of "small."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 02:36:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're diligent about water changes, have experience keeping tanks, and have easy access to quality food, its not as hard as you think. TONMO.com has some awesome resources and I'd be happy to answer specific questions. I'm on my second octopus now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>See ya later, I'm just going to skate out of here!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 02:43:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 10:15:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I always had to special order mine. They don't keep them in stock and it usually takes the supplier a few months to get one in. You can also buy them online sometimes!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 10:16:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Got it! In that case, maybe that tank is fine!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 21:54:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I enjoyed octo-proofing the tank! It was kind of a puzzle. Nylon screen around the overflow works well. For he lid I used pavers to weigh it down and refrigerator child locks to secure it even more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>See ya later, I'm just going to skate out of here! (x post r/SeeYaLaterLosers)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 02:48:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>See ya later, I'm just going to skate out of here!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 02:50:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 02:51:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>x post from r/SeeYaLaterLosers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 02:52:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>x post from r/SeeYaLaterLosers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 11:53:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not my app, either.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 11:54:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love this!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 11:42:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>What constitutes a "fair play violation"? Is that just a euphemism for cheating, or is there more nuance to it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Possible new squid species observed!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 23:33:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 23:34:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Relevant article: https://www.msn.com/en-us/video/newspolitics/mysterious-deep-sea-squid-spotted-on-live-cam-in-the-gulf-of-mexico/vi-AAw4yS7?ocid=spartandhp</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Possible new squid species observed!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 23:34:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 23:35:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Relevant article: https://www.msn.com/en-us/video/newspolitics/mysterious-deep-sea-squid-spotted-on-live-cam-in-the-gulf-of-mexico/vi-AAw4yS7?ocid=spartandhp</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 10:43:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not a Deaf college, but University of North Florida has a bachelors and masters in interpreting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>An honest pan handler</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 02:19:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The flapjack octopus!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 02:58:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 19:05:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>This post got me looking up his paintings. I never realized how many iconic paintings he did!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 19:06:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think any of that makes the comment of the lady in the post appropriate. If we call it "racism" or not is a matter of semantics (and one you and I probably disagree on), but that can't be used to justify insulting people based on their race. If it's not ok one way, it's not ok the other. Once you start excusing that behavior, all it does it deepen the "us versus them" narrative and divides us even more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Baby Giant Pacific Octopuses! Video in a Facebook post!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 20:30:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Baby Giant Pacific Octopuses!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 20:30:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 01:22:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wonder if those six guys he saved would have wanted to fly with him again? All seriousness, though, it's pretty crazy he did all that for his crew mates and no one wanted to fly with him. He must have been insufferable! Are there any more stories documenting his "obnoxious" attitude?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>(video in FB post) a Nautilus in the wild!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 22:07:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>(Video in FB post) a Nautilus in the wild!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 22:08:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 23:00:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>They all did the same thing to each other (killing, taking land, etc). Doesn't make it right, but it does place the European's actions into historical context.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 02:23:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've noticed the same issue. No solution, though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Looking for a Video</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 16:58:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm looking for a YouTube video I saw years ago. It's an ASL story and I remember it involved going down into a bunker (there were a lot of well done classifiers for the doors going down) and a monster at the end. It chased the story teller. It caught up to him and then touched him and said "You're it!" I want to show it to my students (I teach ASL) and I can't find it at all! I'm hoping someone here is familiar with it and might be able to help. Thanks in advance!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Looking for an ASL video.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 16:58:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm looking for a YouTube video I saw years ago. It's an ASL story and I remember it involved going down into a bunker (there were a lot of well done classifiers for the doors going down) and a monster at the end. It chased the story teller. It caught up to him and then touched him and said "You're it!" I want to show it to my students (I teach ASL) and I can't find it at all! I'm hoping someone here is familiar with it and might be able to help. Thanks in advance!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>We just had four trees removed from the very back of our yard (they were growing onto the power lines). I think I want to get rid of the ferns, but not sure what to do instead (if anything)? Wondering if you all have any thoughts or ideas! Gets full sun and is in zone 9b.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 01:02:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 10:52:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>It does! Nothing yet, but it helps me know where to look!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New Moderator!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 21:54:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello everyone! I am subject3283, and I am your new moderator! I see some real potential for this community, and I wanted to share my vision for what r/KidJokes can become! Right now there is a real disconnect between the stated purpose (jokes for kids) and many of the posts (jokes from kids). I think the true potential of this community is in the latter, jokes from kids. I am a parent myself and can attest that my kids come up with some of the most random, strange, and funny jokes and I think this can become the perfect place to share them! I plan to be more of a hands off moderator. I love to post and participate, but I don't like to dictate how the community should be run (within the rules). I plan to make some css and sidebar changes over the next couple weeks (it's my busy season at work, so please be patient with me). While that's going on, I'll start sharing some content and hopefully make this a great, wholesome corner of the internet! I'd love some feedback from the community! If there is anyone already here interested in moderating, please let me know! It takes a team to run a sub well. I prefer your account be at least 6 months old to moderate. I'm looking forward to this, everyone! :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Looking for a Snoo for r/KidJokes</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 21:56:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just became mod of r/KidJokes! I'd love to have a Snoo for it! Im thinking a child-like Snoo laughing would be appropriate. Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How does the frog tell the giraffe "ribbit"?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 02:21:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>With his mouth!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 11:33:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not an octopus, but still please totally share this with r/OctopusPics! We love this stuff over there!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 11:43:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Baystreet seafood grill. Some of the best sea food I've ever had!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 02:47:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is awesome! That dog just looked back knowing he was tricked!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 02:55:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe what it means is that one student is exerting power over another. Wether it's numerically, physically, socialy, or emotionally. However the bully preceves themselves is irrelevant here. I look at it as distinguishing between two students on equal footing who go back and forth (which wouldn't be bullying) and one student continually dishing it out on another student. Just my two cents. I found that definion very helpful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 11:53:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>For a phone/data, you can go to Walmart and pick up a prepaid phone fairly cheap with no contract. I can't help too much with places to go as I haven't lived in any of those areas, but ask the hotel staff. Most of them are locals and will give you the best advice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Here I come... And I'm gone!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 18:03:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 10:30:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>The business oriented services can do weddings as well. They just don't market to them because the bulk of there clientele are in business settings. Call around and price it out. Interpreters can be expensive, but compared to the budget for a wedding, you might be able to fit it in. Also, talk to your friend and her boyfriend as well. They might know an interpreter who would be willing to contract directly with you. You get an interpreter for less than an agency charges and they make more than the agency pays (win win!). You would just be cutting out the middle-man (the agency). Good on you for being willing to provide an interpreter! I don't know your budget, but if it does become cost prohibitive, be up front with them! The Deaf person isn't super close and I'm sure they will understand.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>All aboard!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 17:40:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It's not much, but I decided to start my own vegetable garden this year!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 00:16:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 10:26:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was worried I made that mistake. What kind of negatives will I get with them being too close together?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 10:38:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I loved in the area close to your work. Not Indigo Pines, but Indigo Plantation across the street. I loved it! I would probably love it more now that the outlet mall is there. Port Orange is also great! You got two good choices! I see a lot of good suggestions, and the beach is always awesome! Theres tons of oppurtunities to do anything you can think of in the water (except maybe ice fishing). Also, we have a state forest near by! Check out Tiger Bay State Forest. It's just large tracs of in developed land with some lakes for fishing and some trails. Its also open to hunters parts of the year, be aware of that if you're hiking. I haven't been yet, but Tamoka State park is just up in Ormond. In the DeLand area (20-30 mins away) we have a couple State Parks with springs, DeLeon Springs and Blue Springs. Sometimes you can see manatees out there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Same concept, different perspective</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 10:44:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A history of the popes</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 01:23:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any papal history books that are good reads? The earlier in church history, the better! Does not need to be from a Catholic perspective, although I'm open to that, too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 21:02:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm so sorry, I thought I replied! I definitely want the file! This is great work!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 21:03:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much! I love this! Sorry about the delay! Great work!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Up, up, and see ya later!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 02:04:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A small octopus checking out his reflection!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 02:33:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 00:30:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've seen ABC Barricades before!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 00:21:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've seen the construction "How your party" or "yesterday how your party" to represent that concept.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Pensacola Bahia question</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 20:25:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm getting ready to seed my yard with Pensacola bahiagrass. I would like to seed it ASAP, but we're expecting rain in a couple days for about a week and a half. Would it be okay for me to seed it now, or would I run the risk of unintentionally over-watering? Would it be better to wait until the rain is done and water it with my sprinklers? My yard drians well. Puddles will form during the rain, but soak in very quickly once it stops. I'm also in central FL, if it matters. Also, I've never worked with this grass before, so if anyone has other tips from all ears! :-) Thanks in advance!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>About 9 months ago I asked for some advice from r/landscaping on this island in my yard. I got a lot of great advice and it only felt right to post an update (before and after)! Thank you all so much!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 21:19:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 21:21:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I should add that it isn't done yet. I have plans to add some more flowers in the future. However, I'm just so happy with it, I had to share!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 22:37:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a hybiscus tree. I just couldn't get past how great the flowers look on it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 00:28:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>None of those here, thankfully! Edit: Your username seems oddly appropriate. If the iguanas eat the gnome that is...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 00:28:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed! That was my wife's idea; she has great taste!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 00:40:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll check it out! Any recommendations?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 01:51:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope. I waited until the next spring to do it. :-) Still used the advice from you all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The topic was teachers sharing ways students try to get out of exams. I thought you all would enjoy this!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 02:46:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 10:57:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>There was also a border I got rid of, for what it's worth. I was just happy how it turned out and wanted to share.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 11:00:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I upvoted you, so no apology will be issued. Thanks for the advice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 11:40:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>A guy I know down my street has it and I thought it looks good. I also have a small patch of it that creeped over from my neighbors house. However, it's just between the road and sidewalk and I want my yard to look a little more uniform. I wasn't even aware some people didn't like it. Also, thanks for the advice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 12:03:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope, I'm in central Florida. Hybiscus do well here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 12:55:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>In the one guys yard, I've never seen his grass get tall enough to have a seed head, he keeps it looking sharp all the time. (That, and his yard being really full and lush was the reason I even asked about it). That does look like my neighbors yard across the street. I haven't asked him about the grass though. Which kind is that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I posted about this bristle worm when it was little, and the general consensus was not to worry too much. Now it's easily over had a foot (that rock is about 6in tall). At what point to you worry?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 13:27:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 13:29:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>More details: He lives in a dedicated octopus tank. I've never seen him go after anything living, and my tank is always free of food particles (which is nice). Is it an issue? Ok am almost certain I only have one. :-) I am currently in between octopuses, so I'm in a position to get a crab or shrimp of it would help. Even if I wanted it gone, is it even possible at this size? Thank you all!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 17:51:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep! I've shared pics and videos of both on here before. Here's my latest little guy: https://imgur.com/4txS9u8</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 23:01:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>The little white hairs on it can sting you. From what I understand, they are not lethal, but it still isn't very fun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 23:31:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>How did you ship it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 02:29:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I say no. Option 1 was literally "Lonely" and option 2 was "Sad." Neither convey the same concept.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 02:37:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know of one sign for this concept. I would sign it OTHER PERSON NOT FEEL SAME also LOVE BACK NONE could work as well. This would also depend on context. When you take that into account, there are probably a dozen different ways to sign it. :-) If you gave us some context, that could help us give you a more accurate idea of how to sign it. As a side note, I love how some concepts don't have an equivalent in another language. It truly fascinates me whenever I come across these, regardless if its English to ASL or ASL to English!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 02:57:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a similar concept to my other post on this thread LOVE BACK NONE or OTHER PERSON NOT FEEL SAME. I don't know if reward would be the right concept in ASL (it doesn't feel right), but returned could work. Which sign were you thinking for returned?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 03:03:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was worried about that. He's huge... I'm not sure anything would want to take him on!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 03:04:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's too elusive for more pics. I only catch fleeting glimpses of him. This is a few months old picture I got lucky with. :-/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>These grow wild in my yard, but I'm not sure what they are. Located in central Florida.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 22:37:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 11:44:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like we solver it! Thanks so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 22:54:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not just assumed unless they tell you otherwise? That's what my school does. I thought that was the norm.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I can hear them both saying "See ya later, loser!"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 12:55:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 13:19:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is there any way to get it in the States? Also, do you have to know German? Both of those might be an issue for me. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 13:26:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! I appreciate it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 19:44:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>For sure, you are an atheist, bisexual British male. I think you are in you have an interest in biology/science and you like axolotls, but I have the feeling you've never kept one as a pet. I was not able to peg down your age, but I'm guessing 16-21. How'd I do?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 21:50:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>A plague? They're adorable! Glad to hear I wasn't too far off besides that! :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 22:25:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm going to need a source on that one ;-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 23:45:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>They're both making an exit. It's a stretch, but I found it funny, so why not?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 01:38:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>TIL! :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 02:12:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>A few thoughts: 1. RID lost a lot of credibility in my eyes by breaking off the partnership with NAD regarding the NIC. This is just a natural result of that attitude (arrogance?) in RID that makes them think they are the end all authority of interpeters. 2. If we had a national alternative to RID, I think most of us would jump ship in a heartbeat. What does that say about their ability to speak for the interpreter community anyways? 3. What happened to Shane Feldman? I'm out of the loop!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 21:39:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I honestly don't know who that was, so probably didn't mean much to me when I read it. Sorry! :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I got this plant as a gift. What is it? How should I take care of it?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 23:19:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>An octopus grabbing dinner!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 01:00:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 01:03:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Once you type in another date, the first date is de-selected.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 02:54:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is almost exactly what ARNI did. They went to high kill shelters and put dogs through a few tests for aggression (a lack of it) and other desired qualities. They would do things like take food away from them and things like that. It's not wrong. I apopted my dog from ARNI, but they definitely cherry picked their animals. Edit: I have no experience with ARNI and cats. It could be a different story with them. My experience only relates to them and dogs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What kind of grass is this?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 13:48:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 13:49:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Few more details. Found in my yard in central Florida. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 18:20:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry for my ignorance, what is a bedding flower? It grows in a carpet and has a seed head, so I assumed it is a kind of grass.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 11:33:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry, wrong tree. Only color in that patch of lawn is green.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New computer being sluggish</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 13:00:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok, I think I know what the issue is, but before I do anything drastic, I was hoping for some advice. I bought a new computer about a month ago. To be more precise, it is this one: https://www.amazon.com/gp/aw/d/B01AWOAUJY?psc=1 amp;ref=yo_pop_mb_pd_title I know you get what you pay for, but I have two young kids and I'm a teacher. My 11 year old laptop wasn't cutting it anymore, so I had to get something I could afford. I use it for simple things. Surfing the web, shopping, simple photo editing. Nothing too intense. However, I feel like even the simplest thing takes way too much power. Today I was transferring videos from my phone to the computer and it took up almost all of the "Disk" column on task manager. The memory is fine. I still have over 100 gb on the hard drive. I think the issue is the ram. Am I correct? If not, what could it be? I am willing to spend some money to upgrade it, but I want to do so wisely. Thank you all so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 19:21:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for the advice! I have a general what SSD are, but are they universal? Can I buy just about any kind and it work out?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 20:06:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awesome! Thank you for the great help!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 13:29:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eventually, but g2 blocks it for now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I know it's old, but it still works!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 14:13:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 12:43:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I grew up not too far from there. You have an uphill battle trying to get this done. Its just the culture of that area. Not that you shouldn't try. The fight in itself communicates something and is worthwhile (even if they do win). It sounds like you have the right ideas. Get your information together, make up pamphlets and get out and canvas as much area as you can. Knock on doors, go to parks, and fill social media with your message. Personally, I think education is more effective than protests. People see protests and have no idea what to do about it. Once again, doesn't make it a lost cause though. In all honesty, and I don't day this to discourage you, but you might not win this. Your up against big business and big money. However, if they win, make them work for it. :-) Good luck to you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[WP] You suddenly have the ability to understand anyone under two years old. Babies and toddlers don't realize this this and say whatever they are thinking in front of you.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 02:58:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 12:29:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's kind of an important detail...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I believe I can fly!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 02:39:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This kid had to get out of there!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 11:48:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My bouncy slide people need me!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 11:49:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 11:49:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>X post from r/SeeYaLaterLosers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 03:07:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then they fired the employee responsible, ran the background checks, and revoked the liscences as needed. There are not people with liscences today which would not have passed a background check. I'm not a Putnam fan (haven't studied him enough to make a decision), but this isn't as big of news as it seems. Edit: clarity</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 00:31:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>A mortgage tends to be less monthly than rent, even for larger accommodations. I got a 3 bedroom house for the monthly price of my 2 bedroom apartment. Just food for thought. :-) Edit: I normally don't go back and edit these things. However, I'm seeing a lot of misinformation in the comments below this one that I like anyone who stumbles across this comment to understand. In the US, for first time home buyers, there are FHA loans. Mine required around a 3% or 5% down payment. It wasn't easy, but it was worth it. Also, you pay for upkeep on apartments. That's why land lords mark your rent up. They make enough to cover their mortgage payment and upkeep. Lastly, buying isn't for everyone. If you're not sure you want to stay in a certain place, do not buy. If you like an area, and it's something that works for you, I highly recommend it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 12:32:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>For the k-12 level, it's different. Students don't often take that initiative to contact teachers outside of school hours. Most of the emails I get from students happen to be during school hours, ironically enough. There's probably a lot of reasons why that's the case. Appathy, knowing you see that teacher M-F anyways, or just the general culture of high school. At my school, admins encourage us to take a break from work, not check our emails, and recharge ourselves. Not that it always happens, but they do encourage it. They (admins) also never send urgent emails to teachers out of school hours, which helps.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 14:45:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree that, if your plan is to only interpret, a diverse educational background is an asset. However, if you might want to go into teaching, a master's opens up a lot of doors for teaching both in post secondary settings and workshops. Its definitely not right for everyone, but it is a good option for others. I know the title is designed to get clicks (worked for me) but it seems a little over the top. Just my thoughts after reading the article.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 15:48:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a valid point. The only issue I see, and I'd love your thoughts, is a practical one. To teach ASL in a college setting, for example, if your masters is not related to ASL, they require a specific number of graduate credits in ASL. Finding a program that offers graduate credits in ASL and integrates those into another masters seems like a dificult task. I personally haven't looked into a program like that, because it wasn't even on my radar until I read our comment. Well there are more graduate programs in ASL now than ever, they're still relatively quite a few. Are you familiar with any programs that have formal graduate ASL classes integrated with other Masters? I should also include, all my information is my own experience. Most of my work now is teaching ASL in a K-12 setting, but I've been in talks with a couple different colleges and the same degree requirements keep coming up. This is also in FL. I'm sure it changes from state to state, but I'm sure other states have separate credit requirements. Thanks for writing the article and responding, so many times I read these articles and never get to ask follow-up questions it's nice to get to do that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I've never seen an okra flower before! One of my favorites I've seen!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 22:49:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Help] Dog behavior I am not sure about.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 01:39:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to say thank you in advance for your help! My dog is exhibiting some behavior I am not familiar with. I am hoping you all can shed some light. My dog, Lucy, is a two year old mix. She's a small dog, probably some kind of terrier or basenji mix. My mom is visiting with her new puppy, Spartacus. He is less than a year old (he's a rescue, so we don't have an exact age). He is a small chihuahua-mix. Maybe a third the size of Lucy. When they first met, there were no issues. They sniffed each other, Spartacus would lay down and let Lucy sniff him, and she pretty much just acted more dominant, but no aggression. Lucy has just started coming up to Spartacus, while he is laying down, and putting her front paws on him. It looks like she's pawing or kneading on him. Then she mouths his neck. None of it looks agressive and he doesn't growl or nip at her (no signs he's fighting back). Spartacus just freezes. Is this concerning behavior? As I said, it does not seem agressive. My theories are that she is asserting dominance or, possibly, trying to "mother" him. I would love your insights! Thank you so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 02:12:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I get irked by the whole gorilla signing thing whenever it comes up. They don't know sign language. At best, they are trained to repeat a gesture, but it is not a language.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 12:19:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>The way some people respond is my least favorite thing about this sub. Here is someone who is proud of their accomplishment, in their own yard, and people just love to rain on their parade. I don't see an issue with constructive comments or ideas, but downing everything about it is too much. I'm happy for you, OP!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 12:20:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>That took me too many times to get. Good one!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 18:34:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you saw a person begging for money, what would you do?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>First time ancient coin buying question</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 03:04:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I recently learned that ancient coins are actually be something I could afford and subsequently have been interested in purchasing one lately. I'm really more interested in the history than starting a full blown collection but, before I buy, I wanted to ask you all a question. I've been checking out vcoins (if you all know any better sites, please let me know). I've noticed there are several lots being sold "as found." Here is an example: https://www.vcoins.com/en/stores/zurqieh/171/product/lot_of_33_ancient_bronze_coins_as_found/990471/Default.aspx Are these coins that were sorted and determined "not worth cleaning" or is there the possibility of finding some real interesting coins in a batch? Does anyone have experience with buying these lots? Would it be interesting for a first time buyer or is it better for someone with some experience/knowledge? Thanks in advance for the advice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>First time ancient coin buying question</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 09:59:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I posted this on r/coins and someone recommended I try posting here as well. I recently learned that ancient coins are actually be something I could afford and subsequently have been interested in purchasing one lately. I'm really more interested in the history than starting a full blown collection but, before I buy, I wanted to ask you all a question. I've been checking out vcoins (if you all know any better sites, please let me know). I've noticed there are several lots being sold "as found." Here is an example: https://www.vcoins.com/en/stores/zurqieh/171/product/lot_of_33_ancient_bronze_coins_as_found/990471/Default.aspx Are these coins that were sorted and determined "not worth cleaning" or is there the possibility of finding some real interesting coins in a batch? Does anyone have experience with buying these lots? Would it be interesting for a first time buyer or is it better for someone with some experience/knowledge? Thanks in advance for the advice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 10:48:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I appreciate the advice! That's what I thought, but I wanted to be sure. Greek or Roman Coins for sure. I've had an interest in both cultures. The Roman Coins seem like you get better quality for what you pay, but I do have much more of an interest in the Greek side. I'm not tied to any specific period or person, though. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 12:09:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am interested in Biblical history/locations. Those coins have piqued my interest more than the others. Do you know any good resources?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 12:11:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even when I kept one in an aquarium, I wouldn't let it climb on my hand like that. I feel like that's how you get bit! :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 13:36:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's fine! You helped a lot already!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 16:44:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've noticed a few on vcoins, but I haven't been impressed by the quality of those. Does that tend to be the case across to board with those?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 21:33:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't know all of that. Thankfully, that link is just an example. I saw several lots on the site. I will take careful note of where they are shiped from, though. Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I decided to buy myself a snowflake eel for my birthday yesterday! I named him Longfellow.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 20:30:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 23:34:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! Will do!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 23:35:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 23:35:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought so! Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 03:02:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like literature. It also just kinda made sense. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Snowflake eel questions</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 20:48:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello everyone! I shared a post yesterday about being a new snowflake eel owner. I have a couple species specific questions I'm hoping you all can help answer. My eel is young, about 8 in long. I've read full grown eels need to eat about once every 3 days (give or take). Do younger eels need to eat more often? Also, when I feed him, how much should I give him? Currently, I give him one frozen krill at a time (he does fine with frozen food). In your experience, how much should I give him? Secondly, I'm curious about tank mates. Currently, he has a 75 gallon tank all to himself (except a massive bristle worm). I've been considering a dwarf lion fish as well. But I'd love some suggestions. My saltwater experience is very limited to inverts, so I'm up for trying anything. :-) Thanks, everyone!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 22:36:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the advice! Sorry, but I don't know who Joey is. Care to share a link? My current set up is a 75 gallon with a sump running a reef octopus skimmer (180, I believe). I'v been keeping freshwater tanks for years and years. (Still have one, actually). I've also been doing salt water for a couple years, but I've only ever kept octopus in it (those are the inverts I was referring to). I wanted to do something a little new for me, but I've never kept eels before. So here I am! :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 22:45:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's all good, you had no way to know what experience I have or don't have. I never heard of that guy, but it sounds like he has good taste in stocking a tank. :-) I'll check it out. Thanks again!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 03:26:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm an ASL teacher and this would be my exact answer!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 13:29:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hold</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 15:15:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>The biggest employer in Volusia county (which includes all the cities you listed except Palm Coast) is the public schools. I'm not sure if that was relate in anything you are interested in doing, but that is what it is. In Daytona Beach itself, the service industry is huge. Hotels, restaurants, retail the racetrack hires tons of seasonal workers as well. I've made the commute to DeLand and back, and it's definitely doable. Housing on that side of the county is a lot cheaper, though. Besides the schools, and possibly the hospitals, there's not one big employer that sticks out. Specifically, there's not a lot of manufacturing in Daytona Beach.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Swear word sign? Alternative meaning?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 21:56:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I saw a sign used today in a surprising context and I'm not sure what is going on with it. I'm hoping you all can help. The sign is a B handshape with the thumb out brushing against the bottom of your chin and moving away from the signer. For an analogy, it's thank you but lower. I learned this sign as "F-you" however I saw it used in a church setting and no one batted an eye. Is there an alternative meaning for this sign? Did I just learn it wrong? I learned it in FL, but I'm currently in MO, in case there is a regional difference. Edit: there's some confusion on the sign being used. It's the same as in this video in the very beginning: https://youtu.be/gKngS7dbrNs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 05:30:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jefferson City right now. It's part of a conference I'm attending. I teach in Florida, though. :-) If you're in the area and interested, PM me! He signed it multiple times. It was a small-er group setting and the F-you would have fit the context of his sentence, but not the environment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 05:31:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>That makes sense in context and I'm glad it's not just me. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 05:33:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>This song uses the same sign in the beginning after the "not my responsibility" sign. Around 5 secs in. https://youtu.be/gKngS7dbrNs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 05:34:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've seen it used by deaf in vulgar ways as well though, that's why I was so confused that no one seemed to care.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 05:35:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely is a Deaf Church. The signer was a Deaf man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 05:44:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I happen to be at a church with a CODA pastor! So I guess it's not a standard Deaf church, but the do have ASL services, so I count it. Looks like you found me for the next few days!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 05:50:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is! I just met him and his family this week, but I've enjoyed meeting all of them!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 13:24:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok, and that goes back to my question. Why would someone sign that in church and nobody would care? I wanted to get an interesting discussion going about this. I think it worked. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 13:30:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good! RID can use some competition!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 13:48:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, but I doubt RID will agree to this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 20:26:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was a Deaf person signing it. But from what I gather for other comments, it looks like it's an older sign for too bad. It's all good, it's just a fascinating discussion for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 15:14:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>OP has a 4 year degree. They want to go back for an associates from an ITP.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 15:17:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nobody has said it yet, so I'll add it in. In most places you don't have to be nationally certified to work as an interpreter. An EIPA level can get you into educational work, some states have a state credential, and some video phone companies have their own screening process. The ITP course work would be valuable, you most likely will not have to wait 5 years to work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 19:02:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sorry, I misread your comment. Please excuse me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 19:05:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you sad?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 19:56:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>30k is a low estimate. All of those buisness expenses are also tax deductible, so it's not as bad as she's making it out to be. I made more than 30k as an educational staff interpreter (typically a low paying niche in the interpeting field) in a much smaller city. I think it's definitely worth it if it's something you will enjoy. With loans/payments like that, you're going to have a hard time with any job, especially if your living somewhere with a high cost of living. Unless you're willing to locate somewhere cheaper, just make sure you approach this with realistic expectations. At least with interpeting, you will be in an in-demand field and have a marketable skill you can take anywhere. You can also start working in most places without a national certification. There are options like the EIPA and some companies and agencies have their own screening. That is all highly dependant on your location and I don't know enough about your state to speak with confidence one way or the other.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 20:16:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>delete</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 20:24:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>What are you too ugly to have ever happen?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 00:17:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>What do you mean?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 00:44:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>The sole mod of that sub was not active anywhere on the site in quite a while. I'm the mod now...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 01:21:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes... I believe you are :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Everytime I watch this show, I notice different jokes! When Michael explains why he got his card taken away, he's wearing a fake thumb (a traditional magician prop)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 19:43:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 21:59:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's impressive...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 05:24:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Try r/Florida also, if you know where in Florida, that would help. You're looking for a needle in a needle stack.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 14:22:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is possible! In fact, there's a whole swath of experienced interpeters (mostly older ones) who never went through formal education. ASL college classes are a fairly new development. However, it is not easy and could take you longer than you expect. I worked as an educational interpeter for years before a shifted into education. I never got my RID certification (I hold an EIPA 4.5) but I know a lot of certified interpeters who didn't study asl in college. You need to look at it like a two part deal. Learning ASL and learning how to interpret. To learn ASL, the college classes do help and speed things along, but it's not necessary. However, to make it work, you have to emmerse yourself in the Deaf community. Not just going to events, but making friends with Deaf people on a real level. That, and community classes are very helpful for teaching the things that aren't always clearly explained. That will teach you the language. To learn interpretering, which is a whole other skill, the only way to make it work without a college program is mentorship. It's difficult to find, but there are skilled people out there who are willing to teach one on one. In the past, and still today, churches play a key role in this method. Although, im sure there are individuals out there willing to share as well. It's all about building those relationships with the community. As of right now, RID, the certification body for interpeters, only requires a 4 year degree in any subject, so that's not an obstacle. It is possible. Not easy, but it can be done! I will also add this, college classes do not guarantee certification either. However you go about this, you will get out what you put in. There are plenty of people who go through interpeter training programs and never interact with the Deaf community. They don't tend to get certified either. If there are any other questions I can answer, I'm happy to do so! I hope this helps and provides a little bit different of a perspective.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm working on a new way to get damsels out of my tank. My LFS sold me this today to deal with them.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 03:27:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 03:29:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm just kidding. I bought him cause I wanted a lion fish! :-) He is going to take care of some damels for me, though! He's in a 75 gallon tank. He does share it with a snowflake eel and 5 yellow tail damsels (for now).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 12:19:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've done this with mollies before! I tried with guppies, but they seemed more sensitive to salt water. Way cool!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I don't usually take good fish pictures, but I like how this one turned out!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 02:19:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 02:56:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I'm trying to avoid getting stung. :-) I've read up on it alot and it seems like a pretty horrible experience!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What do we know about Ivan the VI or Russia's personality?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 03:09:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just finished listening to a podcast about him and I found it fascinating (and tragic) he lived his whole life from 4 years old until his death in prison. Do we know anything about his personality or what mental state he was in? Do any sort of records or statements excist that shed some light on him? Are there any sort of historical comparisons which can give us some insight? Thank you so much and I'm looking forward to reading your answers!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 04:25:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't do it, but I don't block my nose at all when I'm under water. I'm not sure if I just conditioned myself not to mind a little water or if I somehow keep a small air pocket in my nose. I never thought about how I do that until now!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 12:32:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>This guy needs at least 75 gallons. However, there are dwarf lionfish that do great on around 30-40 gallons and up. They are easy to care for. They use to be used to cycle tanks (not recommended anymore) for an idea of their toughness. Just always be aware and alert when your hand is in the tank. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 14:20:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Deaf events! Use whatever little ASL you know and start trying to communicate with Deaf people. I would definitely know your manual alphabet and the signs "WHAT" and "SIGN." Then you can start asking the Deaf how to sign things. :-) It sounds trite, but if you start doing that, you will learn so much and meet some really great people, too!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 20:39:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is correct. Awesome fish!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It's been a little slow lately! How about a glass octopus to liven things up!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 20:43:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 23:07:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>GFO?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 23:10:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 00:05:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm going to guess yes, but not many assuming you get a dwarf species lionfish. Hopefully someone who knows more than me can chime in. I've never kept one of the dwarf species, so my knowledge is a little lacking. There's a lot of great web sites out there that have some really solid information!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Doesn't compare to other posts I'm seeing on here but I'm really proud of my first okra harvest!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 02:54:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 10:52:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>The opposite! It just keeps coming!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 10:53:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure yet. My wife likes them fried, so maybe that. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 10:53:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great eye! Spot on!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 10:54:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 10:54:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure yet. Maybe fried. Depends what were in the mood for. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 20:58:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I planted them mid to late April (I forget exactly when). They were already a foot and a half or so tall when I got them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 23:24:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>That seems a bit overestimated, especially for a dwarf, but better safe than sorry!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 13:01:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great pic!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Man beats on a memtaly-disabled blind worker in a minion costume for an Instagram "prank." Owner comes out and puts a stop to it.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 02:09:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 02:09:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here's a news article with more information: https://www.google.com/amp/www.news-journalonline.com/news/20180711/disabled-man-in-minion-suit-attacked-in-daytona-suspect-says-it-was-for-video%3ftemplate=ampart</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Beat up a mentally disabled blind worker for an Instagram prank... WCGW?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 02:19:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 02:20:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here's a news article with more information: https://www.google.com/amp/www.news-journalonline.com/news/20180711/disabled-man-in-minion-suit-attacked-in-daytona-suspect-says-it-was-for-video%3ftemplate=ampart</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My damsel likes to live dangerously...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 03:04:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 03:15:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a snowflake eel he's starting down. The eel gets a kick out of chasing my damsels around.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lionfish help</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 13:17:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ive had my first lionfish for a week now, and the little guy still isn't eating! He's about 8 in long, so he's not young. He was also wild caught the day before I bought him, so I know that's quite a shock to a fish. From what I seen, he seems healthy. He swims, (mostly slowly, but he will zip around sometimes) and perches on my live rock. He's in a large enough tank and my perimeters are fine. I have not noticed any weight loss, but his color has darkened up (he was slightly pale when I bought him). As for feeding, I try to give him silver sides and krill daily. He's gotten use to my hand and stick (no more attempted attacks) but still not eating frozen foods. However, what worries me more, he hasn't touched the damsels o have in there. I thought he would start with those. People who have kept lionfish, am I being impatient? How long did yours take to start eating? Anything I can do to help him along (specifically with live food)? My biggest question is... will he let himself starve to death? I can't imagine he would, but it's crossed my mind. Any thoughts or insights? Thanks in advance!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lionfish help needed</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 02:25:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really need some lion fish advice. I'm new to lionfish, but not to the hobby. I posted to r/aquariums this morning, bit I'm hoping for more success here. I've had my first lionfish, a volitan, for a week now, and the little guy still isn't eating! Here's some details on the fish and the tank: He's about 8 in long, so he's not young. He was also wild caught the day before I bought him, so I know that's quite a shock to a fish. From what I seen, he seems healthy. He swims, (mostly slowly, but he will zip around sometimes) and perches on my live rock. He's in a large enough tank and my perimeters are fine. I have not noticed any weight loss, but his color has darkened up (he was slightly pale when I bought him). As for feeding, I try to give him silver sides and krill daily. He's gotten use to my hand and stick (no more attempted attacks) but still not eating frozen foods. However, what worries me more, he hasn't touched the damsels I have in there. I thought he would start with those. People who have kept lionfish, am I being impatient? How long did yours take to start eating live food? Anything I can do to help him along (specifically with live)? My biggest question is... will he let himself starve to death? I can't imagine he would with food in the tank, but it's crossed my mind. Any thoughts or insights? Thanks in advance!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 00:01:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Will those little shrimp be sufficient for him right now? It doesn't seem like there would be enough meat there!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 00:01:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Will those little shrimp be sufficient for him right now? It doesn't seem like there would be enough meat there!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 00:15:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>This! I use the around the foot ones, too!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 02:20:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like Chamblin Book Mine in Jacksonville! I guess several places look like this! :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 13:29:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>CaptinValor on YouTube does it with songs. You have to turn on the captions. His signs are great, but his facial expressions are outstanding. I'm not aware of anyone who shows the gloss with stories, but I'm hope someone else shares! It would be a great resource.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 21:55:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would love to know the back story on this one!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 23:35:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>What asspect of your program took your programer the longest to write?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 11:04:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>How are you keeping the substrate at an incline? Mine always wants to level out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 11:22:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Makes me glad I live on this coast!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 22:00:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sorry, I don't understand how light diffusers keep the substrate angled. How does that work?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 02:22:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everyone else on the planet has emotions that are, at best, content and, at worst, deeply depressed. You're happy, but you have to watch everyone else be miserable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 15:03:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought it looked familiar</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 23:06:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Without knowing more about you, it's hard to narrow it down. I'm going to be very general. Deaf Advocate (very broad, often involves informing people of deaf people's rights to have interpreters). Deaf education (teaching the Deaf, mostly children). ASL teacher (some people are against hearing ASL teachers, but it can still be viable and needed employment, even for hearing people). I've also seen police departments hire officers fluent in ASL and use them whenever a call involving the Deaf comes in. They also get a lot of interaction with the Deaf community (not always in a negative way). Any kind of social work, vocational rehabilitation, or pastoral work can also bring you into extensive contact with the Deaf community particularly if you're fluent in ASL. Obviously, for any of these, you are going to want to be fluent in ASL before you undertake any of them. There I probably saw my missed. But these are what I can think of off the top of my head. I hope it helps!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 23:46:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>How on Earth do they figure that survival budget? 53k is quite a bit more than you need to survive in many places even with a family of 4!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Going... Going... Gone</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 03:23:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 12:08:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. I live in Daytona Beach area and do just that. I'm a teacher and am the sole breadwinner for a family of 4.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 12:11:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you. Anyone questioning the numbers is downvoted to oblivion. No answers given. For what it's worth, I gave you an up vote.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 14:55:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>First, I don't know what you mean by "typical family." Everyone is different and there's no one size fits all. Also, I'm not really comfortable discussing finances with a stranger on the internet. Vaguely, I use to make much less still no where near the 53k mark. We have nothing that really offsets our costs except for Florida Healthy Kids. I'm not saying there aren't issues, but it's disingenuous for people to claim that you can't survive in FL without making 53k annually. There are plenty of people who do. It's totally possible in many areas of our state.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 17:31:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>More or Less did an interesting story on him! Here's the [link](https://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/w3csvq3y)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How does he walk so fast?!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 13:41:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 04:25:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sea weed, like it went potty. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 10:46:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Full disclosure: I'm hearing. Some Deaf don't like it. Most don't care, especially if you are a hearing person with ties to the Deaf community. Most Deaf do have an issue with people who use ASL for work and then have no interaction with the Deaf outside of that. Don't be that person. I think as a science teacher you will have less pushback than as an ASL teacher. You must have fluency in both the language and culture to make it work as a hearing person, though. I hope that answers your question. If not,please feel free to follow up! :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 15:00:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is the reasoning for that? Is all notation illegal or only jotting down your time?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 15:32:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just don't understand the point. Does it open the door to some kind of cheating if the allow notes?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How much to feed lionfish?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 01:16:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>My lionfish is finally eating frozen food (yay!) but now I have another question. I can find plenty of information online about frequency of feeding (around every 3 days, give or take) but nothing about how much to feed. He currently eats silversides with some krill thrown in as a snack. How much should I feed him during any given feeding session? Edit: he's about an 8 inch volitan.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How much should I feed my lion fish?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 01:17:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>My volitan lionfish is finally eating frozen food (yay!) but now I have another question. I can find plenty of information online about frequency of feeding (around every 3 days, give or take) but nothing about how much to feed. He currently eats silversides with some krill thrown in as a snack. How much should I feed him during any given feeding session? Edit: he's about 8 inches long now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 12:41:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think cost should be a huge factor. You can immerse yourself in the Deaf community anywhere. However, keeping those student loans low/non-existent is a beautiful thing and will pay off in spades down the road.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 13:47:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wouldn't. They are capable of moving around themselves and often will move outside of water between tide pools and the ocean. Also, you don't want to run the risk of getting bit or stressing the animal. If you really need to move it, try using a net. Like the kind you use to scoop fish into a boat. If you are 100% determined to do so by hand, your best bet is to quickly and confidently grab one or two of it's legs and rush to the water (or wherever else you want to move it). Again, I don't recommended this! Also, if you live in Australia and the octopus has blue spots on it, do not try to move it by hand. Trust me... :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 12:12:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Signing time is great for what it's designed for, teaching kids ASL vocab and making it fun for them. They do have a series called Signing Time Sentences that never got as big but does go into the grammar. As a kids show, it's great. It won't make you a fluent signer, but you will learn a lot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 04:18:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>You become King of the internet pirates. You now have an army of neck-beards who live in their parents basements and broke teenagers. You try to rally them to action, but they are more interested in watching movies and eating Doritos. You kingdom stagnates. One day, you die and no body notices. None of your subjects attend the funeral.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 11:12:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also standard for hurricanes, too. Stops patio furniture from becoming projectiles!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 21:11:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've never heard that one. I have seen people anchor their boats away from shore and take a smaller boat back. My guess is that it would also depends on the kind of boat. I don't see that working well with a fiberglass boat. I hope someone else chimes in who knows more!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Get it little guy!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 21:30:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 11:27:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 01:29:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do both! I have a 20gal freshwater tank and a 75 salt tank, but not a reef tank. I've dabbled in corals, but not for me!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>An old acquaintance set this as his profile picture!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 23:10:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 00:43:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ist there a sub for screenshots when the phone needs to charge?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My lion eating in slow-mo! They strike so fast!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 01:09:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 01:12:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's a young volitan in a 75 gallon. In this video, he is eating a frozen silverside. It took me several weeks to eat frozen food, but now that he does, he won't stop! He's in there with a small snowflake eel and a damsel (one of five original). I think that covers everything!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 01:21:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would be the name! Ha ha!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 10:16:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for lettinge know. I'll try again after work today!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 10:30:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>LUNCH is more popular in different regions. I'm in FL and, in my experience, LUNCH is far more popular that EAT-AFTERNOON.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 10:57:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was fascinating!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 13:11:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>How safe is it to support larger tanks with cinder blocks? I've always had it drilled into me you should never work under a car if it's on cinder blocks. However, tanks can get heavy, too. What's the safe weight limit for a tank on them?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 23:00:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, but surly less than that is still dangerous. Right? I'm seriously not sure</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 01:00:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>They are also have concrete and rebar inside them when used for construction. Im not saying the above picture is unsafe, I'm just wondering what the limit is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 13:12:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Weigh in... Lol I might make a separate post later today if this comment doesn't get any traction. Thanks for the I fo, though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 17:29:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is that Trinity Baptist College in Jacksonville FL?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 10:27:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a crazy feeling when they grab you, for sure! Great pic!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 11:10:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't have those people I could use ASL in my life with until I started learning ASL. You have to put yourself in those situations where you need it more than once a month at a Deaf Event. The key is, you have to build relationships with Deaf and HoH people. Not the kind of "I want to learn ASL, hang out with me" kind of relationships, but find some deaf people around your age with common interests and bond over those. I teach ASL and my students who do the best are the ones who do just that. Also, don't let the negativity get you down! You've already proved you can learn another language, so you just have to get yourself in those situations. It makes a huge difference!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 01:24:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm in zone 9b and a new gardener (started last Spring). I've tried googling this, but I'm not sure how to ask, which makes it hard to get an answer. I noticed a lot of my plants are starting to be ready to harvest and dying off. This leads me to a couple questions. Can I plant more in the Fall? Are their certain plants I should or shouldn't plant? Also, I still have a lot of bell pepper plants that weren't very productive. Should I rip them out or leave them through the winter? Thank you all so much for the help!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 11:25:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Central FL. My potatoes died (and we're harvested) and my carrots matured (and were delicious). My cucumbers also died after being pretty productive for a while. It's outdoors in the ground. Thank you for the info on the peppers!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 16:06:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is great info! Thank you so much!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Easily the most photogenic fish I've ever owned!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 03:08:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 10:19:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had to look it up... I kind of regret naming it Livingston now! Spot on!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 10:19:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 10:58:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I should also add he's currently in a 75 gallon. I've made post in the past about my concern over his eating habits. That's no longer an issue. He has discovered frozen food and hasn't looked back! I actually need to distract him so I can feed my snowflake eel. It's a good feeling when things go right!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My very photogenic lionfish!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 01:09:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Came across this interesting possition in a game. Black to move.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 18:36:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 22:30:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>That line leads to a loss.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 22:31:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right start, but King has more options than e1 and can prolong it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 01:35:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dont we all? :-) I found it interesting because my opponent lost it. He went for the queen which gave me a win.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Seeking advice teaching my son chess</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 01:49:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to teach my four year old chess! I started him with checkers about a year ago and he's really taken to it. He understands the rules and can play a game without help, although he's totally clueless when it comes to strategy. :-) Given his interest in checkers, and that he watches me play chess on my phone and wants to move the pieces, I'm thinking it's about time to introduce chess to him. Is four too young? What age kids have you all had success teaching? How did you do it? I'd love to hear your experiences teaching your children (or other people's kids) chess! Thank you in advance!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 12:19:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's fine! If black captures the queen, white plays rook to d8 and black can't stop the checkmate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 12:34:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was my first thought. She doesn't look old enough to be running her own lab!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 15:23:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought so! That's why I found it so interesting. :-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 01:15:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is it too late? I want in!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cuddle Fish!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 23:28:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Get out!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 12:26:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 12:33:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>