<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject4479</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 00:56:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love his 'stache. This looks sick</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Any tips or help?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 01:26:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've found that I love the idea of drawing and being creative but I can't draw in a style of my own that I'm happy with? I can copy art very well and use those chances to learn things about drawing and painting (like how heavy handed to be and such) but I have difficulty drawing things in a way I enjoy. Any tips or advice? Thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Do y'all see brighter colors when manic?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 01:18:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've noticed that when I become manic everything gets more intense, including the world I see. The sky is more blue and the grass is more green. When depressed though, the world seems dimmer and more monotone. Do you guys get this too?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm so tired</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 01:43:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am tired all the time. I've had tests done and nothing is physically wrong with me so I'm assuming it's just the depression but damn even on a good day I'll still only have like 3 hours of social contact before I need to go home and nap. It's insane. Anyone else experience this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 01:48:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes exactly. It helps me a bit to know if what type of episode I'm having but it's weird none the less</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 01:49:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow yeah when I ride the bus manic I love seeing all the colors</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 20:30:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a similar thing with my anxiety where if there's too much stimulis I'll have a panic attack but for some reason my mania usually cancels out most of my anxiety.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mania and sleep</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 10:07:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm naturally very tired. The doctors don't really know why but I'm just naturally more tired I guess. I think this is why when I'm manic I'll experience everything except the lack of need for sleep. I don't ever want to sleep when I'm manic unless I'm trying to make time go faster so I can do more but it's not not being able to sleep, I just don't WANT to sleep. If I'm active I feel awake but I could always just lay down and sleep. Does anyone else get this? Sorry if there are any mistakes or if anything is worded weird I'm on like 3 hours of sleep for the past 36 hours so</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 10:25:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah lmao I feel the exact same way</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 10:28:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha iconic</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 09:24:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're amazing too friend!! I'm glad Reddit can offer a community to you that gives you so much support and I'm glad I've joined it. Have a good day!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Advice?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 09:34:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used to cut a lot but I've been on and off for the last year, and clean now for a few months. I still get the impulse to cut but usually it goes away quickly. But I'm hypomanic bordering manic right now and I'm going to some antique shops and graveyards with my girlfriend on Friday the 13th (date was a big concidence) and I got the impulse to cut deep crosses on my wrists to "protect myself". I realise it's crazy but the impulse has been sticking with me. Any advice on how to get my brain to calm down?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>