<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject3977</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-28 10:00:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>A friend of mine is a giant, 6'9 260lbs, covered in tattoos from his head to his feet has a mohawk and several piercings was rolling around on the floor with a kitten talking to it in a baby voice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-28 13:32:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah it was, it was also grey, fluffy and was a rescue that was missing half his left ear...we named him lefty.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-10-24 06:25:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>you've probably already seen this but if you're willing to drop a few grand this ones cool http://www.droold.com/i/413-An-LED-Mau5head-Replica-That-You-Can-Wear</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-01-05 06:43:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>-Manhattans if you don't have a lot of money is decent pizza and cheap beer. But you're going to see a rough crowd -Murder Mart is open 24 hours and got its name from yes a murder but there's no reason to be scared going there. -church street is awesome but really touristy so try to avoid the traps, mediocre food with high prices. -Everyone here is really friendly and loves to meet new people so don't be shy and enjoy yourself! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-01-17 03:15:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think he's trying to make fun of that yellow dress ebay pic you know this one http://www.buzzpatrol.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/01/asos-yellow-skater-dress-nsfw.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-19 22:36:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>i always get to excited when vermont get mentioned in a post...fuckyea vermont</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-07 00:11:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice try Burlington PD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-09 08:29:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>i get way to excited when i see any post including Vermont.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-23 01:33:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I myself have small breasts, its best if you don't comment on the size of them even if its a compliment, focus on the things you like about them like her nipples or how perky they are. Hope that helps!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-06 19:14:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oslo Cosmetics http://oslocosmetics.storenvy.com/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-17 22:52:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>This guy has some control issues, instead of talking to her and asking her why she has all these items he takes it upon himself to just throw away HER stuff without any regard for how much money she spent or how often she uses it. I'm so angry at this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-18 17:04:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you sold prints of these i would love to buy them!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-05 19:26:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just made a comment. We did it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just bought a water. We did it!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-06 19:29:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-30 07:41:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't need to cum everytime we have sex. Sometime I just like the closeness and making you happy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Adopted a senior pug. It's taking time but I think my other dog is getting use to him</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-30 14:18:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What happened to Didgeridoo Guy?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 21:26:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I use to see him play on Church Street all the time, occasionally with another man playing a flute. I don't think I've seen him in a couple years. He use to wear a wooden mask and sometimes have a fake crow or small wooden animals around him. Anyone know what happened? Church street in the summer isn't the same without him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-04 00:53:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Glad to know he's still out there!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-04 05:42:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess I don't spend As much time on Church Street as I use to. I'll have o keep an eye out this year.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-05 03:15:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good point, I don't think i saw him last summer either. Though i missed Didgeridoo guy and he sits in place, i'm sure i'd miss him easier since he's on wheels.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-17 03:51:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for this! You were able to put into words what I was not, this the feeling of wanting to take care of a little one. I really appreciate you being honest about the baby stage from your perspective. I feel like everyone i ask is so sure that i will fall in love with being a mother right away. I agree it is irritating when these feeling bubble up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-17 03:52:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for the subreddit suggestion. I am scrolling though its top posts and I appreciate the like minded people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I just became a MOD! We did it!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 02:00:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[misc] Does anyone else do skincare when they can't sleep? Me at 2:45Am and having to get up at 6:30.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 14:53:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 19:06:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I appreciate the information, I have a lot of my skin care regime passed down from my mother. Hopefully this helps with my ever clogged pores.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 01:59:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its the Hell Pore mask, normally just for noses but I get crazy blackheads on my chin.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>After 9 years of neglect and abuse Jack was dropped at the shelter with painfully infected eyes, rotten teeth, front nails missing and severely infected ears. He was left blind, partially deaf and toothless. 2 years later and he doesn't let his past stop him from enjoying his golden years.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 12:45:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 17:34:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dropping him off at the shelter was the right thing to do. Their loss is my gain!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 17:37:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>We think he's a mix of Pug and English bulldog. His body seems to thick to be all pug.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>