<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject2097</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-20 00:41:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Either a million one dollar hooker bots or one million dollar hooker bot. - Bender</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Could be amazing for glow or just finding a dark shot.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-29 06:03:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>It took me so long but I bought a blacklight flashlight and immediately realized the benefits this could have. Took two pics with a normal led flashlight and one with the blacklight from the same location for both light and disc. Obvious results. Led flashlight https://imgur.com/4SgbpRD BlackLight Flashlight https://imgur.com/R3Nn17r Not sure the mean these go for but pretty nice. Hope it helps. Side note, it doesn't make all discs glow. The one in the photo is not a glow disc. About 3/4 of mine all did though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-29 17:30:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seems to be mostly the color that determines the intensity though a few of my pro and star plastics have a much stronger glow than my champions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-29 18:41:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's the same one I have. Works great.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-30 17:48:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>In the picture I'm about 10' away. The beam doesn't need to be centered on the disc for it to start lighting up. Could easily do a sweeping pattern till you see something flash. I took it out last night and most of the plant life doesn't respond to the light so its pretty easy to see anything else.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-30 21:33:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you've never been Ludington, Mi has beautiful courses nearby and flip city is within an 1.5 from there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-09 21:40:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>That hole is a beast. Love you, Kensington.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-12 21:08:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>If your Wi-Fi keeps dropping it more likely something interfering with that channel than it is with your wiring. Throw away that damn 2.4 Ghz cordless phone already.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-15 08:08:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lucienne's quest</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-17 22:48:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cant upvote this enough.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-19 20:14:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>You've already said that. Source?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-19 20:16:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>What kind of music do they like?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-19 20:52:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Blackboard lives matter!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-19 20:57:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hate it when the wheel of fortune puzzle is already finished.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-19 21:06:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's disgusting. Not to mention she's a beast of a woman but gotta mention it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-19 21:23:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Frank: It's the same old story. Boy finds girl, boy loses girl, girl finds boy, boy forgets girl, boy remembers girl, girls dies in a tragic blimp accident over the Orange Bowl on New Year's Day. #160; Jane: Goodyear? #160; Frank: No, the worst. #160;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-20 21:32:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lions, tigers and beers...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-22 12:47:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wife actually has this for when i call.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-22 16:04:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believed you until you said willow was nice. It's nothing but clouds of evolved super mosquitoes and 6 ft wide lanes or your searching in rough that rivals the density of the Congo Basin.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-22 16:07:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do a weekend trip up the west side to Ludington every fall. They have gorgeous courses in close proximity. The Leviathan, The Goliath, Beauty and the Beast. Also, it's worth it to hit up Flip City coming or going. If you're coming off 96, White Hall township course is very nice as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-22 16:12:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Came here to see this. Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-22 16:59:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I play it several times a month since its closest and it trains you for tighter shots. Hitting a lane anywhere else is cake when you can do willow. I just don't think it should be on anyone's bucket list of courses to play. If you like it that's awesome. It does need some love I guess. Lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-22 19:28:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Has to be dolphins with their complex social groups. They're already planning war. Source: I know a dolphin.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-23 19:07:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>That wind chill has no effect on electronic devices as they're inanimate. Well then I guess this fan on my cpu is doing nothing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I read that article on Forbes of the 10 signs of a bad company. Applied and hired at a new job. So long, Comcast!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-24 06:23:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-24 06:24:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://www.forbes.com/forbes/welcome/?toURL=http://www.forbes.com/sites/lizryan/2016/03/07/ten-unmistakable-signs-of-a-bad-place-to-work/ amp;refURL= amp;referrer=#6ac03a0c7fad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-24 06:31:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>If that's working well, try a sidewinder or a teebird. The tb will be off-putting at first but as it breaks in will be your best friend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-24 14:32:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did some celebrating last night and definitely could have phrased this better. I had already applied and got a different job. I was told yesterday while I was reading that article and tallying up how Comcast hits all ten of the marks. Now I'm putting in my two weeks and the sense of relief is unbelievable. My favorite line from that article was, "No job worth doing breaks down into tiny, measurable parts." Just makes me laugh now. I had 17 different metrics to hit on a daily, monthly, yearly schedule there and most of them are out of your control.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-24 16:06:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Diversity stole my bike.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-24 17:12:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm on the fence about this table.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-24 18:26:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is turtle me on right now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-24 18:29:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm outraged. Where are we trans-species supposed to go?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-24 18:31:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wrote an essay on shrink wrap cause I wanted my argument to be air tight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-24 18:36:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>What sorcery is this?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-24 20:05:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Randy...I am the liquor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-25 04:48:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://m.youtube.com/watch?v=g9Z33IWrKSI</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-25 05:21:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Forever traumatized.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-25 16:49:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Instructions unclear. Shot by police.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-31 02:26:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got into an argument with my wife one night over who loved me more, the dog or her. She insisted she did. So another night I locked her and the dog in the trunk of my car for an hour. When I opened it up the dog was clearly happier to see me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-08 14:53:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have a kitten that makes jazz hands when on his back so named him aljernob.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-20 11:02:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>This has the feel of a farside cartoon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-26 13:31:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Michigan here. Yes. Playing after a fresh snow can be fun as you can see your exact marks as to where your shot landed. Sometimes can be rough if you hit straight on and the disc will disappear in a single slit in the snow. As long as its above 10 freedom degrees and you can feel your hands. Go for it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-26 15:02:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>No that's petting. Poutine is when information is relevant or applicable to a particular matter.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-04 02:46:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe gays should be able to protect their marijuana farms with guns.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-04 11:24:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>In most native American tribes, the men would go out hunting and fishing all day and bring food back for the women to prepare. Then after the meal the men would lie with the women of their choice. Only a white man would think he could improve upon that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-06 09:31:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have not participated though there are frequent leagues at rolling hills as well. Beautiful course. Willow metro park usually has signs up for league play as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-10 23:19:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just curious then as someone with no college education that just climbed the ranks of corporate America since 18, is $30 an hour decent in skilled labor. I still feel undervalued in that I can do so much in my current role.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-11 02:45:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well it took 12 years in my former role to get I to this. I work with fiber data distribution for major isps and had to put up with a lot of shit over the last decade to get here. What I was wondering was what you answered in how a college grad perceives that (lower-middle) pay scale compared to what they expect. I just wanted to know if it was worth my time to go back after my kids are out of the house. Lot of hate on my previous comment. Guessing those are college grads working for less.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-14 11:45:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's clearly an egg roll.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-17 17:06:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>And this is why my new cat is named Babou</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-20 03:21:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yogurt is amazing. How have I never tried yogurt!?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My wife wants me to remodel our staircase.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-20 07:38:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I told her I'd need a step-by-step guide.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-27 19:17:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alfred is a free app that allows you to record, set up motion detection, sounds, night mode, etc with extra mobile devices. I have my old iPhone 4s in my garage using them as security feeds. Works pretty well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-11 19:21:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>5/4 people have a problem with fractions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-18 00:39:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>100% of serial killers have agreed to using Dihydrogen Monoxide in their life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-23 03:42:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm no expert but if the Goonies has taught me anything it's that your God damn right there are traps for everything everywhere. Your everyday piano could be a pitfall trap.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-29 03:18:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pick me! Pick me! 15-20 drinks a night for the last decade. Haven't been drunk in years. Not proud of this, just got to the point of not functioning life without. Also terrified the cumulative hangover might literally kill me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 14:43:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I miss Upright Citizens Brigade</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-01 04:13:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unabridged version of count of Monte cristo is fantastic if you're into murders, robbery, treasure seeking, sword fighting, betrayal, political sabotage, sailing, and cold calculated revenge.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-01 15:44:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, also with the French dialect some descriptions can get a little confusing but it was still a great read.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-05 15:07:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Came here to say this. Still keep the uncle johns around in case my Wi-Fi is acting up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-05 19:16:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>My dog loves Frisbee so much that i refuse to ever take him discing with me. Awesome dog but he's an obnoxious prick when a disc goes flying that you don't want him to chase.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-07 19:13:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel this often. Sober me knows what I want right now, but I can't be responsible for what I want after a few drinks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-12 02:03:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do teenagers ever look in the mirror and also have a burning desire to slap the straight-billed, tags-still-on, baseball hat off their head?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-12 06:51:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll take trucker hats. Any day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-14 21:05:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know several people that have worked there. All of them hired in with great attitudes and spirits and then comcast crushes the shit out of their souls till they were a mere husk of a human being. Then what little happiness they had left was destroyed by the general public.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-15 16:49:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>That wood be a problem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-15 17:32:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>"You mean the panties your mother laid out for you?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-18 22:43:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have had one for a couple years now also as a gift. It very rare that it comes out of my bag, maybe once quarterly but it has saved a few so it's paid for itself. It is not that easy to use though. If you can't see the disc it's almost impossible and also typically takes longer than just manning up and walking in to get it. Maybe I need more practice with it but it's not that often that I get one wet. I think it's the opposite of all the losers talking trash on here. If you have one in your bag you just won't throw in the water anymore. Better to have and not need than to need and not have. Happy fishing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-21 07:59:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seems like a poultry problem to have.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-23 22:17:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed with this. I'm primarily forehand and started with over discs. Wasn't until about my 5 year of playing that I trained and started with under. Went from around 250 to 400 on an average drive. Plus the control and flight prediction is spot on. Most new players are just trying to throw as hard as they can and an overstable gives them some prediction on where they will lie. Moving to under takes more finess. Your just trying to barely exceed the speed of the disc and releasing for the right angle to shot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Aww yeah...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-25 14:29:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-29 02:45:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Completely accurate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-01 01:04:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Came here to day this. Dang it, Mitch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-04 12:59:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to say, duh. Lol, you're comparing an under to an over. Throwing under is recommended for beginners as it is much easier to turn the disc over or exceed the speed of the disc to achieve its flight characteristics. They are both great drivers but it takes a hell of a throw with good control to properly throw a destroyer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-04 15:22:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I too had this happen to me. It was a cyclone I got my first ace with. I called the number back hoping it was a joke but just kept getting ignored but the voicemail greeting was the dudes name. so Fuck you, (blank) Cook, from southeast Michigan. One day I will run into you at willow and retribution shall be swift.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-04 18:08:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, this was about 4-5 years ago when I just started really taking the sport seriously. Didn't know about DGC back then. Hit a slump after that for a couple months as I wasn't very comfortable with my other discs. Bought new cyclones and could never get any to replicate the same. Hope karma came back around on that guy though. 5 years later and I still remember his name. Lol. I did find a disc a few years back with no number but B.Cook was written on it. Who knows, maybe that was one back.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-06 17:37:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let's go, AlREADY!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-17 02:04:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hear a lot about the Harp on here. Is it really that game changing? I've been playing for about 15 years. I can usually drop a Bolt within 50' of the pin on a 400' hole but then I'm always three putting out. Short game is terrible. Currently using Spike by Latitude. Think this would help?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 16:42:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would love a plush dolphin that says "because fuck your dolphin pam" whenever you hit someone with it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-01 21:36:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pogs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 13:29:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of my favorite bad jokes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 19:12:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could always try heroes of the storm. F2P from blizzard. The ranked matches can be a lot of fun with the map mechanics. I also enjoyed shared team xp so none of that last hit nonsense.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-04 01:55:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah,cause it's impossible for people to feel remorse and take a stance against the wrongs they feel they have committed in their life. Total scumbag. /S</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-05 06:26:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have very little body fat. Why am I able to drink 17 doubles of whiskey without even a slur of a word and retain all cognitive abilities? I don't drink that often.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-07 21:15:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Downvotes because of a sincere question. Nice /s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-09 02:32:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's a course in south east, MI called willow. Now I have to get willow at willow.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-10 09:43:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Time Warner does suck. The part of the article talking about wireless speeds compared to packages is completely flawed though. Good luck getting 50% of 300Mbps on any wireless network. Its not freaking possible even on the newer 5Ghz band. Maybe if you were in the middle of a field a mile away from all sources of electromagnetic frequencies. That's why the smaller the package the greater the percentage of data.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-10 20:16:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>My favorite is when I'd work at a business that has all their network gear near a microwave. You'd be surprised how many situations I've seen where people have a router actually sitting on top of one. Lol. Those always seem surprised and even doubtful when I'd tell them they need to move that. Router operates on milliwats compared to a microwave that's 1000 watts both at 2.4Ghz. Then they freak out because they think there microwave is radiating cancer and you have to explain acceptable leakage tolerances on microwaves.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Remodeling the kitchen and pulled the microwave off the wall. He never gave up hope.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-10 23:13:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-11 00:13:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for this. My wife will love it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-11 01:57:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Know a buyer?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-11 07:38:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Finally going to bed after ripping down walls. Downvote for your skepticism is silly since it is after all reddit. Haha, but I swear this actually happened. Only reason it ended up here was cause my sister insisted I post it. Cheers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-11 07:46:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Late reply, just got done cleaning up. House was built in 42 with a lot of haphazard additions over the years. The microwave had no cabinets above it and was just used as a shelf. A really nasty shelf. Very happy to be rid of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-11 07:48:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whole Thing was held up with toggle bolts. Not a single freaking stud. Asshats.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-15 10:37:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have an air quality test done specifically to check for mold. Happened to my sister. Contractors had just covered it up with new drywall after a pipe had burst in the upstairs bathroom. Took years to resolve in court. On my own experience as I have had to put thousands into the home I am in, foundation (inspect when it rains), electrical ( pull the panel cover off and check for water damage and shoddy workmanship), plumbing (make sure lines are relatively updated and the water heater is current), roof (especially around the chimney where water can pool) and is it well insulated. Don't spend hundreds of hours like I have if that's not what you're up for. Happy hunting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-16 10:33:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sopapillas!!! I'm from Michigan and Panchos is one of my favorite stops when I go to Texas.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-16 23:11:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>You don't have to join a league to become a better player. There is misinformation everywhere and I have found that finding what works for you can be very beneficial long term. Of course, playing with more experienced players can help but honestly watch some videos and hit a field up and learn the discs you are using. It mostly comes down to muscle memory which comes with time just letting them fly. If you consistently release your discs the same you will begin to notice different flight paths and the strength needed to achieve it. If league isn't your thing just go causally. That's all I've done for 15 years now and it becomes a thing where you can literally see the shot in your minds eye on were a disc will end up. Keep on throwing. It becomes such a release to go throw with some friends. Also, as a side note, pick up an understand driver. Those tend to work out better for new players as you don't have to throw out your arm to achieve the flight characteristics of the disc since they will typically have a lower speed rating. Good luck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-23 00:57:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Never tried dynamic. Looks nice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-08 12:59:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because I couldn't hear you...over the sound... of now I'm punching you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hurry up already Netflix. What is this content from?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-17 04:39:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-17 05:18:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's disappointing. So much wasted awesomeness.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-17 05:24:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry in advance for this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-17 05:30:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hang on, Lana. I'm stacking rocks in order of descending size.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-17 05:32:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only limit is your imagination. Pew pew.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-20 17:50:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Instructions unclear, house is down to studs now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-21 01:42:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Car keys used to have two keys. One for the doors and one for the ignition.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-23 13:07:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>...and that was just one of the accidents.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-28 13:39:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Puts the skill in skill trade.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-29 06:54:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>A ruse? Brrring, brrring. Hello. Hi, it's the 1930's. Can we have our words and clothes and shitty airplane back?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-01 02:02:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>The key word in these statements is "individual". Guarantee they're still going to sell based on market areas.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-03 14:47:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks Obama.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-03 14:51:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Serious question, how much beer do you drink?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-14 13:05:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's way better. I had a meat grinder show up on my steps with sausage casings. I think I had an epiphany that I want to make bacon sausage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-14 15:57:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can we just stop supporting ea already. Gee whiz, they're the comcast of the gaming world.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 00:59:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>They better hide this. I don't think Cliff is around anymore to thwart the Nazi threat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 00:45:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just maybe the reason Canadians are so nice is that their geese harbor all their anger.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-06 16:17:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mars McMarsface.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-09 11:40:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Johnny bench called. He wants his glove back. Reference for a old best up vagina, apparently. Missed this so many times.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-16 14:04:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>This isn't the way to Country Kitchen Buffet, woman.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-17 08:46:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pogs!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-25 06:09:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>High five! Myself! No friends!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-25 15:07:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pogs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-29 08:39:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>If your ass isn't on fire then they weren't good wings. You should thank him for those endorphins.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-02 23:02:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe they need some competition. The coal industry should switch to mining roast beef.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-08 20:47:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was so fed up with people bringing there speakers and blasting garbage that I finally brought mine and just played whale mating calls as loud as it would go. Just trying to enjoy the nature while I throw. Head phones are way less likely to mess up anyone else's experience. If I have to play through next to someone blasting the Pussy song by Lords of Acid with my 10 year old daughter throwing with me it pretty much makes me want to break your speaker over your face.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-08 20:53:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Feel free to ignore my original comment. You're going it right sidearm Austin. Hadn't read the other comments earlier.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-08 21:01:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't believe you cut all those poor trees down to find your disc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-08 21:06:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Summer helles. Seasonal unfortunately cause it is delightful. This is coming from someone that literally drinks every kind of beer that I haven't tried yet. Started keeping a log a few years back and am approaching 350 varieties this year. Need to travel more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-12 15:21:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Storks can't do it all. It's the cranes that bring the big babies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-28 08:00:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hear dodo birds were delicious though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 05:37:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's sherbet. Dammit Ernie.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-18 14:53:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did a bike tour of Detroit against my will not too long ago. Was actually very nice. Checked out a lot of street art and the downtown area was well kept.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-18 21:27:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha. Just a sister dragging me along. Although it sure felt like at gunpoint.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 02:35:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does he also refer to flys as sky raisins? Your dad is awesome!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-14 08:02:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was wondering the same thing. Even though the 80 thousand is not accurate it's still on horrible taste just like holocaust jokes. Hopefully it was the southpark reference that did it. Faith in humanity 2 of 10.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-14 08:34:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>First we need to get I'm contact with Merriam or Webster. Second we change the definition of Nigger from "Used as an insulting and contemptuous term for a black person" to "Used as an insulting and contemptuous term for a person of any race that believes their race is superior or in any way better than another". This will stop the riots when neo Nazis are called one and the same.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-19 12:17:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess you could say they weren't allwhite.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>DIY: Easy to make solar eclipse viewer.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-20 06:03:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>LPT: If you have a plastic lighter that has run out of fluid try rubbing it between your hands. The extra heat will cause the remaining gas to expand and usually give one more light when desperately needed.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-22 14:38:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-22 16:30:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Verified this works. Unless it's a bic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 17:58:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like a sausage fest. I'm in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-26 01:05:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I learned this from Sister Act 2.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-30 12:31:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did this in a work meeting once when the boss was going over a bunch of changes. I proudly announced after some lame changes that I had something that says, "Otherwise" and calmly handed him a folded piece of paper. He was not amused.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-08 10:54:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>TiL Soccer players would be criminal soldiers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Heading up to Ludington MI from Detroit to check some courses there. Any recommendations along the way?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-22 12:01:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Obviously a little detour for Flip.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-22 12:53:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought I had played everything in SE MI. Never played the Gulch. I'll check that out when I get back. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-22 15:03:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty much my home course though I'm not a resident. Washtenaw parks do a great job.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-23 01:21:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Never heard of it. Looked it up. Absolutely going by there. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 21:19:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I first met my wife in 9th grade on the first day of school. She was assigned to sit next to me in science class. My first impression was fear and confusion. She was "Gothic" I guess. She had on super baggy pants that had at least 36inches of room around the ankles. Black lipstick, plastic beaded bracelets up to her elbows and piercings through almost every place one could have on ones head. I say almost became shortly after the teacher addressed the class this girl decides she needs a nose piercing and shoves a safety pin through her nose right next to me. Blood running down her face so the teacher sends her to the office and I'm just sitting there like a normal boy thinking wtf just happened.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 21:58:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>As fate would have it seemingly. School came easy to me so I took advantage and came and went as I pleased. Eventually had to make up some credits so did night school, summer school and even mail order classes. She was the opposite. School came a bit harder but found herself needing the same credits. Turns out she was in all of my extra classes through night and summer and without all the normal cliques of high school she was actually a pretty nice person. We developed a friendship and that seemed the end of it. After high school I heard she was moving out of state and that seemed the end of our bond. About a year later my sister went to a concert and ran into her. When my sister told me the next day I went to her parents house to "see about a girl". She came over that evening and we've been together ever since. She looks unrecognizable in comparison to that first day we met and if someone had told me then that she would be my wife I would have never believed it but here we are with two kids and a great understanding of each others needs and a love that literally gets stronger everyday. I always thought that was the lamest phrase but there is truth in it. On mobile, sorry for any typos.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 23:36:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah and I hate sitcoms. Thus fate. Lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-26 15:24:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Little jealous. I'm 40 minutes out and usually only get there once a week. Worth the trip every time. What happened with the new holes going in there? I saw a sign at 14 for some optionals to be added but never saw it again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-28 09:32:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rodents of Unusual Size? I don't think they exist.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-28 09:36:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rodent of Unusual Size? I don't think they exist.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 08:33:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cherry Blossom Trees pollute river: couple devastated over aftermath.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-06 12:42:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like the ponds at lakeshore. Nice course. Great throw shop.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-06 13:17:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm usually on reddit or praying. Solitude is an amazing experience.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>