<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject835</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tori Amos angriest songs</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 14:48:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>What are Tori Amos #8217;s angriest songs? I love Alanis Morissette and I love Professional Widow. Are there any more songs that are angry/ish?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Zombie by The Cranberries</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-14 02:19:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was wondering if anyone knows any other songs like Zombie by the Cranberries. I love the powerful vocals and the sound of the guitars and drums.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A perfect day Elise</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 01:19:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I listened to  #8220;a perfect day Elise #8221;. Are there any other songs by her that are like a perfect day Elise? I like how grunge-y it sounds. Would love recommendations for songs like this and any other good Harvey so gs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How do I fit hanging files into the Mikael desk drawer? It is too thin and too shallow for the drawer. Is there a trick?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 20:40:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Recommendations</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 20:16:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love 90s grunge and rock music. I love Alanis Morissette #8217;s anger, tori Amos, and pj Harvey #8217;s  #8220;a good day Elise. #8221; Does anyone have any recommendations for angry/emotional rock/alt rock 90s singers like these?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Starting out</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 22:14:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hopefully this is the right sub for this post. I #8217;m interested in storm chasing. I have been all my life, and I #8217;ve done tons of research on it. Knowing how dangerous it can be, and how educated you need to be, what do y #8217;all recommend for me? What apps really help for keeping up on the weather, what books are recommended, are there any classes I should take? I #8217;m going to take the SKYWARN spotter training class to become certified soon, and I would like to prepare for the upcoming tornado season. Any recommendations are appreciated!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Wut</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 22:35:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Radial Velocity Radar</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 20:35:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>What apps allow me to see radial velocity. I truly am not sure what this means, but I have these apps and I was wondering if I could view it on any of these: mPING, Seasonality Pro, WU Storm, Weather Channel Storm Radar. If none of these have this capability, are there other apps that do? I #8217;ve heard of RadarScope... what do y #8217;all think of that app? Are there any websites for viewing a radial velocity radar?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 18:17:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the advice, and also where is the chase?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Books</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-12 18:15:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any good books / guides on storm chasing, tornadoes, or severe weather?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Book titles</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 02:02:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does anyone know the title of this book? It #8217;s about a guy whose wife or girlfriend gets taken by a cult or society. It #8217;s a mystery thriller. I forgot the name of the book so if anyone knows it let me inow</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 17:00:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cool thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 18:55:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok I know what I described was pretty vague but I posted it here because I thought it was a long shot but at least worth trying</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 04:30:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>This might be it! Thanks so much for the suggestion</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 04:30:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>This isn #8217;t it, but I #8217;ve heard of this book. How is it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>MacBook memory</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 03:08:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a late 2011 13 inch MacBook Pro with 4 GB ram and an i5 processor. It #8217;s so slow, and I have to restart it a lot. Through research, I #8217;ve heard that adding memory can help. If I added 4 more GB of ram to get 8 GB, will this significantly help and is it worth the money, or should I just get a new MacBook? Also, I checked Logic #8217;s CPU meter. The meter goes to the max level even before the song begins playing... such as when I #8217;m clicking a region or even closing out of the project.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>True crime, non fiction, or fiction recommendations</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 03:42:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I enjoyed movies like Three Billboards Outside Ebbing Missouri and Wind River. I know that there are cases in real life where people are raped and murdered and there #8217;s injustice related to the investigation and the case. It angers me. I was wondering if there are any books with similar subject lines. Maybe similar to Missoula by Jon Krakauer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Book suggestion</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 21:44:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I enjoyed movies like Three Billboards Outside Ebbing Missouri and Wind River. I know that there are cases in real life where people are raped and murdered and there #8217;s injustice related to the investigation and the case. It angers me. I was wondering if there are any books with similar subject lines. Maybe similar to Missoula by Jon Krakauer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 03:36:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I sent you a PM</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 21:55:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I run Logic Pro X on my Macbook, which is the main task I do. My MacBook is pretty old, and I don #8217;t think it #8217;s powerful enough to run logic, but I thought I should try adding ram, replacing hard drive, or using an SD before I shell out money for a new MacBook. It #8217;s slow starting up, opening applications, doing tasks as simple as opening up an application such as finder, safari, preferences, etc. It also heats up really fast and the fan gets really loud.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Vegas and Surrounding</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 02:38:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi there! Hopefully this is the right sub for my question... if not, feel free to point me in the right direction. So, I #8217;m flying into Vegas in the morning on the 13th, and flying out on Monday the 18th Day 1: Fly into Vegas, see Red Rock Canyon Day 2: Joshua Tree National Park Day 3: Death Valley Day 4: Nevada/Extraterrestrial Highway* Day 5: Eastern Arizona Day 6: Vegas So, the asterisked one is something that isn #8217;t a must see, but everything else is. For all of these day trips, what do you recommended seeing, and are there any alternatives? I am willing to drive more (up to 3 1/2 hours) to maximize my time. Thanks! Edit: Aldeady have been to Grand Canyon, Hoover dam, and Zion</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Logic on MacBook pro</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 03:18:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m running Logic Pro X on my late 2011 MacBook Pro with 4 GB memory and 500 gb disk. I can #8217;t run logic without it going really slow, crashing, and overloading the system. Looking on Activity Monitor, I see that Logic Pro x is using about 5 GB more virtual memory than real memory. I was wondering if this is why Logic is malfunctioning and slowing down my whole computer, and if so, how do I fix it? I #8217;m thinking about either getting an external hard dive, getting a new internal hard dive, or adding more RAM, but I want to get the most effective one. Also, I checked Logic #8217;s CPU meter. The meter goes to the max level even before the song begins playing... such as when I #8217;m clicking a region or even closing out of the project.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Saguaros</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 16:39:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was wondering if anyone knows where I can find saguaros or similar cacti in Arizona, southern Nevada, or southeast California. I #8217;ll be staying in Vegas, and I can do about a 3 to 3 1/2 drive from Vegas for a day trip. I #8217;ve tried looking at maps of where saguaros grow, and it appears I can drive to one of these areas, but I don #8217;t know where the best place to see saguaros would be (in driving range.) Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is this normal for anorexia?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 21:35:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was diagnosed with anorexia and bulimia a few years ago, and it got better over the next few years, but recently I think it #8217;s gotten really bad u think. One of the things I #8217;ve noticed is that I #8217;m losing sleep, I feel super hydrated, I #8217;m feeling more angry. One of the biggest things is that before now, whenever I didn #8217;t eat I always felt hunger pains, but now I forget to eat meals and then later I remember I forgot to eat, but I felt no hunger pains. I #8217;m also losing hair. Not a lot but it #8217;s coming out in small clumps. None of this used to happen before but I don #8217;t know if it #8217;s stress but I feel like it #8217;s tied to my anorexia. Any thoughts?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 21:42:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea about the same time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Should I bring this up with my therapist</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 16:41:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here are some things that I #8217;ve noticed and wondered if these are any signs of disorders or symptoms or whatever. I #8217;ve been diagnosed with PTSD and clinical depression, so this might be a part of those. 1. Severe mood swings and bad irritability 2. Swinging from severe emotional numbness to intense emotions (such as moments when I can #8217;t stop crying, then feel fine) 3. Paranoia (people are watching me, tracking me, etc) 4. Loss of sleep 5. Times when I feel I can go run for miles without stopping or wanting to start a new life, then feeling like I can #8217;t get out of bed. 6. Feeling like people are abandoning me 7. Feeling like people are constantly blaming me for things I didn #8217;t do Feedback would be appreciated</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Scrapbooks</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 06:57:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi there! I recently took a week long trip and took lots of different photos. I thought a scrapbook would be a cool idea way to present them, but I feel like there won #8217;t be enough room. Ordering online photo books are not preferred for me because they can be a little pricey. Any recommendations? What should I do with my photos?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 21:16:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I forgot you can add pages to scrapbooks! Definitely going to start the long process of picking which photos to keep and what to not keep</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Desert Books</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 05:29:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was just in the Mojave high desert out in Southern California and southern Nevada. Out in the middle of nowhere, I had heard about the high crime rates in some of the towns and some of the towns being hot spots for body dumping and murder. Any non fiction books about murder in the desert that you #8217;ve heard of that can help with my research. It #8217;s pretty scary being out in the desert, what with the big sky and isolation, but I want to know more about if there actually is a lot of crime and murder there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Guitar tips</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 19:46:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any tips on making software guitars sound more realistic? Aka adding feedback, adding glide/legato sounds, velocity, strumming etc. I know this is vague and a long shot but I don #8217;t know how to play guitar and want to add guitar to my songs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Feeling lost</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 02:27:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>TW: Sexual Assault, self harm, death of loved one  #8212; #8212; #8212; I #8217;m feeling really really bad. I hate myself, I hate my body, I #8217;m having trouble with my eating disorder, I #8217;m having trouble processing my sexual assault, I #8217;m having trouble coping with losing my best friend in a car accident. I #8217;m struggling with my depression and anxiety and panic attacks and feeling worthless and like an object after my sexual assault. I feel so lonely and I #8217;m working a lot because my parents wanted me to get a job but they keep saying I #8217;m not working enough. My parents just focus on my bad choices and don #8217;t see how hard I #8217;m working to stay strong and healthy and keep going. Last night I had a bad breakdown and I didn #8217;t actually want to die but for the first time ever I tried slitting my wrists. It was really deep and at first the blood was lighter red but when I cut deeper it turned dark red and started pouring out more and I got scared but I didn #8217;t stop. Eventually I stopped and told my parents what was happening in my life. Again my parents just focused on all my bad decisions (ie, lying about small stuff once in awhile) and my dad is giving my mom the silent treatment because he thinks she #8217;s  #8220;taking my side over his #8221; and  #8220;coddling me, #8221; and it hurts so bad and I don #8217;t know what to do. I try to tell myself that I #8217;m trying my hardest and I #8217;m a good person but I don #8217;t believe it. What do I do?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>