<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject5003</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 20:49:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn it #8217;s like his legs just gave out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 13:45:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>When local girls waning to talk to me. Only to find out it leads to another web sight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 14:35:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please tell me the full story lol. I need to know what was the outcome was.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 21:50:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>A Toppers. Anytime I #8217;m telling a story. Some dude aways seem to have done it or seen it better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 21:59:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m korean and something about Mexican girls. When I see them. I #8217;m like a clay in their hand. They can mold me how ever they want.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 22:08:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>My parents were hardcore Christians. Naturally Michael W Smith and the News Boys were the music I was told to listen to. But little do they know I had Nirvana CD Stashed between the mattress. One day I asked them about Nirvana. My dad looked at me with the most serious look and told me that it #8217;s the devils music. I should of told them I like devils music. But didn #8217;t.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 00:39:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I heard this song back in 99 when I was in conversion therapy in Wisconsin. It was one of the toughest time in my life. Last kiss did not help the situation. But the song Solder of love gave me great hopes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 00:49:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can say. I #8217;m glad. It is one of the worst thing I have ever gone through back in 99 in Wisconsin. I hope it goes nation wide.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 13:06:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>When she karaokes with me in the car. Like she sings really loud with me. Btw Neil Diamond is our go to. Lol good times never seemed so good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 13:09:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>They think I #8217;m high too but in reality I #8217;m korean and high.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 18:43:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I when up to a girl I really liked. I opens the the conversation by saying.  #8220; I wish I can show you picture of my junk so I can make it super awkward #8221;. Lol that line finally worked. I am Married to her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 18:57:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>My friend and I were playing out in a field and it was one of those July early August dry summer days. We took fire works we found in my parents bedroom they forgot about. We lit couple of them off and next thing you know the field was on fire. As we started to panic and started to throw sand on it but it just spread so fast. We both decided to get on our bikes and take off. But sure shit here comes my brother and his friend wanting to know what #8217;s happening. I remember telling him.  #8220;There is fire back their and I don #8217;t know how it started  #8220; My friend and I both split off and when home. When I got home I looked myself in the mirror and my face was black with dirt. So I took a quick shower and layed low. Waiting for the cops to come and get me. All the while I can hear the fire truck in the back. In the end cops never showed up. My brother never snitched on me. But I burnt down most of my neighbors field of hay. 8-9 years later my brother brought it up and we laughed about it pretty hard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 19:04:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>In my self-pity I was listening to Sinead O #8217;Connor nothing compares to you. My brother drive 2 hours to take me out to have a brother to brother talk. He said.  #8220; you #8217;re korean. Plenty of girls have yellow fever #8221;. Lol made my night. And that #8217;s all it took to snap me out of it all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 19:11:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Every now and then I eat half a fruit and lay it around the house an night to make my wife believe she sleep walks and eats. When my wife farts in public I aways take the blame. My wife dose not sleep walk or eat at night. Even though she really believes it now. And I #8217;m too far now to tell her the truth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 19:15:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I approach it like how I approach my wife in bed. Aways at different angles. If on angle doesn #8217;t work. Try different angle until one hits.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 19:29:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>My parents aways knew. She said my clothes smelled like fire. And the shower was full of dirt on the corner. She put it all together and knew I was involved. My mom and dad said it took all in them to not laugh at me at dinner time because I was so quiet and looked like I was up to no good. Lol Needless to say. They try to pay Mr. Jim for his loss but he didn #8217;t accept the money. All he said was it was a mistake. They never brought it up because they wanted me to bring it up. And after all of them years she finally said it #8217;s about time you owned up lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 23:28:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>WOW. that is really nice job.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 16:37:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s like she pulled something from depth of hell.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 18:36:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can #8217;t get them pregnant if I #8217;m not having sex.  #129300;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 10:57:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>So basically. Not your problem vs. my problem. But you and me vs. the problem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 12:37:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like I #8217;m watching. RENO 911</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 16:21:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eating ramen half way. Then getting asked  #8220;is everything ok for you #8221;. It happens every time I go out to eat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 18:28:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>What #8217;s stree tart?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 00:01:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bugs bunny when he would wear the red dress.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 11:00:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m so happy for Chicago</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 03:48:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I see they also charged you. Your pants and a knee.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 18:04:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>And when cops show up. They are aways Ready to play the victim.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>People of reddit. What do you look like?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 18:29:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 18:39:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Watching my partner making fun of someone for their unchangeables. My last partner was really being loud about this girl having one leg noticeable larger then the other. I just said. Everyone has that. Some more noticeable then others. We broke up that night. I just couldn #8217;t get over someone that can be that mean.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 18:41:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>My partner in the beginning said to me. I only let you yell at me because I love you. I have since started to go to counseling and really get to the bottom of my issues.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 18:44:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do or do not. There is no try.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 18:46:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>And extremely repetitive</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 18:48:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol welcome to the club</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 18:50:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel you. My life #8217;s mundane and never a headliner. But sometimes I wish I was.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 18:53:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah yes the old Timberlake. I #8217;m glad he bye bye byed that hair style.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 18:55:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you serial?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 19:01:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well. Sounds to like a good time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 19:10:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll tell you what. Last time I let someone know how beautiful my inside was. They asked me if I wanted to give them one of my Kidneys.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 19:11:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do your friends ask you to buy the beer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 19:14:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yikes. The cold hard truth. But seriously. You gotta have some friends.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 19:14:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol.  #128514; #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 19:16:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>If that was you. 10/10. I swear to you. If there is someone better looking. I really don #8217;t wanna know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 19:16:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like everything in reddit. Just enjoy the ride.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 19:17:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s how it aways starts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 19:18:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just know korean and Japan.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 19:20:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll take a hard pass on that one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 19:22:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>One guy did on here. And he was Jay jayed all out. He was Dynomite. I gave him 10/10.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 19:24:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just be a 16 year old and hang out with people. Lol shit gets better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 19:25:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice. I #8217;m a huge fan. Love the emo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 19:26:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then I bet you #8217;re thicker the Heinz 57.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 19:39:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m a fan of her. I have her greatest hits. As for her looks lol. Not my cup of tea.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 19:45:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol I #8217;m korean. I #8217;m 37. Look like I #8217;m 22 so I #8217;ve been told. Often I get asked what collage I go to. No hair on my face. Legs. Armpits. Or my arms or body. I really don #8217;t sweat or my partner tells me. No Oder at all. I know the struggles. Lol. I don #8217;t know if you can relate. But I have never used Deodorant. It also doesn #8217;t help I can #8217;t seem to gain mass. So 5 #8217;7 at a whopping 141 lbs lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 01:43:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Medical marijuana.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 00:04:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love that he went strait for that ass.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 19:57:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Asbestos.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 17:23:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>She would of been lot cooler if she put that 99 cent sticker.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 12:57:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>After she reviled that she was 12. He knew Chris Hanson was right around the corner.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Meet fluffy. Our South African Boelboel. In time he will be over 200lbs. But as of now I #8217;m enjoying his tiny body.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 16:52:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 17:57:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s really funny watching him walk. He trips over his own feet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 17:58:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>His dads huge and his mom was just as big. So I #8217;m hopping he will turn out the same.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 18:04:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. They are protective dogs that is used to fight off lions. Not that we have lions here in Michigan. But it is A very smart dogs. That will protect the family.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 18:33:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol well. I have misspelled the word. I #8217;m sorry about that. Thank you for pointing that out. As for me I #8217;m not too familiar with the breed. But I am doing research on them. And I think I will be fine since I have a large back yard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 18:36:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well. I am learning as I go. But from my understanding they are great with kids and they are very protective. They also need large yard to run around. Other then that. It #8217;s going to be a nice dog to have around. This is actually my first big dog so I #8217;m very excited.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 23:22:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Amazing and reddit is proud of you #128077; #127996;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 00:29:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. I spelled it wrong</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 00:30:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>He is not interested yet. But we are planning on it. I have been talking to different vets to fined the ones we might like. I #8217;m really looking into making sure fluffy is going to have a good life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 00:31:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s crazy. But I love him so much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 00:33:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I found one closer to me. But I have to let them keep him for little bit. But I think it will be worth it. I #8217;m going to miss him a lot but he will be well trained.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 00:35:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well. I have found some one that will train him. I #8217;ve done the background check. The lady seem to know what she is talking about. Little expensive but it #8217;s worth it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 00:52:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow this is going to be huge task. But I better get more involved. I guess it #8217;s nothing like my little Chihuahua.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 00:56:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>What kinda food would you recommend. To feel fluffy. I mean. What brand.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 00:59:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh god lol. Don #8217;t get me started on them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 05:27:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes I am very much landing on posting again. Yes I do live on the farm. So he has a lot of room</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 10:34:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>This just keeps getting better. Lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 15:44:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>If the IRS sniffs up your ass hard enough. Soon or later they are going to get a mouth full of balls.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 23:20:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are amazing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 00:02:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you. So much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 01:51:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 02:12:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Entry level welders helper and maintenance. Hopefully I #8217;ll move up the latter sooner then later.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 02:13:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m going to work hard so I can somehow get there. Thank you so much for the positive vibe.  #128512;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 02:14:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 02:29:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m more or less excited for the benefits. Now after 7 month of no Insurance lol. Luckily my kids never got hurt or sick. Knock on wood.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 02:30:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oil. For Exon</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 02:32:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really negotiated what I wanted to get payed. After going back and forth. This is what we settled on. They were going to pay be way less.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 02:34:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>You looking awesome bro.  #128077; #127996;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 03:02:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes I did. And it was super fascinating. I watched their body language and how they captivated audience. With Clinton I used this tactic. when I was getting interviewed. the person that asked me a question I would only look at the person that asked the question and I act like no one was in the room. I wanted to make them feel like they are the most important person in the room and how their question is the most important question. With Obama i looked at his hand gestures and when he smiled. Although they are very similar. I felt Clinton was much smoother speaker.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 03:08:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I commented on this one. They are very fascinating. I think not just in job interviews. I think I can use what I learned and apply it to everyday interactions. The way they make everyone special I think is number one. Now I can see why the ladies loved Clinton.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 03:09:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg thank you. It just feels better knowing I can provide for them again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 03:11:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will. Thank you. Hopefully I #8217;ll post my first day picture.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 03:15:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol well then my first day is going to be Tuesday of 5th so I #8217;ll post.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 03:20:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>No I will be working the lines from Illinois to Michigan. Although I might be in some refineries to do patch jobs. But mostly in right of ways.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 03:21:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I figured. Worst thing they could say is no.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 03:25:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>First year 3% after 12month 6% match.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 03:26:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol I miss spelled. That #8217;s on me. But you are right it is Exxon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 03:27:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 03:32:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just looked up Obama speeches and Clinton speeches. If you do look it up and watch then. Pay really close attention to their hand movements.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 03:36:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes both of them. They speak slower and if you watch Obama he does lots of ahhh when he #8217;s thinking. And as for Clinton he almost looks like he #8217;s picking his words. And he also does that scrunching his lips and squints his eyes. Just super fascinating. They just look so relaxed and in control.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 03:39:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish I can answers that. I #8217;m not really sure about that. I #8217;ll learn more about it on the 5th. And I #8217;ll get back to you on that question as well. Just because I #8217;m also curious about that as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 03:40:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really hope this will be my career and just like anyone I #8217;ll have my bad days. But as long as I keep marching forward. I think I #8217;ll be an amazing compliment to the team.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 04:00:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I don #8217;t feel I #8217;m bashing the company. In fact I #8217;m very excited to be part of this company and the strong culture.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 04:27:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I say look up Obama yes we can. Also look up Secrets of bill Clinton #8217;s charisma. More less watch Clinton.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 04:27:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bill Clinton.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 22:45:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude awesome progress. Keep on Keeping on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It #8217;s true and real</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 02:23:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 12:35:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe she kisses fish to get to fish sticks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 10:24:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is your dad Randy Marsh?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 10:33:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pepper Ann</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 22:18:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s waisting July ham.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 13:52:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Keanu Reeves.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 23:45:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>In mother Russia. You are still in style.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 10:33:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>All grown up and ready to grow out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 17:10:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>In orphanage. I had to eat fast or the older kids took my food. Now if I try to eat slow I don #8217;t enjoy my food. And my wife aways tells me no ones going to take my food. I say bull shit they won #8217;t take it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 20:04:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn it #8217;s like modern day sandlot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 08:57:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well that got heated really quick.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 00:27:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>From the looks of her calf and ankle ratio. I can tell you she is thicker then Heinz 57.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 20:08:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol this made me smile so much. The look on his face.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 22:35:23</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Jerry it #8217;s not a lie. If you believe it #8221;. - George Costanza.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 12:59:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I was 7th grade I wrote a letter to my crush, telling her how we would be great together and even went as far as drawing her a picture of Aladdin and Jasmine. She returned the letter wrote never on it. It didn #8217;t help we went to same church. So that Sunday after church my mom asked me if I wrote that letter while my dad shaking his head and laughing at our dinner table. My mom thought it was sweet. I had a talk with my dad about how to pick up girls.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 15:07:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope this becomes forever trend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 07:25:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Them Napoleon Dynamite boots killed your outfit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 03:00:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t see Geraldine. That #8217;s is my moms name. And it #8217;s been most popular in my house hold since 1990.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 15:01:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>But the waist line is so unrealistic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 22:31:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s no for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 22:47:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, I generally come in at least 15 minutes late. After that. I sorta space out for an hour. I just stare at my desk. But it looks like I #8217;m working. I do that probably for another hour after lunch too. I #8217;d say In a given week I probably only do about fifteen minutes of real actual work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 03:48:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Life comes at you fast.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 08:40:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s like I #8217;m watching hood Infinity War.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 08:48:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s what she said.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 22:09:12</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;I don #8217;t wanna grow up. I #8217;m a Toys R us kid.  #8220; - so long and good night toys r us.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 22:11:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>She has that Hank Hill ass.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 22:13:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the first time I #8217;ve seen his comment have a thumbs up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 10:30:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>His nipples look like milk duds.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 10:54:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>This guy also owns a dodge Dakota</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 11:01:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit. The ending was the icing on the cake.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 11:09:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I live close to it as well. It #8217;s aways been so trashy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 11:27:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn Kevin Hart came out of nowhere.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 11:35:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I gotta say. I use to be like her. But I broke that habit about a year ago. And I feel great. First couple of weeks were hard but I #8217;m glad I never went back on it. Now I cringe when ever I got mad about some bull shit other peoples FB post. Or envious of other people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 11:46:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was like I was watching Michael bay film.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 20:25:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too. I was thinking Heirs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 20:26:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Korean dramas.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 20:27:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course he did. So Jesus can be a carpenter.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 19:27:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>She has aged well. Still looking good.  #128077; #127996;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 21:52:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>You didn #8217;t just stand up. You jumped up. We are proud of you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Jisoo, Jennie, Rosie and Lisa. Of Blackpink</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 23:55:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 00:06:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let this man cross the border. Him and his family. America needs this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 01:39:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I should have known. You are correct about the order of the names. I put their names up their.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 10:12:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>That heart tattoo is kind of in an odd place to be. Next to that magnificent piece.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 10:16:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>You don #8217;t agree with it so You think it #8217;s mental illness?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 10:33:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then why would you say mental illness? And I #8217;m sorry for saying you didn #8217;t agree. I assumed and that is my fault.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 11:08:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you tell me where you got that report from? If you can #8217;t tell me the source of the study. Please be quiet with that garbage and go sit in the corner and poop on yourself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 12:40:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well after reading and doing little bit of research. This is what I got out of this. People with tattoos are more likely to have sex more, earlier age of losing virginity, and more likely to not use comdoms (rawdog). Also have you ever been to prestigious campus? Go and see please. Just about everyone has tattoos. So in my conclusion. This research must of been done by some nice people aka neck beards. Who probably complained about girls aways going after bad guys with  #8220;mental illness  #8220;. I wander if they think ancient Natives had mental illness. Either you are a fedora wearing, M #8217;lady shouting guy. Or you just don #8217;t like art. Either way take art as is. But calling someone mentally ill for making personal choices like getting tattoos is not nice. Maybe you should get some tattoos so you can get laid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 15:33:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well your response was what I was expecting. A typical defensive response from a neck beard. Good talking to you m #8217;guy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 15:37:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha Yea, typical.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 15:59:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok lol I would fuck me too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 16:14:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>NO.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 16:20:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>NO</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 17:03:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>NO</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 02:09:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>What will you do. I #8217;m near Chicago. And I would like to go.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 02:47:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>What are the age limit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 02:51:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok we wanna come.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 03:51:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s good looking steamed ham.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 11:22:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn someone should of gave him some Act Rights.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 13:37:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>No I don #8217;t know what you mean.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 08:11:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>It just looks like a loaded diaper.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 17:25:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>That just shows you how much bounce them sticks have.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 18:52:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck yea. Great song for an awesome World Cup.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 20:34:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg bless you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 22:39:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Too much surgery. Still pretty though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 09:13:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Serious question. What dose this workout do?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 09:47:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>And that suit cases name in Macaulay Culkin.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 18:22:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you. Lol I have to try this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 21:22:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Real question is. How do they poop?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 09:08:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>He better talk to LaBron about that magic hair line grower.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 13:01:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would taste the rainbow.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 14:53:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Makes me wanna call the manager on her before she can call the manager.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 19:56:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>She is just so amazingly beautiful</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 23:01:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shots fired.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 11:13:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>My mom has that one. I never know how important rice makers were,until I got my CuCoo rice maker. Now I make everything with it. Steam pot, cake, chicken soup, basically anything you can make in a crock pot but much faster. Oh yea it makes rice as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 11:14:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not my proudest boner.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 11:30:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why is stuff aways happening In Florida? Seriously. What #8217;s in their water.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 15:58:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>They do this because 1 they know you #8217;re not going to finish it. 2 you #8217;re going to lose it. Either way. This is the equivalent to getting bag of chips. All air little substance. I Pity the fool who falls for these trick.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 10:50:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well let #8217;s not go crazy with that talk. Easy on the stripper on faces. One enjoys stank strippers ass from time to time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Alma Michigan</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 15:41:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 17:09:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is first time being here for a job. I travel a lot for my job. Mostly in Michigan Indiana and Illinois. And I gotta say Michigan has to be one of my fav places to be working.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 18:44:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it #8217;s amazing. I don #8217;t know. I just love nature and farm lands. I think it #8217;s so beautiful. You are very luck you have that option to walk 5 mins to see amazing views.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 19:02:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then sounds to me I have to go and see Ohio. I have no doubt that it won #8217;t be beautiful. Once I have little time I #8217;ll go to Ohio. Where do you suggest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 20:19:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am enjoying it. So much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 20:20:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I will have to go and check it out. And when I do. I #8217;ll post another picture. I #8217;ll take your word as well. I #8217;m sure it #8217;s stunning.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 21:12:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>McConnell will push a bill that will make people with lips be deported.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 21:44:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would love this scenery everyday of my life. Lol one day I #8217;ll get it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 21:44:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 23:12:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Their are so much. I was looking at the map all the places you can go. Omg. Lol so much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 00:01:17</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;These nets. They do nothing #8221;. -Rainier Wolfcastle</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 16:08:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just wandering what is the bedding. Ive been using paper bedding. Is this bedding better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 18:16:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much for your input. I #8217;ll try the fleece.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 22:43:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude. I knew a good friend who went through a divorce. Lost everything and lived in his suv from Walmart parking lot to meijers parking lot. He would go through trash like the people in the picture looking for stuff. People tried to help him but he didn #8217;t want it because he wanted to get out of it on his own. At the time he had IPhones 7 plus. You never know peoples situations. Don #8217;t be that trashy person looking down on people. Maybe you should of offered some assistance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 22:51:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like the boy out ran her when the bear was chasing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 23:05:07</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220; I #8217;ll take famous panties for $500 #8221; - Sean Connery.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 03:10:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re doing great bro.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 05:55:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good lord. I can #8217;t get enough of kdrama and kpop.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 06:00:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>You sound dumb.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 06:06:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would you rather date a well mannered korean or shitty dirty Chinese? OP see how stupid this question sound? Fuck China. Have you ever seen the Chinese tourists? Fucking slobs. That #8217;s why most of the Asian countries don #8217;t like Chinese.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 06:50:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s my go to when I #8217;m not working or out of town fir work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 02:28:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck yea!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 12:39:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Frankly this is how I feel when the beat drops.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 22:07:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll aways upvote for her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 22:12:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most under rated natural beauty</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 20:04:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Trust no 1.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 10:47:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Man of class.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 12:12:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>This isn #8217;t a regular bison. This is M. Bison.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Almost bumped into this morning.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 13:01:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Grand Haven Michigan. Working.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 17:39:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 17:39:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can #8217;t even imagine the pain. Omg.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 17:40:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the chair idea is really dumb. Last night people sat inform of my room just talking really loud.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 17:52:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was the last min hotel I had to get. I didn #8217;t think it was going to be this bad. But all in all the older people that owns this place is nice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 17:59:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks.  #128077; #127996;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 23:21:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where ever their is a person denying an LGBTQ person. Mike Huckabee is there to comfort the denier in the name of religion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 23:31:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fast food Infinity War. McThanos is destroying everything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 09:21:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seems like she #8217;s living the dream.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 09:42:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why didn #8217;t they just dump it in a trough and line people. Damn it this grinds my gear.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 20:50:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>That guy is hung like a horse.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 14:57:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>If Yan can cook. So can you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 22:21:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love this. But I seriously thought I was watching an episode of the Office.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can you tell me who won in this sowing competition? Mine is right and my little girls is on the left. Male 37 vs girl who is 7. If she wins she will get a new Barbie.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 01:24:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 01:37:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol now I know. I #8217;m not the greatest. Time to take her to the store.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 01:39:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I tried to make the Barbie classy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 01:40:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>We are going to the fabric store.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 01:47:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I admit it lol I #8217;m no good at it. It was a fun competition with my little girl. Yes she is getting a new doll and fabrics. Plus we had 30 mins to finish so it wasn #8217;t the best.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 11:30:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also makes there head look huge.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 23:30:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>How are the people in construction treating you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mike was too strong.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 07:20:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Damn I feel bad for her.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 10:26:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 12:45:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>You would be surprised how slow someone can be. My coworker once thought Chrysler 300 was a Bentley. When you could clearly see the Chrysler logo. Just slow.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 13:13:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>It looks like Bentley until you pull up next to real Bentley.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 18:51:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol well I have a Bentley for sale. Low miles.  #129315;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 10:37:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought little guy at the end had dr Phil hair cut.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 10:53:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Phoenix is Harvard of online collages. Yes it #8217;s more then legit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 11:20:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was a joke. I think everyone knows those online colleges are a joke.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 11:22:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s a hard pass for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 12:25:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I went to Phoenix. So what do you expect. THIS IS A JOKE!!! #128512;. Lol,haha and lmfao. Is that better?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 14:49:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude lighten up. You #8217;re taking this to serious</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 15:35:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are very smart.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 15:38:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not even close.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 20:53:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>GREAT SCOTT!! This is beautiful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 22:26:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesus knows how to party. When the alcohol ran dry. He turned water into wine to keep the party going.  #8220; go on and keep this party going #8221;. - Jesus.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 01:16:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know beauty is only skin deep. But damn this girls got some thick ass skin.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 10:20:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you think hrt made you gain weight. I know I #8217;ve gained a lot being on progesterone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 10:40:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m going to be really frank with you to lol. If you wanna lose weight. It #8217;s super hard ever since I #8217;ve been on Estrogen. Progesterone. And spiro. It takes forever. Before I transitioned. I could eat and not gain. Now all my weights go to my thighs and butt. Not that it #8217;s a bad thing. I #8217;m just sick of my thighs rubbing in hot summer days.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 10:49:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s ok lol. We are in this together.  #128516;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 10:55:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kobe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 17:28:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>My questions is. Why dose Jesus look like some European?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 17:53:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>He better live up to his name. He better be thicker then Heinz 57.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 02:08:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is one pixel away from being a radio.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 15:45:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>If it works it #8217;s not stupid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 08:26:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wth lol people will post anything. Lol I think you are very delusional.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 11:35:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>If they make the movie. I hope they will have Nichols Cage as Mueller. I feel Mueller seems like a guy who will talk really loud and soft when he #8217;s interviewing people. And John Candy as Trump if he was still alive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 11:37:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wander if he knew that people loved him on Reddit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 11:49:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stoner bashing time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 11:51:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok thank you. That #8217;s awesome. He seems like a nice guy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 10:28:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>He is stout and he hates governments.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 11:23:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t know who #8217;s watching other 1 million but I know I watched it at least 299 million times.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 17:54:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m joking lol but I did watch a lot. It #8217;s my rest of my life jam.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 18:15:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m Do Min-Joon. From My love from another star. Lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 15:32:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I watched this movie. But it was the 2nd time watching it made me really appreciate the film.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 11:17:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are better off by listening to pod cast or audio book.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 12:38:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn #8217;t adopt. But I was adopted. At first my they told my parents no because I was too old ( I was 10). So my parents flew to Korea to talk to the agency in person to make sure that I was going to go with them. No matter how much I loved my adopted parents. I just never felt at home with them. They adopted 2 other Koreans. But they came when they were 6 month. I love my family and they are my world. But even after 24 years being in the states. I aways felt lot more relaxed when I was around more eastern Asians. Listening to korean music and watching korean shows really eases my anxiety. I remember one of my teachers told my mom some kids are broken before they come to America. Just because I was scared to talk. I never heard my mom yell. But that day I knew I was going to be ok. America is a scary place.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 12:39:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dr feel good by Motley Crue.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 20:26:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>They all look like they are involved in MLM.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Are they  #128059; or  #128054;? Either way. I #8217;ll take one please.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 11:47:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 12:03:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>They are so cute. I just wanna be surrounded by them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 12:50:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol me too. But they are real and they are spectacular.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 11:46:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Extra dry gin. Drank it for the first time in my freshman year in high school. I was so wasted that I fell down the stares. Now the smell of it makes me sick. I can #8217;t even drink chocolate milk because to me it smells like gin. Or be around pine trees because the tree smells like gin. Needless to say. That was my one and only alcoholic drink I have ever had. Just because I promised my mom I #8217;ll never do it until I was 21. But once I turned 21. I didn #8217;t see the need to start.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 20:27:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Once you snatch the grape out of my hand. Then you can leave the dojo. - kung fu master.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 20:46:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you try that now. You can #8217;t.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Give me back my child.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 11:18:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 12:54:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is how I feel when someone picks up my fur babies. I aways make sure they are treating them like how I treat my fur babies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Family isn #8217;t whose blood you carry.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 21:21:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 23:45:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Trump is like Biff from Back to the Future. And Lorraine is Melania.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 00:17:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really? Lol if true that #8217;s crazy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 00:19:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are wrong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 01:01:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sports almanac 1950-2000 If your name is Biff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This warms my heart.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 17:06:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 18:11:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s amazing how his hair went from top of his head to his face.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 12:42:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>And calling girls dames. Broads and toots.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Creepy trash.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 22:00:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 12:14:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just a little bit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 19:07:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>On top of them. Their was no reason for him to even touch anyone. He doesn #8217;t know her like that. Most he could do is maybe a hand shake at the end of the funeral.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Omg this is so cute. I want a hug like this</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:17:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>