<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject4333</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-15 01:28:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>'Hush' on Netflix. You can't make a better home invasion/horror. A deaf woman is stalked by a killer in her home, sounds simple, but it is an amazing and absolutely terrifying film.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-16 12:28:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well this is s true story, the adderall actually helped, but for the sake of the joke it doesn't need to</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just a healthy reminder that this still exists..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-18 04:20:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How do we feel about Louis CK 'sexual assault' allegations?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-20 21:38:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-20 21:41:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not going to repeat favorites that have already been mentioned, however I don't see how Daniel tosh isn't on any lists. So cleverly offensive it's hard not to appreciate his vicious, witty black comedy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-21 00:38:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I just picked this site out of the litter. There's a boatload of articles reiterating the same information on the topic. Looking at it subjectively, it's totally possible. I just feel like he's too self deprecating and socially anxious to pull that kind of shit. But then again, you really never fuckin know man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-24 16:25:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I got my first time over with last week, terrifying. But thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-25 00:13:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think rule #1 in life is to never smoke crack</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-15 14:35:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kanye actually went OFF, like two paragraphs in that article. Pretty harsh stuff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Police Find Three Bodies in Ohio After Woman Calls Police While Her Abductor is Sleeping</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-16 14:25:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-16 15:37:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you explain "whiskey dick"?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-28 05:34:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is going to look brutal in the toilet after that coffee.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-10 20:28:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Other</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-11 06:31:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yesmovies.to is the best streaming site on earth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-27 06:41:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>When you want to downvote the topic but upvote the courtesy of posting it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 05:10:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is /b/ ? (For a noovbie)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-05 18:56:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol, I didn't think so. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-05 19:13:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was just a question man...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-05 23:41:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hardo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-06 03:04:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah well I clearly didn't know anything about satanism when I asked the question did I? No. I asked the question to learn about it from first-hand satanists. However, the majority of you guys are just over sensitive and bitching me out when I was clearly just attempting to get information while also being respectful and saying your religion is refreshing and honest. So no, it wasn't a stupid question. I, like most people, know nothing about satanism - so I asked. Fuck off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-15 05:39:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I intern at a corporate healthcare company. Im on the marketing and communications teams and, very ironically, everybody else on the team is completely introverted. I used to be this way, so i totally understand, however i battled out of it the best i could by forcing myself to converse and grind through small talk. But these people are something else. None of them have the social skills to say "good morning" or "have a good day" at the end of the work day. They can't make eye contact while speaking, they take purposely take conversation into a dead end street so they can get out of it and go back to huddling in their cubicle. And if you're wondering if i'm the weirdo who talks to much-i'm not. Ive had many work environments where i was the introvert and it made me extremely uncomfortable so i dealt with it. People in other departments agree with me that they're so painfully shy, i have no idea how they got into communications. The IT team is MUCH more talkative!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-15 13:37:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whoa interesting thanks!!!!!!!!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-16 04:02:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I legitimately said you guys know 100% more than me which is why i asked for advice, dickhead. Take your negatively elsewhere</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-16 14:00:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice dude. I was asking if it was too strong to do for my first monologue in my first acting class. That's what i was asking, stop being a fucking prick. I was asking for possible other suggestions, i wasn't asking for some asshole to criticize me for looking for help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why is there no sign of David Parker Ray's wife anywhere on the internet?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-20 00:51:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>David Parker Ray was a serial killer, better known as the "Toy Box Killer", who raped, tortured, and killed dozens of girls in his $100,000 torture dungeon. From my understanding, he committed these crimes with his wife-who would take part in all of it. However, i can't find anything about her on the internet? Her name, picture, or sentencing is nowhere to be found. Can anyone provide insight? Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-20 01:32:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awesome, Thanks!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How scripted are talk shows?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 05:30:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-23 16:07:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was fuckin terrifying man. At the time i was just running away because i didn't want to get in trouble (even though i didn't do anything? probably just an instinct) but i didn't grasp the gravity of the situation until i found out he was a legitimate sex offender.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 22:03:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry bud but i would've done the same thing that she did. Maybe it's because i'm from Boston and the streets are an absolute war zone (however i have learned from living in Vermont that you can't act like that as an adult). She wasn't in the wrong for yelling at him to get out of the road, the guy was clearly drunk and deserved to be yelled at. Also, the fact that you said she deserved the reaction (him trying to attack her and her girlfriend and also screaming WAY worse shit/threatening her) is pretty extreme. You risk crazy people reacting in crazy ways when you yell at a bad driver, but nobody deserves to be afraid for their life and almost assaulted. Come on man, be better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-26 17:30:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ugh, true. Do you need me to PM you my pierced nips?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The police chief of my city</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-29 04:34:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-29 05:01:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not - it was posted on the Vera Institute of Justice's Facebook page.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-29 15:57:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Burlington VT!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-27 00:02:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Isn't 'wreck less' driving technically good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-05 18:06:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>The support for this notion from people all around the world is strange to me. I totally agree with it, however when somebody suggests this in the U.S. it's considered rude and borderline racist depending on the immigrant.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just watched "The Autopsy of Jane Doe" and holy fuck it was terrifying (and original) - What did you guys think?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-07 01:08:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-07 04:52:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>What does scare you?! Oh man, it scared the living shit out of me and i watched it at home. In the theaters i would've been covering my eyes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-07 14:14:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>yesmovies.to :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-07 14:15:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll definitely check that out!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-07 14:43:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry bud but feeding your child isn't a state of mind</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-07 17:11:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean the premise was very original which i loved. It kept me guessing for a good amount of time and sometimes i was too scared to guess. People who yawn at this film perplex me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My post of our police chief made the front page about a month and a half ago (Sorry, just discovered this sub!)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 06:23:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 17:29:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>"You should name your baby Rio.....orrrrr gas station"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 05:07:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>best question by far</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-27 22:34:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>WAYNE FEDERMAN. God, he could not resist cutting joe off every time he tried to speak. He was genuinely annoying, uninteresting, and came across as a babbling idiot. I'm a fan of his work, but he does not belong on a 3 hour podcast.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-27 22:37:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-27 22:37:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes! He's been on multiple rundowns in the Skye days</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 18:06:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>LOTSA....... ....... ......... ...... HOSTAS!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-31 03:22:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Paraphrasing Joe Rogan: Only idiots take polls.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-31 15:02:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>A god amongst men. Belichick should feel honored</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 05:23:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait... is this why Burlington Highschool goes by "Seahorses"? I'm originally from Boston and moved here 2 years ago so i have no idea</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 05:54:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know the difference between the two, i was just curious - but wow, i did not know that! I always thought it was such a funny name</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Don't wait until the last second to shovel out your car and get it off the streets like i did! Parking ban starts at 10!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-14 03:32:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-03 21:47:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Uhhhh no shit dude. Why is everyone so cunty about five fucking dollars? This is one of the funniest things they've done in months i'm so pumped fake or not</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-06 15:11:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>If that was 99% of us we would've been hit by that. I would not want to throw hands with caleb</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-10 15:20:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks that what i was thinking. They've been making decent set ups, but the punchline to my one liners are way better than the punch line at the end of my bit. Great tip tho thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-10 15:22:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for taking the time to respond like that! If you have any videos of your sets that you would like me to check out, send em over!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-10 17:50:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>mehhh, not really. Stories are strung together by jokes, not necessarily one liners.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-10 18:35:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah true, that makes sense</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-23 14:50:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rick has worked really closely with Johnny Cash. Joe would fucking love this dude.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-24 00:40:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Finally!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-24 16:17:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stowe, VT?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Free college is Racist</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-02 18:47:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-12 05:53:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>The internet has changed my life in many ways and, considering I was born in 1995, it played a huge role in my life and the juxtaposition of finding out who I am with an excessive influx of influence coming from all directions. I will only post two for the sake of your eyeballs. 1. My freshman year of college I was a criminal justice major, dead set on working in law enforcement with a hope of someday making it to the DEA. I went to school in NH where you get put in a holding cell for having a pipe with marijuana residue in it. I was a normal kid and did drugs in moderation, which i realize sounds kind of hypocritical. My experimental phase of drugs was a result of the internet and the wide open window it provided for unfiltered, useful knowledge and shared experiences. I learned more about the useless war on drugs from the internet than I ever did in any classroom. This, paired with the CJ program advisor telling me that any job in the field would require a polygraph inquiring about my drug use in the past 5 years, funneled me into a more fitting career path. 2. While I was growing up, nobody got famous from being funny or entertaining on the internet. It wasn't nearly as accessible or widely utilized as it has been as of late. It's been a very quick leap from being forced off the dial-up internet by my mother so she could make a phone call to literally being able to stream Pay Per View events on my cell phone. Making videos and drawing in laughs and views from all over the world, while making a living, has never been something that I was raised to think as "possible". Yet, it is something that I am currently trying to do. There is a popular comedy/sports website that I have been in touch with over the past few months and one of the employees recently asked me to make a video for them. I have zero experience in videography, however comedy is something I have a great passion for. I recently gathered two other kids that I have met once or twice and started to make a plan for a video I wanted to do. They are videography weapons and I enjoy being on camera so it was one of those "meeting of the minds" ideas. The premise that was requested by the company was simple and stupid (interviewing drunk college kids); however, I finally had someone who wanted to see what I could do. We absolutely nailed the video and it is currently being edited (hopefully being finalized in a week or two). The point being is that the internet opened HUGE doors for me. Being "creative" was only a thing for music, drama, and art kids growing up and I was never really "socially allowed" to show that side of myself. It was a side of me that has been aching to come out ever since I was a kid. The internet showed me that not only is it okay to be openly creative and take risks with creative ideas, but it allowed me to give it a shot. I really hope it works out because this is something that is so new, so possible, and so revolutionary. Sorry for all the words - I told you, it was for the sake of your eyeballs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-12 06:04:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wrote this tonight in a one liner for my second open mic. I guess i'll go kill myself now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-24 06:43:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was pulled over on the side of the road. Sorry about the mirror, couldn't really protect it from vandals smashing it in the middle of the night. Then again, this is an OSHA subreddit not a community for mirror etiquette.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-24 22:15:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I work directly across from fenway park - the roof deck allows me to watch sox games and see live concerts for free! It's awesome!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 16:16:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>They have done several in the past. Bill's been on JRE several times and Joe went on Bill's a couple of months ago (for the first time i believe!)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-11 01:07:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where can i listen to this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-13 04:43:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Breathtaking***</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-20 05:40:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow I'm feeling like a real sociopath. Whenever I rewatch The Office (literally a few times a year, sad i know) I can't help but belly laugh whenever this scene comes on. Helplessly scrambling to pick up loose chili all over the carpet - such a great bit. I can see how you can feel this way, though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-23 15:33:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Phenomenally large adult sons.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-27 02:59:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll give it a shot man, thanks! Any chance you have a picture of the part it goes around?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-27 05:24:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>isn't there already a clear ring around that tho? i tried putting the small black ring around it and it won't fit, the coil won't screw in because it's in the way</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-27 05:43:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>The coils don't have bands. Of course i threw away my user manual like an idiot but i can't find ANY use for those tiny black rubber bands anywhere on the internet. I just changed the coil again because the bottom of the last one was kinda loose. Did nothing. Ahhhhgh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Fenway Park  #127345; #65039;eing dank as fukk</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 14:01:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 22:29:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>try r/idiotsincars</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-12 19:49:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>281 miles^</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-12 21:34:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>How long/ how much money do you think would go into it before she's up and running? Tough question, I know. Just really trying to figure out if i should buy it. I got him down to $150.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-12 23:09:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-13 00:41:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>i like the way you think</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-17 04:57:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Late to the party here, but there is this chick that I used to go to college with who put snapchat story up a couple of months of her and her friend smoking with her friends dog. The dog was literally in a BOX with a fucking hose coming out of it. That was the only air hole. They were just blowing fucking smoke into the hose. I messaged her and was like "not fuckin chill dude, not at all". She didn't answer, but about a half hour later she put up a picture of the dog with a caption "See, she's fine! Everyone stop freaking out. She actually loved it." Fucking idiot, huge loss of respect. I'm glad I wasn't the only one who messaged her, tho.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 17:45:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fun fact - Shaq only hit one three-pointer during his NBA career</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-29 03:40:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>If i had gold i would give it to you sir</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Piston ring help</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-09 23:11:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a 1978 Garelli Sport that i'm fixing up, however the (2) piston rings were broken when I got it. I'm trying to find the right rings for it, but the manuals only specify the length of the piston ring end gap, not the size of the ring itself. Can anyone help? It would be greatly appreciated as this is one of the last things I need to get her running. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-10 03:33:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks man I just ordered them!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ignition points won't open</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-10 03:41:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey guys, I posted earlier today about Garelli piston rings and my question was answered. However, I am pretty stuck with my Garelli. I bought a cylinder head, gaskets, spark plug, and now piston rings are in the mail. I'm super new to this so I didn't even check the ignition points when I first brought it home. I spent all day yesterday and most of today trying to figure out why my ignition points won't open. I move the flywheel in the marked direction and they don't even budge. Has anyone had this experience? I can't get a spark because of it and I can't properly gap the points if they don't even open in the first place. Thanks reddit!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-10 05:27:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's the best way to take off the flywheel cover? Is the tool to do so expensive?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-10 05:31:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you man. I wish there were as many Garelli how-to videos on youtube as there are Puch. This is my first mechanical experience ever and it's a struggle for sure</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-10 17:59:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for the response, but what screw loosens the points? there's a flathead screw behind/between? them that seems to only loosen the entire points mechanism from the stator plate, not the points away from each other.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-11 09:51:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>GTA at its finest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-18 04:09:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha thanks man I actually fabricated one out of an old iphone charger! Waiting for my new juul charger in the mail now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 09:03:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol to the bias here. McGregor threw a lot of landed, clean, tough punches to Mayweather in the first few rounds. This post, not surprisingly biased considering its the boxing sub, is disgustingly leaned towards floyd. Yes, he tired him out. Yes, he has more stamina. Yes, he outboxed him. But don't you damn take away Conor's performance in the early rounds.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 15:43:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's about it? Did we watch the same fight? Listen, Mayweather won. He outworked the fuck out of Conor. But to actually sit here and say that Conor didn't snuff the shit out of Floyd in the early rounds is insane. Watch it again man, I know you're here to defend boxing by any means necessary but the obvious bias is pretty embarrassing to see on your end. All those solid, pointblank shots from Conor and whoever wrote this post writes it off as nothing. "Floyd is smiling at him" in the first round. FLOYD WAS GETTING HIT THE FIRST ROUND. Hit pretty good I must say, and I bet you were shivering in $50 Money Team tshirt when it was happening. But once Floyd makes some connections, OP labels them as "vicious" and uses other dick-sucking adjectives that make you guys look so desperate. Idc that Floyd ran around the whole fight, that's his game and that's how he won. But holy fuck you are a miserable person if you can't admit that McGregor caught him WAY too many times for you comfort when he still had stamina. Grow up. Clean it up. When you get punched in the face A LOT more than the other guy, you usually lose those rounds. I'm not a boxing expert, but I think I at least get that #8212;fair enough?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 15:50:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>No but I think credit is due where credit is due and whoever wrote this post is so biased that they literally can't even do that. He WON those first 3 rounds. It was obvious, you guys are the only ones saying he didn't and it's fucking pathetic. Floyd won. He won by a long shot and we all know why. He's a master and he tired him out and then beat the shit out of him. But Conor was slugging the fuck out of Floyd in those early rounds and Mayweather couldn't do a thing about it. You're telling me that Floyd meant to get punched in the face? Or are you actually afraid to admit that Conor was quicker and more dangerous than him in the early rounds when he had stamina? Grow the fuck up, man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 16:46:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>To deny Conor his power and agility is asinine. He surprised floyd, he surprised all of you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 17:11:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't understand how you can try to argue that Floyd intentionally got his face punched in for 3 rounds. He had to switch up his technique 3 times to find something that worked. Jesus man, he's not perfect. He was getting outclassed the whole fight? What does hat even mean dude lol... You're saying he was outclassing Conor for 3 rounds by repeatedly getting his head snapped back? Agreed, he is the GOAT. But Conor found smacked him around pretty fucking good for 3 rounds.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 17:15:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love how you're saying that Floyd could have dodged every single punch Conor threw at him. Are you telling me that Floyd intentionally ate uppercuts and jabs and straight lefts? I'm sorry buddy but the only reason that he didn't dodge punches was because Conor was quicker and stronger than him when he was energized.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 17:22:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, he lost rounds 1-3, which was the point I was making. OP gave Floyd those rounds. He lost those rounds, fair and square. He got hit hard and often. If you think Mayweather actually won those rounds because you believe losing them was part of his master scheme then pull the boxing glove out of your ass.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 17:01:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 17:42:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn, retail doesn't begin until July '18 in MA</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 14:05:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>You might be the biggest stereotypical boxing hardo I've seen on this sub. "Yes Conor won the first few rounds"  #8212; awesome, that was my only point. Congratulations on wasting 20 minutes of your life typing up that passage desperately trying to prove how much you know about boxing. The only thing I was trying to say was that Conor won the first few rounds. That's it. OP said he didn't, I said that it was a completely biased opinion and all of you agreed with it because you have an inferiority complex when it comes to your sport. So don't say "nobody is saying that he didn't win those rounds" because that is literally what the fucking original post says.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ULPT: Low on cash and still want to go out drinking? Sneak small nips of booze in your pockets and order mixers of your choosing. If the bartender questions why you're only drinking soda, you can tell them you're the designated driver.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-10 19:41:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-11 02:28:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, ordering 7 Cokes in a row might be a little suspicious. But you could always say that you're just trying to stay awake. You also don't have to say anything, you're right. But you never know!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-11 06:43:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>[5] The way you phrased that just made me laugh out loud pretty hard, we'll played.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 00:28:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>This sub confuses me. Aren't doctors like these to blame when your friends overdose? He overprescribes, you get addicted, heroin becomes the cheaper option? Seems like a lot of you guys are celebrating it when you're getting hooked up but putting the blame on others when the inevitable happens. Not even trying to be a dick. Genuinely curious because it's a very confusing stance. Edit: Anonymous downvotes don't speak very well for your argument if you don't have anything to say.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 00:41:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>In this certain scenario, it seems like it is the doctors fault. That is an absolutely absurd amount of pills. I just don't understand the drug porn. If this stuff is ruining your life why are you gloating about it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 00:56:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great way to think, bud.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL DEFCON 1 is actually the most severe level #8212;it happens when nuclear war is imminent and requires the most readiness. DEFCON 5 is the least dangerous.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 03:57:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-27 17:05:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, OP copied my only post to make it to the front page. Nice u/BriannaBertles</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-27 17:06:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>First time being copied. Super weird feeling lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-01 20:05:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Negative, Anal beets.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 04:59:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahahahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 22:24:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice, stole my picture from a couple of years ago. Look in my post history, state is Burlington, VT.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 22:27:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>u/billthesmallkitten probably didn #8217;t. Hope he #8217;s enjoying those really ironic karma points.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 14:07:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>You sound like a really cool guy, would totally want to hang out with you! Get some help buddy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 15:29:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tape Deck Heart by Frank Turner</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lena Dunham smells like damp clothes and gentrification</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 17:41:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 18:25:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>The people want what the people want</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 20:43:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, because Donald Trump isn #8217;t the most hated man on Reddit every single day. What are you even talking about?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 00:43:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>What?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Did Michael Scott create ELI5?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 05:20:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lupe Fiasco very accurately breaking down net neutrality</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 06:35:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 05:01:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re a man who takes his garbage seriously. Respect.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>PsBattle: This friendly couple holding up a welcoming sign</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 05:24:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 06:00:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gay Retard is a wild YouTube name</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This Lifesaver killed and ate it #8217;s twin in the womb</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 19:03:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>There are two types of festival-goers</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 00:31:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Any Massachusetts Moped extraordinaries?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 23:35:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve posted here before, mostly last summer when I first scooped my  #8216;78 Garelli, but as the winter grew colder, my ambition to fix up my moped dwindled. I am SO close to getting her to start. I #8217;ve replaced all of the parts that I #8217;ve needed to replace and, from my very amateur opinion, the only thing I need to figure out is the timing. I #8217;ve seen a fair amount of MA posters here and I was just wondering if there are any of you out there that could possibly help me out. Since Lucky 2 Strokes officially closed, I #8217;m running out of options and I really want to experience my moped to the fullest. So if there is anyone out there willing to help, I #8217;d definitely be willing to compensate and I #8217;m comfortable driving to pretty much anywhere in Massachusetts. Please comment or PM if you can help #8212;Thank you!!! Edit: Extraordinaires*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 17:22:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re a good man</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 16:37:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah, my cameraman did. He posted it before he told me he was going to and I certainly would #8217;ve told him not to considering there #8217;s absolutely nothing positive that could #8217;ve came from it. I formally apologize to anyone I #8217;ve offended for trying to reach my goals and follow my dreams!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 23:27:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m sorry man. I really shouldn #8217;t be trying to aspire to anything. God I #8217;m a fucking idiot, please forgive me my dude!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>