<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject5935</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-18 05:28:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dont want to reduce the number of keyboards you have to use necessarily, bc that is part of the fun. But check out Synergy if you haven't. Mouse and keyboard sharing software, works cross platform.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-20 05:28:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>on the Das... They are the Rosewill Double-shot Greens + RGB Mod set for bottom row. http://www.rosewill.com/gaming-products/gaming-accessories/keyboard-accessories/rosewill-rikc-13003-mechanical-double-shot-keycaps-green-104-keys-with-key-puller.html https://www.massdrop.com/buy/28245</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-20 08:24:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, I'm enjoying my start into the Mech World. I'm finding it can be as expensive as guns. These TekMats just make great mousepads, I use my Glock one for actual cleaning. But, yes, I too have a 1911. *Delivery:* http://imgur.com/El6ugfj</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-20 08:39:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Totally agree with that, guns + keyoard combinations would be interesting and fun to see. I got it for free from a friend, it was their spare that they didn't like. But its this one: http://palmettostatearmory.com/bushing-compensator-stainless.html Edit: It came in that package, but it is not that one. I am guessing the 397 is what he replaced this with. Not sure what this is... but ill ask.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-20 19:23:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its actually a gun-cleaning mat. You can find them here: http://tekmat.com/handgun-mats/1911</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-22 21:21:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>They are DSA, so the option is there... i guess I can change it on Bastille day lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-22 21:27:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>sounds like someone is sour on the ole **red**, **white** and **blue**.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-22 21:58:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dammit, picks up phone, calls mom "Mom, do we have any Dutch in our Ancestry?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-23 00:43:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Nope, its where that dark blue comes from.](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/0/0d/World_map_of_civilian_gun_ownership_-_2nd_color_scheme.svg/1920px-World_map_of_civilian_gun_ownership_-_2nd_color_scheme.svg.png)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-23 01:03:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Didn't have to, she just showed up one day and said she preferred to walk across MX Cherry Greens... so I let her stick around.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-23 04:07:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe its how the set is supposed to come, considering its called the "[Patriot](http://pimpmykeyboard.com/dsa-patriot-keycap-set/)" set and manufactured by an American Company. I would say it's not really baffling at all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-23 07:55:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah buddy! Best friend has the Red Ranger and I have the Green. Surprised they have survived this long.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-24 21:52:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now only if you could control your Switch with it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-24 22:12:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>oh, well thats still cool then. Thanks for the info.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-25 00:10:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good choice, those clickity clacks are the best imo. I would also get different types(material) and styles of keycaps to test with each one of those as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 03:04:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Comfort Level 1000</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-14 00:02:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Curiouser and curiouser</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 00:02:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Thanks for the Quake beta key Bethesda, this is gonna get me some karma for sure!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-02 17:35:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love it. Easy to use and barely notice it's there. Used to carry a fat billfold that would accumulate a gift cards, masses of receipts and business cards. Now i am restricted to 8 cards I need and cash and couldn't be happier.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-02 20:02:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why would you not? I would never take a job where I cannot carry. Next you're gonna ask me something really stupid, like why would I take my gun to dinner with me... Google "Luby's 1991"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-02 21:13:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Appendix carry. No holster. And yes, I keep one chambered. Trigger safety is enough.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-02 22:03:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have not considered it. Been carrying this way for almost 2 years without any worries. I will look into it though, thanks for the recommendation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-05 15:06:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, nobody needs a gun, but nobody needs a cell phone, electricity, or the internet. They just help and we sure do enjoy them. The only thing anyone really *needs* are food, water and shelter. My Great Great Great Great Great Grandfather(that 5 greats) was an original Texas Ranger and he was sure as hell happy to carry a rifle and 6 shooter rather than not. Its been this way for generations. I was raised with guns and they are just a part of daily life whether you are going out to feed the cows or headed downtown for a nice dinner date, you had a gun with you. To help me better understand where you're coming from, I have a few questions for you: What country do you reside in? State? Have you ever shot a gun? If so, what was it, a rifle, shotgun, handgun?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-05 15:20:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are guns outlawed where you live? Are you legally allowed to own them?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-05 16:41:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn, that doesn't sound like a nation of free people to me... or very fun. Are you a "subject" in your nation? I also have this [AR](https://pof-usa.com/p415-edge/) with this [scope](https://www.amazon.com/Aimpoint-Minute-Angle-CompM4-Sight/dp/B001CJ2LQ4) if you want to come to Texas and shoot something fun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-05 17:01:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>On what part? Making fun of your nation, and you being a subject, no. just joking. Inviting you to Texas to shoot my guns, heck yeah. I would be more than happy to take you to the range and teach you how to shoot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-05 17:07:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>This guy knows whats up. It pisses excellence. Seriously could not be happier. Only thing I will say is its a 14" Barrel and you have a 2" muzzle break that is welded on. So in order to suppress it, ii will need machining. If i just take the break off,(also machining) i will need to get it registered as an SBR first and that costs $$.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-05 17:13:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn man, get a hold on em while you can. And I know what you mean, I am getting me a Radical here in a couple weeks when I go to Houston just so i can have something suppressed. If you haven't looked into their pistol variants, def do that before buying anything else.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-05 17:15:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reply to your Edit: Yes, you can, you just have to meet the 16" legal minimum for it to be classified as a rifle. If you take the break off and attach a suppressor, only 1 stamp for suppressor, bc it will still be a full rifle and not SBR.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-05 20:07:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>LMAO, you cannot get arrested for just that knowledge. If you ever do end up over here and want to shoot, like I said, I will be happy to teach you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-05 21:32:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why you no like death poking your fingers when you type!? lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-07 22:24:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Screenshot](http://i.imgur.com/NX2nbCq.jpg) I just wonder where he's hiding the gun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-08 13:45:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>You would have no knowledge that I am carrying at it is concealed dumbass. And if you did by chance happen to find out I was carrying, unless you own the property, or have some pull with the owner, and put up a 30.06 sign, there is not a damn thing you can do about it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-09 00:07:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are *quite* ridiculous, the only way you will see my firearm is if you come in a bathroom stall with me while I am taking a shit. If by some chance that does happen, I am sure that you would have to worry about a sexual harassment lawsuit more than I have to worry about losing your sale. Glad you can make Vendor decisions, but unless you have a 30.06 on your front doorway in 1 inch letters in both English and Spanish, I can enter your establishment and you cannot kick me out for carry a concealed weapon. BC 1. That is the law, 2. You would know know I have it, and 3. It is illegal for you to ask me to strip to see if I have it. Guess what buddy, plenty of your salesmen/women are strapped all the time and you are none the wiser. Learn how to America.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-09 00:31:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>oh, sorry, didn't realize you're Canadian and need a RPAL before you can buy a handgun. Must suck to not be free.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-09 04:47:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really hope you have an Imperial Star Wars sticker on the bottom.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-09 06:08:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well that works too. Nice idea. Pic?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-09 22:08:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>A fedora good sir, you are missing a fedora.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-09 22:10:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Caught OP in Library [typing away](https://media.giphy.com/media/bAplZhiLAsNnG/giphy.gif)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-10 05:49:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is a good keyboard, and you can order it from elsewhere, like [MechanicalKeyboards.com](https://mechanicalkeyboards.com/shop/index.php?l=product_detail amp;p=1896), for a bit cheaper(maybe not with shipping). I would steer clear from Amazon as much as possible for keyboards and keyboard accessories.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-10 06:08:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, 1. You will typically either find crap on there that cant be found many other places, or 2. The same manufacturers/re-sellers that sell keyboards and accessories on Amazon, do so at the same price or cheaper on their own site. I would rather deal directly with manufacturer or re-seller who has a deal with the manu. rather than Amazon then re-seller then manufacturer. I have personally purchased from Amazon, but that was when Mechanical Keyboards had a lot more products on there and most were Prime. So...Shipping, that was literally the only advantage to Amazon vs the MechanicalKeyboards.com site.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-10 23:34:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>You only flip the space bar on one of them?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-11 06:03:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess so. Do your thumbs get confused, or have you just gotten used to it now and when you swap keyboards? Like after a couple strokes, you know where you are or after 5-10 mins? I would feel like my fingers would get confused. When I swap to my Pok3r from a full setup it always takes my fingers a few minutes to adjust and remember all my layer keys.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-14 23:10:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very neat! Do you think you would ever be open to doing video tutorials showing the process on how you make them? I would find that really interesting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-16 16:57:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you like guns, I would suggest getting a Gun Cleaning Mat. They are basically the same material as mousepads. TekMat makes some cool ones at decent prices.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-16 18:08:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here is one that I own and use as a [mousepad](http://i.imgur.com/OKUc8Xe.jpg) so you can get an idea.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-25 03:51:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is the [Panda stack](http://www.smsl-audio.com/productshow.asp?id=123) too pricey for this guide, or just not something that you would really recommend? For ref, I have some MK3's that I'm wanting to push. Edit: Or are you just trying to not put it up bc its a jewel and you want to buy one, but want it to be in stock when you have the cash together?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-27 17:24:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right on, that makes sense. Thank you for the response. And I prob have it [sitting on my desk](https://i.imgur.com/HjF5KFH.jpg) now thanks to it not being on this list. So thank you for that as well. Your reviews are great. Live long and prosper. Edit: fixed link</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 20:22:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have been carrying with the Vanguard 2 Advanced for about 2 weeks now. I must say that I do prefer it to how I was carrying... Much safer and secure. Thank you, [blazelate](/u/blazelate) for the advice and referral.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My Green Ranger finally has his sword again after almost 20 years!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-08 16:13:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-08 16:33:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh no, are you Sid... from Toy Story?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My Green Ranger finally has his sword again after almost 20 years! (x-post /r/nostalgia)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-08 16:55:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Looks like Christmas came early!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 00:01:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 00:04:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha, my best friend had the Red Ranger and I had the Green. And totally know what you mean man, my Green Ranger has a [bald spot](http://i.imgur.com/tM0D6Ff.jpg) on the back of his head... but his [face](http://i.imgur.com/6ve0FPe.jpg) is good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Full grab bag of keycaps from the recent drop. (June 2017)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 08:16:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 08:21:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would say so.You can review for yourself though to compare. I went ahead and made [another post](https://www.reddit.com/r/MechanicalKeyboards/comments/6gdu3p/full_grab_bag_of_keycaps_from_the_recent_drop/) with pics of them all pretty much organized. Direct to [album](http://imgur.com/a/ROPtH)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 08:22:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have to agree, I would definitely say that the grab bag is worth it. Some keys are by no means exceptional. But you do get quite a few that are great.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 08:31:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, yes they are.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 08:38:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>tbh, I cannot tell material from PBT or ABS on these. I assume they are mostly PBT. I do have quite a few SA caps in here. I am a collector for what I like. By all means, look through and if you have questions about anyone, lmk and I will be happy to give you more info. To give you the true WAN color from what I have on my desk isnt that easy atm as I have been drinking and the its night time so I have a lot of unnatural light to tell me what they are. Pics are with a Canon T6 and the lights in my room on. Best I can do rn.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 08:40:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>For sure, as long as it is mutually beneficial and both of us feel like we are winning. I'm all for hooking you up with the caps you want as I just collect for fun and personal aesthetics.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 08:59:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nothing in particular. I enjoy the Camping Keycap set for the most part. Most of my keyboards have SA keycaps on them so I will be happy sticking with those. Not to say I'm unwilling for a DSA trade.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 09:35:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just checked and unfortunately dont have any that you listed... Sry. Closest my bag would come would be a 1.5 blank out of the 40's</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 09:59:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cheers to you too man. I am happy to share if its not something I want.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 18:15:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>sure man, that is one I am willing to part with. PM me the details.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 18:16:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you look through em, I am willing to part with some of the duplicates for you. Just lmk what ones you want and we can work something out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My Pok3r wasn't feeling well and puked</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 16:01:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 18:23:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, I enjoy it and think it looks super cool too. The only keys on it that kinda bother me are the "C", the "OO"(where . gt; go) and the "_-" keys bc they aren't made for that row. But i have gotten used to typing on em already and dont really notice it when i got back to another keyset on another board.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 18:26:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>don't think you pinged him correctly. I got you, [harjoat](/u/harjoat)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 18:39:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>[G O](http://www.jmlalonde.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/04/green-light.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 19:10:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do have a ton of keycaps left over from the grab bag, this is by no means all of them. But the variety of what I have wont fill in the gaps of what I want on this keeb. Overall I am extremely satisfied with the amount that came in the grab bag. I have sorted them all into snack or sandwich ziplock by color and some by keycap type. (I can upload pics of those later if youd like) Only thing I was a bit unsatisfied with was the quality of some of the caps. But that is to be expected when you buy in bulk as many were some that just "didnt make the cut" to be sold regularly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 22:57:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right! SA are hands down my favorite family of keycap.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 04:37:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Datamancer](https://datamancer.com/product/datamancer-oaken-60-keyboard-case/)... I got it during a drop on MassDrop though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My home lab is finally clean enough to photograph.(Details in comments)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-29 01:25:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-29 01:27:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Home lab is configured as follows: 3 x Dell C2100's running esxi 6.0 1 x Perc6i Raid Controller 8 x 2TB Old Dell Drives 2 x SAS6ir Raid Controller 4 x 500GB WD RE4's in each server. 3 x CS24-SC's running latest version of FreeNAS 2 have 4 x 4TB WD Reds 1 has 4 x 2TB WD Reds ESX servers are using NAS Servers for shared storage so they can run in HA and DRS. Networking equipment is all the Unifi line by Ubiquiti Networks. (I would only suggest their WAP's the rest of their equipment has a long way to go) ToR switch is a Unifi-24. Gateway is USG-Pro-4. Cloudkey for cloud access to unifi equipment. 2 x Unifi AC-AP-Pro for WAP's. Hammer me with any questions you have, happy to answer them. EDIT: fixed vmware product feature typo DSR -- gt; DRS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-29 02:19:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good question, friends have asked that as well. 1. Primarily air flow in between the chassis. 2. It is slightly easier to upgrade RAM and do work inside the chassis when they are not right next to each other. (Taking the lid off can suck when they are really close bc the rails only slide out so far before locking. Then you can unlock them, but risk pulling down a 40+ lb server on your ankles by accident. I can do a video sometime if you want.) 3. Easier Cable mgmt with more space 4. Its a 42U rack, I have the space, why not?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-29 02:39:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're right, in general it doesn't other than them being placed apart like you said(yes, them not touching helps as well). But it does help airflow in my case bc I have a box fan placed where I took the picture from... shoulda notated that. I cant really afford to raise my floors and run a true DC quality HVAC system just for some 10 year old servers in a lab at my house... yet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-29 04:59:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Loud... They are in a living room I don't really use.  #160;  #160; When they boot, it can get bad; otherwise its really not that bad tbh.  #160; If you have an AC window unit or anything of the sort, you can compare the noise to those. My 15,000 BTU room unit produces just about as much ambient noise as all those combined do.  #160; If anyone has a recommended "cheap" decibel meter, Id be happy to purchase it and get a valid reading for you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-29 06:13:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of them came that way, and aesthetically speaking, yes that makes sense. I purchased the red square ones separately as two came without trays. But from an engineering standpoint, the others(red squared ones) fit better and have HDDs placed in them. So i just use the others to fill the slots, they arent fully closed either so I know what ones are free. If you are wondering about "why drive placement" it is the wait the controllers are wired for the RAID configs I have and I'm too lazy to rewire them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-29 16:12:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you have a white paper or a KB article to reference? Or is this just your assumption?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-29 23:47:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>They work fine, but not great. The red square ones fit like they are built for it. The blue circles just require a bit of force on some of them, but others are just as good as the red square ones. It is like the QA process wasnt as good for the blue circle ones.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-30 05:23:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>soooo... no sort of documentation. Just a "tribal knowledge" kinda thing. [Smells like](http://www.reactiongifs.us/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/pile_of_shit.gif)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-30 05:36:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for your more elaborated answer, I do appreciate it. I still wont take your word for it until I see documentation from Dell or another manufacturer of the sorts. No offense meant, but if its not documented, then its just opinion. If we really want to get into it, I can setup my DSLR for some video and I can get some type of confetti drop to show the air flow(dont wanna F up my servers though). We can do some actual "lab" tests on the lab for airflow... if you really want to get into it. But like you said, its a home lab, it is for learning. I dont have anything setup to DC standards from power to cooling. TBH, I have more storage and higher licensing that 80% of SMB's out there. Yeah, it may be a small lab, but learning to build, configure and maintain vmware, MS and linux OS's and features for a small budget has been wonderful for my career.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-30 15:47:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Concerning 1U gaps, many people think that it improves cooling if they space servers by placing gaps between systems and cover those gaps with blanking panels. This is not recommended for Dell equipment. It is the higher pressure in the back of the rack that drives hot air toward the lower pressure in the front cavity. The pressure drives air through the gaps between servers and the gaps around blanking panels. In recent tests, we have noticed that the leaks between blanking panels have a more dramatic effect. Even if the gap size is the same, it is more restrictive for the air to flow the entire length of a server than the short distance it travels through a blanking panel gap." ^that is exactly what I wanted to read. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-02 04:33:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>What surprises me is the small amount of views of the video.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-02 22:43:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>"dont cut the face of the dummy Dwight"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Your move ASUS</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-11 21:10:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-11 23:07:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right. Like what that L1 had to tell me was anything even remotely proprietary.... or helpful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-11 23:19:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Scholarpedia has so much more value in it though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Remember that time Obamacare saved Fry's life</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-12 06:34:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-12 16:38:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://i.imgur.com/0yR5H5Q.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 18:09:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like that they put "Winning Keycaps" in 5 different bags. That makes it a bit more exciting. Also, last time I ordered they shipped out next day, and the order arrived in 3 business days. Ordered on a Tuesday, shipped on Wednesday via USPS, and arrived on that Friday.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 18:35:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Female USB plug(s).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 18:38:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here was my last [grabbag](http://imgur.com/a/ROPtH) all laid out... idk if you want to count them all though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 19:39:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will def be open for trades or sales to you when my bag comes in. I dont use either of those. Also, here is my [grab](http://imgur.com/a/ROPtH) from last time if you want any out of there. I will get em all back out when this drop comes in and take better pics then too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 19:44:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just got my [shipping notification](http://i.imgur.com/b44ACiK.png)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 20:23:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does anyone know, or wanna guess at how many bags they had going out this round? Trying to guess my odds on getting a winning keycap.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Grab Bags, girlfriend approved. (Story in comments)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-25 21:44:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-25 21:47:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I ordered myself a grab bag and was really exited to get it in the mail today. I told my GF about it the night before when we spoke and mentioned that I had to make sure I was online at 11AM CST to buy it.(She thought that was hilarious) Turns out she was kind and savvy enough to remember the website I mentioned, go to it the next day and refresh at the right time in order to get me another one. She didn't tell me about it, so it was quite a nice surprise coming home to after getting let go early due to weather.  #160; Perfect timing with [Harvey](https://www.reddit.com/live/zhq2dckl56k9) hitting and not wanting to leave the house.  #160; Moral of story, tell your loved ones about things you like and sometimes they will surprise tf out of you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-26 21:42:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol, I am a salaried employee as is everyone at my company. I am an IT Solutions Engineer. Closing the company a bit early on a Friday when our markets arent worried about IT purchases in no way hurt us.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Full-size Puke and a mini Puk3r</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 18:05:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 18:18:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>dont think you tagged him correctly: /u/harjoat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 18:41:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>oh wow, I got mine on Friday and it shipped on the same day we ordered them.  #160; Where are you located? I am in Texas.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 19:28:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well that is shitty... You are geographically closer to the shipping location than I am. Guess they could only ship out a certain number of orders per day.  #160; They shipped from "CUSTER, WA"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 20:03:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can agree with that.  #160; I just really like the SA profile and wanted those on both. The keycaps on these two boards are from 3 grab bags. One in June and two last week.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 22:15:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>[1976](https://www.massdrop.com/buy/nineteenseventysix-sa-keycap-set)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-30 01:21:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Pimp My Keyboard](https://pimpmykeyboard.com/grab-bags/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-30 05:57:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its the [Datamancer](https://datamancer.com/product/datamancer-oaken-60-keyboard-case/) case. I got it from MassDrop when they had they last drop.  #160; I will say that I cannot speak to the RGB bc i dont own one, but this Pok3r MX Cherry Green with Blue LED's works great.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-30 06:37:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ear plugs and blank keycaps = better compromise.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-30 06:37:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is no final. You are in this now, you are in this until death.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-30 07:58:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is from 3 Grab Bags in total. One last time in June, and two this time; one of which the GF purchased for me w/o my knowledge That should put your mind at ease lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I would trade my Plumbus collection for a ride in this thing (Austin, TX)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 20:26:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 22:19:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks mate. That is my daily driver at work. The Pok3r is what I use at home mostly. Put my DAS in the closet lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Explosion at a Refinery in Port Arthur, TX (9/19/17)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-19 21:34:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 05:37:45</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; https://github.com/qmk thanks mate! I guess i didnt just go deep enough down the rabbit hole from here: https://github.com/qmk/qmk_firmware</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-28 18:38:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>They're all the same mate. Don't worry about the numbers. XDA are a uniform keyset.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-28 18:44:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>for reference, here is my [Planck with XDA sitting next to my MK2016](https://i.imgur.com/PYxmYBS.jpg) with *mostly* SA R3 keys with R1 on the top row(s).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-28 18:56:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Positive ghost rider! that does work for getting the keys in the correct place.  #160; Still doesn't help with programming the PCB board though. If i want to create a custom layer or change what those keys are mapped to, I have to remember that they are swapped via the PCB paths.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-28 19:00:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>oh dude, I am a dumbass. I was totally not thinking about this the right way. Thank you for your clarification! Also, I greatly appreciate the work you have done making this project possible for all!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-30 01:48:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seems the only logical thing is that you must write something in [Planck](http://planck-repl.org/) on your [Planck](https://olkb.com/planck/).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Only roughly 10 social media videos out of 22k Concert goers?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-03 06:29:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just dont get it. I have only seen about 10 different social media videos that haven't been censored away. If anyone can help explain this or link me shit, that would be great.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-03 06:53:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Something higher than .05% of the ppl attending considering how everyone and their mom has a phone out at concerts in 2017.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-03 16:03:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, that [looks like a shit ton of phones to me](http://specials.mystatesman.com/kendrick-lamar-acl/media/secondary1-mr_duywfw6.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 03:06:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>thanks bot!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 05:18:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Found what you asked for: https://www.liveleak.com/view?i=956_1507066205</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 05:25:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>this was prob it: https://www.liveleak.com/view?i=956_1507066205</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 06:07:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here: https://www.liveleak.com/view?i=956_1507066205 look at the woman he goes up to at the :30 second mark. He then applies pressure to her neck to check for a pulse and blood slowly runs out of her mouth as one would expect in this situation. He then moves on bc the individual has expired.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 18:38:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>At least you used word-wrap!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 19:07:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Afghanistan is waiting for you buddy!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 19:25:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Had a Football coach in HS take a kid out a game and send him off the field, to the locker room for using the "N" word. Guess he shoulda just let him play and not hampered his free speech.  #160; Yes, I live in Texas.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 20:49:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>They put it back up now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 03:22:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just asked a buddy who is stationed in Seol and has been for the past year about this. He said he only read the first one, but he said it's mostly BS and that they have many video games over there as well as plenty of public gaming cafe's. He did mention that they can't play GTA at all. So there is some legitimacy to the censorship, but he said its not as bad as this post makes is seem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 04:20:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is it: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oSnu1HdXZ7k</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 05:24:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am guessing bc that is when it ended. They gave out the tip line information. The only thing we probably missed after that was a *that will be all* line.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 05:58:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Need help finding apparent video of Marilou Danley in airport acting crazy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 06:15:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>My gf told me she saw a video on FB yesterday, 10/3, of Marilou Danley yelling in airport.(No not the video of her arriving back in the US today) She said Marilou Danley was acting all sorts of nuts and clearly on drugs. She said the video was shared from a bystander and not a security cam. Any information or a link on this video would be greatly appreciated.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 06:21:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 07:19:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do we know? I would say it's too grainy of a film for a conclusive decision.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 07:51:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed. My gf just told me about the video and I wanted to see for myself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 16:32:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Longtime lurker here... just started posting in this sub this week. I think more people are here now more so than ever before bc the whole country knows something stinks to high heaven about this. I'm noticing that people are easier to red pill, or red pilling themselves with this one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 16:36:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is exactly what I came here to find out. Thank you for making this available for all!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 17:33:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed. The masses posting about LV is making it rough for them to keep up with censorship, which has helped I think.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-06 04:32:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looking forward to the Pursuance Project launching. With that type of communication, we will get a lot further.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-06 18:44:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>cognitive dissonance</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-06 18:58:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can someone show me resources for Dot.Obliterate (the apple iphone secure wipe feature they mention)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-07 01:15:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>If skyscrapers are holograms, why would TPTB waste slave resources on building them?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This is one of his more reserved posts.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 04:51:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Oh how the cookie crumbles...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-29 18:48:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 20:46:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Global Warming at its finest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 19:10:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was the MK2016 board from [MechanicalKeybaords.com](https://mechanicalkeyboards.com/shop/index.php?l=product_detail amp;p=1504)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL a baboon operated as a railway signalman in the late 1800's</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 21:55:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 17:20:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ubiquiti is "Enterprise" but i consider them high-end consumer to SMB and not Enterprise. If you get one of their Unifi or Edge lines, they should last you 5-7 years w/o issue. Check out the Unifi Security Gateway and the EdgeRouter X. Those may be options. I personally own the USG-PRO-4, but wish I could afford a nice SonicWall or Cisco.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 01:59:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>After reading this all I could hear was Darryl saying "You take them all at the *same time*"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cleaned up a place I'm Renting [2208 x 1242]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 18:39:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ready for Take Off!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 18:41:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 00:06:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you, I am glad you think so. I did it bc I have three dogs I wanted to clean it up for and it was very satisfying for me. Internet karma isn't necessary, I'm just glad it's being appreciated.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 00:12:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol, he still has yet to thank me for the work. First thing he said was, "well why didn't you get those last two blocks of the sidewalk?" I couldn't because my long hose busted and all I had was a 15ft garden hose then the pressure washer hose... I'm not getting another hose to finish up the job before I move out. I'm satisfied with my work done.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 02:07:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know, I know. I told customer service they forgot my "G" keycap... They said they cant source me a single keycap... **so they are sending me a whole new set of Solar Alphas!**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL that the CIA declassified German recipes for invisible ink</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 19:45:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 22:47:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why would anyone not? It is a link to a government website... not like it is any less secure or tacked any more than any other site you visit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 22:53:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. Tell them to reboot a minimum of 3 times. 2. Make sure apache is running. 3. Reboot the web server bc Nancy said that is what you did last time. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W8_Kfjo3VjU</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 23:46:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you please ELI5?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 04:43:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>oh noes! I'm gonna be an MK Ultra subject now... damn.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Grab Bags Back in Stock! Get em quick!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 19:50:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 22:35:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stand Off Wall Mounts</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 22:36:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's called a "[roundshot](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Round_shot)"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 20:59:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well... It does look like a [water bottle preform](https://www.alibaba.com/product-detail/28mm-Pco-neck-pet-preform-water_60296727240.html).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 23:40:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/mallninjashit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 17:32:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is an AR15 spreadsheet that some user posted here a few months back. I cant for the life of me find the google doc or user though. Wanted something to keep track of my Polymer 80 PF940C build. Also wanted to try and be as cost effective as I could with it. Any input is appreciated.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 18:07:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks man, I am really diving in feet first with this. Those items on there are just one's I threw in so there would be some data on there. I have already started looking for deals and such on my private sheet, still have a lot to decide on... But I did find me a PF940C in White for $119.99 shipped thanks to gun.deals, so I at least have a start!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 22:17:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>thanks for looking out, will def check around.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I didn't think they lived that long.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 19:25:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Submitting my application for the Space Force today. Can't hit shit, but it looks good.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 18:39:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 18:40:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wanted to build a Storm Trooper Pistol and figured a Polymer 80 would be the perfect platform for that. The complete build list can be found [HERE](https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1YQbp8_jJD8qIYJW43q32KRuguwmsHmHmbnIFFfw8LwM/edit?usp=sharing).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:40:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not a sticker, it has been cerakoted on. However, the guy who did the cerakote did have to use a vinyl sticker in that shape in order spray over it. He has a machine that helps him with all that though. Go to any store around you that does custom cerakoting work and they will be able to help you out with stickers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:41:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is cerakoted white. The original slide was black nitride and I had a buddy just cerakote it white. For the logos, he essentially cuts out and stickers and puts them on there before spraying and peels them off after.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:48:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here is the basic process if you want to learn more about it. (**Bonus**, he does the imperial logo in this video) [https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0I0\_7vvQ4M0](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0I0_7vvQ4M0)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I was told you would appreciate my Imperial Pistol.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:13:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:15:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>The black thing the gun is sitting on? That is a Glock TekMat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:22:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry, shoulda mentioned this is a x-post from /r/guns. It's a Polymer 80 build. I have a build sheet on that post.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:36:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Red and Green! Lol, no, I don't but they do make them for the 9mm.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:39:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>$39/50rd https://exoticammo.com/products/9mm-tracers-red-and-green-50rd-box</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:42:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Didn't even think about the blue stripe, that would have been a nice touch. My cerakote guy is gonna a redo it bc he isnt happy with how the back turned out. I just wanted to shoot it this weekend and I still think it looks great. But I may ask him about that when he redoes it all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:48:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can build one. Just go to my other post and check out my spreadsheet. All parts can be ordered online, no FFL required.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:58:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol, /r/totallynotrobots</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 06:15:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, and it's a custom cerakote job on the upper(slide) and the lower came that way. You can see my full build list on my other post.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 06:17:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just a stamp for the can. Unless you get a fake and just aesthetic can. This gun needs no licensing or registration afaik. (In Texas)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 06:26:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tbh, the slide is the only thing you'd need done custom. The rest I ordered online. And idk where you're located, but I like to get my cerakote work done locally. Google cerakote shops in your area and they will be happy to help you out. The guy who did this slide normally works on e-cig mods, but I just took him my stripped slide and he gave me this back. That part is not classified as a "firearm". Edit: go to my other post to see my build list.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 06:33:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>cmd+r  gt; cmd.exe  gt; C:\\Users\\GenGrievous\\speech.exe</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 06:54:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's an RMR cutout plate cover. I can take that off and put an RMR sight there. Google "trijicon RMR" and that is what I will eventually have on there. They're a bit pricey, which is why I don't have one yet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>