<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject6903</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-21 00:58:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nobody said anything about not being able to "enjoy" WDW without a drink, but as adults, it's nice to know where to find one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-21 01:15:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is this about? What do you mean? I'm going to Universal next week and I'm not familiar with what this is all about. I understand that Ollivander's is a Harry Potter reference, but is this a show?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>First-timer... Help me be strategic! (One day trip!)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-21 01:17:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>UPDATE: We've decided to add one more day to Universal, mainly because we'll save quite a bit of money by buying a 2-day pass and because we're staying off-site. We planned on keeping our last day of vacation open to hit up Disney or Universal, depending on which one we felt like we needed more time at. But, we'll have our luggage and it'll be easiest to store it with family who is staying on property at Universal then pick it up there before heading to the airport. Sounds like we'll want two days anyway based on all your comments! ----- I'll be heading to Universal Studios next week. I've never been in the park before. Any advice to help me maximize my time there as a newbie is appreciated. I only have one day, so I'm planning to do as much as possible, but I realize that will require some research, strategy, and planning!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-21 01:31:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a great tip! My boyfriend and I are going for the first time and we weren't planning on getting a photopass. We'll be on our own for most of the trip, but his dad, stepmom, and young siblings are also going so they'll probably get one. Good call!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-21 01:53:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I'm going with my boyfriend, but we're absolutely willing to be separated if that's an option. Great advice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-21 01:58:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sure I will. Huge Harry Potter fan. We left the last day of our trip open so if we feel like we didn't get enough of Disney or Universal, we can pick the one we'd like to spend more time at. Will probably end up being Universal by the sounds of it in this subreddit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-21 01:59:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh!!! That's awesome. Thanks for explaining! Good to know you have to go through the show to get chosen. Appreciate it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-21 02:15:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. Start counting your macros. It's hard but it's eye opening when it comes to knowing exactly what you're putting in your body on a daily basis as opposed to how much of each thing (protein, fat, carbs) you *should* be consuming each day to reach your goals. That also helps you plan your diet for the day easier, so if you really want to eat a donut, you can plan for it. 2. If you've only been CrossFitting a few months, it takes longer to notice real improvement. It took me a few months to just not "die" during the workouts! Stick with it and I promise you'll grow leaps and bounds. You won't be able to imagine doing anything else!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-21 03:50:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, I never *want* to shave my legs, but, you know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"I'm so sweet, rub my belly!" Just kidding...  #128520; #128520; #128520;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-21 03:53:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-21 04:04:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think that about people and pets ALL THE TIME!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-21 14:33:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>We're going for Christmas and based on your advice, we just reorganized all our fast passes and reservations to use this strategy! Thanks!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-21 15:02:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, people sure love to hate, don't they? I appreciate your advice. I'm not a complainer at hotels, restaurants, etc, because usually I know it won't matter if I do mention things, but knowing that they take them seriously could help them out with future guests -- and me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-21 16:01:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Amen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-21 19:19:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't see where to buy Fast Passes for Universal. It's not showing up on the ticketing portion of the website.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-21 19:23:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Found it! I added the tickets to my cart, but they didn't prompt me for add-ons, but I found the section for that. Good to know! Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-21 22:00:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't try to swap your Frozen pass. I've been trying to get one and they're sold out every day Dec 25-28.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 01:22:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh no! We weren't planning on coming back until later in the afternoon/evening, we thought that day trippers and people with kids might be heading out. I suppose with holiday parades and whatnot, it becomes trickier.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 02:20:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>So is it true that if you have a dinner reservation inside the park, you can get in? Because that can be arranged for the two nights we planned to come back...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 14:22:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>We get into Orlando around 10:30a on Christmas Day... we've read that Epcot has the best chance of not reaching capacity due to its size so we're planning to spend the whole day there. We do have a lunch reservation inside... On Monday, we're going to take our chances at MK and if we can't get back in later in the afternoon, we'll tour the resorts and check out the Christmas decorations. We'll go back to MK on Tuesday if we have to. We know the park will be packed so we'll stick to our plan of going early to knock a bunch of things out in the AM and we'll just have to be flexible in the afternoons and roll with the punches!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 16:44:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm curious about this, too.  #128527;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 16:50:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Splitting drinks is a good idea. Will cut the cost in half, too, while allowing you to finish in time for the fireworks. Good info!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Surveillance video shows 'Santa' passing out candy canes before robbing Memphis bank</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 17:38:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 17:44:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like what you said. It's VACATION. Right on, my friend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 17:46:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why do so many Memphis drivers forget that they have a turn signal?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 21:10:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yay!!!! Congratulations! That's so great.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-23 16:53:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which version is the "intense version"?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-23 18:15:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Congratulations! What a great picture!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>May be a stupid question, but...can't find the answer. Multiple tickets + WDW app...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-23 21:43:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi everyone! Heading to WDW for the first time on Dec. 25. I've done an insane amount of research and I think we have a pretty good strategy laid out. I also have a handy "pocket guide" with useful tips and tricks I aggregated from all of your threads in the subreddit! My question is... We didn't purchase all of our tickets at once (four tickets were given to us and we purchased 2 additional 1-day passes. They are all currently linked in my account in the My Experiences app... I've made all our FP+ reservations. As long as all the FP+ reservations are made under my account and that's where all the tickets are linked up, it shouldn't matter which ticket we use on which day, right?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-25 14:18:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've lived here five years and came here knowing nothing about the city and where to live, etc. Memphis is what you make of it! Ask questions, be nice to others, be aware of your surroundings (like any place), and be open to new experiences and people! I absolutely love it here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Got to WDW at 8 a.m. today and knocked out all the great rides without ever even using a FP+. Got them done by 11 a.m., so we could enjoy the rest of the day and relax!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-26 23:53:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-27 00:35:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>We are currently using Uber/Lyft and the experience has been GREAT!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-27 00:37:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>We went to MK today, busiest week of the year...got there when it opened at 8am and knocked out each of the popular rides without a fastpass before 11am! We were able to leisurely take on the rest of the day stress free.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-27 04:13:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you've never used it before, you can use a promo code and get your first ride free... on both Uber and Lyft. They are the exact same, just different companies and they run the same. We've had great luck with both so far in Orlando this week. If anyone else in your party hasn't used them, they can, too. Depending on how many new users you have, it can cut your costs down significantly. I'm happy to give you a promo code if you message me, because it benefits the person who gives it to you, too. ;) OR...if you use a promo code, then share your own personalized promo code with others in your party, they will each get a free ride for creating an account and you will get credits for every person who uses yours.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-27 04:15:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now that I think of it, if neither you or your girlfriend have ever used it, you can get four rides free (two from each company), plus if you share your code with her and she uses it, you'll get an additional two rides (one on each). It's a steal and much more comfortable and easy than a cab. No cash required.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-27 04:21:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Our trips from Hilton Orlando to any of the parks has been between $12-16 each way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-27 12:34:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>The crowds got pretty thick, but I don't believe they did any type of closures at MK. We took an afternoon nap offsite and were able to get back inside later. Crowds significantly died down after 9 p.m.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-27 17:57:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unfortunately, the latest Uber we've gotten was at 11 pm, but there are so many circling the resorts, I wouldn't think that would be an issue. Nobody else seems to be using them and there are a ton.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-27 18:00:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah! Definitely take advantage of being first time users. At Epcot and Hollywood Studios, Uber and Lyft can pick you up right at the front. At Magic Kingdom, have them drop and pick you up at Polynesian Resort, it's a 5 minute walk from MK and so much easier. We haven't been to Animal Kingdom yet so I don't have any pickup/drop off advice for that, but I assume since it's less popular that they can drop you off right at the front.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-27 18:13:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>This tip is saving our lives this week! Thank you!! We've been able to knock out all the rides before 11 at each park, go home and nap, come back for dinner and casual strolling while scoring some last minute fast passes for good rides!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-27 18:14:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for this tip! At lunch this afternoon, we were able to get Frozen passes for 12:30! We're finishing lunch now and our FP+ will be ready by the time we arrive next door at Norway! Best advice ever.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-27 22:38:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Space Mountain, Splash Mountain, Haunted Mansion, Thunder Man Railroad, Pirates of the Caribbean, Mickey's Philharmonic, Little Mermaid... we did the same thing today at Hollywood Studios...Tower of Terror, Rockin' Rollercoaster (twice), Great Movie Ride, Star Tours...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-27 22:38:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Space Mountain, Splash Mountain, Haunted Mansion, Thunder Man Railroad, Pirates of the Caribbean, Mickey's Philharmonic, Little Mermaid...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Have you ever seen Universal Studios Orlando close due to it reaching capacity?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-28 19:04:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>We're at Universal Studios right now and it's pretty crowded. We purchased an after 4 p.m. express pass so we could run home and pack our bags (leaving tomorrow) and stay later tonight when it might be less crowded and cooler. What are the chances the park closes and won't allow us back in? And for the people switching from Island of Adventure to Universal Studios for fireworks or the parade, are they out of luck if they choose to walk instead of taking Hogwarts' Express?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-28 22:04:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>We are heading back and while they are still long, the wait times are down from when we left around 1. Hope we can get back in!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-28 22:04:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha, we sure didn't time this right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-28 22:45:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep. Sadly, we didn't choose the date... my boyfriend and I are tagging along on a surprise trip that was planned for his younger siblings. We got some screaming deals though, so we really can't complain!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-29 01:14:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah!! We got back in. Made the right choice buying the "after 4 p.m." pass. We're cruising through the ones we didn't get on early this morning before the crowds got crazy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-29 01:15:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's interesting!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-29 01:16:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of the employees told us it's a ghost town the week after New Years.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Thanks for your advice! Top tips that helped us have a great first trip to WDW!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-30 00:57:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was my first trip to WDW and my boyfriend hadn't been there since he was a kid. I did some major research, mostly here on this subreddit, and the valuable advice y'all gave me helped us have the best and most efficient trip! 1. Get up early and be at the park when it opens. We were able to knock off all the rides we wanted without even using any FP+. If the lines are short, save your FP+ and rebook them for something else you'd like to ride later in the afternoon. If you get all the rides you want done, use your FP+ and tip #2 below to score the best rides again. 2. Use the app aggressively. You have to use all three FP+ before you can book another top tier ride. Our trip was planned too last minute to get the best rides, but we were able to snag Frozen one afternoon immediately following a great last minute lunch reservation by refreshing the app (modify an existing pick by flipping back and forth through morning/afternoon or different times or deliberately use your last FP+ so you can use a fourth pass on any ride you want.) We also rode Soarin' a second time the same day by using this approach! 3. Take a nap break! We went super early and hit all the rides we wanted to... went back to our hotel around 11 a.m. and came back in the evening for dinner and a few more rides or a show. We still got everything we wanted done but avoided the busiest (and warmest) time of day. 4. If you're staying off property, use Uber or Lyft! We never waited more than 5 minutes for our ride. Didn't have a single bad experience and staying about 20 minutes off property, our ride never cost us more then $17 before tip...even during surge pricing. If we had rented a car, we would've had to pay $20 to park at each resort per day and another $20 for parking at our hotel per day -- on top of what the rental itself would cost. 5. Split meals. My boyfriend and I split every meal and never left hungry. Portions are HUGE and this cut down on expenses significantly. Thank you all for your great advice! We didn't wait in a single line longer than 15 minutes and everything seemed to work out in our favor...it was all due to research and having a plan, but also knowing how to be efficient. We wouldn't have had a clue if it hadn't been for all of you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-30 15:27:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, we were able to book top tiered rides no problem after using all our FP+. We rode Frozen in the afternoon, then were able to book Soarin' for 5p.m.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-30 16:19:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everyone kept telling me that next week the parks will be "ghost towns" compared to how they were this week.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-30 18:22:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Welcome! I live downtown, too. You're going to love it. If you like lifting weights, check out CrossFit Hit  amp; Run... it's downtown, located on the South Main side. They've got a free class for non-members every Saturday at 10 a.m. if you'd like to check it out without committing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-31 01:59:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Download the free Walt Disney Experience app. You can link your tickets to it and make all your FP+ and dining reservations with it. You will never have to visit another Fastpass kiosk again, plus like I mentioned, if you aggressively refresh the Fastpass options, you'll score some hard-to-get reservations.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-31 02:00:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah!! That was the best advice we received! Longest line was 15 minutes and that's because there were six of us trying to do a ride together.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-31 18:48:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's actually Hidden Lake, located at the top of the trail at Logan's Pass along the continental divide.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-31 20:02:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>We just used Lyft this entire past week at Disney. We stayed off property and never waited more than 5 minutes for a ride the entire time. Our costs were crazy low, even during surge pricing, and pick-up and drop-off at every park was easier than we even expected. Happy to answer any questions you have!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-31 22:06:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I completely misread what you wrote as "Crater Lake." Sorry, you're absolutely right. ;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New iPhone case featuring the Grand Tetons!  #10084; #65039; #127956;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-31 22:10:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-01 16:20:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I asked an employee about our chances of getting back in that day, he told me the week after New Year's Day will be a "ghost town."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-01 16:23:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, I happen to think they're pretty grand.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-03 17:04:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Carved, Llc. They have a Facebook page. They do other things, too, not just phone cases!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-04 17:06:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Birthday party?  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-04 17:11:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha, I don't know. I was trying to think of reasons you'd even want one!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-04 18:09:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>They were also out of cauliflower, lemons, asparagus, and kale. And that's just the stuff I was looking for! Of course, they did have the huge bags of lemons but if you wanted a single lemon, you were out of luck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-04 20:36:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha, yeah, I'll have to come up with some stuff!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-04 22:55:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>The day they were out of everything was yesterday...Tuesday.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Great cabins to rent in Arkansas?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-05 00:33:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey everyone! I live in Memphis, but I'm originally from the northwest where there are always dozens of great hidden gem cabins to rent whether it's through the National Forest Service or an Airbnb type. I love weekend getaways to the mountains, forests, etc... and would love any log cabin referrals you can provide! Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-05 02:11:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>That view is incredible!!!!!!! Thank you for sharing!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-05 03:23:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why's that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-05 04:51:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because they're healthy? I made salmon and wanted a side. Tough to find a side when they're out of everything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-06 03:53:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>We went in the evening when the parade started and the line was exactly one hour...it was the shortest we saw the whole trip if you couldn't get in at 7am with the folks staying on property. I should add, this was the week following Christmas but before NYE, so we heard it was the busiest week of the whole year.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-06 03:54:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Us too... we were also told that the weeks following Christmas and NYE would be like a "ghost town," so they'll probably have better luck than we did. We were outside at 6:30am to get in at 7am just to see the place before it got too crowded to move.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-06 16:38:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's very nice!!! Thank you! I'll be checking that out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-07 17:22:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>If it was due to lightning, I'm sure it was canceled for the safety of the crew setting up even more so than the runners. That's a lawsuit waiting to happen. Runners may not care and might've been willing to run, but employees and volunteers....? That's a different story.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-07 17:27:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>These cabins are amazing! The one built around a rock and another with a waterfall view! Incredible. A little expensive for me, but I can absolutely see why! Worth saving up for unless they allow one night reservations! That I could do on the fly. Thank you for sharing!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-07 17:44:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I know what you're saying. I'm not a runner, but I saw that same situation here in Memphis when the St. Jude marathon was canceled two years ago because it was too cold. You pay to get there, pay for lodging, and that is just disappointing. I'd be livid. All there is for tourists here is Beale Street... At least the runners heading to Orlando have Disney World!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Keeping our options open...  #128514;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-07 18:19:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-07 19:52:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gorgeous eyes!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-07 20:05:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know. You're talking to a girl from North Dakota living in the south. It's hilarious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Keeping the humans up all night is exhausting...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-08 16:30:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 16:36:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is the $500/night average I saw for Wilderness Lodge last month due to the construction and high demand? Or is it always that expensive?? I'd love to stay there next time, but dang...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 16:37:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was there last month and we went to check it out... outside you really couldn't tell any construction was happening. The only evidence is that one wing is blocked off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-10 00:02:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yup. Me too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-11 16:38:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>South Main in downtown has some good AirBNBs walking distance to bars and FedExForum.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 19:57:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey there! My friends and I run a group called Memphis Supper Club, you can find it on Facebook. We are all transplants who have grown to love Memphis! Our next event will be a "brunch club" edition downtown on Jan. 29. I'm working out the details, but feel free to join the group. Memphis is obviously very different than Portland, in almost every way possible. Being from the northwest myself, I can honestly tell you that it doesn't have a ton of people who *love* the outdoors...there is a lot of litter, trash, etc... but Memphis does have great qualities and you will learn to love it for what it is... a town with incredible history, great music, and a lot of people who want to make it better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 20:03:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh -- and as far as church goes... Christ City Church in Midtown is fabulous. The pastors are down to earth and their sermons are well explained and easy to relate to. Check them out... you'd think the pastors all came from PDX with their beards, hipster clothes, and all that. ;-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-13 16:48:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is amazing!! Great work! It's always inspiring to see someone's hard work pay off!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-13 16:56:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Vacations aren't nearly as much fun when you know you'll be paying it off for the next year or five...because you're doing it this way, you'll be able to enjoy yourself and not worry about the financial side of things with a cloud hanging over your head. It'll all be worth it!!! Keep going!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-13 18:09:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>No problem! We're planning for 1 p.m. to cater to those who want to go to church before day drinking. =)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-21 22:16:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I was an extra once in a movie filmed in Utah... drove four hours, got a hotel room, and made $64 total for the whole day, but I did it because it was cool to see how it was all done and the experience...not for the money. I'm almost embarrassed to share what movie it was.  #128514; #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 20:17:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like that one! A few other music ones we've seen... Southaven Sounds, Southaven Soul...I think Bluff City Blues is my favorite "music" one so far.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 20:18:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a good one!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 20:18:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Grizz City Grinders!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 21:11:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha, that's probably why it had such a good ring to it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Our gym is a pit bull gym!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-28 15:11:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-28 15:35:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha, he's super sweet! Guess the stigma around pit bulls overshadows that...I keep getting downvoted.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-28 17:21:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha!! It's true. Poor thing looks at me with those eyes and I have to stop what I'm doing to pet him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-28 19:06:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love when people bring their dogs to the gym! It's not a typical workplace, but you actually do see more and more companies allowing pups at work. I think it takes away stress and they're a welcomed sight when I walk into the gym at 6 a.m. half asleep. It makes me glad I got out of bed to workout! Plus, I live in a condo downtown and I'm gone a lot, so I don't have a dog myself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-28 20:49:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are a couple ad agencies where I live who have dogs in their offices all the time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-28 20:50:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ha! You're good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 00:09:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>You assume it's my dog...I was just loving on him. No need to lecture me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 06:43:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course!!! He's adorable!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Don't worry, I wasn't reading that.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-31 14:57:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Don't worry, I wasn't reading that.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-31 14:57:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-13 02:02:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's hilarious! The good ok' days.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-13 16:43:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Carol Lott, she's absolutely wonderful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-13 23:21:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm glad you worked it out. I don't use the site to book campsites, we usually do first come, first served but it's always September so there are a lot less people in the park. We do, however, use the site to book cabins and it's the same stressful situation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-13 23:23:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>About five years ago I took my Mustang convertible on that road and it was a disaster...mainly because my car is so low to the ground, it kept scraping the weeds and rocks in the middle of the road that were higher up due to the deep tracks from other vehicles. On motorcycles, as long as the road is open you should be fine because you'll be able to weave around the challenging portions. Of course, it's a super slow ride so it takes a lot longer, but that's part of the fun to see the scenery.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"Just watching TV. Nothing to see here..."</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-15 13:48:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-15 16:59:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's not new. They've been doing that forever.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-17 16:44:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>For an entire month every year when they close Riverside for MIM, it completely disrupts downtown living by forcing traffic and trucks along Front St instead. We have a spike in crime, hit-and-run crashes, and trucks thinking they can fit under the railroad bridge. I'm not a fan.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-17 21:54:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://www.wmcactionnews5.com/story/31809331/festival-season-in-downtown-memphis-creates-traffic-headaches-accidents</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-17 21:57:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>And I've personally seen at least THREE trucks get stuck under the railroad bridge on Front Street just before Nettleton. It blocks the entire street until they can get themselves unstuck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-19 16:46:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're not looking to make reservations, you might check in with each campground's host when you arrive. They can tell you when people are expected to leave so you can grab a site on the first come, first served basis. Otherwise, check out recreation.gov to reserve campsites at the places you're interested in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Learning to knit so I can make blankets for NICU babies... this is my first one!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-20 16:00:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-20 16:29:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was my favorite part, too! He's so weird.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-20 16:36:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Interesting! I can't stand seeing people in commercials that have nothing to do with them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-20 16:39:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's our favorite campground...the one we all meet up at first when we're traveling from all around the country every September for our big family trip. Our favorite loop is Loop C. We go in September and usually have our pick of the sites, but August will be busier for you. If you don't have much luck, I'd check in with the campground host to ask if they know of anyone leaving that day, then hang out at Pray Lake until they leave.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-20 17:13:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>My friend started a nonprofit called Triple Heart Foundation! She had triplets very prematurely and created this nonprofit in their honor. Her surviving triplet is doing amazing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-20 21:55:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg. I LOVE nacho cheese cups. Reminds me of hockey games when I was a little kid. Fifty cents for an extra cheese cup.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-20 22:02:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>WMC is the official media sponsor, so they will push it out right at 6 a.m. on Wednesday. But like these guys mentioned, the Songs of the Day have been spot on for two years in a row: http://www.wmcactionnews5.com/story/34503133/songs-of-the-day-hint-at-bsmfs-2017-lineup</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sweet potato chicken cordon bleu tots! Food truck at a brewery win! [3024 x 4032]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-20 22:12:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-20 23:40:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry. I thought since I was just learning, it applied here since it could also be considered discovery, growth and it was also about something bigger than the individual item itself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-21 00:16:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gotcha. Thanks for explaining. I can repost. Would you like me to delete this one then?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 21:18:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>We went for a day and a half and, as adults, that was plenty of time. The trick is getting there as soon as it opens (or an hour earlier than that if you're staying on property) so you can knock out all the rides without standing in crazy lines. We were successful with this strategy at Christmastime. The Harry Potter rides should be done first since you can't use fast passes for those, but if you go extra early, you won't need fast passes for any of them! And they don't tell you about it, but fast passes are available for after 4pm for less money. We got the park hopper, but I think you could do one park on one day and do the second park on the next day as long as you make use of the early hour benefits!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>There is no denying that Memphis has some incredible sunsets!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-23 01:39:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-23 16:32:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>CrossFit Hit and Run, hands down. There is one in Collierville, midtown, and downtown. Downtown, for the win. Great community... Getting ready to start our Friday night lights workouts tomorrow downtown for the open. Starts at 6pm. Stop in to watch or come to the free 10am on Saturday if interested in checking it out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-24 16:42:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can drivers stop pretending Martin Luther King Avenue is a four-lane road? Just because it's wide, doesn't mean you should make it two-lane in each direction. I agree that it SHOULD be, BUT IT'S NOT!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-24 16:46:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do I get one? Cost? Do you have a website?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cat yoga is the best yoga!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-25 20:57:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cat yoga at Crosstown Arts!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-25 20:58:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 14:09:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>They weren't really down...  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-28 14:54:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cool, thanks! If you're in Memphis, there are a few resale groups on FB you could post in, then you don't have to deal with shipping. People will pick them up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>These best friends got the same haircut to trick their teacher so she wouldn't be able to tell them apart.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-02 01:04:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I had a photo post go viral last night, it's up to almost 100k upvotes, but my karma stopped at 6,995. Any idea why?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-02 14:43:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a fairly new Reddit user, I've encountered subreddits that require a certain number of Karma before being able to post, so that's he only reason I'm curious about why my karma points stopped despite having a viral post?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-02 15:43:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>On all my smaller posts, they did appear to be 1:1.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-02 15:59:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gotcha. That's good information! I appreciate your help!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-02 16:02:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, it was at GreatClips!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-02 16:58:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Huh? I just liked it...not a bot!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-02 16:58:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Google it! It's been picked up by tons of media.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-02 22:09:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>My post got 102k upvotes in 20 hours and I only have 6,889 karma.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Beer. Knitting. Coolest girl on the airplane at 10 a.m.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-03 19:36:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-03 20:05:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Flying MEM to CVG... it appears to be an option on all Delta flights.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-07 16:57:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Meditation nook!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Arkansas woman who overcame rare skin condition dies unexpectedly</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-07 19:37:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Barely fits in his tree and clearly doesn't know where to find the scratching post...my rescue kitty.  #10084;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-10 20:14:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Trying to design a rustic bedroom using a red, buffalo plaid blanket as the accent piece... Any suggestions for comforter/sheets colors or patterns?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-13 14:49:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-13 18:24:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>We got a super rustic wood bedframe/headboard. It's going to be awesome. Thank you for the input! I appreciate it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-13 19:10:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I rather liked your use of the word "crispy." =) Made me laugh -- and I knew what you meant!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-13 21:34:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awesome. Thank you! I love the idea about going white because it would be easy to change up the look to do something new with each season, but I'm also worried about keeping it white (I have pets). I'm leaning toward a basic, light beige coverlet and white sheets... then I'll add more flare with decorative pillows -- at least one (probably burlap) customized with something nature-y that will be seen first when someone walks in the room. The coverlet I like comes in all colors at a good price -- so maybe I'll do both. ;-) Every time I walk into a bedroom that has white bedding, it's so refreshing for some reason!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Booked our trip for September! Staying at Hidden Moose Lodge -- what else do we need to do?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-13 21:56:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Last year, we stayed at Hidden Moose Lodge for one night before heading to Glacier National Park the next day... we wished more than anything we could've stayed longer! Before heading to the park, we hit up Whitefish Distillery and rode the chair lift to the top of Whitefish Mountain Resort. We've tacked a few extra days onto our annual September trip to spend more time in Whitefish/Kalispell. What else should we check out? We like places that are quirky and awesome... and we never leave out the Bulldog (we are still tourists, after all). Where else?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-14 02:42:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Believe it or not, the blanket case from the Canada area at Epcot. I just couldn't pass it up.  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-14 11:54:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Excellent!! Thanks! I'll add it to the itinerary.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-14 23:40:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whoops. =)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 13:45:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now that's funny. What on earth is that doing there? Seriously.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Taking pictures of my sushi (who doesn't?), when his little head popped up at the perfect time...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 14:06:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 14:25:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, no way! Take out all the way. I wish I had those skills.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 16:56:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg, yes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Taking a picture of my sushi (who doesn't?), when his little head popped up at the perfect time...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 16:57:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-16 00:49:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's a needy, clingy, super snuggly rescue with a broken tail. We adore him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-16 13:02:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, you're a troll. And if that's what you prefer, be who you want to be.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Flower is bigger than the dog (yes, he's fully grown)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-16 21:33:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Melted wax adds to the decor on this bar...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-19 01:31:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-19 03:40:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>ME TOO.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #127925; "Oh, a sailor's life is the life for me..." This sailor is so mad at me right now.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-21 02:26:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cheap flights -- but rental cars are pricey! Any suggestions?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-21 15:29:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>We generally drive to Destin, but we were hoping to fly in April because the flights are reasonable. The only problem? Renting a car adds another $400! I've found shuttles that are $50/person each way, so that's still getting pricey... any suggestions? Are there any options I'm overlooking? We stay at the SunDestin, so it's about a 30 minute drive from the airport.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-21 17:47:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow. This site is awesome! I can't believe I hadn't heard of it before. Brilliant! Thank you for sharing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-25 00:51:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>You guys are super sweet. Thanks for being such a valuable and supportive part of the CrossFit community.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-28 14:02:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>While I don't condone monitoring people's activity, I do see that you've posted this in every state subreddit that I follow. That's called spam.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-28 14:03:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>This person posted it in every state subreddit I follow.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-28 14:09:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>You could really book anywhere downtown and be within walking distance of the stadium, but the DoubleTree is directly across the street and it's pretty nice for the price!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-28 16:49:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Spot on. Six months in advance and they will fill up. Of course, there are some first come, first serve campgrounds, but if you want the peace of mind, go ahead and book 'em!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-29 16:39:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, they're delivering it to downtown for you. Not individual residences.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-30 19:30:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whaaaa? How'd I mess that up? Thank you. =)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-07 16:22:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>As for your hammocks, some campsites are wide open and others are more nestled in the trees. It all depends on the campground. The more popular and touristy campgrounds seem to be more cleared and open. I'd be more worried about critters myself! You're brave!  #128521; Though I had a night-time bear encounter at Bowman Lake that would prevent me from ever sleeping outside of a tent...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-13 17:00:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was the best part, for sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-24 21:44:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah! Where was this exactly? Was it a rental?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ohio boy surprises his 5-year-old sister with a Disney princess photo shoot -- super cute.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 15:52:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Badass sweat angel</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-28 15:34:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-28 16:32:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-28 17:15:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is Kelsey.  #128540; You know, the whiny one from 6 a.m.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-28 20:03:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, don't be embarrassed. Own it!! Work hard. Who cares!  #128521;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 01:04:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you were a good internet sleuth (or had as much time on your hands as me), you would've looked at his posts and found the video he posted of one of his lifts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 01:05:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Absolutely. Shoot the owner an email and he'll work something out with you. Our gym kicks ass.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 01:06:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>For sure. I'm good at those too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 15:53:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awesome! See you then!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 18:08:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>None of my inputs from the weekend synced, so I manually added them this morning and reconciled my account successfully. Now, an hour later, I'm trying to go in to add some new reoccurring payments and the login page loads, but when I enter my info and try to log in, it just spin and spins and spins... won't bring up my account. May 1, 2017 2:59PM UTC [Investigating] The web application is experiencing performance issues for some users. We are investigating it and will provide updates. For the time being we are throttling mobile sync requests</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Baby sloth  amp; stuffed elephant become the best of friends.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 23:42:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-02 23:43:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I requested an invite yesterday or the day before... did anyone get it? I know I'm slow to the club, but I just discovered Slack.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My cat refuses to use the pet bed I bought him... not a big deal, but I just know he'd love it if he gave it a chance!! Any advice to get him interested in it? I've tried catnip spray and covering it with his favorite blanket.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 16:50:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-04 03:54:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's been about a month. Haha, I feel like it's just taking up space.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-04 03:54:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! We'll give it some more time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-08 16:45:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Belle's Tavern in downtown Memphis!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Any awesome downtown rentals or penthouses y'all know of?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-17 20:27:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm helping a friend move back to Downtown Memphis from Europe. I live downtown and I'm familiar with most rental properties since I've hopped around a bit myself, but a lot of the rental properties are smaller, shotgun style rentals and not many larger than a 2 bedroom. We're looking for something a lot bigger with a pretty decent budget (for Memphis anyway). Anyone have any leads for us? Again... looking to rent, not buy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-17 22:30:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're right. I have just the person to check with about that... Thanks for the tip!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-18 04:03:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's where I live so I'd like her to live out that way!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-18 13:50:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Amazing sign at a Mexican restaurant</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-21 02:44:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Child's missing stuff animal, 'Lamby,' sparks rewards offered from Oxford, MS police department, Ole Miss, and local businesses</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-25 17:31:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-06 16:45:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good "down home" meal, I'd say Silver Caboose, but it's in Collierville, one of the suburbs. Great southern meat and three, though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-06 16:46:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I second this... go check out the Memphis-Shelby County Room at the library on Poplar.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-14 12:45:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've never heard of the Conrad mansion. What's that about?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>VIDEO: Ridiculously long snake slithers from hood as pickup travels down roadway</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-20 16:06:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When you're drunk, but you've just gotta know!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-29 21:56:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>RECOMMENDATIONS NEEDED: Best cat brush for a cat who hates to be brushed?? It's hot AF and he's shedding everywhere!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 20:02:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Rafter drowns on north fork of the flathead river -- be careful out there!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-18 00:13:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Greetings from the desk of Sheriff Chuck Curry, For Immediate Release On Friday, July 14, at about 6 pm. The Flathead County Sheriff #8217;s Office received a report of a drowning on the north fork of the Flathead River. The victim had been rafting with friends when their raft flipped on a hazardous section of the river just north of Glacier Rim known as the  #8220;shelf #8221;. All three of the occupants of the raft were thrown into the water. The raft got stuck in the hydraulic below the shelf. The victim helped the two other occupants to shore. The raft became dislodged and he attempted to swim after it to retrieve it but drowned in the process. None of the occupants of the raft were wearing a life jacket. An initial search of the river Saturday evening by North Valley Search and Rescue, Sheriff #8217;s Office personnel and the Two Bear Helicopter was unsuccessful in locating the victim. On Saturday, members of the Flathead County Sheriff Dive Rescue team and North Valley Search and Rescue resumed the search. Divers were successful in locating the victim in about 15 feet of water in an eddy below the shelf. The victim is identified as Lee Alan Gebro, 44 years of age, from Minneapolis Minnesota.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 17:07:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Find some time to road trip to Polebridge Mercantile, pick up some huckleberry Bear claws and beer, and then take the road up to Bowman Lake for the afternoon. You won't regret it. Bowman Lake is one of the most scenic views in the park and it's one of the more remote spots so it won't be as busy as the other lakes!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Help me pick a room -- what's the difference?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 17:42:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi y'all! I've cruised one time -- a long time ago -- and barely spent any time in my room because it was the cheapest interior option. Now, I'm older and I suspect that I'll be spending a little more time in the room than before. What is the different between the different parts of the ship and the different decks? More specifically, we're about to book a 7-day Caribbean cruise on Carnival Magic for mid-December. Pros/cons of back, middle, and front of ship? What's the difference between all the decks? Deck 1, 2, 3, Mezzanine, Promenade, Lido, Serenity, Spa  amp; Sports, etc? Too many options for this amateur! Any advice is appreciated.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 18:08:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is exactly the type of info I was looking for... thank you so much for the advice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 18:09:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much!!! I'm pulling up the deck plan now. Great advice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 18:10:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!! The common theme here seems to be...avoid getting a room near the public spaces. Great advice about where we think we'll spend the most time. I feel like such an amateur! Thanks so much for your help!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 21:33:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! This is very helpful!! Nice touch with the pictures. Answers a lot of questions!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-01 02:04:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sent! Thanks! I appreciate that!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-07 17:29:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>The park is so busy these days, there will likely be a whole bunch of people hiking those trails, especially the high line. From what I remember, you couldnt hike it alone even if you wanted to.  #128521;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-08 19:16:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Since others have already offered to help, I thought I'd just comment to let you know that your hedgehog has more Instagram followers than me. ;-) Nicely done.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-08 20:32:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wanted to thank y'all for the advice! We ended up booking the very last balcony port-side and it happens to have guestrooms above and below us, per your advice. The only downside is that we had to make the choice between port-side and position on the ship, so we opted to go port-side instead of being in the middle of the ship... so we're at the front. Luckily, neither of us have ever gotten sea sick, so if we do... it'll be a first!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-10 15:18:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Polebridge actually has a bar, too, and the employees there often go hiking on their days off, so they'd be good people to hit up!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-11 14:02:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, I guess since you're in October, that may not be the case, actually. We go to the park in September every year to get away from the crowds...so in October, they will be even thinner.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ended up with our own private garden at a bed  amp; breakfast in Montana!  #10084; #65039;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-14 17:03:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-14 17:41:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Absolutely! It's Hidden Moose Lodge in Whitefish, MT. This particular room is the Garden Suite.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-14 19:52:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was one of "those people" who scolded a couple teenage punks who were running off into the trees on the trail to Hidden Lake near the visitor's center. Signs posted everywhere and they were up to no good. ;-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-14 19:54:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's not a bad idea. I agree that you'll most likely be able to find a campsite at one of the private campgrounds around the area (maybe even make a reservation), just outside of the park... then get to Two Med super early and wait for folks to leave.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Enjoyed our own private garden at Hidden Moose Lodge in Whitefish... 26 days until we get to do it again! Not that I'm counting. ;-)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-14 19:56:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-14 23:47:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Spin classes kick my ass when it comes to cardio, and I've noticed that my recovery is so much better since I started spinning again!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-15 16:40:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I, personally, would drive. That way you can make your way to the park on your own time, stop where you want along the way and camp where you want along the way. My family drives from Grand Forks, ND (4 hrs west of you) every year and they camp along the way. Plus, I know you're going to GNP to do the backcountry thing, but having a vehicle there is the way to go. There is so much else to see and you don't want to have to deal with logistics the entire trip.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-16 16:18:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ain't that the truth! I think it's kind of sad in a way. Watching this reminds me of a simpler time. There's just so much clutter now!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-17 19:02:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey! I'm currently going on Week 11 with WAG and I've noticed major changes. I had loosely counted my macros in the past, and saw some results, but was rarely consistent and had a hard time holding myself accountable. I think the program is worth it if you need that accountability factor. They give you the macros you should be hitting and they adjust them as you go... I started out with 145 protein, 240 carbs, 65 fat, and 25 fiber... They start you off at rather high numbers to see how your body reacts and adjusts, then drop them as they see fit. I'm now at 145p, 180c/160c on rest days, 50f, and 25 fiber. When I was weighing in at the beginning, my weight fluctuated between 168 and 171, and yesterday I weighed in at 161 and it fluctuates up to 164, so I'm definitely losing weight... and because they require front/side/back photos each week during your check-in, you can see the changes... I absolutely have results. Plus, my coach doesn't scold me or make me feel bad, just suggests ways I could do better or different modifications I can make... Your meals rely 100% on what your macros are and I've been able to get into a groove that has changed my relationship with food completely. I used to be a snacker and whenever I was bored at work, I'd go to the vending area to find something to snack on. Now, I still snack, but I'm totally OK eating a container of apple sauce or yogurt and no longer feel the urge to snack when I'm not hungry. I've been able to identify the boredom/hungry feeling and actually move past it. Today for example, I ate 2 eggs and 2 pieces of toast for breakfast, a chicken pizza I made myself for lunch, apple sauce, yogurt, all the black coffee I want, a diet coke, post-workout protein shake, and I'm planning to have an apple chicken sausage on a bun for dinner, with a dessert of gummy bears and pistachios to round out the numbers I have left, which is usually carbs/fats for me. There is also a private Facebook group for Team WAG members that has been super helpful and encouraging. It's a very active group of people posting their pictures to inspire others, their CrossFit wins, no matter how small, recipes, ideas about how they plan for vacations, etc. Bottom line... I love it! When you sign up, you have to commit to at least 3 months... but now that i'm passing that point, I'm absolutely going to stick with it. I was hesitant at first because of the price, but it's working for me, so I'll make it work in the budget. =)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-18 17:04:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm currently on mission to hold my handstand forever -- without walking. Looking forward to incorporating this into my practice! Will report back!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-18 17:17:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm going to Gray Bear Lodge in Tennessee in October. Very reasonably priced for a nice weekend retreat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can't put my finger on it, but I don't trust this guy.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-19 22:22:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When I nap, he naps.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-20 01:05:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Booking excursions through Ship Mate app... anyone used it?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-20 20:21:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have any of you ever booked an excursion through the Ship Mate app? Or do you always book through your cruise liner? There's an excursion that guarantees they'll get you back to the boat or they'll reimburse you and pay all extra costs if in the "rare" chance something happens to make you late. It's $40 cheaper through Ship Mate. Thoughts? Experiences?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I've never had a GoPro. Buying one now -- but which do I buy and why are certain ones not available?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-22 20:21:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Correct me if I'm wrong... The GoPro BLACK cameras are more advanced and more suited for serious videographers? If I'm wrong, let me know, because that's the only reason I've narrowed down my search to the "silver" models. I've also been reading a lot of the "GoPro Hero 3 Silver vs. Go Pro Hero 4 Silver" threads and whatnot... With that being said, why am I able to easily find a brand new GoPro Hero 3 Silver, but not a GoPro Hero 4 Silver? Every Hero 4 Silver I find is refurbished and costs almost as much as the GoPro Hero 5 Silver. And if they aren't selling more recent models brand new, why is everywhere (GoPro, Target, Costco, etc) still selling the original GoPro Heros? Bottom line... I'm OK spending $200-250, but everyone is saying a GoPro Hero 4 Silver is so much more worth it than a GoPro Hero 3 Silver... but I can't find a new Hero 4 anywhere. What do I do? I'm officially confused. I'd like to stick to the $200-$250 range because I know I'm going to spend another $100 or so in accessories and batteries. But, I don't want to settle for a Hero 3 if there is, in fact, a GoPro Hero 4 around somewhere and I'm just too novice to know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-22 20:52:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for explaining! So, basically it sounds like... unless I want to buy a GoPro Hero 5 Black for $400 or I find someone willing to sell their existing GoPro Hero 4 Silver... The GoPro Hero3 Silver is probably my best bet for buying brand new?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-22 21:06:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm really finding them on Amazon. I've got a big trip coming up in 2.5 weeks that I'd really like to have it for. I'll branch out my search and see if I can get it shipped quickly. Thank you so much for this list!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-22 21:08:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Memphis, TN. I admit I haven't looked on Craigslist or any sites like that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-22 21:17:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where would I be able to rent it from?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-22 21:21:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>That might be an idea... I'd be able to have it in time for my trip, but have some more time to save up for the best one for another trip I've got coming up in December. I'm just such an amateur, I'm not sure I'd need the latest model.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-22 22:07:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm finding some Hero 4 Silver options on Ebay in "like new" condition for around $209 that can be delivered before end of August. I'll probably give that a shot!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 03:11:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just bought the GoPro Hero 4 Silver for $250 on eBay...it includes three batteries and a Bacpac, as well as the plastic case and a few other extras. Hope it's legit!  #128563;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 16:41:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Glad I stumbled upon this thread! I, too, will be visiting in Sept.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 18:23:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>It looks like you had a great trip!! Congratulations are in order, too! =)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-24 16:57:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you're the asshole. A quick phone call couldn't prevented a massive fight.... which sounds like it probably ruined her birthday.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Challenge: How many liquor bottles can you fit in your pants?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-24 17:44:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-25 17:00:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can we talk about the Starbucks on Union Ave for a second? Using Union Ave in the morning is extremely frustrating because both directions end up being a line for Starbucks. Starbucks is not *that* good. Who is waiting in that line and causing traffic jams every morning? I seriously want to hear from you. WHY?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>love the colors and use of shadows in this shot of lake mcDonald</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-25 19:20:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-25 19:24:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Avenue is NOT a two-lane road. It should be, but it's not, so quit driving like it is. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-26 14:37:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeaaaah, I suppose you're right.  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 07:03:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!! That's exactly what it is. Appreciate the quick help! Now...I wonder what would happen to my cat if he were to eat it. Just curious.  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 07:08:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dang! Glad I didn't touch it. I'm cool about bugs most of the time, but this one was too big. We don't have huge insects up north.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 07:11:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Precisely! Once I scared him away from the door, he crawled into a crevice in the wall. I inspected the same area from the inside to make sure it's all sealed and it looks to be fine. But, now that I know bugs that big are living in the walls, I'm a little itchy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 22:39:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gross! I wonder what the spiders thought they were going to do with it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-30 16:33:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now I feel stupid! I hear them all the time, but have never seen one! I didn't realize they were so big. Thank you!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-31 04:18:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi Charlie!!!!!  #10084; #65039; #10084; #65039; #10084; #65039; #10084; #65039; #10084; #65039; #10084; #65039; #10084; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-31 21:28:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi Overstock! How about this one? I love a rustic look and buffalo plaid... I live in Tennessee, but want my bedroom to feel like a mountain getaway! http://imgur.com/m307bad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>He's like a dog. He will absolutely eat it if I turn my back for one second.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 03:14:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 16:02:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>This breaks my heart. We're heading to the park next weekend and while I knew there were wildfires, I didn't realize how bad they were until yesterday. That chalet is historic -- there's no replacing that even if it's rebuilt, you know?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 16:48:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was funny, so I posted it. He's always going to be allowed on the couch. If I cared enough, I could've eaten at the table. This post is not that serious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 16:49:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha, I don't want him to scram. I think he's adorable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 17:17:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha, it was a habanero chicken apple sausage with baked potato! But close enough. ;-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 17:35:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>My pleasure! I'm glad you enjoyed it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Northern Lights Saloon extended its season!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 20:02:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Northern Lights Saloon extended its season to September 17! My family always goes to Glacier the second week in September and we usually miss the saloon by just a day or two... but this year, they will be open the entire week we're there! I've been going to the park since I was a little kid and I've never set foot inside!  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 22:22:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whenever we go in September, it's already thinned out quite a bit. I would guess that Labor Day weekend is the last major weekend for the park... things are hit-or-miss about whether they're open after that. We love going in September! But, don't go TOO late in September because the lodges, shops, etc, will eventually start closing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 22:32:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>With all of that being said, I highly recommend the second week in September. We literally get Bowman Lake damn near to ourselves each year.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 22:36:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not worried about it all. I'm incredibly sad to hear about Sperry Chalet, but I've been to the park countless times during wildfires. This wildfire is burning a very small area when you think about how huge the entire park is, so the east side won't be affected, which is where a lot of tourists go. Going-to-the-Sun Road remains open and all the activities like horseback riding, red bus tours, etc, are still going... even around Lake McDonald Lodge despite that lodge closing early. It truly shouldn't affect you much unless you were planning on staying at Lake McDonald Lodge.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 22:40:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Absolutely. Sorry, I'm just seeing this message. I just responded to you on another thread. We're camping at Two Medicine Campground, Bowman Lake, etc... the park is seriously massive and there are two distinct sides separated by the Continental Divide... the Sprague Fire won't affect the east side at all... and it hasn't impacted much other than Lake McDonald Lodge (and Sperry Chalet, of course) and that's because employees live there and they didn't want them breathing smoke for another couple of weeks. For people who are just visiting, coming and going, it shouldn't be an issue.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 00:51:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ha! Nice. We're coming from Tennessee. Hey, neighbor! There are a ton of other campgrounds since St. Mary is only hard-side camping right now. Google Bowman Lake...during the week we're going, you'll have no problem getting a campsite and the view is absolutely absurd it's so gorgeous. It's my favorite place in the whole park. I can give you several other camping recommendations if you'd like, but that's my #1!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 00:52:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Another thought... if you decide it's too smoky for you (I honestly am not worried about it at all), Yellowstone isn't far and Banff is reasonable distance, too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 18:58:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Butter, chives, and a seasoning called Nikki's Hot Ass Seasoning.  #128514; That's it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 18:59:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well damn.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 19:03:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like people in the park on this thread are saying the conditions might even be affecting the east side by next week.  #128563;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-03 15:38:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm reading some headlines and I'm thinking now that if you're driving, you might feel it was more worth the trip at another park this time around. They're evacuating portions of the park and I have a feeling Going-to-the-Sun will close before too long.  #128531;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-04 03:45:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll be there next week, too. Saturday-Thursday. We're starting at Two Med and we've rented a forest service cabin near the north fork of the Flathead... so that should be interesting. I expect it to be pretty smoky, but the park is huge so we'll just readjust the plan if needed. We're also planning some time at Bowman. Just hoping I can get a scoop of Huckleberry ice cream in Apgar before fires get too close!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-04 07:24:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm right there with you! Will be in the park the exact same dates as you. I think you have the right attitude and we'll just need to be flexible and open to the fact that our vacations aren't the priority, you know? There will still be plenty to do and plenty of park to explore... I just hope that other structures in the park are spared and everyone stays safe. After what happened in the Great Smoky Mountains last year, its scary how fast conditions and the fires can change. Just be safe and be flexible. The park is massive and gorgeous...you'll have a good time no matter what! Plenty to do and see!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-05 18:41:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the update. I've been hearing that Two Med  amp; Many Glacier is hit or miss... how much you can see just depends on the day. National Weather Service is predicting a slight chance of rain on Friday... let's hope that comes through. I'm so worried about Lake McDonald Lodge, I can't even stand it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 14:06:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mom is too tired to even deal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 14:19:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>You'll probably have to take Highway 2 to St. Mary and the east side of the park. You're not going to be able to drive by Lake McDonald. You can stop in Apgar if you'd like to see the lake...it's got a beach and a great view. Stop at Eddy's for huckleberry ice cream while you're there. I'd imagine that the campsite hosts might frown upon you sleeping in your car in the campground's parking lot. But, I'm not sure. It wouldn't hurt to just roll up to the site host and ask... I would assume that it's probably comparable to someone parking their RV in the parking lot instead of renting a site. Of course, the folks who do the backcountry camping have to park their cars somewhere. I'm sure you can find someone to ask in the park when you get there. I'll be in Glacier next week, too. I'm glad you're not letting the fires ruin your trip, but I do hope you'll come back to see it in all of its glory another time, too! The views are incredible and I don't want you to be disappointed because they won't be as spectacular this time around. I've heard the east side is smokier some days and clearer on other days... Many Glacier, I've also heard, is one of the clearer places you could check out. As of right now, I don't think the Highline is closed...I've been scouring the headlines and I haven't read that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Any Montana news stations streaming the announcements and public meetings about the fires?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 16:26:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm very interested in watching the public meeting on the Sprague Fire scheduled for tonight at 7 p.m., but I'm not familiar with Montana news outlets... which one would be most likely to stream the meeting? Have any been streaming the announcements daily? Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I miss this sweet little cat every day. We had 20 snuggly years together.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 20:02:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>GoPro Plus...without a GoPro 5?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 20:08:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just bought a GoPro Silver 4... and thought the cloud functionality would be awesome, only to find out that the auto-upload only works with a GoPro 5. Ok, amateur mistake. Should've done my research... so the question is... if you don't have a GoPro 5, what is GoPro Plus good for? Is it worth the money? Sidebar... I'd love to edit videos rather than just the simple splicing options available with GoPro's editing tools, but the software recommended doesn't seem to work on my Surface 3 (my computer isn't badass enough to handle all the fancy editing software). Can anyone recommend an editing software (free, preferably) that an average computer would be able to handle but isn't just your boring hard edit capabilities?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 20:11:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wanted to say THANKS again! I got my GoPro Silver 4 and it's in perfect condition and the picture quality is fabulous. I sincerely appreciate you guiding me through the process of picking the right one!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 20:23:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good info!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 20:47:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>They do... that's how I found out about the public meeting, but it didn't have any info about how to watch it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 20:47:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I'll look into that software!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-07 12:34:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>It keeps giving me error messages though when I try to upload via desktop. It took all damn night being on the phone with support and trying to upload my video to the cloud using Quik. And the videos weren't even long or large files. I tested out my camera at a football game last weekend. They're just short bullshit clips. I'm so frustrated! She told me on the phone it's probably because I was pulling the files off of my external hard drive rather than my camera directly. She also told me I should use Quik not desktop.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-07 12:38:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm having a hard time watching my videos playback. They freeze up. It's probably because my Surface isn't powerful enough. I've had this same issue with the other editing program I tried.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-07 16:21:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm using Resolve 14, Public Beta. I'm pretty sure my resolution and frame rate are the default... probably highest, because I haven't touched any settings yet. I just got my GoPro and shot some clips over the weekend so I could get used to it and figure out the editing process before a trip I'm taking this weekend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Workflow help needed... I have a Surface 3, iPad, and iPhone... please help if you can!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-07 17:30:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just bought a GoPro Silver 4. I used it last weekend and recorded about 12 pretty short clips so I can get used to it and figure out best practices for easy editing, etc, before a trip I have next week. I'm running into several problems getting the footage off of my GoPro and available to edit anywhere. 1. iPhone apparently doesn't have enough space no matter how much I delete to download a single clip, even a short one. 2. iPad has the same problem even though I have no other photos/videos on it. 3. Surface doesn't have enough space. So, I put the files on an external hard-drive. 4. When they're on an external hard-drive, I can't edit them with any type of real editing software because my Surface can't handle it. 5. I decided to try GoPro Plus so I might be able to edit them on my iPhone or iPad by accessing them in the cloud... but I can't seem to get any of my videos uploaded to the GoPro Plus cloud. I keep receiving error messages when I try to upload them manually via Desktop. When I tried to upload them via Quik App last night, it took several hours and it appeared to be complete, but the clips still haven't shown up in the cloud. I was on the phone with GoPro Support last night and she told me it would work if I tried uploading to Quik directly from my camera. It didn't. I don't have another couple of hours to wait on GoPro Support only to have them tell me something stupid. So, I'm here begging for help. I've invested way too much time in just trying to figure out how to go about making even simple edits using the computer, phone, and tablets I have... and we're not even talking about long clips right now. I'm about to go on a trip where I'll be filming long hikes and drives! I'd love to know I'm actually going to be able to do something with this footage when I get home. Please help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-07 17:46:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, I did try the web uploader first. It fails for the "larger" files and it appears to work for the smaller ones, but then they disappear and never show up in the cloud. Even my "larger" files really aren't as big as you'd expect from GoPro footage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-07 19:30:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>iPhone: 28gb iPad: 12gb Getting a new computer probably isn't an option right now... Good to know about GoPro Plus. I knew the auto-upload from camera only worked for the Hero5, but I thought I'd still be able to manually transfer videos. Sounds like I'll probably just have to invest in some other cloud storage in order to edit with Pinncale or something on my iPad or iPhone unless I want to edit one clip for a quick share moment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 03:52:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I'll look into that!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>We will get to Glacier Park...and nothing -- not wildfires or Delta AirLines -- is going to stop us.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 14:08:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Our flight was supposed to leave at 8 a.m., but Delta delayed the flight one hour due to a "pilot rest" issue. The one-hour delay would cause us to miss our connection to Kalispell and the only other flight would put us in at 10 p.m. Unwilling to miss a full day in the park and set up camp at midnight, we canceled...and rebooked last minute on United. This is the one trip we take every September and we look forward to it more than any other vacation we take. Nothing....and I mean, nothing is going to stop us from coming, let alone miss even one damn day in my favorite place. P.S. My parents met working at Glacier NP... I can honestly thank GNP for my life.  #128514; See you soon, Glacier! We've been missing you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-15 20:46:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>The park never closed due to fire. One section of Going-to-the-Sun closed. The rest of the park is open and accessible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This bar and restaurant's website is fart-slobber.com.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-17 18:06:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The warning label on this ladder</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 14:23:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-28 19:22:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was rude.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-28 19:22:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Amen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-28 19:24:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you spend the money on that alcohol package instead, hopefully you'll drink enough to where you'll just pass right out anyway! ;-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-28 19:26:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Absolutely. Make it happen!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-28 19:27:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm glad you came to those realizations! I know this is Reddit and all, but nobody likes "that guy" except... "those guys."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-28 19:49:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>How is wanting to be active on Reddit by asking a question rude? Give me a break. 99% of everything on Reddit could be googled. Get over it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Property management company suggestions?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 16:41:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>We're about to buy a new condo and will be looking to rent our current condo out in Downtown Memphis. I'm about to start researching, but would also like to hear your recommendations and personal experiences with individual companies. I'd appreciate any insight y'all can provide!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 16:50:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or... a bed for two.  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 16:52:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know about you guys, but I upvoted this simply for the fact that your shirt is AWESOME.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 16:57:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any specific reason? Or just overall terribleness?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 17:19:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good to know. Thank you so much for your input!! I appreciate it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 20:12:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mine too. I got him as an adult and have had zero luck getting him out of this habit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 20:14:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got my cat as an adult... so he had already developed this habit. So far, nothing has worked to get him to stop. He's very obvious when he's about to pounce at my arm because he whines like he's begging for something, then he pounces. I always push him off the bed, so he *should* get the drift, but it hasn't stopped the behavior.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 20:15:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope!! I'd do it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 22:02:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you. I'll give it a shot! ANYYYYTHING!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Port itinerary changes, lots of cancellations... can i use this information to receive onboard credit on carnival?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 17:30:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>We're cruising with Carnival on Dec. 16. We've already received an email that our port itinerary has changed significantly due to the recent hurricanes. A lot of people in our Facebook group have decided to cancel as a result. We're still going... but I was wondering if there was a way to receive onboard credit since I don't plan to cancel? Any advice?? **UPDATE: Due to the number of people canceling, it appears Carnival dropped its prices, so I was able to receive an onboard credit for the difference of the price drop.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 19:11:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>We actually don't board until December... so I was thinking with so many people cancelling, they'll drop the rates or something along those lines. I just don't know if they're known for price matching the new deals since we booked a few months ago.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 19:12:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Personally, I don't mind the itinerary change at all. I still haven't been to any of the ports we're going to now... I was just wondering if there is any chance that the cancellations could cause a price drop that I might be able to benefit from and the best way to go about checking on that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 19:13:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're probably right. I think my best bet is to just monitor the rates and wait for a significant price drop or something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 20:28:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been trying to check... the Carnival website is down right now (of course). But I'm finding it hard to find my exact cabin in order to check base price on that. I also read that if you have already paid for your whole cruise, you're basically screwed... which is unfortunate. You would think paying it off early would be looked upon as a good thing -- but it looks like that just hurts you when it comes to price drops.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>We had a smokey view for our annual trip in september... so we booked schnaus again for january...can't wait to see it in the winter!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 20:49:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 22:45:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm pretty sure we got the early saver program... Thanks for the guidance on CruiseCritic! I'll check that out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 19:27:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know why you're being rude... The itinerary change has led to a lot of people canceling their trips, so the cruise line is dropping the price in an attempt to fill the ship. Why should I have to pay a higher price just because I booked it in advance and opted not to cancel like everyone else? By the way, I did get a $200 credit because of the price drop and because I was an "Early Saver," so you can go ahead and pay more if that's what you want to do, but money doesn't grow on trees for the rest of us.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 19:28:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the info everyone. I called and was able to get a $200 onboard credit due to the price drop, most likely caused by other people canceling.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 19:33:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I found on Carnival that the price of my room dropped $200... I called, politely asked them to price match it, and they did because we were part of the "Early Saver" program for booking early.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 23:04:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Schnaus Cabin up near Polebridge! Not technically inside the park, but super close to the Bowman entrance and stunning views of the park from the porch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 19:54:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's the cruise I'll be on! I also read that there is a good chance they could switch the ports back to the normal itinerary because I'm hearing that they might be ready by then.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 22:21:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your shower tip is great!!! That's very helpful and one I hadn't heard yet! Appreciate it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cozy hammock surrounded by woods and trees.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 14:31:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 22:15:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Carnival Magic, Dec. 16-24 Hollaaaaaaa!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Best car service to get to Port Canaveral in Orlando?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 22:25:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>We #8217;re flying into MCO and were curious about whether any of you can recommend a good car service to get us to Port? We don #8217;t want to take a shuttle...we prefer a private car. Thank you in advance for any guidance you can provide!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-24 16:58:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope! It #8217;s a cabin you rent for yourself, but it fits a lot of people with a ton of twin beds in an upstairs loft and a couple of double beds downstairs Here #8217;s the link: https://www.recreation.gov/camping/schnaus-cabin/r/campgroundDetails.do?contractCode=NRSO amp;parkId=75207</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 21:48:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually, kids under 3 years old don't need a ticket! You'd just have to pay for yourself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 22:04:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Solid advice. =)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 22:16:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you book it early enough... and are part of the "Early Savers" program, you are eligible for price matches... so if you notice the price drops later on your room category, they will match it and reimburse you in the form of onboard credit, which can be used if you purchase the Cheers package while on board, or at the spa, gift shops, etc. I'm going on a Carnival cruise on Dec. 16 and I now have $400 in onboard credit simply because I paid attention to the prices and called them when I noticed a drop.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Polebridge in January... do we need 4-wheel drive?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 22:19:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>We're renting a forest service cabin near Polebridge in January... do I need to have an intermediate SUV to drive those roads in the winter? Or would a small SUV or car work out just fine (smaller rentals are sooo much cheaper)? Any guidance is appreciated! Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 15:13:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks y #8217;all. Very good advice. We opted for the full-size SUV... and as for the  #8220;don #8217;t go to Polebridge #8221; warning... that #8217;s not an option. The entire reason for our trip is to see our favorite cabin (Schnaus) in the winter. I do appreciate the heads up about how the rental companies will react, so I #8217;ll keep it on the d/l that I plan to break their rules. I also have rental insurance through my insurance company... needless to say, we #8217;re ready to take the risk. My dad is meeting us and being from North Dakota, he #8217;ll be prepared for whatever comes our way so at least if something happens, we won #8217;t be alone in the middle of nowhere.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 15:16:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Schnaus Cabin! It #8217;s our favorite.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Grammar matters.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 22:30:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 21:41:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>This does not work. Don't fall for it. Waste of your time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 18:07:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I read an article this morning that said national parks that charge admission fees will stay open. I sure hope that #8217;s the case... I #8217;m on my way to Glacier National Park right now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 18:15:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sometimes you have to book the day before, too, just to make sure you get the days you want. The website is crap and it isn #8217;t fair to anyone that it comes down to that... but as long as they allow people to book three days at once, it #8217;s what people do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 01:13:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Creepy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hates having his picture taken, but he chose to sit there so...  #128248;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 00:35:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 03:04:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I kinda love him.  #10084; #65039; #10084; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My cat acts weird in the mornings...what #8217;s going on?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-22 14:48:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>My cat, Morrison, is so sweet and snuggly most of the time. He follows us around the condo and finds our laps the second we sit down... However, in the mornings he #8217;s become a different animal. Around 7:30a, he will start to almost growl (it #8217;s still a meow but lasts longer and sounds different than his happy meow) at me and attack my arms. I can see it in his face when it #8217;s about to happen, so I #8217;ll move my arms when he jumps and he immediately jumps off the bed. When I finally get up, he #8217;ll chase me and swipe at my feet and ankles. Why is he doing this? It just started a few weeks ago. His food bowl is full. His water dish is full. He #8217;s not hurting me at all, but what #8217;s he trying to tell me??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-22 15:41:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>[UPDATE: Video of this behavior from this morning](https://www.dropbox.com/s/bte6ntk8nxlo3l0/Video%20Feb%2022%2C%208%2026%2011%20AM.mov?dl=0)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-22 22:56:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>You may be right... i guess he doesn #8217;t do it on weekends, so that makes sense. I #8217;ve played with him a little bit here and there before I leave, but probably not enough. He #8217;s about 3 years old... no, he doesn #8217;t go outside.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 14:21:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t blame you for not wanting to pay her, but look at the big picture here... Is it hard for you to find people to watch your bearded dragons? She was willing to do it...and stay at your house. Your friend got sick... she couldn #8217;t help it. She didn #8217;t leave the house a disaster. Her friend did. I #8217;m sure A is mortified. First ask yourself if you will ever need to ask for her help watching your dragons again....and that could help you make your decision. I #8217;d let it go and pay her but explain that her friend did a shit job cleaning up it actually cost you more money. Don #8217;t pay the  #8220;friend. #8221; A can decide if she wants to pay her friend out of the money you pay her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 18:41:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cyndii Joe Hartley at Salon Lulu does my hair. After trying so many people in the six years I've been in Memphis, I'm so glad I finally found her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 18:42:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I third this... they're amazing. And they always remember who I am when I call, know my vehicle, and remember the last maintenance they did on it. Last time I was in there, they remembered which two tires we replaced before even pulling it up on the computer. I didn't even remember that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 14:20:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s disappointing NPS doesn #8217;t have the money to turn them into cabins to rent like they did with several Forest Service cabins. That #8217;s a great way to preserve them, while at the same time allowing others to enjoy and appreciate the history of each cabin. The funding provided to NPS is shameful and only continues to break my heart.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The triangle ice cube in this cocktail caved in...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 02:21:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 05:50:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s exactly what I thought!!! My boyfriend didn #8217;t see the  #8220;egg yolk #8221; so I didn #8217;t include it in the caption because I felt crazy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 15:00:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, agree with the majority of people who already commented. You #8217;re seriously fighting with someone via text about whether a meme was appropriate. That #8217;s the stupidest thing I #8217;ve ever seen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Heading to Hot Springs this weekend -- would love your suggestions!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 17:09:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been to Hot Springs a few times and I'm coming back this weekend, but bringing a friend who has never been... I'm familiar with all of the touristy spots, but would like to hear your recommendations for some more gems that are off the beaten path... restaurant recommendations? Things to do other than spas? Also, we'd like to go on a hike or two... any recommendations for nearby trails that aren't going to be the super busy touristy ones? We'd like to see sights and get great photos (she's a photographer), but would like to avoid hiking with 100 other people if possible. Thank you in advance for your advice! Kels</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 02:54:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awesome!!! Thanks for the suggestions!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 09:59:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you #8217;re not wanting to be his friend after he confessed his feelings for you, it sounds like you weren #8217;t that good of friends in the first place. Sounds like I #8217;m in the minority here, but I kind of think you #8217;re being an over sensitive asshole by not at least having a conversation with him to tell him straight up how it made you feel. I know I #8217;ve gotten drunk and said things that felt appropriate at the time only to wake up and have that  #8220;oh shit #8221; feeling. It #8217;s the worst. I #8217;d give him a shot, but for fuck sake, if you #8217;re not interested, do not  #8212; I repeat  #8212; do not let the guy sleep in your bed and cuddle! That does make you an asshole.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 10:01:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Judging by the flag and the Prisoner of War tire cover on the back, he #8217;s simply trying to show his support for the troops or make a political statement  #8212; in a unique way. The gun might be an odd choice (especially in Memphis), but I doubt he #8217;s trying to incite terror.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 10:04:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Take it down.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 13:38:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>You asked our opinion so I #8217;m not sure why you #8217;re arguing and getting defensive when you get a response you don #8217;t like. I think my reasoning was pretty clear.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 13:20:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>In that case.... an Edison bulb could look badass there and make the old seem cool!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 13:22:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. Not a guy. 2. Keep your insecurities to yourself.  #129325;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 13:22:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great! Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 13:22:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Badass. Thank you for the input!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 16:56:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m not even sure how one  #8220;types like a dude. #8221; But  #129335; #127995; #8205; #9792; #65039;.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #8216;Crossfit #8217; gym from 103 years ago</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 22:29:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #8216;Crossfit #8217; gym from 103 years ago is still standing</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 22:48:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 01:17:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Old bathhouse in Hot Springs, Arkansas</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 01:18:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Except it had super old school rowers, med balls and wooden dumbbells!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 13:36:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s on the right behind the pommel horse. Kind of hard to see in the pic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 14:29:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anything from Hot Sauce Harry #8217;s in the collection??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 14:37:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just sailed on the Magic in December and I thought the food was excellent. So good, in fact, that I ordered multiple entrees every night (totally living up to the American Glutton reputation). I thought the burger bar and burrito bar were amazing and wish I would #8217;ve eaten there more. The buffet lines were out of control. Anyway, I had the same experience in the spa... I was very uncomfortable with her trying to sell me hundreds of dollars in products afterward and kind of took the  #8220;relaxation #8221; part away because it stressed me out when she wouldn #8217;t take  #8216;no #8217; for an answer. I also agree that the excursion meet-up situation is a cluster and we NEVER received our excursion tickets. We almost missed one because we had to stand in the guest services line once we realized we were supposed to have tickets delivered to our room the night before. We had never sailed with Carnival so we didn #8217;t know the drill... they kept mentioning tickets and we were like,  #8220;wtf? #8221; Apparently the problem happened because we got a room upgrade, but....still, that happened two weeks prior to the cruise. They should have that figured out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 15:28:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was a rowing motion though, horizontal. Not vertical pulls.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 12:36:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just when i was thinking,  #8220;I wonder what this actually looks like.... how fast do these actions happen? Will people notice that I #8217;m trying to do this? #8221; This is a GREAT example of what this mindfulness and awareness looks like. And damn! I #8217;ve got a lot of respect for that guy!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 12:43:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any advice for doing this in a situation or encounter with another person? Will that person be able to tell that I #8217;m trying not to react? Right now, I suppress and smile in an attempt to not show my frustration, then do the analysis later... but it often then builds up and feels much worse afterward and I often regret not responding in a productive way that would help me understand why that person #8217;s words caused me to be frustrated or annoyed in that moment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 12:50:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve got a GoPro Hero 4 Silver.... would the 5 Session be better? Or should I just stick with what I #8217;ve got? I don #8217;t use my GoPro as much as I thought I would, but I still love having it.... basically, I don #8217;t need two but have a hard time turning down a great deal!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 11:58:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve moved five times in six years and... I #8217;ve never heard of those ones.  #129335; #127995; #8205; #9792; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 13:48:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, if you can #8217;t find anyone to vouch for them recently here on Reddit, I #8217;d steer clear. There are definitely some slumlords in Memphis and people who own properties but don #8217;t even live here to manage them or make sure it #8217;s being done well. It #8217;s a problem. With that being said, there are plenty of reputable landlords and property management companies so I wouldn #8217;t settle for something questionable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The fried crab garnishing this Bloody Mary</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 23:17:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 00:16:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pittsburgh, PA</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 01:07:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wild Alaskan Grill in the Strip District</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lyft decorates it #8217;s drivers with shamrocks and rainbows</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 15:05:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #8220;My future #8217;s so bright... #8221;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 20:45:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 12:34:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d be down to join if you wanted to start one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 12:17:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Send this to the group text from me,  #8220;How fucking old is that guy?? Get your own damn Uber and stop expecting other people to take care of you. Take responsibility for yourself. #8221; He should be embarrassed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 12:21:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone is an asshole and it #8217;s not you. Your boyfriend sounds like a dick. Get outta there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 12:26:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Social media......Boiseans are really great about accepting new people. I speak from experience. I #8217;ve moved away, but every single friend I met in Boise was through Twitter and they #8217;re better friends to me still than the folks I #8217;ve known my whole life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 00:36:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>You go to the gym to workout.... not be judged by people standing outside. God that #8217;s messed up. And seriously, you think they #8217;d have something better to do. How boring is their relationship that filming people working out from the outside is entertainment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My loft sanctuary</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 00:40:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My loft sanctuary... managed to give our downtown city condo a  #8216;log cabin #8217; vibe.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 00:41:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 12:17:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually, we don #8217;t deal with it at all. We #8217;ve lived here about six months and haven #8217;t noticed any. Very odd now that you mention it!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 12:20:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope, I think putting a rug on carpet looks weird. And the wood beams and duct work make it hard to hang any art without it looking too busy. I think it works though because what you don #8217;t see is that this alcove is part of a full loft master suite that has wooden wall hangings, a dresser, full sectional, desk, two TVs, and a six foot wooden candle holder on the wall that I made myself. It #8217;s plenty decorated. Ill get a picture...standby!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 11:30:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don #8217;t forget that she constantly made excuses and defended herself for going on the show with a  #8220;I just went for the free drinks #8221; attitude. I thought she was insincere and annoying in that book and it made me start to look at her differently...it #8217;s only gone downhill from there after reading interviews and seeing her contradict herself with her paid Instagram posts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Big gulps, huh? Well, see ya later.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 14:36:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 02:32:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>And it was a joke, so... ;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 02:35:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you name calling the 357 other people who used this pic on the internet? Just wondering.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 13:36:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>We stayed in a rental on the Oregon coast last year that had two bath tubs outside overlooking the water. Photo evidence: [Double bath tubs overlooking the Oregon coast](http://imgur.com/QXuD2nH)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 13:47:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Am I the only person getting a blank page with just their names on it? What #8217;s even the point of them having this? That #8217;s so weird.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 14:00:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>No lie, that #8217;s 100% what we were thinking when we saw them!!!! Cialas, ftw.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 19:56:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>If they were really smart, they #8217;d hold off on setting a date until ABC approaches them to do a wedding special.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 15:13:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was going to say that...line it with wine bottles.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 15:24:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>No idea, but I #8217;m still digging it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 15:28:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>When you posted that, I thought you made it up to caption the picture yourself! Come to find out she actually posted that shit. Bonnie and Clyde? Really? Are they robbing banks??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 18:31:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>The worst part is that Arie will read this and not click on it. He #8217;ll think it #8217;s legit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 18:40:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be honest, if a parent company asks any local TV station to do something like this, they will. They can #8217;t afford to say  #8216;no, #8217; or they will be fired. News directors are a dime a dozen these days...they all say they are ethical, but when it comes down to it, it #8217;s hard to find one that would actually stand up to the person who signs their paychecks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 22:08:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>If that really even happened. Seriously, he #8217;s so disgusting I wouldn #8217;t put it past him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 22:19:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree! This just proves how incredibly boring he and Lauren are. If you want to do an April Fools #8217; joke, do better. He #8217;s a walking cliche.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 23:42:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds about right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 13:20:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve spoken to Lyft and Uber drivers who only drive during those hours because the clientele is a little better because the majority of time it #8217;s airport rides. If not, it #8217;s only $6/day to park so it could be cheaper to drive yourself depending on how long you #8217;re gone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 13:22:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Celebrity or RC.... Those who are saying Princess might be older. I cruised Princess with my boyfriend and we were the youngest people on the boat... we were in our late 20s.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>After 10+ years with that yellow beauty, I said goodbye and joined the Subaru family with the white Forester 2.5i Touring on the left. There were tears...of joy!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 14:26:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 03:36:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ha! You can have it. It wasn #8217;t worth keeping, sadly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 13:09:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>What #8217;s drifting?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 12:40:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. Invasion of privacy. 2. Porn isn #8217;t funny. It #8217;s cool if he likes it, but leave it there. Don #8217;t force it upon other people. A previous poster was right... something else  #8212; anything else  #8212; would #8217;ve been better. 3. A prank is switching the mouse settings so the buttons click as if you #8217;re left handed. 4. He should know when to apologize. Even if it was a prank, the moment he found out it upset you, he should #8217;ve accepted that and apologized for taking it too far. The correct response would #8217;ve been,  #8220;I thought it was funny. I #8217;m so sorry if I took it too far. I guess I didn #8217;t think about all of the reasons it was a bad idea. You #8217;re right and have every reason to be pissed. I won #8217;t touch your stuff from now on. Please accept my apology. #8221; Not the asshole.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 12:42:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love this!!! How creative! It looks great. I #8217;d absolutely sit there with a cup of coffee... perfect place to get some work done.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 12:48:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>What charity is it? Because Arie himself is definitely not worth $200.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 03:44:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Depends on the cruise line I guess... my boyfriend and I cruised Carnival at Christmas and drank free in the casino every time. The servers recognized us as good tippers and we were treated great the whole week despite not making big bets or spending a ton of time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 03:46:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s not true for Carnival. We bet low bets at the minimum tables and were treated like royalty by the servers because we tipped them... nothing major, but we tipped them with chips every time they came around.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 13:47:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Free drinks and better service. We had the drink package, but we never hit our max number and we absolutely should have almost every day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 15:00:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is so incredibly disappointing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 14:52:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds to me like your actions and the party planner #8217;s actions could #8217;ve possibly taken the attention off of the VIP, who paid the money and threw the party in the first place... which makes you both assholes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 19:18:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why was it so exclusive then? Was there an occasion to hold this party?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 02:40:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I went through the exact same process. Still kinda wonder whether the 90s are really  #8220;old school #8221; yet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 12:23:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don #8217;t help friends move. Make those assholes hire a mover next time and then they can bitch when the movers break something. What #8217;s the moving company gonna say?  #8220;Not our problem. You should #8217;ve paid us to pack it for you. We #8217;re not liable for lost or damaged items. #8221; I #8217;d pull that verbiage from a movers contract online and send it to these punks. Between however many of them are living in that house, they could drive Uber for a weekend to come up with the money if they #8217;re that broke that they #8217;re willing to act like jackasses over it. Also  #8212; where can I get my carpet replaced for only $150? Inquiring minds want to know!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 14:45:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not the asshole, but time to re-evaluate the relationship. There #8217;s a reason he booked this without you...what #8217;s the real reason? A previous poster said separate vacations are normal if they #8217;re like girls weekends or something and I completely agree. To just go on vacation alone isn #8217;t normal if you have a girlfriend... he #8217;s either got someone else going with him or he #8217;s looking to hook up. Personally, if my SO wanted to go on a vacation together, I wouldn #8217;t dream of booking it without him or doing it alone. I love every vacation or road trip and day trip we take together. Even when I have to travel for work, I wish he was there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 02:11:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>A VRBO in Newport, Oregon!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 22:49:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s a great way for your gym to rally around you and keep your mom #8217;s spirit alive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>He #8217;s the epitome of stealth.  #128580;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 18:43:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 13:38:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d like to see what his message said in order to make a more fact-based decision. It doesn #8217;t sound like you #8217;ve moved on. Of course he #8217;s reaching out because he #8217;s dealing with something internally.... or maybe his pastor gave a sermon that really resonated (happened to me once.) Regardless of why he reached out, he did it  #8212; which is something most people will never do. And if he is dealing with something, wouldn #8217;t it have felt better to show him that you #8217;re still the bigger person and that kindness is always the way? That #8217;s the message he should #8217;ve gotten as a kid and eight years later, handling his apology with kindness would #8217;ve probably made him feel even worse about his past behavior than you turning around and being an asshole about it. Now he #8217;s probably thinking,  #8220;Well, he #8217;s a dick. Now I #8217;m glad I gave him that swirly in high school. #8221; Also, your response could #8217;ve deterred him from reaching out to other people he bullied who would #8217;ve really liked to hear an apology from him. My vote is always to kill them with kindness and be the better person. Therefore, I #8217;ve come to the conclusion that you #8217;re kind of an asshole.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 12:54:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are a lot of Civil War battlefields around Memphis and I #8217;m sure there are some on the way to Smokey, too. Plan to stop at some of those on your way. You #8217;re right, GSMNP is a haul from Hot Springs, but worth it! You might consider hitting up Mammoth on the way from Hot Springs to GSMNP. That would break up the trip nicely.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why did I get a seat assignment, but my colleague who booked before me didn #8217;t?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 16:48:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll start out by saying that everything turned out fine and she got a seat, but I #8217;m curious about why this happens... anyone who is familiar with the process, please weigh in! My colleague and I were booked on a Delta flight later this afternoon. Yesterday, we called our employer #8217;s call center to change to an earlier flight. She gave her information and was switched to the earlier flight, then I did mine with the same call center agent. This morning, I had a seat assignment, but she was listed as  #8220;standby. #8221; I know very well that standby in Atlanta is bad news. I went on the app to look at the seat map and there were 7 open seats and I was even allowed to change mine. In fact, it allowed me to change my seat all the way up until we boarded! My colleague was never able to pick a seat and she kept getting the notification that her seat would be assigned at the gate. Gate agents at our originating airport kept reassuring her that she #8217;d get a seat and this was normal... they were right. She did get a seat. But why didn #8217;t she get a seat when I got one yesterday? She was booked on the flight before me. Thanks for any clarity you can provide! Edit: I #8217;ve read other threads about this, but it still doesn #8217;t make sense. She is not a Medallion member, but I haven #8217;t reached Medallion status yet either, though I am closer than she is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 16:56:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>We booked using the same call center and the same agent through our employer. They never book us on basic economy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Booked my flight on the wrong day, but got travel insurance... are they going to charge me a change fee?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 23:55:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>First of all, before everyone comments about how stupid I am -- yes, I'm well aware. I'm an idiot. Thank you for noticing. Long story short... I booked a one way ticket for Sunday, April 22, but meant to book it for Sunday, April 29. I didn't realize my mistake until I got the "check-in" email just now. I did buy trip insurance. The website is trying to charge me a $200 change fee. So, I'm now waiting for a customer service agent to call me back (wait time of 90 minutes). Are they going to charge me that if I have trip insurance? Do I need to lie about my reason for changing to avoid that?? I thought this was why a person buys trip insurance... in case they have to change their plans! UPDATE: I was honest and very nice to the customer service agent, they agreed to drop the entire change fee with no pause. Probably had everything to do with my loyalty to Delta and my attitude and tone when I called. I also asked to speak to his supervisor and gave him good praise.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 01:32:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re my Reddit hero. Thanks for that message.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 01:32:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>They dropped the entire change fee for me. I #8217;m so grateful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 03:54:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I bet she was drunk.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 04:15:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>She looks so plastic. I used to love her, but I #8217;m so disappointed she ditched her  #8220;girl next door #8221; appearance to get so much work done. She just didn #8217;t need it!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>CrimeCon 2018! Anyone going??</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 05:21:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anyone going to CrimeCon in Nashville this year? I just signed up. I #8217;m curious to know how the sessions work... do I need to pre-register? Get in line early for the ones I want to attend? Any advice from those of you who have gone in past years is appreciated! Looking forward to it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 06:03:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m not familiar with podcast row. Looks like I #8217;ve got some research to do! Just signed up today.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 14:08:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I found out about it so late that I #8217;m only able to go Saturday. That session is on Friday. Hopefully someone else can attend that one and report back though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 19:57:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same. I #8217;m only three hours away and was just glad they still had tickets!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 22:42:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could it be because of the behavior of these people though? Just to name a few of the most recent examples... 1. Making fun of people at the gym. 2. Making fun of people who are transgender. 3. The list goes on... I hate to point out the obvious, but when you go on TV or become a  #8220;celebrity, #8221; you are putting yourself in the position for people to criticize you  #8212; good and bad. Now I don #8217;t agree with everything that is said on this subreddit, however, I do think many of the contestants in recent years have displayed bad and/or questionable behavior and because they #8217;re in the spotlight, you #8217;ve got to expect they #8217;re going to be called out for that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 02:57:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you read my comment, it definitely doesn #8217;t say that. However, this is Reddit. And while I want to read more about peace, love, and puppies, I also know that #8217;s not going to happen. If you want nothing but love for people like Arie, a subreddit isn #8217;t the right place to look. I #8217;m sure there #8217;s a Bachelor forum that is full of over-the-top positive fans if you do a Google search. Also, thanks for the correction in my terminology (for real)!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 03:45:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn, seriously?? That #8217;s disappointing to hear. The fact that everyone from Dateline is going to be there is the reason I #8217;m going. I definitely hope I don #8217;t walk away feeling that way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Blue crab and cheddar mashed potatoes [2048x1536] [OC]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 15:11:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 02:36:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s the way to do it! I was going myself, now I #8217;ve got two girls coming with me but we are all on the same page about the fact that we #8217;re doing whatever sessions we want to do. We #8217;re not planning anything really together except dinner!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 13:28:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like them more after seeing this exchange.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 13:31:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who doesn #8217;t steal jokes? Let #8217;s get serious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 13:42:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for this insight! That #8217;s very helpful. I #8217;m looking forward to it. A little stressed out that I won #8217;t get into the one session I #8217;m really excited about...so I #8217;ll be there extra early.  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 13:53:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>They do psych evals only to cover their own asses in case someone goes off the deep end. They don #8217;t actually care if someone displays  #8220;worrisome signs #8221; as long as they pass the overall test.... that helps them get the crazy  #8220;entertaining #8221; people on TV, but covers them if that person goes batshit on someone or jumps off a cliff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 13:58:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Am I the only one who actually wants more Corinne? I seriously did think she was hysterical and very entertaining.  #128514; #128514; Go ahead, downvote me. I know it #8217;s coming.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 17:22:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>What #8217;s a shit rag?? I missed this whole thing apparently!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 23:25:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m laughing so damn hard. My cubicle neighbors are probably like wtf. If only they knew.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 13:43:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Her  #8220;obsession #8221; with being handicapped? Because she mentioned it on this thread as part of her story, she #8217;s obsessed with it? Someone needs to set you straight: A disability is part of someone #8217;s LIFE. It helps shape who they are, makes them unique and to be honest, it would make the conversation on The Bachelor a lot more interesting... that does not make it an obsession. Get a fucking clue.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Working from home.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 15:12:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Working from home</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 15:16:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 16:49:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too! I actually loved CrimeCon. Some people commented on this thread that it was exploitative and insensitive to families of victims... and I didn't feel that way whatsoever. I thought everyone who spoke was there to speak on behalf of victims and none of it was exploitative. I didn't visit Podcast Row, but I do get that feeling from podcasts every once in a while... that they are making fun of situations and don't always have a lot of tact, so I can see how if they had an experience with a podcaster, that might make them see the whole conference in that light. The Dateline crew being there was the #1 reason I went... it was great meeting them and I loved their panel. I enjoyed hearing about the challenges of their jobs, as well as how they keep in touch with the families they cover and how those families are now helping other families and it's a big community. I wish I had more time to speak to each of them during the meet  amp; greet. I was at the end of the line and I felt like by the time I got there, Josh, Dennis, and Andrea were so tired of seeing everyone fawn over how much they love Keith Morrison. They seemed drained and I can't blame them. I only had enough time to get out one thought -- and it ended up being directed at Keith... but his response made my whole day! I was also surprised by how much I enjoyed Nancy Grace's presentation! I was only in there to get a better seat for the Dateline panel coming up next. I had never watched Nancy Grace, never cared to because I only heard negative things about her from other people, but I was really touched by how passionate and emotional she is about everything that has gotten her to this point. I didn't know her story and I appreciate that she takes every single case she ever tried personally and that's what drives her to keep holding people accountable and advocating for those victims. Overall, the experience was absolutely amazing... I'm planning to go to New Orleans next year... just wish it wasn't in JUNE! Damn it's going to be hot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Would love to stay at Wilderness Lodge...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 01:27:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi everyone! We #8217;re heading back to Disney for our second time in July. Our first trip was on Christmas last year. We wanted to stay at Wilderness Lodge but the prices were crazy! Through surfing Reddit back then, I had come across a post about a way you can buy credits from people who own timeshares or something? We had already made other arrangements so I didn #8217;t dig too deep into the research. In July we #8217;d really like to stay at the Lodge. Is anyone familiar with what I #8217;m talking about? Or are there any ways to book I should know about to save a few bucks?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 04:26:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahhhh ok. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 13:52:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like the peddle bike driver was the asshole.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 14:39:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>More like the people who ride the peddle bikes... However, in this case... if you read what actually happened and if the driver of the peddler was actually trying to race a trolley and cut it off to park his peddler, he was the asshole.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 14:48:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>A good sibling would never make the other go to graduation. That #8217;s just plain miserable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 15:38:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>How long would you say you meditated for to achieve this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 21:45:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Take it up with the news outlets reporting it... That #8217;s what the articles say: "They were going along the track when she blew her whistle, and evidently he thought he could speed up, beat her. He turned too short in front of her and she hit him," the man said. The witness said Sprock N Roll tried to race past the trolley despite the trolley operator ringing the bell. We reached out to Sprock N Roll and the company and they released the following statement Saturday Night:  #8220;While attempting to park on a road we have accessed for 3 yrs we were struck by a trolley. The trolley never slowed as it rear ended us turning us perpendicular to the front. See debris from the wood and a passengers to-go box showing how hard we were hit  amp; far we were carried. #8221;  gt; gt; http://www.wmcactionnews5.com/story/38177059/trolley-pedal-tavern-collide-in-downtown-memphis</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 22:26:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Give the news a call...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 22:03:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>We thought it might be more geared toward adults than some of the others... but it #8217;s not really coming up on any lists citing the best place for adults who don #8217;t have kids. I #8217;m still in love with the fact that it #8217;s modeled after the national park lodges so we #8217;ll probably choose it regardless.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 13:05:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Poly appears to be booked up. That one has popped up on those lists!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 04:32:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fanny packs are so worth it. LOVE.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 13:16:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where did the picture go? I don #8217;t see it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 13:25:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d submit the pictures. Guaranteed if the Pax gets charged a cleaning fee, he #8217;ll turn around and make his friend pay it  #8212; or quit ordering rides for his super drunk friends...which will help another driver down the road.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Caturday</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 01:50:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 23:01:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I could see Robby on the back page of a Kmart ad, for sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 02:29:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>You don #8217;t need a permit to camp in campgrounds, only backcountry. Most campgrounds are first come, first served... so you #8217;ll want to get there early on the day you #8217;d like to camp if possible. The good news is... there are a ton of campgrounds and some off the beaten path, so you #8217;ll find something eventually! I #8217;m sure others can weigh in on your best bets and strategy if you can #8217;t get there early... my family goes in September and January so we have no problem finding spots. My favorite is Bowman Campground (best views out of all in the park, IMO), but more challenging to get to...which sometimes means it #8217;s less crowded! Second favorite is Two Medicine Campground... it #8217;s one of the most popular, but also has quite a few campsites. Enjoy your first trip! It #8217;s an incredible place.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 02:56:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>They should be paying you time and a half for those hours over 40. Let #8217;s be serious. It #8217;s called OVERTIME. Or.... you should take a long lunch or leave 30 minutes early. Your boss is actually breaking the law by not paying you the hours they #8217;re asking you to work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 18:07:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>As much as I support bring your dog to work days, seems like there are probably rules about that in a hospital.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 01:30:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also... if you can #8217;t find anything inside the park on your first day, stay at one of the campgrounds just outside and then try again early the next day. We stayed at a campground on the outskirts of the park (Devil Creek Campground) in September when there was a voluntary evacuation due to wildfire and it ended up being a great space despite being near the highway... you couldn #8217;t hear any traffic and there were a lot of recent bear sightings! It also had the nicest porta potties I #8217;ve ever seen! They took great care of the place. So, I #8217;d recommend it if you encounter a lot of full campgrounds inside the park.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 01:21:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have fun in Fargo, ND! ;-) (I grew up an hour north of there) For real though, you #8217;ll love Glacier and every trail you take will be breathtaking! Enjoy!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 01:40:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be completely honest, there isn #8217;t a lot to see between the two places. You #8217;ll find that eastern Montana and all of North Dakota is pretty boring when it comes to driving. If you do feel like stopping along the way, stop at Theodore Roosevelt National Park and explore the Badlands. Just make it a mini park tour! We used to go to Medora on field trips in school....  #128514; #128514; in case you #8217;re tired of camping by then!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 02:17:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not the asshole. Everybody has their limits.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Purrito.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 04:42:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 15:37:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Until it rains....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 03:21:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>But  #8220;Heavenly Creatures #8221; IS totally creepy. Clay figures having an orgy.........for real.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 03:24:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to punch Jared in the face. Go home.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 04:05:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>My favorite place. Had a grizzly bear encounter camping there when I was a kid! I #8217;ll never forget it. Coolest story I #8217;ve got.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 16:23:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was probably 11-12 years old, I #8217;d guess. The day before, my dad caught me putting on deodorant and freaked out. I insisted it was unscented, but he said it didn #8217;t matter and animals could smell it. I didn #8217;t listen and continued on with my day thinking he was overreacting. That night, my cousin and I slept in the tent with my dad and my brother slept in his usual spot in the van. Around 6 a.m. or so, my dad unzipped the tent to go to the bathroom and a grizzly bear walked right in front of the tent. He describes it as the side of the bear being within five inches of his face as it brushed by our tent. My dad zipped up the tent and woke us up, told us to be quiet and still because there was a bear in our campsite. We could hear the bear walking circles around our tent. Then it began digging into the dirt next to our tent, from inside it sounded like it was right next to our tent, but it was actually a few feet away when we looked later. Because of the deodorant incident the day before, I was 100% convinced the bear smelled my  #8220;unscented #8221; deodorant and was trying to find me. We cowered in the tent for about 10 minutes as the bear hung around our campsite. Eventually he left our site and walked down the road of Bowman Campground. At that point, we all ran into the van. I specifically remember jumping on my brother and him being so pissed at me for waking him up until we told him the story. Later that morning, campers began walking around camp, talking about the bear, and finding places where it had scratched at trees and gotten into stuff that people had left out (obviously they got in trouble for that). We recounted our story for the rangers and learned it wasn #8217;t the first sighting they #8217;d had that in camp that summer. It was an incredible experience and I #8217;ll never forget it. To hear my dad tell the story is the best... he even uses sound effects to bring it to life for people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 04:09:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>They would probably exploit your fear of flying and make sure you make it to the end simply for the fact that you #8217;d be forced to face your fears every single damn day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 04:15:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even if you didn #8217;t tell them that, they #8217;d probably figure it out pretty fast! However, depending on you level of fright... that means drama so it could work in your favor!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This first 1:1 date is.... amazing!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 02:52:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Smash that shit, Becca! Arie deserves it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 02:54:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve seriously never seen The Bachelor franchise encourage violence. And it #8217;s actually appropriate! I #8217;m a fan.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 02:56:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I bet the guy enjoyed it just as much as she did!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 02:58:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>No way. He gets his alone time. They have to do some kind of  #8220;activity. #8221; They never just sit around and talk the entire 1:1. He #8217;ll get the same alone time as other 1:1 dates.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 03:03:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s good TV though... they #8217;ll do what they #8217;ve gotta do for ratings. But I can get behind your  #8220;hate any Arie attention #8221; statement. He #8217;s such a fame whore it #8217;s amazing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Colton dated Ali Raisman.... and *spoiler*... what are his real intentions?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 03:53:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 03:54:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did appreciate the end of the article,  #8220;And for what it's worth, even though Raisman and Colton's relationship was fairly short and had a very unique and public beginning (hm, kind of sounds like The Bachelorette), they did seem happy while it lasted  #8212; and seem to still be supportive of each other now. That's the best kind of ex to have. #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 04:02:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Apparently he also uses the word  #8220;professionality #8221; in regards to his face, so we #8217;re going to have some fun this season. I hope they keep him on... we can put a whole  #8220;model dictionary #8221; together.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 04:05:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you #8217;re forgetting that she signed up for last season... and then signed up for it again. Of course they #8217;re going to use what happened to her last season!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 18:15:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Saw this thread when I was searching for an answer to a question before I post... kateish, as a lawyer in town, do you know any attorneys who would charge a small fee to show up in my place to contest my ticket? I'm going to be out of the country on the date that I'm supposed to show up for one I just received. I've always just shown up to court and had them dismissed without a problem. I'd hate to pay it knowing that there is a chance I could get it thrown out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 15:01:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re really worried about the attention this sub is getting? I think there are bigger things to be thinking about right now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This is a cat who was so traumatized/terrified of the outside that he would run and hide every time you opened the door. Three years after being rescued, he finally ventured outside to our closed-in patio  #8212; and he loved it!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 01:06:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 01:32:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was the best decision I ever made! Can #8217;t imagine my life without this little furball.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 01:36:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just for some additional context: A good samaritan found Morrison so badly injured that he couldn #8217;t walk. He ended up at the emergency vet three times, first for a fever and severe wounds, again with a fever of 105 degrees, and a third time because his wounds wouldn #8217;t heal. We still don #8217;t know what happened to him, whether he was attacked by another animal or hit by a car, but I know that he remembers.... I sincerely believe that #8217;s why he #8217;s been so terrified of the outdoors. He #8217;s the most lovable cat, I just know he had to belong to someone before this all happened to him! With all of that being said, I #8217;m so glad he #8217;s part of my little family now. My life is infinitely better with him by my side! Warning: these photos may be tough to look at... they just show how far he #8217;s come! https://imgur.com/gallery/DediXS6</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 02:25:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thank God for the person who found him and the rescue group that took him from the animal shelter! He was on the euthanasia list before the rescue group stepped in!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 02:35:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Amen to that!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 13:32:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>He #8217;s done it twice now! Both times outside. I #8217;m so happy!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 16:41:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would feel the same way if I didn #8217;t have such a secure patio. We #8217;ve never let our cats outside because they didn #8217;t have a contained space. All of my cats lived to be 20+ too... probably because we didn #8217;t let them outside.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 01:42:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>May I ask how he got cast on The Bachelorette if he had charges pending? He was convicted May 21 for something that happened in 2015. When was he charged? And when was his background check done for the show? This makes no sense to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 13:47:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ohhhhhh interesting. I didn #8217;t know that! Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Business Class International on United... is there a bathroom exit for window seats?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 21:41:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some colleagues and I are flying business class to Hong Kong. We're on the 777-200 that does not have the brand new Polaris upgrades... Question... do the window seats in business class offer a way out if you have to use the bathroom while your neighbor is fully reclined and sleeping? Or are you stuck there?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 23:04:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gross.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 23:32:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, it's the EWR-HKG flight with the 2-2-2 arrangement. We chose the middle seats for our flight to HKG because they were available next to each other, but we couldn't sit next to each other on the flight home if we did that, so we compromised and I got the window because I prefer window seats... and my colleague said she is 100% not able to sleep on planes, so it won't bother her if I have to crawl over her or make her get up. We'll see how it goes!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 23:32:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thankfully it's not a four across... it's 2-2-2. So ideally, the middle seats are the way to go... one of our flights that isn't an option because we booked too late, but we reached a compromise for that leg.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 01:57:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Boooooo! I would #8217;ve loved a window seat with nobody next to me. That #8217;d be a dream come true!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 02:14:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I #8217;m sure it #8217;ll be fine. The only reason I even like the window is because I can lean on it to sleep, so if I can recline, I have no need for the window. Will be badass to fly over and see these cities for the first time in the early hours though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 02:15:03</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128514; #128514; #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 02:19:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Serious?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 03:30:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll be in Glacier the same week! We fly into Kalispell and rent a car there. I #8217;m not sure you could rent a car in the US and return it to Canada (if you can it #8217;ll be expensive), so you might have to bring it back into the US if that #8217;s where you choose to start. Renting a car in Kalispell isn #8217;t cheap because it #8217;s a popular place, but it #8217;s worth it, IMO. We typically splurge for an SUV or pickup, though it #8217;s not required unless it #8217;s winter. In Whitefish, check out the Hidden Moose Lodge. It #8217;s a local, family run lodge and it #8217;s absolutely beautiful. They paid attention to every detail when building and designing the place. We camp and stay in first cabins for 4-6 days, then finish out the week at the lodge living the high life. Our favorite trip every year!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 12:50:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the heads up!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is it an ankle break or sprain?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 13:11:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>33, female, 159lb... Last night after three glasses of wine, I crashed and burned on uneven ground while getting into the car. The pain was really intense for a few minutes, but about five minutes later, I got out of the car and walked inside with no real problem. This morning, I can #8217;t walk. Even the slightest pressure on my foot hurts. Is that normal for a sprain? Or could it be broken? Was the alcohol masking the pain last night? My ankle is a little swollen, but the pain is out of this world this morning.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 02:16:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want Jordan to stay just because he #8217;s such an idiot. I love it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 02:20:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>That guy was putting on a show to build his ridiculous brand.... I think Jordan believes he #8217;s smart, which makes it even better!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 02:21:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 02:25:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>HAHAHA. True story.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 02:30:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>He #8217;s also a sex offender, so I #8217;m with you on that one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 02:55:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>What?! What did I miss?! Pooping on the floor?? That #8217;s just not normal... I just asked my psychologist friend what that meant....  #8220;Anything bathroom related where people are going not in the toilet or saving it in bags or buckets is usually related to a personality disorder (like antisocial), psychosis, or bipolar disorder. #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 02:57:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>He was found guilty in late May of sexually assaulting a woman on a cruise in 2015. Will have to register as a sex offender.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 03:43:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>OMFG. No way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 03:44:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you watching the same show the rest of us are watching?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 04:35:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I literally LOL #8217;d at that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 21:35:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Am I the only one who sees the glaring typo in that tweet? On another note, I #8217;m excited it #8217;s open!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 00:38:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Another northerner in Memphis!  #128075; #127996;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 02:14:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Grand Forks, ND... right on the ND/MN border.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 11:32:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I think you posting this screenshot and sharing tea right now could definitely hurt your friend #8217;s chances of getting on the show! I #8217;d delete this post until she either makes it...or doesn #8217;t! Once she #8217;s on, share! And if she doesn #8217;t make it, it #8217;s always really fun to read about their experiences in the casting process!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 05:33:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, breaking up to live alone is GOALS. I #8217;m going to bite my tongue because I don #8217;t want to jump to conclusions and judge you for saying that, but I will say this......... Having the independence and self worth to realize something isn #8217;t right for you? GOALS. Having the motivation to leave when staying would be the easiest thing? GOALS. Having the courage to be alone instead of in an unhealthy or unfulfilling relationship. GOALS. Think about that  #8212; then take a solid look inward before posting on this thread again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I #8217;m drunk.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 20:01:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>In case you missed the sign on the door, they put a sign on the door.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 20:02:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 20:08:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re probably right! I hadn #8217;t even noticed that. Makes it less funny.  #9785; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 20:37:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not true! I walked through about a foot two years ago downtown! It was amazing!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 14:16:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Boom. If you won #8217;t be in a bad position by not getting the job and wouldn #8217;t plan on taking it anyway, this is exactly how you handle it. He will remember you and think about that encounter every time he thinks about asking those questions to the next woman in his office.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The cocktail names on this menu come from the staff #8217;s real life travel experiences.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 10:06:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 10:41:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Red cocktail with leafy greens: https://imgur.com/gallery/9nYEPzI Too sweet at first, but under the red, it #8217;s yellow and delicious! As for the story... waitress couldn #8217;t explain!! I feel like they should know the story behind every drink name!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 21:57:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>GO VIKES!!!!!!! We go to the Green Beetle downtown for football Sunday #8217;s.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 06:23:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re my hero.  #128514; #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 06:27:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have no reason to defend yourself. You #8217;re a 21 y/o college student. Free drinks are free drinks! Party all you want now... as you age, the hangovers get so bad it #8217;ll put the brakes on those amazing drunk nights! Enjoy them while you can!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 14:52:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s also not easy to pick huckleberries, which is why they #8217;re so expensive. You have to pick them one by one and you #8217;re treading bear country the whole time you #8217;re doing it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 15:15:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>They were probably an authorized charger.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 15:22:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right on. If someone gets hurt, they get hurt. I sprained my ankle just walking last week because they repaved the road and it was uneven (2 inches higher than the gutter). People will get hurt no matter what... doesn #8217;t mean everything that #8217;s fun in the world should be banned. Ride at your own risk.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 15:24:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Commercial Appeal said helmets are  #8220;encouraged #8221; but not required by City of Memphis. I rode one yesterday without a helmet and a Bird employee even asked me how it was driving when I was stopped waiting for my boyfriend to catch up. She didn #8217;t say anything about helmets. They don #8217;t care.... the app has to tell you to wear one so they won #8217;t be liable when you crack your head on the cobblestone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 15:28:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Update, please OP!! We #8217;re rooting for your sweet kitty!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 17:33:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>People get hurt by cars all the time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 20:54:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s a good question. I #8217;m not sure what the laws are in TN.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 21:16:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I totally think he is!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 22:22:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have to say though that getting hit by a scooter probably won #8217;t kill a person... more than likely kill the rider (if anyone) and only if they happened to be going full speed...and the riders signed a waiver via the app.  #129335; #127995; #8205; #9792; #65039; Just all seems very unlikely. So, I still think that the argument that they #8217;re not safe and should be banned is invalid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 23:30:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait. Softporn movie?? Looks like I #8217;ve got some Reddit reading to do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mr. Adams? Did Kyle kill him or did he kill himself?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 01:00:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>When Kyle appeared and told Mr. Adams to be quiet, did he convince Mr. Adams to kill himself? Or did he kill Mr. Adams? And why? Because he was helping Leila? I missed something there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 01:42:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got hooked. Watched the whole season! Like others, I was confused but you #8217;ve gotta stick it out. It all comes together. Quitting after an episode or two because you #8217;re confused isn #8217;t the answer. ;-)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What kind of spider is this? I just watched it build its whole web! [Memphis, TN]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 04:56:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 00:40:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn #8217;t necessarily care which way she went, but I definitely thought she was going to go for Tess. I do think it was weird that she ended up with the roommate because there was zero hint or chemistry there throughout the whole series.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 13:58:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>The guy who was basically manipulating them into killing themselves and one another is the son of the woman who created the virtual world. I don #8217;t think there was a much bigger explanation because they wanted to make it a cliff hanger to leave it open for another season. With all of that being said, I do think the  #8220;cliffhanger #8221; was poorly done and while I still enjoyed the series overall, there were a few questions I had that could #8217;ve been answered if they didn #8217;t try to squeeze the first season into six episodes. I think they left a lot of footage and backstory on the cutting room floor. They also may have decided to switch gears mid-season because it did seem a little random and unorganized at times. For example, all the foreshadowing and build-up to make us think Leila is into Tess, only to have her all of a sudden sleep with two guys in a matter of days and somehow fall in love with her roommate that barely played a role until the last episode. That was all kinda weird.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 14:08:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not the asshole, but I wouldn #8217;t be answering the phone at 9:58-59 if I close at 10. Fuck that. They can wait.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 19:14:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go the liquor route. Better value.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 19:15:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>They will sell a double, FYI.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 19:44:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not wearing one. Never wore one to bike either.  #129335; #127995; #8205; #9792; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 19:45:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Belle Tavern has deals during all the games... and the best bourbon selection.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 22:53:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d just fall asleep in there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 17:11:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope. I #8217;d punch his ass too. Without hesitation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 18:44:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do it!!!! I mean it... submerging in the glacial lakes is the most cleansing and incredible feeling! You #8217;ll feel like a new man afterward!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 18:46:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>10% Happier... so much free content and guided meditations.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 02:30:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>HAHAHAHAHHAHA. Your description of Arie made me LOL.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Friendly pax tip: 1 air freshener is plenty! And thank you!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 01:39:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I follow this sub because I enjoy reading your stories and knowing what to do/not to do as a pax... as I weigh the options of whether to drive or not drive myself... Tonight, we got a Lyft to a restaurant and the air freshener was so extreme that by the time we got there 15 minutes later, I felt sick. I #8217;m currently in the Lyft on the way home, same deal. As a passenger, too much air freshener is definitely a bad thing. I #8217;d rather be in a car that has an odor than have too much air freshener. Just my 2 cents in the event that I can help y #8217;all get more tips! I respect what y #8217;all do and sincerely appreciate the service. A friend and I were talking last night and I wish we could quantify how many lives have been saved because of Uber and Lyft. I know I made some poor decisions before it became a service, mainly because taxis don #8217;t take cards and I never carry cash. So, THANK YOU!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 01:55:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you counted four, that #8217;s exactly how many air fresheners I counted in my first ride tonight. So good job.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 02:04:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>For your own good, please don #8217;t.  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 03:50:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m the  #8220;type? #8221; Really???? I tip more than 50% regardless. And five stars, with a friendly comment about the air freshener in hopes they #8217;ll fix it. Way to jump to conclusions about me, though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 04:26:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, I don #8217;t tell them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>SPD pedal suggestions? Is it easy to swap the pedals back and forth?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 16:38:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi everyone, My boyfriend and I are about to buy a Peloton... he's going to get the Peloton shoes with the package, so he'll have the LOOK cleats. I spent years trying to find a pair of cycling shoes that fit my wide foot and I finally found some a few months ago, but they use the SPD cleats. So, I have two questions: 1. Do you have any recommendations for a good SPD pedal that will fit on the Peloton? Or will any SPD pedal do? 2. Is it easy to switch back and forth between the custom pedal and the Peloton pedal? Or should my boyfriend just buy his own SPD spin shoes if I'm going to buy a special pedal for the bike. Thanks for any guidance you can offer! I've done some searching, but am having trouble finding answers to my specific questions. P.S. I'm so excited!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 16:45:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Got it. Thanks for the info!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 17:39:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wear Tiem shoes... they appear to only have the 2 holes for cleats... link here: https://www.tiemathletic.com/collections/slipstream/products/slipstream-black-black I'm definitely NOT an expert and I really don't know anything about cleats, etc... so I don't know whether they can actually fit a LOOK cleat. I can't find anything on the Tiem website to tell me they can.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 20:43:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's what we're going to do... my friend gave us a referral code, so we were thinking he could just buy the shoes with that, but we'll just use it for other things since it'd be better in the longrun for him to get fitted, etc and buy the right shoes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 01:00:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s what we #8217;re doing. We just made the purchase!!! So excited.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 22:42:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mine comes on Tuesday! I #8217;m SO excited!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 03:14:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to upvote this over and over and over...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 16:12:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had the same questions last week... I ended up ordering from a store rep instead of ordering online so I could ask a lot of my questions. They told me the same thing... I did get the pad in the mail already (bike arrives tomorrow), and the pad is stiffer and thicker than I expected so I think the bike should be fine on my carpet. I'll follow up with you tomorrow when I get my bike if nobody else weighs in!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 16:25:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just got an email that due to an  #8220;unforeseen supply disruption, #8221; my bike won #8217;t be delivered today. No estimate on when I #8217;ll get it. Kinda angry, not gonna lie. =(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Bike delivery canceled...  #8220;unforeseen supply disruption? #8221;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 16:29:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m super sad! This is what I #8217;ve been looking forward to all week... It was supposed to arrive between 9 a.m. and noon. They refunded my delivery fee, but didn #8217;t give me anymore information about what  #8220;unforeseen supply disruption #8221; means or when my bike will be delivered now. Waiting on the call from XPO... Anyone else ever have this happen? UPDATE: I called XPO and the woman who answered tried to call the warehouse but it had already closed, so she couldn #8217;t provide me any information. Next, I called the sales rep who helped us buy the bike. She was super nice and apologetic, and said there certainly isn #8217;t a supply issue. She sent me the number to Peloton support and said they will be able to reach out to everyone involved to help facilitate the new delivery. She asked me to keep her posted so she can help speed things up in any way she can. I called Peloton support, and the guy was great. He told me he #8217;s going to reach out to the warehouse for me tomorrow, and he also plans on reaching out to XPO and filing a complaint with management if it turns out to be something that went wrong on their end. Overall, I #8217;m disappointed, but I #8217;m very impressed by the level of customer service Peloton has shown so far and that goes a very long way with me. ADDITIONAL UPDATE: It took an entire week for XPO to get back to me. They finally called on Monday, Aug. 13 to tell me that they only deliver to my city on Tuesdays, but unfortunately they were full on Tuesday, Aug. 14, so I wouldn't be receiving my bike for another full week, Aug. 21. I find it absolutely ridiculous that I called a week prior, when they probably could have fit in our delivery -- only to finally have my call returned 6 days later when they're schedule is too full. Of course, I'll be out of town for work on Aug. 21 and won't return until Monday, Aug. 28, so hopefully my boyfriend will be able to take the day off to wait for our shipment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 17:01:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>The email said they will be calling me when they have the reschedule details. If I don #8217;t hear from them by noon, I #8217;ll give them a call.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 17:09:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m going to be VERY unhappy if it takes a month... why are they even scheduling delivery dates if they #8217;re short on supply? I feel like Peloton should manage people #8217;s expectations on the frontend when they are buying the bike! Ughhhh... sorry to hear that you had to wait so long. Glad you love the bike though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 17:19:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>For sure. Good idea.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 18:01:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, don #8217;t worry... I #8217;m going to make some calls. What I don #8217;t understand is why they didn #8217;t tell me this yesterday when I called to get the delivery window... surely they knew then that they didn #8217;t have my bike.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 02:13:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I #8217;ve seen a lot of the comments both on Reddit and Facebook about them not having live classes recently. I wonder what #8217;s up with that!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 02:22:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just updated the original post with a little info about what happened when I followed up today... I should know more tomorrow when the Peloton support team gets in touch with the warehouse. I #8217;ll keep you posted! I #8217;m happy that their level of customer support seems to be really high.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 13:16:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Inconvenience I #8217;m sure. They didn #8217;t tell us it wasn #8217;t coming until we were already in our delivery window, at home waiting for it... despite calling the night before to check in. They had every opportunity to tell us they weren #8217;t coming.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 17:14:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ughhh!!! I still don #8217;t have a delivery date either. My patience is running thin.  #9785; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 18:26:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>We ordered it through a sales rep at a store over the phone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 18:26:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>No updates at all. I #8217;m on vacation now so I #8217;ve quit reaching out. Will see if they get this sorted by the time I get home.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 14:06:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Absolutely love that island!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 01:23:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>There was a whole presentation at CrimeCon by podcaster Bob Ruff that laid out the timeline of events. Very eerie and a lot of holes in the case.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 20:01:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Update... or non-update... It took an entire week for XPO to get back to me. They finally called on Monday, Aug. 13 to tell me that they only deliver to my city on Tuesdays, but unfortunately they were full on Tuesday, Aug. 14, so I wouldn't be receiving my bike for another full week, Aug. 21. I find it absolutely ridiculous that I called a week prior, when they probably could have fit in our delivery -- only to finally have my call returned 6 days later when they're schedule is too full. Of course, I'll be out of town for work on Aug. 21 and won't return until Monday, Aug. 28, so hopefully my boyfriend will be able to take the day off to wait for our shipment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A sketchy dive bar with a sense of humor</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 21:13:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 21:40:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wasn #8217;t that brave.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 18:17:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just hope you get your bike... I bought mine in July and I'm still waiting to get it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 18:18:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll be interested to hear if you get yours on your delivery date... still waiting on mine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ordered July 30 -- still no bike.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 18:32:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Update to this post that has fallen down the subreddit because it's been several weeks: [https://www.reddit.com/r/pelotoncycle/comments/95c483/bike\_delivery\_canceled\_unforeseen\_supply/](https://www.reddit.com/r/pelotoncycle/comments/95c483/bike_delivery_canceled_unforeseen_supply/) For those of you who have recently ordered -- I do hope you get your bikes on your scheduled delivery dates... but want you to be aware of some issues I've been having because I certainly wasn't prepared for the amount of frustration and disappointment I've experienced in waiting for my delivery. I wish someone had given me some information about supply issues upfront to manage my expectations and prevent us from taking time off of work to wait for a delivery that was never going to happen. \----- My scheduled bike delivery on Aug. 7 was "canceled due to an unforeseen supply disruption." It's been three weeks since I ordered it and... still no bike. Hopefully it'll be delivered tomorrow. Of course, I'm out of town for work all week so even if it does arrive, I'll have to wait another week to try it out. Our sales rep said they are experiencing an "unforeseen delay in deliveries countrywide." So I'm a little surprised to hear that people who ordered after I did have already received their bikes. I'm extremely disappointed in the Customer Service department... they started out responsive and I initially felt like they cared, but they never actually reached out to close the loop with me about our delivery date or act as a liaison between me and XPO. They did send me a survey, in which I responded that I still have no bike so I'm not prepared to rate my experience until my ticket is closed. Speaking of XPO... They didn't get back to me for an entire week after I called to find out why my bike was never delivered on Tuesday, Aug. 7. When they did finally return my call, it was the following Monday, Aug. 13 and they said they only deliver to my city on Tuesdays, but they were too booked to delivery our bike the next day (Tuesday, Aug. 14). So our delivery date is, instead, Tuesday, Aug. 21 and I'll be out of town. For the second time, my boyfriend will have to take the day off of work to wait on our delivery. Never mind that he had already taken one day off of work three weeks ago only to get the delivery cancellation notice DURING our delivery window. I plan on sending a full explanation of our experience and disappointments to Peloton once it's all said and done. Waiving our delivery fee certainly doesn't make up for my boyfriend having to take two days off of work for this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 18:45:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Considering I work for FedEx, I feel like they could have shipped my bike that way and I would #8217;ve been happy to assemble it myself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 20:23:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>They did refund the full shipping price, so that was good... but the cost of missing a full day of work exceeds $250.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>UPDATE: Peloton finally arrived... totally worth the wait. Had the best ride today with Ally Love!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 21:57:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>It took a month, but our Peloton finally arrived! It was well worth the wait... took my 5th ride this afternoon, this time with Ally Love. Her perspective, positivity and energy is everything!  #8220;For those of you who have been to hell and back, and we can still see that ash on your forehead, I want to say,  #8216;Welcome home. Welcome home. #8217; #8221;  #8220;You know how fortunate you are to sweat right now? Wow. #8221; She #8217;s absolutely right.  #128522;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Good tattoo parlors in Kalispell/Whitefish?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 22:47:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Heading to Montana next week and have been wanting a mountain range tattoo for quite a while. My parents met working in Montana, so it #8217;s always been a very special place for us. I #8217;d love to get my tattoo on our annual trip. Any recommendations for a place to get it? Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>