<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject4644</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Look what I saved today!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-16 01:48:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How my friends cat rides in the car</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-13 02:22:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-13 15:32:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm trying to figure out how to put image links in comments from the mobile app... once that happens though, you'll get your fix, you cat junkie</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-16 05:12:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are absolutely right.. I feel like an ass. Here ya go, 2 good ones of her, just for you!! http://imgur.com/a/VUn92</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-16 05:13:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>If anyone wanted to see a couple more pictures of this crazy cat, here ya go! http://imgur.com/a/VUn92</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-20 03:05:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well shit.. I read the rules too. I didn't know what VPN meant until just now.. sorry</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This is my cat, Bowser. He is very tired after a long morning of playing with a burrito wrapper...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-20 19:09:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-24 02:26:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does your cat go absolutely crazy in that thing?! I have one of those for my cat, and he is like a whole new cat when he plays in his. He turns into a god damn psycho!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-01 01:41:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>What kind of sick bastard puts the roll on that way?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-01 01:55:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>That guy is a god damn boss. Pure. Genius.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-03 03:03:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why does it matter? Our very nice OP just gave someone a free game, no reason to be a dick about it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-16 21:30:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are very little situations that can't be resolved by being nice. There are not many instances where being mean or rude will do you better than being nice. So, I always try to be as nice as I can to everyone, and it has really worked well for me, because people will often go out of their way to help someone who is nice to them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>After 18 years, today is the day this sweet little lady gets to take her forever nap.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-26 20:47:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-27 00:14:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I could be wrong, but I can't help but notice something in its eyes, does he/she have a problem with his/her kidneys?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-27 03:09:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Was she a feral? Mine that had a wierd kidney thing was a feral when I found her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-27 05:02:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks everybody, I really appreciate your kind words. She is chasing mice and taking all the best naps now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-28 19:54:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Paul Rudd. Good looking, and funny.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-28 20:06:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>College professors rarely give any shits about you. If you miss class and get an F, that's your fault. You are just a number to them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-31 00:14:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just switched to Verizon from Sprint a couple months ago, and I have not had one connectivity problem.. with Sprint, I couldn't make a call from my own apartment, had to walk outside and go stand by the mailboxes to even make a call. Sprint sucks big time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-04 04:18:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn, those are some nice honkers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Help a Titan out...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-01 04:57:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am trying to solo the Abyss on HM and I cannot make it up onto the ledge by the second lamp.. I've watched videos and such, but just can't get it. Everytime I go to jump, the weight of darkness hits me about halfway in my jump and I cannot even get close.. Anyone have any great info the can give me to do this? Am I missing something?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-01 05:45:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah ha. Okay, that is great. Definitaly going to give it a go. Thanks a lot fellow guardian!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-07 03:28:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Paulaner Hefe-Weizen. It's the best.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-24 15:57:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I heard Rock Band was coming out, I was pretty excited, but I never really got into all the other instruments. Now that this news dropped, so did my man panties. I'm pumped for this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Misc] Exotic Engram from Xur</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-27 16:00:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Been slowly building up my vault with Hunter and Warlock equipment so I can start a new character, since I currently only have a Titan. Got on this morning to see what Xur had to offer. So I buy an upgrade for my Invective, and decide to spend my Motes of Light on a Helmet Engram hoping for a Hunter or Warlock helmet. Purchase it, run to the cryptarch, and BOOM, Obsidian Mind! Looks like I'm starting a Warlock today!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-27 16:57:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright, I just might do that! I have been on the fence about which new character to start, but with my Obsidian I got today, and then buying HoPF pretty much seals the deal for me. Warlock it is!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-27 16:58:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm kind of the same way. I love my Titan, I just want something different to change things up a bit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-27 16:58:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just may do that. Thanks for the advice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-27 16:59:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a bunch of stuff put away in my vault for both Warlock and Hunter and I have just kind of been waiting for something like this to happen for some motivation to actually make one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-27 22:59:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do have Bad Juju! I finished an exotic bounty for it about a week ago!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-11 17:49:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn... all this gold getting thrown around, and I'm here like  #175;\_( #12484;)_/ #175;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-14 03:26:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a pretty poor teaching strategy. The teacher should make a test for him that will allow him to meet the same objectives as the other students, but not have his low reading level become a reason to not test what he has learned. If he answer all 27 and only missed 4, maybe his reading is better than people credit him. This is just a shit way for this teacher not making accommodations for this student's disabilities.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-31 21:31:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could you ELI5? I have never used any type of torrent stuff before, so like what torrent site is good, how do I do it, etc? You know, newb questions...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-31 21:46:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's awesome, thank you for answering for me! I will give it a go later!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-08 05:42:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shores of Time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-11 17:13:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have ran VoG only a handful of times, and from my experiences there were the people that were good at the relic and nobody else would want to run with it. Other times, if someone offered to do the relic and didn't do it well, everyone would get mad and someone else who had some experience would do it. That is just what I have seen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Material Exchange Question</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-23 00:28:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know that material exchange has become a thing since HoW dropped, and it is great. I am wondering how to exchange my Ascendant Shards for Ascendant Energy... I can do it the the other way with the speaker, but I have a lot of shards, and not enough Energy. Is there someone else I need to go to for this or is the speaker the the main guy for this?... Any help is great! Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-10 23:25:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll run it. GT: mealsMD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-18 18:12:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>RED DEATH!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-26 23:57:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you can, there are some really cool things that are in southern oregon that may be reasonable to hit on your way to crater lake. First, in Winston, there is a drive through and walk through zoo called Wildlife Safari. It is pretty cool if you like that kind of stuff. Second, the Oregon Caves farther south are a really cool stop as well. It is a nice stop and you can check out and take a tour deep into some really cool caves. Third (time permitting), Hells Gate jet boating excursions up the Rogue River. You can do half day or full day trips that are pretty fun, especially if you get a fun boat captain and a fun people on the boat with you. Oregon is a pretty cool place. There are quite a few destinations not too far of of I-5 that are pretty dang cool. Have fun, relax, and enjoy our delicious microbrews!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-26 23:59:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>And most of these stops are just off or I-5 if you end up coming down that way instead of the coast route.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-04 18:16:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shit! Well, at least we still Meyers.....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-07 18:18:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>We're a simple minded folk</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Toshiba LED TV keeps switching between very blurry and normal every 2-3 seconds.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-30 05:41:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>So the title says it all. My 50" Toshiba LED TV keeps switching from blurry to normal every 2 to 3 seconds and it will not stop. I just turned it on and it was doing this. It was not doing this yesterday. The TV is in a room that stays at about 85 degrees, but I have never had this issue before. Any suggestions or information would be greatly appreciated. I would upload a video of it but I do not know how on my phone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-31 19:17:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I was a little kid I always thought that after you had sex, you would not be able to do anything for a couple days.. Like stay home sick or something. I have no idea why I thought that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-04 23:48:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn, the Sounders have no chill</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-05 01:22:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>The heat makes them irritable, like my bowels</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-05 20:44:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lamarcus Aldridge and Google Fiber.... I am starting to become envious of those living in San Antonio</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-20 00:41:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>75</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-24 23:34:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>The first day that I had my license, I was parking my car and misjudged my turning and hit another car. I left a small dent and about a 3 foot long gash in the side of this car. I panicked when I saw a lady and her son watch me do it, she looked me dead in the eyes and said "I didn't see anything" I said thanks and drove off. That lady was a saint. To this day I feel bad for what I did, but it was my first day with a license and I panicked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-27 00:20:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>My step dad actually played football with him for a couple years at a JUCO in Idaho called Treasure Valley. Said he was a pretty nice guy, but was a little on the wierd side.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-01 20:59:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is in my hometown. Everyone I know that attends the school is okay. 10 confirmed dead so far :( extremely unfortunate for a small place like Roseburg.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Chris Mints, the hero that charged the UCC shooter to help save others is doing fine after having surgery to remove 7 bullets. What a guy.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-02 15:17:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-02 15:25:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chris Mintz* is his name. Not Mints. Damn auto correct.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-02 21:03:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here you go for anyone that has interest in a gofundme for Chris and the other Survivors and families of the UCC shooting. https://www.gofundme.com/s75ge9y4</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-02 02:02:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I learned a little about this game in an adapted PE class I took in college. The ball we used had some kind of noise maker built into the ball, so it make a beeping sound when it was thrown or hits the ground. It is actually super fun. The ball is kind of heavy though so if you don't protect sensitive areas it may hurt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-20 17:41:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fire in the Sky. It's a movie about a guy getting abducted by aliens. It was shot in various locations around the county in Oregon I live in. The scene where the find him alive and naked was shot right in front of an old (now) shut down market in Winston, Oregon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-21 22:42:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm glad he got suspended; I'm not glad it is during FF playoffs...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-09 19:19:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know I am a little late to the party, but when I was in 6th grade, I was in a 6th/7th blend English class. We were sitting in groups of about 6 and one of the hottest girls in school at the time was in my group. She was (looking back now) kind of one of those "middle school sluts" that has a new boyfriend every week. She was the only girl in the group and she was asking all of the guys in the group how often they masturbate. Most of the guys said a few times a week, everyday, but when she got to me, I was at a loss of words because I had never done it and was unsure of a normal amount, so I just said "occasionally"... went home immediately after school and dry jerked myself raw. Found out a few times later that lotion and a couple pictures of hot girls really helped the process. After that, just like any middle school boy, I did it whenever I had the chance. TLDR: girl in middle school asked how much I masturbated, had never done it before, discovered something beautiful. Edit: words</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-10 02:51:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was at that game! craziest sporting event I have ever seen in person. That place was rockin sooo hard during that comeback</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-08 07:39:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>What teams we you watching? I have a friend who I went to high school with that plays in Italy for Seamen Milano.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-14 20:48:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Imelda Staunton will forever be Dolores Umbridge</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-27 02:25:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>One time I was in a bunker and had to put the numbers 4, 8, 15 ,16, 23, 42 into a computer every 108 minutes. I did good for awhile until some people came and messed me up....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-30 00:26:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>What a coincidence... seeing this posted and this is the same day... http://espn.go.com/blog/pittsburgh-steelers/post/_/id/19272/watch-james-harrison-and-friends-use-a-medicine-ball-to-play-volleyball?ex_cid=espnfb</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Potential first time home buyer with some questions about what might happen at a meeting with a lender tomorrow</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-07 02:53:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tomorrow, my fiance and I are going into a home lender in our area and we are going to talk about what it takes to get this process rolling. Background on us: both of us have just finished our first year teaching and we like the area we are at, and are tired of renting. We pay $1150 in rent a month right now, and we want to buy our first home. I am worried what might happen tomorrow, because between the both of us, we have around $200,000 in debt with student loans and our cars, etc. Our combined income a year before taxes is about $70,000, and both of our credit scores are higher than 670. I guess what I am getting at is, those of you with experience in this, what are we more than likely going to be told tomorrow? Or what tends to happen with people in our similar financial state. Also, any helpful advise or questions should we ask during our meeting? Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-01 06:41:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>But now you die!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This guy is currently in the store yelling at the manager for overcharging him on a case of Pabst.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-15 22:55:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-16 01:59:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did not see a handicap tag in the guys window, and he seemed perfectly healthy, besides a Pabst beer gut. I know often times just because someone doesn't look it doesn't mean they aren't, but I believe with all my being, that this man was not handicapped. I just think he was just too pissed to care.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-16 05:19:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is! Roseburg to be exact.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-16 05:20:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes it is! In Roseburg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-17 04:01:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>3456</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-29 01:05:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just missed it at black friday! Would love to get chosen for this! Thanks for doing this!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-01 20:33:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pick Me! Pick Me!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-15 19:04:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry about the problem, but that looks fuckin groovy man  #9996;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 02:12:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>What a cunt</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just a few days after pulling 4 Tyreke Hill cards... awesome.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-23 05:24:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Discerning the Transmundane quest question</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-26 05:43:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I am at a stand still in this quest. It will not let me progress to the collecting of the blood. I gave the Lexicon to Septimus and now it will not trigger the next phase... I know I am supposed to be level 15 for it to continue, but and I am level 24 and still nothing... anyone have any suggestions or help you could offer me? Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-26 23:15:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have done everything I need to continue the quest. Even in the quest menu all of the diamonds are completely filled in. It will just not let me move to the next step for some reason..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-19 21:33:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pick me! Pick me!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-22 05:09:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would love to get a piece of that BF1 action!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-17 18:30:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey Adriana! I used to follow your public snapchat, and it seems for a while there, you had issues with people reporting you. Why the fuck would someone follow an adult performer and report when she is doing sexy stuff? Wtf. Anyway, have you just kind of given up on the public snap and moved to a private one? Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-17 17:26:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can't sell my legends collectable</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-20 22:31:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got a 2003 Orlando Pace collectable when I completed the legends live event the other day, but I am unable to sell it.. When I look at the auction house, there are a bunch for sale, but mine is non-auctionable.. also, is there a set for each of the legend players that I am not seeing? Cause if i can't sell it, I would at least like to put it in a set towards Pace.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-21 00:59:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have completed the first Brady set. I am almost level 18, but if there are legends sets for each of the legend players, I'm still not seeing them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-21 01:43:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I figured it out.. I needed to do all the madden wheel sets at least once... cool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>AVCHD to DVD. Please help!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 16:42:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know if this is the place for this... but I am a football coach, and I am having a few issues trying to put game film onto a DVD. The camera we are using is a JVC that records and saves in AVCHD format.. I just recently purchased a DVD Writer to take the film from my camera and burn DVD's for my other coaches and what not. The DVD writer came with the software NERO. It seems that the AVCHD format will not burn to a DVD and play on my computer or DVD player... what do I need to do to make this happen? Would prefer a free/cheap solution to this problem if possible.. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 18:15:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the response. The issue is that it is about 160 separate small videos... they start and stop after every play, so there is really no extra video that needs taken out, Unfortunately..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 00:49:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>They can do it, we just play on Friday, and would like film before Monday of the next school week......</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-26 19:00:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nothing, cause I'm broke as shit lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Apparently I was sent to collections..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 13:43:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>So, my wife and I rented a house for about a year and a half. We had our power through Pacific Power. We moved out in June because we found someone to take over the lease, and they did so in July. Well I guess we either forgot to pay the final bill, or thought we had paid it, but actually didn't. I don't know. Whatever the case we are sitting here right now looking at our credit karma and it says my wife was sent to collections a couple days ago.. We logged into Pacific power and it said they sent the last email in August stating we had a bill of $120 and some change. We never received any other type of correspondence, no other bills or calls or anything saying that we are past due or are about to be sent to collections since then. We have also not recieved any notification yet that we are in collections.. What should I do now? Do I call Pacific power and try to talk to them? Do I just call the debt collector? I don't know. Any help would be greatly appreciated.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 17:58:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the responses, I really appreciate it. We just spoke to Pacific Power and they have sold it to a collection agency about 2 hours south of us. We just tried calling them, but they are closed until Monday, so we will be trying again then. The lady from Pacific power said that the "should" remove it from my credit once it is paid.. I will make sure to get all that in writing, obviously.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-28 01:33:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used to work at a subway as a closer. Cleaning the nozzles was one of my closing chores. I had to use a clean bowl and fill it with the bleach water used for cleaning dishes and take each nozzle off, clean it, and let them sit for like 30 minutes in the bleach water. I tried getting away with not doing it once and got in some trouble...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Credit question relating to a mortgage</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 20:43:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wife and I are trying to purchase a home. We went into the bank 2 months ago and when we got our credit pulled, mine was great, and hers, not so much. When we went in, the only reference of score we might have was the free fico scores that are offered through our credit cards, and they were pretty damn close to the actual  #8220;middle #8221; scores that showed on our actual credit report.... Those scores only change once a month, and her most recent one pulled on 1/23 #8230; Since then we have had substantial payments towards our credit cards, and had a collections account closed #8230; If we were to go in, say tomorrow, would the credit pulled by the bank be as of that day, or from like 2 weeks ago like we are seeing online? So basically is the score constantly changing, or is it just updated every few weeks, and we need to wait?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 20:53:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay. I checked credit karma and it seems they have everything up to date... Hopefully it will reflect that way when we go in again!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 21:49:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just thought I would let you know, we went back in a few weeks ago and re-ran our credit scores, and after all those payments her score went down by 6! Wtf! Anyways, our PMI at a much higher rate than it should be, and we had to pay a little extra to get our credit rate down, but we are 10 days away from closing! It all worked out in the end I guess lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 22:23:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow.. I just had my game pass expire, and literally just put in Halo 5 to play with a buddy, and it is giving me the same thing it said for you.. "Looks like you need to renew Xbox Game Pass". I just want to play some Halo!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Did we get a solution to the problem of not being able to play some games after Game Pass expires? I haven't been able to play Halo 5 for seven days now...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 17:36:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know it was brought up a few days ago, just don't know if we had heard of a solution yet. Seems a little ridiculous that this is happening.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 17:55:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do. I have a physical copy of the game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 18:07:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have not tried this yet. I will give it a go.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 23:07:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I cancelled it. Didn't have enough time to warrant $10 a month for it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 00:50:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not yet, been working all day</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 00:00:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>My buddy and I have been calling it Valhalla</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>