<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject4510</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-13 23:49:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have a 7 week old son. I am going back to work full time and my husband will be a SAHD. Right now he probably does 75% of feedings and changing as I EP and they usually happen at the same time. We split the cooking and cleaning duties pretty equally I'd say.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-20 19:36:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rock N Play has been fantastic for us. Also our Pack N Play came with a changer/napper that comes off to use separately and it gets used a lot, especially the changing table side.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-22 00:36:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your period will regulate soonest if you just continue to take the pills despite any bleeding you have. Just keep taking them and you should be on track by month 3 on the pill.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>OS update yday, now MMS not loading?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-11 19:39:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anyone else having this issue or any fix ideas? Using stock messaging app</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-23 03:17:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi there. I EP for my 12 week old. My biggest suggestion is to make sure you're eating enough calories. I don't know if you're constantly hungry like me but you need 20 calories/oz pumped so perhaps experiment with a few extra snacks per day and see if that helps at all. Otherwise lots of fluids and some people think a Gatorade per day helps them replenish electrolytes which helps supply. Good Luck!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-23 19:45:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>My almost 3 month old doesn't have a schedule yet either. The only structure I've tried to give him has been waking him by 6 pm if he is napping and shooting for an 8 pm bedtime. His naps are still pretty erratic and we go with his flow throughout the day otherwise. Depending on how much activity there has been during the day, he sleeps for 3 hr stretches at night if he had a lot of naps or will sleep 8 hours if we were out and about. We do not intentionally keep him awake otherwise and get him a nap if he is fed/changed and still cranky. I hope this makes sense. He sleeps in his crib in his room in case you're wondering about that aspect.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-28 20:26:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>OP, I am an attending physician who is not that long out of residency. You don't have to tell me but I'm going to assume you may be in a surgical specialty. If not, I would think you'd get more time and almost be forced to take more time. I understand your situation is very difficult. I would suggest taking the 4 weeks and just pushing back graduation but I do understand where you're coming from. Physically you probably could swing it but it is not the best thing for you, baby, or patients. Do you have a physician mentor you could reach out to about this? That might be worth a try. It's difficult for people outside of your situation to have perspective about your reality. Getting another job isn't an option. Nothing against those with advice, just saying that OP having this question isn't as unreasonable as it may seem. PM me with any questions. I have a 12 week old, SAHD, but I'm an attending with much more flexibility at this point in my career. Good luck with whatever you choose and prioritize yours and babies health no matter what. You can't do your job if you're not healthy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-02 16:06:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just the other day I sung to our 3 month old and made funny faces he likes to distract him while DH cut his nails. Worked like a charm.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-05 00:16:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Congratulations! I have been EPing for 5 months now and didn't intend to. We had the same struggles and attempting to latch really upset my LO and therefore upset me. There's a great facebook group if you're on fb that is helpful to those exclusively pumping.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-05 01:57:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes but it is searchable. Just type in exclusively pumping. Over 10k members. Also there's a secret over supply group if you make more than your LO eats per day. I would comment in the regular group that you want to join and an admin should message you. Feel free to pm me any pumping questions too!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-13 15:45:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Strange Wilderness</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-24 19:29:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Similar story here. Now that we have a baby, we have set the precedent that we are staying home Christmas Eve and day. In past years, we tried to split the time extremely evenly and everyone was still irritated. You can't be everywhere at the same time no matter how much you wish you could. We did Christmas with in laws weekend before and head to my side weekend after. We are loving it and they're getting used to the idea. Good luck and enjoy your holiday!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-27 16:54:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you ask if it can be mixed into something that tastes better?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-29 21:40:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>My baby has been "sleeping through the night" for 6 weeks. It feels like it has been 6 months. How quickly everyone forgets. I try to take these comments and gain perspective from them. LO won't be this little and precious for long, so I smile and nod. They're annoying but are also expressing some insecurity about something in their own lives with these types of comments.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-11 13:05:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you have a keurig? If so I've found that the plain hot water you can get from it is much hotter than the hottest tap water and the bottles warm super quickly!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-14 21:26:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your total cholesterol is truly irrelevant because total is a calculation that adds up all the different types of cholesterol. Your HDL cholesterol is sky high which is good cholesterol so this is excellent. This high HDL makes your total high. Your LDL, or bad cholesterol, is a little higher than ideal but under 130 and you'd be perfect. You do not need medication, just some improvement in diet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-15 12:01:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's basically just a bookkeeping thing where anything on lab reports as out of range is flagged. There is always context. There is no point in which HDL becomes too high, the higher the better. Exercise helps to raise it and women typically have higher HDL at baseline because of estrogen. This partially helps their longevity. The 90 something year old women in the world almost universally have nice and high HDLs. Consider yourself lucky! ;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-15 19:39:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>We aren't on facebook either. I find that giving a little by allowing others to post a limited number of pictures of our LO, after they ask, goes a long way. You have to do what you feel comfortable with and if people aren't following your rules you should definitely speak up. There is no way to avoid having our kid on social media all together but I see a distinct difference in proud grandparents vs. myself documenting their every move without their consent. Some may disagree but this is how I look at it for now. As an aside, there is a great app called Notabli that we use to post pictures and videos and it's specifically designed for kids. It's kind of like scrapbooking and we have a very limited group of people we invited and who follow along. May be worth checking out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-05 16:07:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Once they can roll themselves it's fine to leave them. Just make sure you aren't swaddling anymore so they can physically move again if they need to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Adjust calories w/fitbit</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-17 21:26:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do any of you adjust calories that appear in my fitness pal if you have it linked to your fitbit or am I best served just sticking with the keto calculator kcal recommendation? Thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-17 22:40:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-19 21:33:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are definitely gaining muscle. If you plan to stick with Crossfit the scale is going to become irrelevant. If your clothes fit better and you're performance in the gym is improving over time, you shouldn't even bother weighing yourself. It's going to frustrate you even though you're a lot healthier. Also when I did crossfit I had to eat a lot, you may consider increasing calories a little bit to see if you start losing. Good job!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-23 17:54:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Need to see HDL and LDL</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-25 13:54:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>While it won't fix the underlying problem, you really need to be drinking a ton of water. That will help keep it under 12 but if the parathyroid continues to become more and more hyperactive, you may need it removed. That has nothing to do with keto and if anything you want to continue to lose weight so that in the event of surgery, you're a low risk patient.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-25 14:03:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kirkland (Costco brand) broccoli cheddar soup is my favorite and it's 3g net carb per 8 oz. Usually fits my macros easily and very rich and filling.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-25 16:20:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I tend to do things cold turkey to get them over with so we just stopped giving them one day. He went on a milk-out-of-a-cup strike of sorts for a few days and would only drink water but we kept offering and now he's drinking milk out of his cups. Started reading him a story in his room in place of his bottle before bed and it's working out ok so far. Although I do acknowledge he's been pretty easy to transition from stuff like this throughout his life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Coca cola freestyle machines</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-26 13:41:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does anyone know if the flavorings you add to powerade zero are still no carb? Out of the bottle powerade zero grape is fine but I got a little nervous with the machine thinking that if the grape flavor going into plain sprite is the same as they're giving me for powerade zero it might be full of sugar. Maybe there's no way to know but I like a treat along with my five guys bunless sometimes. Will just skip it if I have to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-26 14:27:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>My baby naturally wants to touch the stove and stick his fingers into outlets. I don't let him do it until he naturally grows out of it. Sleep training is one of the best things we ever did and he is very well rested and thriving. We did it for him, not for us.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-26 14:53:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think this recommendation mostly is in place to help parents avoid direct sunlight as much as possible. Like if you can't use sunscreen, the babies just can't be out in the hot sun. In reality, if there's no choice and they're going to be out in the sun, sunscreen is the way to go. Maybe try some on a small area of skin ahead of time to make sure no reaction.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-28 01:56:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anything outside your house after 7 pm that you enjoy doing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-29 01:05:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes if I was OP wife, not cheating, and turned up pregnant after he had a vasectomy, I'd be freaking out at the urologist and demanding my husband go for sperm testing immediately! Either that or I'd prepare for the second coming of Christ.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-29 18:06:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I only do it to keep my calories down. Just started skipping breakfast since I felt just as hungry at lunch time whether I ate breakfast or not. Do whatever works to keep you within your macros.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-07 03:12:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a female with a ton of male friends, I always make it a point to meet and include their SOs in our interactions. I wouldn't want my husband going out 1 on 1 with a female friend all the time so I just always include him and my friend's SOs in everything we do. It works out fine and makes everyone more comfortable. Sometimes you have to flip the situation around and be honest with yourself about how you would feel if roles were reversed. Might help you see how you should handle situations like this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-09 02:39:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you can't bunt and can't get the guy on 3rd home with 0 outs (twice), you can't be an MLB utility guy. At least not on our first place team.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-13 13:10:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it depends on your goals. I exclusively pumped so a big freezer stash for me meant I could quit pumping at a certain point and LO would still get breast milk the first year. If I direct breastfeed next time, it will be less important to me personally. Just depends on your situation and/or your goals.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-13 19:16:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>While I wasn't keto when I pumped, your supply drop could have more to do with your period than keto. Although your period irregularity could be due to keto and so on... I think your best bet is going to be get your calories no matter what and let it play out for the next 4-6 weeks to see what your periods do and how your supply goes. Lactating is confusing to the body and then keto is another metabolic change so if I were you I'd just fuel my body and wait and see.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-15 23:14:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Android user and we love notabli. We use it to share pics and videos with family without using conventional social media. I think you can order photo books and stuff directly too but I haven't done this yet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-19 00:06:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Post this to /r/personalfinance and see what they think.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-25 00:11:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was our experience too until I think about 9 months old. Then it became around 6 or 630. Now 13 months old and getting to 7. I think you just have to wait but it'll get better in time. I'm sorry, it's rough. Such a big difference between 5 and 6 imo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-25 14:19:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's no difference in what the medication is, the difference is in the concentration. So basically just check a dosing chart to see what amount is more appropriate to give to your LO.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-25 14:27:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I know, it's confusing. The paranoia we get about giving kids the wrong stuff makes things even worse. I think if it were for myself I'd be like wtf and just grab one haha.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-25 14:37:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think your wife has anxiety and it's manifesting itself by trying to control everything about your daughter's life. This is not healthy for either of them. You need to talk to her about this in depth, but please do not mention how you make 100% of the income. You both have contributions and that shouldn't be the reason why you get say in these decisions. The reason is that you are her father and have been there for her throughout her life and want to be involved. I say this as a full time working mom with a stay at home husband. It would hurt his feelings if my reason for what we should buy was that I make the money so I get to choose.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-26 03:49:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>If she's in the hospital giving birth and is depending on the babysitting, then no, she can't get away for 1 day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-28 22:40:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did exact same thing, Vegas and all. 10/10 would do again. If they are responsible adults and open to your parenting style, go for it. One thing that helped me was typing out instructions for them so they had a reference for common questions and how our days usually go. They appreciated it and everyone had a great time!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-05 01:44:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm interested!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-09 03:12:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think there needs to be a distinction here and maybe it's already been made but are they truly just study partners or are they friends who also study together? Personally I don't think I could spend that much time with someone, even if studying, without becoming their friend. I also don't think there's anything wrong with them being friends. I am F with a lot of M friends and I always make it a point to get to know their SOs just as I make sure my husband gets to know them. If I were you, I'd tell your husband that you'd like to get to know her better and invite her for coffee or something. If everything is how it seems, it would probably relieve some of his stress for you to get to know her better. You could also get more insight into their testing, careers, challenges, etc which may be helpful in your relationship. You don't need to be BFF but I think you would all benefit from the 2 of you knowing each other better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-12 03:39:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Becoming knowledgeable sports fans, not just casual. Understand strategy, rules, etc of any sport. I like almost all of them and watch them a lot, makes it tough to find female friends.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-20 21:21:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>You need to pursue legal guardianship of her and then you would control her finances. However she would either have to consent or her doctor would have to deem her unable to make these decisions for herself if the dementia is significant.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-23 00:01:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>King size bed if you don't already have one. Then get completely separate sheets and covers. If all else fails, separate beds aren't that big of a deal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-30 19:10:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's the difference between a chickpea and a garbanzo Bean? I wouldn't pay $100 for a garbanzo bean in my face.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-01 15:43:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Remember Jerry, it's not a lie if you believe it." - George Costanza</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-11 21:56:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anyone have a mock draft I can look at?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-09 23:39:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a mom of a toddler, Daniel Tiger's Neighborhood. TV gold.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-18 15:33:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>That the flu is nausea and vomiting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-25 15:56:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't ask someone when they're having another kid if they already have one. Don't tell them it's time. Then when they have 3 or 4 don't make jokes about it being too many. If they want you to know about their reproduction, they'll tell you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-02 02:35:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Vaccinate your children. On time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-06 00:30:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>To Kill A Mockingbird</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-08 22:30:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please see a doctor to help with your depression. Do you live close to any large hospitals? If so they may have a residency program in primary care that will see patients without insurance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-10 13:21:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Crock pot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-18 15:30:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Inadequate birth control options</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-21 01:17:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>My biggest concern in this situation is why is your ex girlfriend willing to attend the Christmas events with your family?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-26 23:28:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a female doctor and you are spot on. They're 2 completely different jobs. Maybe a detailed explanation of what each one entails when the education is complete would help him understand your preference for nursing. Nurses do things doctors aren't trained to do and vice versa. It works best in a team based approach. It's no different than saying you'd rather be a nurse than a respiratory therapist, physical therapist, pharmacist, etc. Unless he's purely basing what he thinks you should do on money. I'm not trying to project that onto him but it may be something to think about. Healthcare in any role is a very stressful but also rewarding career. It's not something to do for the money, that will lead you to a perhaps wealthy but unhappy life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Carrie Fisher dead at age 60</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-27 18:52:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-28 14:55:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Use nonstick spray before putting in ingredients for much easier clean up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>You're the worst season 3 question</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 21:31:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does anyone know when I could expect to stream this on Hulu? I can buy it for 20 bucks on amazon but don't mind waiting a month or 2 if it will be free that soon. TIA.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-15 16:07:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fight fair. We don't name call, ever. He doesn't yell as its not in his nature, I really try hard not to but it's more of a challenge for me. Have sex a few times a week, even if you don't feel like it at the beginning. Do nice things for one another. If you have kids, find time to still date each other without your kids. Talk things out. Be considerate in your decisions about how they effect your partner. Etc. Pretty much the golden rule that we're taught as kids is an easy way to simplify how to do well as a spouse.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-05 12:51:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>To Kill A Mockingbird</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-12 18:46:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>My Cleveland Indians making another run at the World Series</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-24 02:31:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>TDB if it's a BFD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-25 13:53:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>One Day At A Time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-25 23:49:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>MLB TV and download a VPN on your computer to put you outside the blank out market. I did read something just yesterday that STO was coming to Vue but don't hold me to that 100%.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-26 12:46:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>If there's no table in the men's room, go right into the women's room and use their table. My husband is a SAHD and has done this while propping the main bathroom door open with the trash can to let people know he's there/see why so there's no questions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-26 20:42:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fake news</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-02 17:51:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>21 Grams</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-05 18:53:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is she interested in? Does she go to any type of preschool? I would definitely encourage you to take her to your sons' events and sign her up for any sports or activities she is interested in. The benefits of sports is huge in girls and it would be a great way for you guys to bond. If she has friends at her school, maybe ask their moms for a play date swap? Not sure if you feel comfortable with that but it would expose her to an adult woman without strings attached. I'm sorry for your situation and wish you and your family the best.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-07 00:46:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cut up redskin potatoes, carrots, can of beer, and enough water to cover the brisket. 8 hours on low, you're good to go!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-07 13:21:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. Star WRs don't win you Super Bowls. Think about the last 5 teams to win them, look at their WR situation. If he can get 12-13 mil per year in the open market, good for him. I would bet it's not with a super bowl contender in the years of that contract. 2. If his name was Joe Smith and he was in the same situation on another team, and the Browns gave him 12-13 million per year, I would think it was a huge mistake. 3. Look at the best receivers in the league, with the exception of Julio, not real factors at the end. TP is 27 years old, not 23. That's a huge difference. I have nothing against him personally and he should get the most money he can, just forgive me if that's not necessarily with us. 4. Winning the super bowl means beating the Pats. We need to do everything we can to have a DOMINANT defense and find the QB of the next 10 years. 5. Just bc we have 100 million dollars doesn't mean we should spend it in an unwise fashion. That just makes us the redskins. 6. Sign him for max 10 mil/yr for 4 years, between 10-15 guaranteed. That's what he's worth. I won't be mad if he gets more than that with another team.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-10 03:22:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shania Twain. Bartender on the high roller in Vegas told us her handlers told the bartender she wasn't allowed to look at Shania.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-24 01:07:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Once upon a child</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-24 01:09:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are locations all over the city</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-24 13:43:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Vistaril just because it sounds fancy and when I use it for acute anxiety patients think they're getting something awesome</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-31 19:21:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's the question?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-31 19:51:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a family medicine doc, I wouldn't be caught dead on a peer to peer call about radiation. I don't know anything about it and tell my patients this very openly. As a doctor, you need to know what you don't know and own it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-02 12:46:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unfortunately I end up telling most of them to schedule an appointment as out office always has same or next day appts available, often with me. Until they come up with an RVU for phone calls, I cannot take time out of my schedule for phone call time. I don't make the system, I just have to work in it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-02 13:14:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Buddy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Breakfast farro, 290 calories per serving</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-02 16:02:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I made this today. Makes about 5 servings. Weighed everything out and total recipe weighed 1044g, 200g servings. Delicious, filing, and easy to make. The Greek yogurt and honey would be additional calories but probably jazz it up without too many added.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-02 16:02:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://patriciaspatticakes.com/2013/08/breakfast-farro-dried-fruit-apple-html/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-02 17:56:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>The conversation between Michelle Williams' and Casey Affleck's characters in Manchester By The Sea</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-02 18:04:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like to eat big portions</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-02 21:58:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>You need to nope the fuck out of these friendships</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-03 15:36:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Water flavoring stain</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-04 03:23:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>They have better stories to tell.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-05 02:19:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pop culture happy hour</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Open access scheduling</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-06 02:35:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does anyone here have any experience with open access scheduling, specifically in primary care? Pros/cons? Details on your model appreciated. I'm feeling inefficient at work where at times I'm overwhelmed but at other times not busy enough. I am also looking to simplify my scheduling template for front desk staff that has no clinical training. Thanks in advance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-07 16:28:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>If he's 14 and a known liar, why is he "off to a friend's house to work on a project" without either of his parents checking on this story?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-07 21:26:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>My husband stays home with our son while I work full time. He does more cleaning than me and definitely more child rearing. I enjoy cooking so I still do a good bit of that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-10 22:03:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rub garlic on fat side, roast for 20 min at 500, then at 325 until desired internal temperature. These can be found online.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-12 13:29:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>How would you feel if roles were reversed?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-14 00:57:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ibuprofen 600 mg as soon as I have the slightest feeling they're starting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-14 18:45:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I'm ever terminally ill, I will try to kill myself by eating all the French fries in the world</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-14 21:43:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just can't, as a woman who works full time and is the sole "breadwinner" for her family, it never ceases to amaze me how most of the sexism I've received in my life has been from other women. Tell her to get a grip.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-15 00:03:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've found taking myself as far away from the kitchen as possible for the night helps, also sometimes I just go to sleep lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-15 15:49:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Little Miss Sunshine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-15 20:52:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your mom needs help for crippling anxiety</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-16 17:52:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Strongly recommend she see a doctor to discuss treatment options including medication. I took it for 6 months after weaning because I was very anxious all of a sudden. Stopped it and doing fine for 3 months so far</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-16 20:40:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>How long do I have to watch Yan swing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-16 22:19:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Children deserve loving parents more than humans deserve anything else. You definitely did the right thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-16 23:11:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>30F, 5'10", SW 235, CW 206, 1st GW 180. TDEE 2080 currently, aim for 1500 cal/day. Working on couch to 5k for a little bigger deficit and to get in better shape.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-20 21:15:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>WWII vets. First hand accounts of the most important modern war.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-21 21:18:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Heyyy, I like my men like I like my eggs, over HARD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-21 21:21:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I drink aldi brand and most definitely grapefruit!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-21 21:35:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>What you should have done is told him that you saw it and how you were feeling. An adult conversation was called for here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-22 14:45:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>That if you shoot a bullet and drop a bullet at the same time from the same height, they hit the ground at the same time. (I know you have to control for other environmental factors.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-23 03:30:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Casual!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-23 15:35:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>For the rest of your life you will have that dream where you registered for a class and completely forgot about it until finals week and you're so fucked. Then you wake up sweaty but so relieved.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 16:21:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pump every 2-3 hours and eat and drink fluids like it's going out of style. Make sure when you pump you empty completely to let your body know you need more. There's an excellent facebook group for EPers that you would likely find very helpful and find camaraderie.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 22:31:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it's private. Go to other breastfeeding groups and ask for an invite. Sorry I forgot about that part.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 21:04:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>This sounds so pleasant</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-05 01:27:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rory Gilmore</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-05 01:58:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>21 Grams</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-05 17:37:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a physician FWIW. Given the location, your experience at urgent care vs at a local ER are likely the same. If you have access, I always recommend a pediatric specific urgent care or ER if possible. I don't mean this to be dismissive of your issue but even at the ER they would not have called in the plastic surgeon for a chin wound. This is done only in extreme circumstances with wounds of eyelids or other areas that are close to sensitive organs or very complex wounds where further procedures or skin grafting may be done. I have s scar on my forehead from childhood stitches and I have to point it out to people. It will fade over time but I wouldn't make a bigger deal about it than you need to. Don't bring it up to people once it's healed and give a matter of fact explanation of it if someone else does. If you make it seem like something to be embarrassed about to your child, she may be self conscious of it for no reason. Most people aren't going to notice very shortly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-06 00:39:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a doctor and a patient I was seeing - who is so obese that she's in a wheelchair - said that she eats salt and vinegar chips because "vinegar is healthy for you". I was speechless.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-06 16:33:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I try to imagine myself having a nice long life and an indulgence here or there isn't even a blip on the radar. Try to imagine your weight loss curve going on for your entire life. This makes the day to day fluctuations easier to take and gets me back on track without saying "ah screw it"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-06 22:02:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, the patent to no treatments available at all and certain miserable death has run out so now patients and families have something to at least try. Do a very small amount of research before commenting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-12 03:52:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Burger King original chicken sandwich. Ooh my the mayo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-12 04:32:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>How was this test done? A blood test? Were you tested for it last year?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-12 04:35:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>SHHHHHHEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIT</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-17 22:32:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lint licker</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-18 12:42:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Absolutely nothing wrong with you. I didn't date until 23 and I am very happy with how things turned out. In 10 years take a look around and I think you'll be pleased with how your dating life has set you up for your whole life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-18 12:50:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I look in their ears I tell them the light is gonna shine through and hit the wall. However I only say this one to people I already know and have a good sense of humor. Sometimes there's no place for joking.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-18 23:41:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've never been stung by a bee</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-19 22:54:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kirkland light.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-20 01:41:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unfortunately the pendulum has swung so far in the other direction that sales reps have lost their jobs and patients can no longer get any samples. The sweet spot was somewhere between all inclusive vacations and not even being allowed to take a pen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-23 01:33:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are some kids who don't stand a chance from the beginning. This poor child.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-23 20:18:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a doctor and this is bad advice. Get to your goal weight, take a woman's daily vitamin if you don't eat much dairy, and enjoy your new found health.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-25 13:10:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm finishing next week. Right now running 3x per week. Do you recommend a 4th run as the long run or just making the 3rd run longer? Not sure when you incorporate a 4th run.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-25 19:06:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>My son was the same way. I think the most important thing is efforts to communicate and engage with you. Is she interested in you, pointing at things, etc? My son started talking all of a sudden around 22 months and is now saying new things every single day. He turns 2 this week. If she's babbling and interactive I wouldn't worry just yet. On the flip side, an evaluation does no harm and if there's an issue the sooner the better to start interventions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-26 13:36:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>ScarJo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-26 13:42:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Primary care doc here. This does sound concerning. How many patients do you see per day and how long do you spend with them? They may think you have enough care time with counseling to bill a level 5 which is 40 minutes of care, 50% face to face counseling. However if this is the case, you should be documenting the time, and the exact minutes of the day if possible. If not, I would start job searching as an audit will have consequences. Not worth it when primary care PA jobs should be fairly available.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-27 01:23:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>The English Patient</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-28 02:16:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Joffrey Baratheon from Game of thrones</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-28 14:49:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mulholland Drive</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-28 15:56:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>During labor, pitocin, and epidural kept wearing off in the left lower part of my stomach.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 02:45:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honda odyssey, 10/10 would buy again</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 12:32:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Give me whatcha got for a pork chop</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-05 16:33:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>How they treat those who work in the service industry</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Redditors who hold up traffic driving slowly in the left lane, what are you thinking?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 21:39:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-11 04:03:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Columbus, Ohio!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-13 00:35:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>To Kill A Mockingbird, not as good as the book but damn close</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-22 01:30:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sending thank you notes, I think they're redundant as I always thank people in person when I receive a gift.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-23 16:54:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Look up the cycle of abuse. You're just in the cycle and if you don't end the relationship round and round you'll go.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-24 23:53:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Almost 31 years old and ran the furthest I have in my life today, 4 miles.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-25 02:20:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Death of a family member with assets</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-26 01:46:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm most concerned that such an issue has caused you enough grief to make a reddit post about it. We're talking about a 4 year old's birthday party right? Or am I in the twilight zone? It's time to teach your child that the world does not revolve around them. Do it now, or the world will do it later and the stakes will be much higher.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-29 22:36:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here's hoping she lives long enough to serve them all</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-01 02:46:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>budget bytes spinach chickpea rice pilaf mmmmmm</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-01 03:22:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tell her it was her generation's job to raise us so I guess they weren't such great parents after all</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-02 00:26:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Asking people when they're going to have kids. Maybe they're pregnant, maybe they're trying, maybe they've been trying for 2 years without success, or maybe they're never having kids at all. No matter what, it's none of your business until they volunteer the information in their own time, if ever.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-02 02:24:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Boss makes a dollar, I make a dime, that's why I poop on company time!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-02 23:58:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Being able to pee standing up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-03 00:01:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>No favorite shampoo but I'm obsessed with Kirkland conditioner</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-03 21:56:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Old navy for casual, new York  amp; company for work</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-06 01:46:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>CONGRATS ON THE SEX CARLOS!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-06 16:12:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gone Girl totally pissed me off. I hated everyone which I guess is the point, but it didn't make me enjoy or appreciate the movie.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-06 19:12:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I chew gum all day long</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 15:33:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a primary care doctor and went through residency while engaged to my now husband. He managed to survive my busy schedule without screwing some random. Quit making excuses for this douche bag.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 20:04:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please stop driving drunk before you kill someone or yourself</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 20:32:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, thanks for clarifying and thanks for not driving</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 20:43:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>He also has never bothered to learn how to read.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-12 00:16:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just leave her be. She's doing great. Your pressure in this area is probably hurtful to her to be honest. There's nothing wrong with her or her life. Please accept that and enjoy your self -sufficient daughter.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-13 03:12:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>The feeling of panty hose on my legs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-13 04:19:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jim Gaffigan ftw</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 16:20:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Come at the king, you best not miss</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 19:20:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're the smartest person in the room, you're in the wrong room Show me your friends, I'll show you your future Not my monkeys, not my circus Don't set yourself on fire to keep others warm</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 15:32:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Longest run ever at 5 miles, also getting better at eating a little more so I don't feel horrible running while still losing weight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 18:32:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know your exact situation but I get a 1099 in January for their contributions to my student loan payments so you'll be taxed on it then I'd guess. Just ask them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 18:33:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Little Miss Sunshine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-18 00:00:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I sincerely hope you get a resolution and necessary treatments for your son. I wanted to comment to say that as an attending physician, who was once a medical student, thank you for talking to the student. If you ever encounter a student again and have an opinion about the interaction positive or negative, please take a moment to tell the physician they are working with in private. It is very useful information to both the doctor and the student which can tell them what they're doing right and where they need to improve. Almost all medical students are eventually doctors and we like to put the very best version of them out there in the world.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-19 02:49:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eat all the food and drink all the water</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 19:46:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Girl, living in a lonely world. I'll see myself out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Thank you Dolans</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 17:55:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a Cleveland sports fan, even with the Tribe's struggles as of late, it is refreshing to have a team to come to with a functional owner and front office that is focused on baseball. The extra noise in town is exhausting and frustrating. I don't think they get enough credit at times although I think us fans are more appreciative now than ever. Go Tribe!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-29 16:33:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you don't like the answer, change the question</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-29 21:29:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it varies by state. Where I live you get a result on about 10 things and the result is typically sent as low risk which is normal. I think an abnormal result returns as "mutation detected". No quantitative results are given on the screening test as the purpose of them is to identify those who need specific testing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-30 22:18:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mussels</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 22:25:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Still like our chances in open AL. If you can pitch you can make WS. Worry about Dodgers when/If you have to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 22:31:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stuck behind someone going the speed limit in the left lane and someone right next to them, also going the speed limit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Indians Austin Jackson robs Hanley Ramirez at Fenway</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-02 03:14:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-03 12:57:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Certain concerns require them to do something else to prepare for the doctor. Usually this isn't the case, so that's why they tell you to bring it up when the doctor comes in. It's sort of a screening process.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-04 15:02:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you read the book? At 6 months old they do not need to eat in the middle of the night but they certainly will. I highly recommend reading the book as he explains all of this. You can skip a good amount that doesn't apply to your situation even though it seems like a long book.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-04 16:05:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was much easier to do the Ferber method after reading the book and understanding why it is a good thing to do for your child. He explains how many hours can pass between feedings at various ages. I cannot recommend you read it highly enough before trying to implement the methods.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-04 23:57:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Zoom out!!!!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-06 16:58:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh no</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-11 02:27:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hope this defense is in shape bc they're gonna be on the field A LOT</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-13 19:37:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Littering</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-13 20:40:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Budget bytes spinach chick pea rice pilaf</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-19 21:51:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good regimens for symptom control (hycodan if appropriate patient), work note within reason, prednisone if cough really bad, delayed Rxs for antibiotics on day 10 of illness if really no improvement, etc. Basically they paid to come in, so provide as much relief as possible without antibiotics. Also education about c.diff typically helps sometimes as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-19 22:00:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Napoleon dynamite</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-22 21:58:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>What kind of job are you looking for and what are the salaries? How frugal are you now, what are your expenses now?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Osweiler not playing 3rd preseason game</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 16:41:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-30 02:48:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rory Gilmore. Absolute monster.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 17:39:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>People with no student loan debt</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tweet from @JeffPassan: Zimmer out for season</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-11 19:41:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 23:36:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Strange wilderness, I find it absolutely hilarious</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-15 03:37:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Got my wisdom teeth pulled after age 30 today. Get that shit done early kids!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-21 00:01:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a PCP and never enjoyed anything about the hospital so take this with a grain of salt. I think with a young family primary care has a great lifestyle. Also, job demand is high and compensation is on the rise. You can get some nice packages/ benefits, especially if going to an area with high primary care need. Paperwork is there of course but if you have good staff it mostly comes down to signing a bunch of stuff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-27 01:11:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>In 2 weeks the lesions will have crusted over and won't be contagious anymore. Also, since they're up to date on vaccines, they had the chicken pox shot at age 1 and likely would have been fine regardless.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-30 12:38:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very much so. I'm a PCP so generally on the low acuity side of things. What I struggle with most is seeing my patients at work with their struggles and sickness. I'm often times just giving support and reassuring them about their specialist care. When I go home, it is often difficult to focus or sympathize with comparably trivial problems that my extended family or friends are dealing with. I struggle because I know that their problems are real to them but I can't help but think about Mr. Doe and his stage 4 cancer or Mrs. Smith and her heroin addicted daughter. It's hard to not think "get a real problem" but who am I to say that? This makes me feel isolated because I don't feel like I relate to people outside of medicine. My other doctor friends get this, my parents, siblings, and non medical friends don't.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-03 19:56:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you breastfeeding and/or on medication for ppd/ppa?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-03 21:35:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gotcha well then it is probably more breastfeeding hormones in play. They are nature's way of keeping you from getting pregnant again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-15 16:02:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mulholland Drive</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-03 01:16:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>True crime garage, the Bill Simmons podcast</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 19:44:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>But win against Oklahoma got us in last year... Each year is different</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Clippers clubhouse manager suddenly passes away</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 01:21:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 01:22:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gofundme set up for family. His wife is pregnant with twins and due in March. Seems like a great guy and numerous tributes from current and former players on Twitter for those interested.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 01:23:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.gofundme.com/the-26th-man-matt-pruzinski</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Alonso at Cavs game</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 01:45:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-25 22:57:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>The flu does not cause nausea and vomiting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 20:27:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Google duo is great</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 01:53:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Our since passed away lab ate our son's umbilical cord almost immediately after it fell off and before we could stop her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 02:45:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm by no means a dog expert but I do have a 6 month old female lab puppy that we've had since age 11 weeks. We had a lab previously but I wasn't involved in the 1st 9 months of training so this was new to me. The great thing about her is that she's wonderful with my toddler son and very eager to please. We haven't had any issues with dog aggression other than wanting to too aggressively play with other dogs/people. This leads to jumping and over excitation when strangers or other dogs greet her. We are constantly working on not jumping. The other big things are chewing which was constant and fairly frustrating until she lost her"baby" teeth at about 4-5 months old. She still likes to chew but isn't mouthy constantly when we're petting her. The shedding we're used to but don't mind as they really don't require any other grooming and we'd rather vacuum some and tolerate hair than have to get a dog to a groomer regularly. Also, I'm intolerant to much barking and have found labs to be excellent in regards to barking if someone comes but quickly stopping once they realize it's a welcome guest. They also don't alert bark to every little thing, person, animal outside. Let me know if any more questions, happy to help with my little lab experience as I can. If she's well exercised, she's a dream. You just have to take the time to walk/play fetch and you'll have a much better time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 01:02:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kindly remind them that the Browns have won a playoff game more recently than the Bungles</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 01:20:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>TDB if it's a BFD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 20:25:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>We do not need a locker room headache. The chiefs are getting rid of him in his prime. Our organization is not stable enough to get him in line.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 01:01:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't see it mentioned here but I use the Garmin Vivoactive HR. I thought the calorie burn was more accurate than my previous Fitbit and enjoyed the GPS for running and biking. All around good activity tracker.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 03:31:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I graduated medical school at 24. Telling people you're a doctor changes how they treat you. Telling people you were one at that young of an age can scare some off. I guess that's how I ended up with a lot of friends who work in some form of health care.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 00:23:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://haveyouhadthatbabyyet.com/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 01:36:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Preventing osteoporosis</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 16:00:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because after the baby is born it is not the OB's patient. Infant withdrawal is a life threatening condition and if missed has dire consequences. The liability if missed is squarely the pediatrician's.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 02:45:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also an option is to not take the benzo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Manhunt: Unabomber on Netflix</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 15:58:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have been lacking time and looking for shows that are a little bit less of a commitment. This was excellent and interesting to me as I was young enough that I didn't know a ton about the story. Great performances and kept me entertained for all 7 episodes. Has anyone else watched?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Setting a timer has helped us tremendously</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 01:34:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just a tip that may help those struggling with transitions. My son is almost 3 and we just started setting either the oven timer or phone timer to notify him it is time to do something else, leave somewhere, etc. I tell him "when the timer goes off we need to go home" and it goes over so much better than if myself or his dad just tell him it's time to leave in 5 minutes. YMMV.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 03:39:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>The conversation in Manchester by the Sea</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 22:49:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Roll tide</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 18:47:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Calories and fluids! I exclusively pumped with my first and eating and drinking helped my supply a ton</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 01:38:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Once you get the acute issue settled, I took sunflower lethicin from Amazon twice per day with my first and never had any clogs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 15:29:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Family medicine physician here. It is very difficult to be in a relationship with a physician. I am probably one of the more laid back ones you will find and I still find myself addicted to it at times. It is more than just a job and therefore the people who are drawn to it often times put it before everything else in their lives. Personally, I am lucky now to have reasonable hours and responsibility that allow me to be a mom and wife as well. You can debate how detrimental our attitudes are to our own mental health and probably come up with a good argument that the ways doctors are wired is not healthy. However, it is this same obsession that makes a lot of us good at our jobs. We have tried to balance it for years with work hour restrictions and wellness programs, but unfortunately most of us will put ourselves through almost anything to do this job. It is similar to a military culture and if you aren't happy in that type of relationship, that is completely fine. You deserve to have your needs met too and it just may be that your girlfriend will never be able to do that for you. Medicine might come first for her forever.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 01:59:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>If it is continuous leave and certainly for short term disability, I make them get an evaluation and participate in either intensive outpatient or partial hospitalization program</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 02:30:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm so impressed. I'm 32 weeks and had to have my husband tie one of my shoes today.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 20:20:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have a 10 month old lab and I remember that biting stage well. Brought me to tears a few times out of frustration. All I can recommend is stay sane and it will pass. She still prefers to use her mouth during play if I let her but as soon as I say stop she does. Have you tried freezing any of the toys? They lose their baby teeth in the first few months so some of it is play but some of it is also that they're trying to soothe. The tincture of time will help the most and then you'll have a goofy but wonderful dog.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 00:29:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kirkland nature's domain puppy food from Costco is good quality and about $17/30 lbs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 16:59:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure how much flavor you're looking for but I buy a bottle of juice I like and dilute it with water significantly. Much less sugar per serving and helps me keep up my hydration. I don't like water much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is your favorite item at the Costco food court?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 13:48:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 12:42:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>We got a Labrador puppy from a reputable breeder when my son was 2 years old. It was very challenging and remains so as the puppy turns one at the end of the month. I would never rescue a dog with children that young due to unpredictable temperament. A puppy with 2 kids under 4 sounds extremely challenging but probably could be done if you are an active family with a good support system. However, in 95% of these situations something suffers, and it's usually the dog.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 14:56:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kid throwing up out of nowhere and the janitor coming to put that saw dust stuff on it before cleaning it up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 15:54:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://forktospoon.com/2017/06/instant-pot-pressure-cooker-vegetarian-chinese-fried-rice.html</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 16:53:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Physician here. Run from this guy. MCAT studying isn't anything to the next 8-10 years of med school and training. He isn't going to start treating you better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 02:26:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>My grandma is 85, a devout Catholic, and a mother of 9. She managed to attend her grandson's gay wedding a few years ago because being Catholic means loving people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 20:27:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>For those struggling with turning the TV off and fits afterwards, a phone or kitchen timer has helped us a lot. Our son presses the button to turn it on and turn it off and somehow the timer telling him it's time to turn off the TV goes over MUCH better mom or dad telling him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 02:41:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Find a different breeder. Our breeder held our puppy because we had a previously planned trip. It was no big deal to them and we picked her up when she was 10 weeks old.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 15:14:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Natural" has taken over as somehow better in our society. In the past, polio, pandemic flu, and countless other health crises have occurred "naturally" to the detriment of entire populations. Nature can be cruel and innovation to protect the human race keeps us alive and healthy everyday. Various ways of delivering babies and keeping them and moms alive are wonderful and should be celebrated.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 15:09:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes I take 1 in the morning and 1 at night and don't have issues with clogs. If you have a clog already I'd take 2 twice per day until it resolves.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 17:53:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your doctors don't know how much the tests they order are going to cost you. Their recommendations for testing are based on the best next steps medically speaking. Always check with your insurance about your financial responsibilities for testing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 17:00:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Get a Spectra and buy adapter to use with Medela accessories. I did this and the little pieces you need only cost like 7 dollars on Amazon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 20:40:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>My 3 year old's favorite: what kind of dinosaur goes to the dentist? A flossiraptor!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>