<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject511</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-21 16:09:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ideate. Normalcy. Unretouched.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-21 16:19:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>My boss always ends a request with: Now is that within your skill set?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-25 13:26:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Slapstick mishap.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-30 19:41:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Communication. 'We need more communication!' At the office this is the answer to everything, also relationships...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Norman has a moment with Norman</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-10 16:27:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Norman was sulking on the couch after a bad day at the office. Norman #8217;s cat, Norman, sensed his owner was feeling dejected and left the room.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Norman Gets Dressed</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-11 17:42:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Norman made a slight noise as he adjusted his tie. He took a last look in the mirror and said, now that's what I call good enough.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-14 17:56:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honey Booboo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-15 17:37:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Blood Hound seems appropriate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-07 17:39:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stan's father, Randy Marsh!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-07 17:44:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oscar Wilde. I'd kill for another novel.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>People who have debated religion or the existence of god, has anyone ever changed your point of view, or made you question your own beliefs? What was said?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-16 14:54:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-18 17:45:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I was a young boy, I was looking for something to eat in the kitchen just around bedtime. I was hungry but I didn #8217;t know what I really wanted so I went to bed. While I was tucking myself into bed my dad came into my room and said, did you get something to eat? I said, I didn #8217;t know what I wanted. He got me out of bed and made me a peanut-butter and jelly sandwich with cookies and milk. When I was finished, he said that when he was a young boy he went to bed hungry most nights, and that he would be sure that I never had to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-20 15:52:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Moon-ing. It's about Sam Rockwell mooning himself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-23 16:51:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>'Just live one day at a time.' Um... What are my other options?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-26 15:44:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mind your business.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-02 17:20:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>- This is fun. -That was fun! - No, on the radio, the band Fun! -...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-04 22:37:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pee Wee's Big Adventure</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-05 15:13:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good times, good times...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-11 18:32:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>For Whom The Bell Tolls. Picked it up because of a Reddit post. Pretty good so far.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-26 17:03:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is there any meaning in my life that wouldn't be destroyed by the death that inevitably awaits me? Tolstoy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-26 22:22:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Little Father Time, from Jude The Obscure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-26 22:30:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Something The Lord Made</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-07 16:00:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for the explanation. Since the Jurassic World movie I have been hearing people remark that birds were dinosaurs, but I didn't understand why this would be. If I may ask a follow up question: Does the scientific community know if dinosaurs and birds (as we know them today) coexist?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-07 18:25:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Onions. When I was little I said I didn't like onions. First my grandmother said it was because I didn't try them. Then she said I was a picky eater. She started putting them into almost every meal: cooked, raw, fried, baked. I kept saying I didn't like them. But she forced me to eat them, saying that I would learn to like them. I developed a complex about onions as an adult. On holidays my grandmother puts big chunks of onions in almost all of the dishes. During supper while I am picking through my food, she repeatedly asks, but why don't you like them. When I say that I never liked them, she says, but why?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-07 19:13:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm in the same boat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-30 17:54:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could you offer any more information on people who think this? Like which culture or sect? Or a source? I'd like to research more. I find this fascinating.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-22 21:35:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>When people put cash or change on the counter instead of in the cashier's hand, especially when the cashier's hand is out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 16:23:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Darren Aronofsky</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ELI5:In the early universe did planets form before stars?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-13 21:22:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>As mass started to clump together wouldn't planets like gas giants form first until they gathered enough mass to begin fusion? What am I missing? Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-13 21:28:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>What about rogue planets? I thought starless planets were a thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-13 21:32:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>That makes sense. Thank you for the clarification.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-20 17:14:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>A brief stint at a fancy restaurant, my job was to refill people's water glasses. I mistakenly poured regular water in a woman's glass who was drinking mineral water. She snapped at me with a grave and severe tone, 'You have just ruined my water!'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-20 20:51:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Her level of reproach was so disproportionate it was comedic. When I think about that memory now I see her wearing a cartoon mink scarf.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-22 19:30:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>When a statement ends with, '...and whatnot.' And whatnot what?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-29 16:14:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reciprocity and compartmentalize: two words I Porky Pig.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-15 19:47:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cowboys and Aliens.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-05 17:20:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Something the Lord Made. An HBO movie starring Severus Snape and Yasiin Bey.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-24 14:41:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>They are cautionary tales.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Kelsey Grammar is old enough now to have another Frasier spin off where an old Frasier has to move in with Fredrick.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-26 13:53:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-26 14:02:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Once I picked up a banana and shook it like an orange juice container.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-26 14:55:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah and an old Niles would just preposterous and wonderful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-26 15:29:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I could imagine Freddie being a cop who hangs out at the local bar. Or even Freddie is a psychiatrist who starts to hang out at a local bar. I could see it either way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-26 16:09:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Cranes are known for their quaffability.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-01 21:32:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seinfeld.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-10 18:04:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Herby Hancock</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-06 14:44:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did anyone else notice everyone mispronouncing 'divisiveness' during and after the RNC? Bernie Sanders and a lot of commenters kept saying, 'diveesiveness'.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-10 19:35:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>We need to talk.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How did the balcony work?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-17 17:23:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is probably a dumb question, but how did the balcony work on the show? Was it real, or just a green screen? Or something else? The outside changed so frequently and seamlessly that it really looks like they were stepping outside. Thank you for indulging me!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-17 17:25:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>To clarify, I am mostly talking about the weather and cityscape seen from the balcony...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-17 19:39:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, makes sense. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-04 18:16:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everything doesn't need to end with a giant energy beam shooting into the sky in the middle of a city.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-04 19:54:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wherewithal. One person in the office said it. Now suddenly everybody is saying they had the wherewithal for this. Or saying someone else didn't have the wherewithal for that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-28 14:35:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd really like to see an older Frasier having to move in with Freddy, whose now a cop, or maybe hangs out at the local bar. I'd also just love to an old preposterous Niles.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-06 17:16:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kind of disappointed, I was hoping to see a discussion about his book list. Instead it's a shitshow about having time to read.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-06 19:59:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, I haven't read any of the books. That's why I said I was disappointed. I thought that others who read the books would exchange opinions of the merits or flaws of the mentioned books. I've read David Foster Wallace, and I like him as an essayist so I'm inclined to start there myself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ELI5: Does immunity mean you can't get in trouble no matter what? Are there any exceptions?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-31 21:12:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even for like treason for example...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-31 21:25:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! So does that mean someone could admit to murder or something and not get in trouble even if the immunity deal was supposed to be about something else?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-31 21:41:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, so if you confess to something outside of your deal you can still get in trouble. But it doesn't have anything to do with how bad the crime is that you committed, just anything outside the agreed upon terms.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Frasier's Pet Names</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-10 20:03:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does anyone know of a good list of Pet names Frasier had for Lilith? This may be more of a Cheers question, but Frasier always had the best pet names. Niles too, really.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I really hope Spider-Man outsmarts Iron Man.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-26 21:05:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>So far we know Iron Man made the new Spider-Man suit and that Iron Man eventually takes it away. The common theory I've heard so far is that Spidey makes his own low-tech suit, or that Iron Man gives him back the suit after he redeems himself. But I really want a scene where Spidey outwits Iron Man, or at least surprises him with his own ingenuity. Spider-Man is supposed to be super smart, and has been known to impress Iron Man with his cleverness. So far Iron Man is always shown to be the smartest person in the room, and usually several steps ahead of everybody, so it would be really cool to see Spider-Man get one over on him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-26 22:39:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would be awesome. There is a scene in one of the comics where Spider-Man puts a tracer on Iron Man and follows him without him knowing. And Iron Man even says that none of his tech detected it, and he's really impressed. I'd love to see something like that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-27 15:51:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah! one of my favorite things about Spider-Man is that he uses his mind to outsmart villains who are stronger or more powerful. I really hope to see him using his wits to win out in the end. I think the best would be if Tony Stark also realizes that Peter doesn't need his tech either to be a superhero, and not feel rebuked but respects him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-03 18:39:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just beautiful!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Phone, a new Will Self Novel</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-09 15:20:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-09 17:12:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't understand why posting a link to a new book review about a famous author in the books subreddit would get down-voted.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-16 17:21:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am so glad you posted this, I've wanted to talk about my experience with Demons for a while. Brothers has become one of my absolute favorite books, but it took me several attempts to make it all the way through and to finally enjoy it. I'm ten years older now then when I first started and I think that dramatically changed the way I view and appreciate Brothers. But now I've had the exact same experience with Demons. I've tried now on several occasions and never seem to get more than half way through. I wouldn't say it's boring, but it is much more difficult for me. All of the characters make it feel more like an ensemble cast and it is difficult for me to distinguish who's who. Also, I would often read several pages and find myself having no idea what's going on, and I felt like this would happen repeatedly. So far, I would get to a certain point and admit to myself that I am completely clueless as to what's happening. The frustrating thing, and the aspect of the book that would keep bringing me back, are the essays, or philosophical portions that I find really interesting. I am hoping, just like Brothers, one day I'll pick it up and it will just click with me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-19 21:42:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure,</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-20 17:48:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kafka can be depressing but he also had a dark sense of humor and enjoyed vaudeville and slap-stick. Some of the absurdities in The Trial are very funny, and were intended to be so. I've read The Trial and The Castle a few times, and with each rereading I've found them funnier. He is absolutely a dark, grave, sad writer but he also had a knack for being simultaneously hilarious situations.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-20 19:24:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have! Agreed, sometimes very funny. In fact, The Castle is one of the funniest books I've ever read, also one of the darkest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-26 16:02:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Denzel Washington in Training Day. I watched it after he won Best Actor. The movie was pretty good, but I didn't think his performance was anything special.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-01 15:33:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>This reminds me of an old Don Rickles story. He was having a business dinner at a restaurant that Frank Sinatra happened to be dining at as well. Don excused himself from the table and went over to Frank asked him if he would just stop by the table and say hello to impress his business associates. Awhile later Frank stopped by the table and Don yelled, 'Damn it Frank! Can't you see I'm busy!'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Pierce Brosnon in Baby Driver</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 14:20:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've seen Baby Driver twice now and I swear that's Pierce Brosnon sitting on the park bench during the Harlem Shuffle sequence. Has any one else noticed this or have confirmation?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 16:18:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cowboys and Aliens. What a let down.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 14:54:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, exactly!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-12 15:44:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I respectfully return the ticket.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 17:30:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know if it's worth a movie, but I'd really like to see what Iron Man was doing during Homecoming. I thought it was strange that Iron Man wouldn't be present while moving all that precious cargo. I'd be cool to see a parallel story that shows him doing something that was even more important than making sure all his tech arrived safely.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why is Thanos collecting Infinty Stones?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 20:27:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>In the comics Thanos is collecting the Infinity Gems to impress death. Are there any theories about his motives to collect the Infinity Stones in the movies? I hope they spend time explaining why he wants them other than 'Taking Over The Universe' or just to be the most powerful being in the universe. But if he is trying to impress Death from the Thor movie then that means they already have a history, and it would be really interesting to learn what happened between them to make Thanos want to start collecting the Stones. I just really hope they explain his motives to make his story have meaning after all this build up. Any thoughts or theories?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 21:31:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah! I think it would be really interesting if they had some kind of flashback scene!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 21:32:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really hope it's not going to be that cliched and boring.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-01 22:41:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great post. I submitted a link weeks ago to a review of Will Self's new novel, Phone. He's a writer that I like a lot and wanted to maybe have a discussion. I was immediately downvoted and someone commented that Will Self doesn't like Reddit, so there's no chance of having a conversation about his new book. Really frustrating. Just because the author doesn't like Reddit shouldn't mean that can't have an interesting discussion about a novel he wrote. I just just chalked it up to the internet being the internet. But it would be nice to have a constructive conversation without just immediately being downvoted.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-03 19:27:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the best response I've seen so far, in my opinion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-03 19:35:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is your favorite?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-07 15:34:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only other big name actor I can think of is Daniel Day Lewis.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-08 15:00:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I loved The Red and The Black, though it's been years. I thought his work made a bridge between instructional novels about social commentary like the works of Victor Hugo and the more psychological novels like the works of Gustave Flaubert, and others. Another book you may like is Bel Ami, by Guy de Maupassant.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-08 20:39:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I pronounce it, Q-teen eighty four.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-10 18:51:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty much any Wes Anderson movie.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is Thanos still from Saturn in the MCU?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-14 19:20:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seems like he's a lot farther away, like a different galaxy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-22 18:50:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Denis Villeneuve. Prisoners, Enemy, Sicario, Arrival. All very different well executed films.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Writing Credits on Seinfeld</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-22 19:48:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Larry David and Jerry Seinfeld often talk about writing Seinfeld, but when you watch the episodes it rarely gives them writing credits. Even episodes I've heard Larry say that he'd written will have other peoples names as the writers of the episode. So did Larry and Jerry just come up with a concept for an episode and others actually wrote a script? Or did they write a rough draft that other people polish? Or is it that since they are creators they don't take writing credit? Or did they just not write the episodes at all?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-22 20:07:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll definitely check this out, thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-22 20:42:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is exactly what I was wondering about. Thank you for such an informative answer!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does anybody know the first appearance of the mighty Thirst Buster?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-25 16:24:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hope that helps you understand</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 15:41:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 16:00:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I couldn't see my post, so I didn't know if it uploaded correctly. So I deleted it and reposted to make sure it uploaded correctly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 16:26:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly. Her point is that she reads so fast that she had to buy a device to keep track of her books because she can't remember what she's read. It's just silly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Luke Cage is pretty much bullet proof, does that mean Thor is definitely bullet proof?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 03:26:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 03:50:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I understand they are not connected, I was wondering about there relative strengths.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Prediction: The new Avengers headquarters is some kind of spaceship.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 14:48:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Secret flying airships are pretty common in the Marvel Universe and they are usually set up as an unexpected reveal. In Spider-Man they made a big deal about the new Avengers headquarters and Infinity War is a cosmic adventure, so I imagine the Avengers will end up in space. My thought is that the new headquarters either holds a giant spaceship or turns into one in some capacity.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 15:23:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, I feel like there must be some special significance with the new facility. They must of moved it for some reason that's important to the larger story.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 15:39:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>have what?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 16:17:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well that's just stupid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 16:41:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, I think it is stupid for someone to point out a grammatical error on an internet comment board without even contributing to the conversation. Comment boards are riddled with grammatical mistakes and people can get along just fine understanding the spirit of the conversation. I do think it's stupid someone feels the need to point out someone else's mistake without actually having anything to say them self. I just wanted to float some ideas about Infinity War for fun, not get nitpicked because I'm not proof reading on an internet comment board.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 17:19:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think they will be remembered fondly. Personally I don't think good characters can be played out. A character's great moments will be admired and highly regarded, the weak moments will just be ignored. Chaplin's Tramp and The Three Stooges have been in hundreds of films and not all of them have been great, especially the later work of the Stooges. We just look back at there best. Tom Sawyer is another character who is remembered for his two most famous novels, not the several weaker sequels.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 18:19:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 21:46:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you. Yeah, it really stinks. I just had a fun idea that I wanted to talk about.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If Ego's plan succeeded, would that have effected Thanos?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 15:04:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 15:28:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Huh, that interesting. So you think it would have worked out in Thanos' benefit. I was more thinking if Thanos would have been at risk, or even death. I was curious about all the cosmic beings really.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 15:31:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah gotcha. Thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 15:36:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I tend to agree. I feel like there are many beings who are more powerful than Ego and would not have allowed his plan to follow through.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 15:43:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a cool idea. Like a cosmic team-up series where cosmic beings work together to deal with other cosmic being trying to take over the universe. There are always a lot of different plans to take over the universe in the MU, it would be interesting to see how it effected the most powerful beings.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 16:18:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's awesome! I'll have to look that up, thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 19:11:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Melmoth The Wanderer, by Charles Maturin. It's a gothic take on Faust. The main character sold his soul to the devil in exchange for an additional 100 years of life. Eventually he ends up just wandering the earth for someone to take over his pact.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 19:15:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Karamazov Brothers. Most powerful book I've ever read. Fun fact: It's the last book Tolstoy read before he died.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-19 01:14:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you're probably right. So far they haven't been very specific.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-19 16:08:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Trial, by Kafka. I work in an office building.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Any love for the Scottish sitcom, Still Game on Netflix?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-19 19:49:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I stumbled across this show and was pleasantly surprised how hilarious and consistently well crafted each show is. To me, it is a classic throw-back sitcom with a great mix of strong writing, physical humor and broadly relatable wacky characters. I also love that it is a Scottish program made by Scottish people in Scotland. There can be a language barrier sometimes, but I think it adds to the show. Also the Scots have the best insults. I haven't heard anyone else mention this show here. Anyone else love it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-19 21:13:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm still working my through, just started season 4. I agree with you, one of my overall favorite things about the show is that you really get a sense that all the characters genuinely care about each other, even if the bicker they're never nasty, and at the end of the day, they have each other's back. Especially compared to other newer sitcoms which can often resort to mean-spiritedness for laughs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-20 00:10:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yup, it has a laugh track.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-20 04:11:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah nice, haven't seen the holiday specials yet!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I've noticed an increase in posts passively aggressively making fun of Reviewbrah</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-20 14:53:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Has anyone else noticed this? I don't like it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-20 15:06:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.reddit.com/r/TheReportOfTheWeek/comments/716v8p/when_youre_faded_af_but_you_have_to_hold_a_normal/ This is the first post on the top of the page right now, it's suggesting that his face looks high and/or drunk.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-20 18:01:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>The making fun part. And it's most usually in regards to his appearance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-21 02:20:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure thing. If someone wants to be a prick, they have the right to be a prick. But this is supposed to be a fan page, negative posts should be pointed out, especially by his fans.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-21 14:47:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you. This is supposed to be a fan page, it shouldn't be clogged with posts of screenshots of him making funny faces or whatever else that has nothing to do with his content. It's not why I subscribe to this sub anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Request: Are Birkenstock lace-up shoes worth the price?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-22 21:03:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I own a few pairs of Birkenstock sandals and clogs and they are some of the highest quality footwear I've ever owned, they last forever and get better with age. I just found out Birkenstock makes lace-up shoes, and I am very interested if they are made with the same quality and standards. But since they are a little pricey and I can only order them online, I'd like to know if anyone out there owns a pair and/or would recommend them. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-22 23:19:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great point!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-23 00:28:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah that's good to know. I have a Nordsrom near by, I'll see what they have first. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>DO any of the Avengers or the Guardians know Thanos even exists yet?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 15:59:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>They know about some of the Stones and the existence of aliens, but are they aware at all of a larger plan at work, or any idea of Thanos?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 16:07:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gamora, Nebula, (and Loki) definitely know of Thanos, but I don't think there is any indication that the rest know about Thanos.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 16:59:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>The other one I like is Amy and David saying their goodbyes on a subway platform. David got into the subway car and just before the doors close Amy shouts, 'Good luck beating that rape charge!'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 17:07:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright, alright. Initially I was just thinking of the Avengers and added the Guardians to my question as an after thought. Clearly I was mistaken. Mostly I'm just curious if anyone knows about his master plan yet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 20:49:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, apparently you're right. Luckily people have no compunction letting me know how glaringly ignorant and wrong I am for asking such a stupid question.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-26 19:01:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a really interesting thought!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-27 16:52:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think many other aspects of the show help solidify the Crane boy wealth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-28 15:42:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would you recommend something as a good introduction into his work?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-28 17:02:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dave Eggers novelized the children's book. You may like to check it out, if you haven't already.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-29 14:27:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cool, thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 18:05:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good boy!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-06 20:57:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I loved Simon Mayo, do you need to speak in riddles for a movie that's 30 years old?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 17:55:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>In a couple of his videos he would turn on his radio during the consumption segment. I liked that!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-20 19:14:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anyone else notice a random Pierce Brosnan cameo?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 01:46:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think he was the guy on the bench with a beard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-31 13:56:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for this post. Dostoevsky is probably my favorite novelist, his longer works are so rich and full of ideas, but for some reason I've haven't read much of his shorter work, only Notes and The Crocodile come to mind. I just ordered this book and look forward to reading these short stories.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-01 14:12:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>That really plucks my feathers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 17:50:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alan Shore from Boston Legal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 21:17:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I read an excerpt of this in The Paris Review and really liked it. I'm looking forward to reading her translation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just realized the title The Truman Show is a play on words</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-20 16:48:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>This might already be common knowledge or incredibly obvious but I just realized the deeper meaning of the title, The Truman Show. Jim Carrey's character, Truman Burbank is the only 'true man' in the movie, everyone else's character is an actor in Truman's life. I only put it together while watching Jim Carrey #8217;s documentary about Andy Kaufman. The way Jim Carrey was talking about the his character in the Truman Show it all sort of came together and made so much sense.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just realized the title The Truman Show is a play on words</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-20 18:43:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>This might already be common knowledge or incredibly obvious but I just realized the deeper meaning of the title, The Truman Show. Jim Carrey's character, Truman Burbank is the only 'true man' in the movie, everyone else's character is an actor in Truman's life. Edit: I posted this on r/movies earlier this morning and someone recommend I post it here as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-20 18:44:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you, I just did!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-20 23:04:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jim and Andy, on Netflix. Really fascinating.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 02:21:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>My opening statement was that my comment might be incredibly obvious. I'm sorry I'm not as very smart as you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 13:57:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I tried to be careful with how I phrased my post, stating first that it was probably already common knowledge or just obvious, and that it was only after watching the Jim Carrey documentary where he makes the connection pretty clearly, did I make the connection myself. I don't post very often, and I pretty much never notice really cool details like this own my own.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sean Evans from First We Feast should interview Reviewbrah on his show, Hot Ones</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 18:47:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 16:57:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Truman Show. He is the only 'true man', everyone else are actors. I just recently learned this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 01:11:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's the video that made me think about the whole thing! Lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 16:07:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Remove the 'u' after 'q'. Always unnecessary it seems.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I've been watching The Andy Griffith Show</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-13 17:35:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hate to say this but I think Barney Fife was cheating on Thelma Lou with Juanita down at the diner.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 15:16:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of my favorite stories. I read it every year around this time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 16:45:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kind of like T-Pain getting awards and accolades for 'I'm On A Boat', a song that parodies his own music, which was generally mocked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My favorite books of 2017, in no particular order</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 16:52:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. William Faulkner - Absalom, Absalom! 2. Sir Walter Scott - The Antiquary 3. Vladimir Nabokov - Ada, or Ardor: A Family Chronicle 4. Jean Giono - Hill 5. Hans Herbert Grimm - Shlump 6. Cormac McCarthy - The Road 7. Louis Guillous - Blood Dark 8. Stendhal - Italian Chronicles 9. Homer - The Odyssey 10. Graham Greene - The Power and The Glory 11. Vasily Grossman - Life and Fate 12. George Saunders - Lincoln In The Bardo 13. Louis Edouard - The End of Eddy 14. Mikhail Sholokhov - And Quiet Flows The Don 15. John McPhee - 2 of Draft No. 4: On The Writing Process 16. Yasunari Kawabata - Snow Country 17. Mikhail Lermontov - A Hero Of Our Time 18. Honore Balzac - Lost Illusions 19. Haruki Murakami - A Wild Sheep Chase 20. Madame de Stael - Corrine, or Italy 21. Haruki Murakami - Pinball, 1973 22. Fyodor Dostoyevsky - The Village of Stepanchikovov: And its Inhabitants 23. Haruki Murakami - What I Talk About When I Talk About Running 24. Ken Kesey - One Flew Over The Cuckoo's Nest 25. David Grossman - A Horse Walks Into A Bar 26. Don DeLillo - White Noise 27. Jorge Luis Borges - Labyrinths 28. Madame de Sevigne - Selected Letters 29. John Green - Turtles All The Way Down 30. Jean-Paul Sartre - Baudelaire 31. David Foster Wallace - Both Flesh and Not 32. David Foster Wallace - Oblivion 33. David Foster Wallace - Everything and More: A Compact History of Infinity 34. Haruki Murakami - Hard-Boiled Wonderland and The End Of The World 35. Virgina Woolf - Orlando 36. Arthur Schopenhauer - Two Fundamental Problems of Ethics 37. Haruki Murakami - Men Without Women: Stories 38. Richard Holmes - Shelley: The Pursuit 39. Celine - Castle To Castle 40. Celine - Normance 41. Celine - Guignol's Band 42. Stefan Zweig - Journey Into The Past 43. Stefan Zweig - Confusion 44. Stefan Zweig - Chess Story 45. Virgina Woolf - Waves 46. Virginia Woolf - To The Lighthouse 47. Saul Bellow - Mr. Sammler's Planet 48. Robert Musil - The Confessions of a Young Torless 49. Robert Walser - Jakob Von Gunten 50. Nathalie Sarraute - Stropisms</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 16:53:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. William Faulkner - Absalom, Absalom! 2. Sir Walter Scott - The Antiquary 3. Vladimir Nabokov - Ada, or Ardor: A Family Chronicle 4. Jean Giono - Hill 5. Hans Herbert Grimm - Shlump 6. Cormac McCarthy - The Road 7. Louis Guillous - Blood Dark 8. Stendhal - Italian Chronicles 9. Homer - The Odyssey 10. Graham Greene - The Power and The Glory 11. Vasily Grossman - Life and Fate 12. George Saunders - Lincoln In The Bardo 13. Louis Edouard - The End of Eddy 14. Mikhail Sholokhov - And Quiet Flows The Don 15. John McPhee - 2 of Draft No. 4: On The Writing Process 16. Yasunari Kawabata - Snow Country 17. Mikhail Lermontov - A Hero Of Our Time 18. Honore Balzac - Lost Illusions 19. Haruki Murakami - A Wild Sheep Chase 20. Madame de Stael - Corrine, or Italy 21. Haruki Murakami - Pinball, 1973 22. Fyodor Dostoyevsky - The Village of Stepanchikovov: And its Inhabitants 23. Haruki Murakami - What I Talk About When I Talk About Running 24. Ken Kesey - One Flew Over The Cuckoo's Nest 25. David Grossman - A Horse Walks Into A Bar 26. Don DeLillo - White Noise 27. Jorge Luis Borges - Labyrinths 28. Madame de Sevigne - Selected Letters 29. John Green - Turtles All The Way Down 30. Jean-Paul Sartre - Baudelaire 31. David Foster Wallace - Both Flesh and Not 32. David Foster Wallace - Oblivion 33. David Foster Wallace - Everything and More: A Compact History of Infinity 34. Haruki Murakami - Hard-Boiled Wonderland and The End Of The World 35. Virgina Woolf - Orlando 36. Arthur Schopenhauer - Two Fundamental Problems of Ethics 37. Haruki Murakami - Men Without Women: Stories 38. Richard Holmes - Shelley: The Pursuit 39. Celine - Castle To Castle 40. Celine - Normance 41. Celine - Guignol's Band 42. Stefan Zweig - Journey Into The Past 43. Stefan Zweig - Confusion 44. Stefan Zweig - Chess Story 45. Virgina Woolf - Waves 46. Virginia Woolf - To The Lighthouse 47. Saul Bellow - Mr. Sammler's Planet 48. Robert Musil - The Confessions of a Young Torless 49. Robert Walser - Jakob Von Gunten 50. Nathalie Sarraute - Stropisms</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 19:21:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's a bit of a surrealist, very dreamlike. Kind of a mix of Kafka and Gogol. If that interests you, I'd say pick a random short story, odds are you'll want to read the next story after that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 17:38:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I cannot remember the books I've read any more than the meals I have eaten; even so, they have made me. - Ralph Waldo Emerson</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Nobody Learns Their Lesson on The Andy Griffith Show</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 22:12:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nobody ever seems to learn their lesson other than Andy and Opie. It's actually one of the most intriguing aspects of the show as a whole. With each season Andy becomes progressively more irritated with the bad decisions and poor reasoning of everyone around him. Andy has become visibly dismayed with everyone's lack of self-improvement, or even self-awareness; his stoicism has turned to bitterness, not just because of everybody's constant stream of zany antics, but also, and maybe even more importantly, because nobody ever trusts his sense of judgement, or will even just listen to him, until the very final act of the show. Understandably, Andy has gotten to the point where he doesn't even want to be involved with everyone's lunacy, isolating himself, burying his head in the newspaper, or busying himself at work, not because they're bad people, but because they've never learned to trust him. He's tired of being doubted and treated with suspicion, but also expected to make everything better again in the end. In this respect, the show as a whole reminds me of a very subtle version of The Twilight Zone, with Andy gradually questioning his sanity and asking, 'Is everyone crazy? Or could I be the crazy one?' I may be over thinking it, but I find Andy's character arc fascinating.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 22:32:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you:) He's a good boy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 00:54:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is a big shift even between the 1st and 2nd season. At first Andy is a silly wide-grinning yokel, making poor decisions like everyone else, in the second season he becomes the straight man, a much more wise, Lincolnesque figure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 00:59:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Barney's departure was absolutely a loss for Andy, his optimism went away.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 01:19:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you are right, in real life Andy Griffith had also become increasingly irritated with his situation, but that development had interesting implications on the character's trajectory in the show, for better or worse.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 02:42:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only people I know that are married are Otis, the town drunk, Mr Fowler, the butcher, Charlene Darling, and just once Floyd the barber mentioned a wife.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 03:02:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>And also so far only two episodes showed African Americans, both times involved joining the military; one episode showed a Native American; and only one episode so far showed teenagers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 22:44:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh nice! Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 02:28:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 18:51:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I use Amazon Music everyday at work. I love it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 19:36:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is a few dollars more, but it's still worth it for me because I wasn't already paying for another music. For being able to essentially listen to any album they offer for digital sale, I still think it's a good value.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 20:07:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>That Barbour jacket James Bond wears in Skyfall.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 21:01:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm Surprised William Kotzwinkle isn't more well known. Doctor Rat, The Bear Went Over The Mountain, The Fan Man: all wonderfully charming, funny, and entertaining books. And he wrote E.T.!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Based on The Writings of Stefan Zweig</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 21:09:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have you seen The Grand Budapest Hotel? I just watched it over the weekend, and it's an immaculately crafted piece of cinema. In case you haven't, I'll try to briefly describe the premise: It's a period piece directed by Wes Anderson set sometime during the World Wars, the main setting is, quite obviously, a grand hotel, and the main characters are a fastidious concierge, a young bell hop under his tutelage, and the young bell hop's love interest, a confectioner's apprentice. The aging concierge is also a lothario who seduces the rich elderly women who patronize the hotel, and the women happily welcome his romantic overtures. The story is propelled when one of the rich women dies and bequeaths the concierge a priceless painting. The rich woman's family disputes this endowment and labels the concierge as a scoundrel. It's all very madcap, complete with an art heist, a jail break, and a secret society. But at the very end of the film when the screen goes black and one might expect to see 'Directed by Wes Anderson', instead we see 'Based on The Writings of Stefan Zweig'. Well I had never heard of the writer! I was so impressed with the movie I decided to order some of his books, and boy was I not disappointed. The first book 'Chess Story' was one of the most satisfying reading experiences I've had in sometime. I read it in one sitting, utterly captivated. On the surface it's a simple story of a chess match on an ocean liner, but the characters are fully realized with profoundly deep psychological portraits, and the chess match, quite nimbly, parallels the loneliness and struggle of human suffering, and the fulfillment and promise of human achievement. I cannot give a high enough endorsement of this book and this writer. Would recommend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Based on The Writings of Stefan Zweig</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 21:21:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Something That I wrote that I thought you guys might like: Have you seen The Grand Budapest Hotel? I just watched it over the weekend, and it's an immaculately crafted piece of cinema. In case you haven't, I'll try to briefly describe the premise: It's a period piece directed by Wes Anderson set sometime during the World Wars, the main setting is, quite obviously, a grand hotel, and the main characters are a fastidious concierge, a young bell hop under his tutelage, and the young bell hop's love interest, a confectioner's apprentice. The aging concierge is also a lothario who seduces the rich elderly women who patronize the hotel, and the women happily welcome his romantic overtures. The story is propelled when one of the rich women dies and bequeaths the concierge a priceless painting. The rich woman's family disputes this endowment and labels the concierge as a scoundrel. It's all very madcap, complete with an art heist, a jail break, and a secret society. But at the very end of the film when the screen goes black and one might expect to see 'Directed by Wes Anderson', instead we see 'Based on The Writings of Stefan Zweig'. Well I had never heard of the writer! I was so impressed with the movie I decided to order some of his books, and boy was I not disappointed. The first book 'Chess Story' was one of the most satisfying reading experiences I've had in sometime. I read it in one sitting, utterly captivated. On the surface it's a simple story of a chess match on an ocean liner, but the characters are fully realized with profoundly deep psychological portraits, and the chess match, quite nimbly, parallels the loneliness and struggle of human suffering, and the fulfillment and promise of human achievement. I cannot give a high enough endorsement of this book and this writer. Would recommend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 15:35:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Niles in Frasier, and Barney in The Andy Griffith Show: two of the best.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 20:01:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/iamverysmart</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A Book With A Great Beginning</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 20:29:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Last night I started reading The Fortune of The Rougons, by Emile Zola and it has one of the most compelling, strangest opening sequences. The story begins with a description of a simple plot of land, a cemetery located in the French countryside. The cemetery was too small to accommodate all of the mortal bodies in town, so every few years the ground was tilled. The old dead were mixed with fresh soil to make room for newer bodies. Eventually the ground became so saturated with human remains and consumed by bones, it became unusable for burying the dead; The plot was abandoned. After years of neglect the site was overrun by weeds, vegetation; monstrous pear trees grew, feeding off the dead. The villagers were horrified by these pear trees and refused to eat the fleshy fruit they produced, except for the children who happily gobbled them up in secret. Eventually the plot was bought by a developer who chopped down all the trees, cleared the land of weeds, and dug up all the bones. The villagers were happy and relieved at the prospect of progress in their community. But the children were not happy, they no longer had their pear trees which gave them their delicious fruit. In an act of vengeful retribution the children stole bones which were piled up next to the old cemetery, and strung up all of the bones throughout the village in the cover of night. The next morning the entire village woke up terror stricken: skulls hung from lampposts and doorways, femurs lined the streets, tibia and fibula hung from windows, and all manner of unrecognizable bone shards were scattered up and down the storefronts. Doom and panic loomed over the entire god-fearing town: the children had their revenge.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 22:15:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've read a few of his books and I've always enjoyed them so I thought I'd start with the first novel of the cycle, but I am not planning on reading them all in order, or at least not yet. My copy was translated by Brian Nelson and so far it is quite good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 14:06:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you, and you're spot on. Maupassant is one of my absolute favorite writers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 16:33:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree with your list. The only other major contender I'd say is Jonathon Swift.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 21:26:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>A few others, And Quiet Flows The Don - Mikhail Sholokov, Blood Dark - Louis Guilloux, Schlump - Hans Herbert Grimm, Life And Fate - Vasily Grossman</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Living Tribunal reference in Doctor Strange</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 17:13:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I watched Dr Strange again last night and still loved it, a fantastic fast-paced movie. But this morning I went on the old Doctor Strange discussion thread and some people were all excited about a reference to the Living Tribunal in the movie. I completely missed that both times watching the movie. Does anybody know where in the movie the Living Tribunal is referenced? also I apologize in advance if it is something totally obvious. Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 17:20:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gotcha, thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 17:27:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was wondering the same thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 19:47:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>You may like to take a look at his last novel, Resurrection, it is a good representation of his later philosophy on life and religion, and it is also more approachable at least in terms of length. Or you may like to check out Hadji Murad, which is a masterful novella he wrote later in life as well. Also, The Death of Ivan Ilyich, which is generally considered one of his masterpieces, will give you his thoughts on life and death. And it can be read in an afternoon. Lastly Confession is worth reading too, it is sort of a spiritual companion to The Death of Ivan Ilyich, and also a quick read.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 21:50:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're ever in the mood for books that definitely will not end happily, I'd suggest the works of Thomas Hardy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 18:04:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>You would eat an egg that came out of you?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 20:58:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is his American Gangster!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 19:51:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>*Pretty good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 17:11:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're ever interested in trying to read The Odyssey again, I'd recommend Emily Wilson's new translation. It's not so stodgy as some other translations.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 16:41:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of my favorite books. It's long, but at least it takes fewer than 7 years to finish.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 20:43:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>1Q84 possibly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-22 15:21:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I read that as food courts/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 16:25:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't have a specific passage but the novel 'Two on a Tower' by Thomas Hardy is full of beautiful descriptions of the heavens, it about two astronomers in an observatory.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 18:58:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>About Schmidt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is Thor definitely stronger than Spider Man?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 14:15:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've read that Spider Man is relatively one of the strongest heroes in Marvel and I was wondering if he was about as strong as Thor. But we've seen Thor go toe-to-toe with Hulk, and Hulk is absolutely stronger than Spider Man. We haven't seen Thor and Spider Man on screen together yet, but is there any chance they are equally matched? Or is Thor just on another power level? I know this may be a stupid question or obvious, but thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 14:22:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh ha! It's my Cake Day!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 14:25:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 14:28:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for the comic recommendation!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 15:06:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Robert Graves has a few books which are very readable. Hesiod, if your looking for more original texts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 22:29:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I live in Baltimore and The Book Thing is the best! The owner is a saint.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 22:34:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>A modern day Prometheus.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 22:35:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>The funny thing is that Capote was the one who was saying it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 19:48:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Read this book years ago. One of the lines that stuck with me was something to the effect of, 'The more he spent, the less money mattered.'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 13:46:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am not aware of Proust giving advice on writing, or explaining his style, but if you are a fan of Proust already I would recommend reading 'Memoirs From a Tomb', by Rene Chateaubriand. Proust was an admirer of his style, and influenced by his attitude towards memory. In general, if you are ever interested in how a writer developed a distinctive style, researching the writers that influenced them is a good start.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The broken pieces of Mjolnir are still on earth</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 18:56:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>It just occurred to me those pieces of Thor's hammer are just sitting in the dirt somewhere in Norway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I had the most awful dream last night involving a woman that I know and a horse</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 18:08:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was on my back, she was atop me, straddling my head holding a power drill. She had me pinned down and she was drilling a hole into my cheekbone. The drill was zapping and popping, my skull was vibrating, smoke was in the air and blood was in my field of vision. I could even smell flesh burning. I yelled, 'What are you doing?!' And she said, 'I'm putting a little horse in your cheek.' And pinched between her forefinger and thumb was a miniature horse figurine. She put the horse on the end of the drill and proceeded to auger the figurine deep within my skull.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I had the most awful dream last night involving a woman that I know, and a horse</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 19:18:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was on my back, she was atop me, straddling my head holding a power drill. She had me pinned down and she was drilling a hole into my cheekbone. The drill was zapping and popping, my skull was vibrating, smoke was in the air and blood was in my field of vision. I could even smell flesh burning. I yelled, 'What are you doing?!' And she said, 'I'm putting a little horse in your cheek.' And pinched between her forefinger and thumb was a miniature horse figurine. She put the horse on the end of the drill and proceeded to auger the figurine deep within my skull.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 00:12:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have no idea! That's why I posted here. The whole thing was so vivid and alarming. I thought maybe someone who is better at this sort of thing might have some ideas. I don't even know the person with the drill very well, she's more of a passing acquaintance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 19:26:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Completely a personal preference, but my favorite Dostoevsky translator is Ignat Avsey.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 16:00:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi, I'll try to answer your questions, though some aspects of this dream have become hazy since it's been a few days. She's a petite brunette in her late twenties, about a foot shorter than me. She has shoulder length hair and olive skin. I'd say we're friends, but not very close. She's an artist and most of our association is me in her studio, critiquing and discussing her paintings. She's also a bartender and sometimes I stop in for a pint. And to clarify, I am not her teacher, or a teacher at all, just another artist. I feel that the event took place in my bed, because it was so vivid that it awakened me from my sleep and I felt that I was in the same location. I don't know if my limbs were restrained, but I didn't have use of them. And although some of this may sounds similar to some kind of fetish, none of this felt sexual. It was just scary. I don't know the material of the horse, but it was shiny and looked durable, maybe some kind of metal. And the horse was small, very very small, like something you would need tweezers to grasp: smaller than a pea. I don't have much history with horses. I think they are pretty, but in general they frighten me. I wouldn't want to be near one, and certainly would not ride a horse. But it's not like I have any childhood trauma with a horse or anything. I don't come into contact with horses in my daily life and it's probably ten years since I've seen one in person and close-up. I own a few power tools, and a power drill, but they are not frequently used. They're used just for little household projects. I'm perfectly comfortable using power tools, and I've never had an injury. She was definitely drilling into the cheekbone, just below the eye socket, right where the cheekbone protrudes. And I distinctly remember it was my left cheekbone. I'm trying to think of anything else. I'm a guy, early thirties. I have frequent nightmares. This is my first time posting here, because this dream was so startling and strange. Thank you for all of your interest!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 20:37:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have you read other works by Hugo? If you haven't, I'd recommend starting somewhere else. My favorite novel by Hugo is Toilers Of The Sea, it's a man vs nature, adventure story with portions of his usual declarative philosophizing. The Man Who Laughs can be a labor at times because of the amount he dedicates to explaining history and lineages. It is similar to Moby Dick in that way. That being said, if you are already a Victor Hugo fan it is definitely worth reading, otherwise French literature has many other options.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 13:23:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tolstoy is a powerful short story writer. You may be interested in 'Childhood, Boyhood, Youth', it's an early autobiographical work by Tolstoy. It gives a lot of insight on how Tolstoy's early life informed his mature work. As far as 'Brothers' and 'War and Peace', keep in mind that the 100 or 200 pages are the most challenging in both. But if you stick with it, they become incredibly readable; they will engross you, and when you finish, you'll wish they were longer. Happy reading!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 17:41:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's one of my favorite books as well. I've read it a few times, and each reading I've identified with a different brother. Truly remarkable story telling. Interesting side note: Brothers is the last book Tolstoy read before he died.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 19:40:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you haven't already, check out Vonnegut. He often has non-linear narratives and stories within stories. Also if you like experimental use of language, A Clockwork Orange is fun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 15:12:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your question was answered nicely by Ralph Waldo Emerson: I cannot remember the books I've read anymore than the meals I've eaten; even so, they have made me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 22:24:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think Life and Fate by Vasily Grossman is one of the greatest novels of the 20th century. It's what War and Peace was for the 19th century.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 22:26:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Much earlier, but Taras Bulba by Gogol tells the story of the Cossack revolt against the Poles. It's short and great.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 20:58:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe Frasier's son Freddy has grown up and become a no-nonsense cop and hangs out at the local bar, but for some reason he has to take care of an older Frasier and deal with his prissy uncle Niles.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Question about Thor and Hulk's strength</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 20:36:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thor and Hulk are shown to be pretty much equally matched physically in Ragnorak. But in the 1st Avengers Hulk punches that flying caterpillar and stops it dead in its tracks. Could Thor have punched the flying caterpillar and stopped it the same way? My guess is that he couldn't. So did Thor get stronger in Ragnorak? Or did Hulk get weaker? And shouldn't Hulk be a whole lot stronger anyway?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 20:45:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never understood how the Hulkbuster vs Hulk fight ended. The building falls on Hulk and then he gets punched, then it just cuts to Banner on the ship. I just can't believe that last punch really knocked him out. I don't know how else they would have ended it though I guess.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 20:46:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 21:55:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Against Nature - J.K Huysmans, Journey To The End of The Night - Celine, Death On The Installment Plan - Celine, Chaos And Night - Henry de Montherlant, The Stranger - Camus, Demons - Dostoevsky, Notes From Underground - Dostoevsky, The Castle - Kafka, The Trial - Kafka, Whatever - Michel Houellebecq, Elemental Particles - Michel Houellebecq, Molloy, Malone Dies, The Unnamable - Beckett, Prisoner of Love - Jean Genet, The Immoralist - Andre Gide, Maldoror - Comte de Lautr #233;amont, The Trouble With Being Born - E.M. Cioran, Nadja - Andre Breton,</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 22:32:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I meant if Thor punched it without his hammer. And anyway, Thor had his hammer and even then, he wasn't shredding any of the flying caterpillars. Also, just so you know too, someone else said those caterpillars are called Leviathans.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 22:46:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't mean to be snarky at all. I didn't know what they were called, and someone else corrected me. Your reasoning makes a lot of sense. Thanks for thoughts, cheers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 14:26:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also, the first great nihilistic novel, Fathers and Sons by Ivan Turgenev.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Could Thanos appear in Captain Marvel?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 20:40:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Captain Marvel takes place in the past, Ronan The Accuser is in the movie and he has a relationship with Thanos, and Captain Marvel will be released before the second part of Infinity War. For these reasons I think it's highly possible Thanos could make a cameo appearance. What do you think?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 16:57:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haven't read the Carlisle translation, but Ignat Avsey is my favorite Dostoevsky translator.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 21:41:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not surprising, but just really great: Stephen Fry narrating Harry Potter.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 21:45:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just loved how Dorian Gray's body was identified by his rings. Also, the description of Quasimodo's skeleton really stuck with me, as eerie, sad, and tender.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When can we expect reviews for Infinity War?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 22:03:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>The movie comes out just next week, is there a certain day reviews will start coming out? I'm really excited. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 16:17:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is that Andy Dwyer?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 14:34:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Staples go in the top left corner.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Who could kill Thanos?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 14:45:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's all but certain that Thanos won't die in Infinity War, but he could die in the sequel. Which Avenger is most likely to single-handedly kill Thanos? Who's powerful enough? Who has the best motivation? Or who is the most appropriate person given their story arc?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 15:05:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I work with a guy who staples the top right of the page. It's madness.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 15:48:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope, we work in a typical office setting and everything is standard letter paper in the portrait position. Almost all of our documents require stapling, and everyone staples the top left except for one person. The crazy thing is nobody seems to notice or care, even people who need to handle his paperwork.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When they talk to the screen, who are they talking to?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 20:23:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello, I just started watching Parks and Rec for the first time. I'm in the 2nd season so far and I love it. But I don't think I understand the format of the show. Maybe it's a spoiler, but do they ever explain who they are talking to? It feels like a documentary, because sometimes they talk directly to the camera, or occasionally give a knowing glance. But so far they haven't actually mentioned a documentary crew. So maybe it's something else? Thanks,</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 20:59:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah okay. Haven't seen The Office yet. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 16:20:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you are part of the conversation, offer your opinion and be respectful. If you are not part of the conversation, let them debate in peace.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 15:05:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>You may like to check out Against Nature, by Joris-Karl Huysman. At some point Lord Henry gives a Dorian a book that corrupts him, this is the actual book that Oscar Wilde was referencing. Though the book wasn't named in the text, Oscar Wilde admitted it was Against Nature during his trial.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 21:24:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, those are incredibly thoughtful gifts! You found a keeper! Here's a few other books that influenced Oscar Wilde that you may find of interest, though it sounds like you are probably acutely aware. But just in case, Melmoth The Wanderer by Charles Maturin, who was Oscar Wilde's Great Uncle. Marius The Epicurean by Walter Pater The Renaissance by Walter Pater</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 01:16:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not sure of the publisher, but Robert Baldick is always reliable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>R/books really is the best subreddit</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 17:16:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't post often, but I come here every day. As a book lover, I am so grateful this community is so often supportive and generous with their time. One thing I love is that even though nearly everyday a select few novels are posted by people reading them for the first time, either showing appreciation or asking a question. Quite often, Blood Meridian, The Catcher In The Rye, Infinite Jest, Crime and Punishment, Catch-22, East Of Eden, Grapes Of Wrath etc. But instead of being critical or pedantic about seeing the same books, this community just seems to understand that people are constantly discovering these books for the first time, and make a point to be encouraging. This is just a great group of people. Thanks everyone!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 17:29:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well since you asked, I prefer physical books to listening to audio books for two reasons, I like the ritual of sitting down with a book in my hands, and that with a physical book I am devoting all of my attention to the act of reading, and also that I grew up reading physical books. I can't really comment on ebooks because I've never used one, but I see how they are beneficial to younger people or students that are required to carry many books around school. But I really don't have a judgement about how other people decide to enjoy their books.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 17:51:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh not at all, I completely understand. It's not so much that I like that people post about reading the same books, but that when they do, they don't get berated with negative comments.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My patient walks 5 miles every day</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 01:43:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>His dog's name is, 5 Miles! My mom told me this joke:)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 17:32:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>For what it's worth, Ignat Avsey is my favorite Dostoevsky translator.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Question about Hulk's Strength in The MCU</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 21:52:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everyone says that the Hulk gets stronger as he gets angrier, but is there evidence of this in any of the movies? Are there any examples?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 22:14:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gosh. I always forget about the Incredible Hulk movie. I'll have to rewatch it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 15:47:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oscar Wilde would tear off and eat a small corner of the paper after finishing every page he read.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 19:42:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ignat Avsey is my favorite Dostoevsky translator. Everything I've read by him has been superb.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 15:48:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for this. People would always say how great this show was, but I had never seen it. When it went on Prime I watched two episodes and thought it was god awful and stopped watching. I might just stick with it now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A Toad Story</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 14:37:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've seen the same toad at the same time, at the same place for three days in a row. Either it's just a coincidence, or me and this toad are keeping the same schedule. Super exciting story, you could even say it's... ribbiting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 15:35:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I should hope not!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 12:44:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 16:50:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Meditations, by Marcus Aurelius.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 20:33:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not OP but the Ignat Avsey translation is my favorite, he also translated Brothers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 21:44:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>NYRB Classics are quite handsome, and they focus on works that are little less well known.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 21:09:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>For anyone interested the book referenced in 'The Picture of Dorian Gray' is 'Against Nature', by Joris-Karl Huysman. At some point Lord Henry gives a Dorian a book that corrupts him, this is the actual book that Oscar Wilde was referencing. Though the book wasn't named in the text, Oscar Wilde admitted it was Against Nature during his trial.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 17:13:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>She's beautiful. Beautiful eyes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 19:19:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a great point. I read Middlemarch and Brothers Karamazov in my early 20's and disliked both. I read them again in my mid 30's and loved them. It was like they were completely different books.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 14:50:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a few first editions but these are my most prized, The Life of Our Lord, Charles Dickens A Moveable Feast, Ernest Hemingway Islands In The Stream, Ernest Hemingway</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>View of my just finished tiny house from the loft</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 01:14:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:33:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! It is!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The view of my new tiny house from the loft</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:40:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:56:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! We made the bookshelves out of redwood. I'm working on an album now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:06:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh and yes, it's on a 26 foot trailer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:07:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! It's online a few places, the best price I found was Amazon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:30:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:40:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's online a few places, the best price I found was Amazon. And thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My tiny house library</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:48:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:03:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! The color is arsenic green.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:06:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Canyon vista lounge chair and ottoman, by Langley Street.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:19:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! We built a platform over the wheel wells.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:03:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>The house is about 208 square feet, and I own about 1,000 books and didn't need to part with any. I actually still have space for more!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:04:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not at all! Me and my friend built it together.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>