<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject4459</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-11 05:03:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel bad that this person (and the person from a few weeks ago) had their dog taken from them. However, I also think they are partly to blame bc they left their dogs tied up while they went inside (and ate lunch, got coffee, etc). If they were more responsible, this would be less likely to happen. Down vote, flame away.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-11 06:15:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>that's a fair criticism. I do feel bad for the person and the dog.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-12 06:48:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why not get the iPod shuffle. It's like 50 and has physical buttons</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-14 07:04:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Keens - it's an old school steakhouse but don't get the steak. Get the mutton. Fantastic</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sunglasses fog up during my runs - suggestions?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-17 21:18:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi. I live in SF bay area and on my morning runs, my sunglasses tend to fog up. If the wind is blowing, the fog usually clears up on its own, but if the wind isn't blowing across/at my sunglasses, they fog up. Any suggestions on how to prevent this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-17 21:43:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same here. When I lived in IL and NY, I would run all winter long in my cold gear tights. Days when it was especially windy and cold, I'd wear some warm up pants over them to help cut the wind. Legs felt fine while I was running</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-18 00:41:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think that is the problem with my glasses, they dont' allow air to circulate and I need the wind to force air over/under the lens.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-30 16:51:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Golden unicorn and LAN Zhou aren't far away. Both are on east broadway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-10-21 00:06:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>May I suggest bringing some toilet paper. A few years back at the NYC marathon, the portapotties in ft wadsworth (starting line) ran out of tp</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-11 18:45:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>for what it's worth - check out this program and see how it compares. I think fall back weeks (shorter long runs) are important to give your body some rest http://halhigdon.com/training/51137/Marathon-Novice-1-Training-Program</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-13 16:25:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a big fan of these gloves http://www.180s.com/pages/catalog_view.aspx?g=1%2c2 amp;y=2 amp;i=92 amp;c=1 The mitten part will tuck into a pouch on the back of the glove</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-01 07:57:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>You might want to head over to 53rd and lex/third. Lever house and brasserie might be too $$ but there are Indian restaurants in the area that would be more affordable. Also have ramen (hide chan) or social eats.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-01 16:40:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it's casa lever now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-01 23:39:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Per se And then finish with custard from shake shack</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-20 03:36:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Check out strobist.com. Under lighting 101, they have a link to two starter kits. There was a recent post about these kits</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-22 07:51:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>My 11 pm is pushed to 1am. Fun</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-22 08:02:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm tired. Just want to sleep</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-01-12 18:23:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here's my favorite running gloves http://www.180s.com/pages/catalog_view.aspx?g=1%2c2 amp;y=2 amp;i=92 amp;c=1 they are similar to the Saucony gloves linked above, but you can roll up the mitten hood and tuck it away so it's not flopping around. Love them, but I don't really have opportunity to wear them in S.F.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-25 03:08:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can't upload raw to Flickr, right</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-03-02 15:40:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>What type of lighting setup did you use for the girl in the rain/wet girl? Love the picture.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-03-03 15:33:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I saw live dungeness at a place in the ferry building. Given the price of the lobsters, I'm gonna guess the crabs were pretty expensive too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-05 16:21:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where in Chicago are you? Most notable differences for me were: rents much higher, apts are smaller, don't think about having a car, and the city has no alleys for garbage (trash bags are put out on the sidewalk). Feel free to pm if you have specific question.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-10 14:39:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go illini! Isn't there another hot dog cart set up on green street at night for the drunk students?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-02 00:42:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>You just missed REI's sale. I'm sure they will have another sale around July 4 or Labor Day. Don't forget the sleeping pad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-05 06:58:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm guessing you are from the north shore or are the type that didn't ride the red line south of the loop or north of Irving park. Go back to Illinois hayseed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-23 03:23:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think Grand Central during rush hour is mesmerizing. Camp out on the steps and watch the thousands of people go through the gorgeous main hall. December in NYC is great. The Christmas spirit is high and all of the decorations and trees.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-25 16:12:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you have the original posted somewhere? I'd like to see the I uncropped version. I tried taking a similar shot but didn't come out as sharp as your shot (fwiw - I was shooting at 50mm, iso 100, f/8, at 20 sec). Nicely done</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-16 05:43:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good choice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-20 16:27:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I came here to do the same</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is my tripod too tall?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-28 18:21:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm 5'7 and I was wondering if you could help me decide whether my tripod is too tall for me. I thought the rule of thumb was the viewfinder should be eye level so I wouldn't have to hunch over etc. Took some measurements and figured that a tripod having a height of 55" without the center column being raised would be about right after I put the ball head and camera on. I received my tripod and head, put the camera on and the viewfinder is right at eye level if I'm standing straight/no slouching. However, it feels a little off, like maybe it's a little too high. I can see through the viewfinder no problem but it feels off. I don't know how best to describe it. So I'm wondering if I should get a shorter tripod (52.5") and raise the center column to a position that is more comfortable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-28 19:17:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I thought about that but I thought I would spend a lot of time trying to shorten them the same amount. Although, now that I think about it, I guess i could just mark them with whiteout or something to indicate where the stop point should be.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-28 19:17:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Seeing the northern lights in Tromso during November?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-31 16:25:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi. I am interested in visiting Norway and seeing the northern lights. From what I've read, the lights should be visible near Tromso in late November. However, one site I saw online suggested that November was not a good time to visit because the lights are not normally visible due to the humidity. Has anyone gone to Tromso to see the lights in late November? If so, what was your experience like. thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-08-01 04:43:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-08-01 04:43:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-08-20 15:31:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>The cloisters and ft Tyron park are great in Autumn. The colors across the Hudson are amazing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-08-22 06:09:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Big fan of amphipods. http://www.amphipod.com/products/holders/music/electronics/micropack-landsport. I can fit cash, keys, I'd, insurance card, metro card, a gel...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-01 18:08:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi All I'd like to learn more about lighting for portraits and posing the subject for portraits. Can anyone recommend a book (as opposed to a website)? Thanks for the help</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-03 03:42:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>This might sound silly but I pretend my dog is running with me and is tired. I try to cheer him on and give him support to make it to the end.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-07 07:02:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rite aid used to have 12 packs of high life for about 8</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-11 15:38:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shitting in public is normal? Really?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-13 06:21:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Baker beach or ocean beach</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-15 00:16:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like going there when it's a little chilly and no one else is there. I find the sound of the waves to be peaceful</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-21 06:55:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can move to areas that you feel are more child appropriate. But watch out, pit bulls live everywhere.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-22 07:59:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Night shot of the city from treasure island is cool; baker beach or headlands for the gg bridge; lots of murals and street art in the mission (clarion alley and the other one escapes me - it's by Humphrey slocombe) and haight street; Alamo square park for the postcard painted ladies shot; shot of the cable car going up Hyde with Alcatraz in the background can be shot at chestnut and Hyde; catwalk at mandarin oriental...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-08 17:37:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Congrats on finishing. I'm not an expert or anything, just speaking from my marathon experiences. I always felt that no matter how well I trained, the marathon itself is a bit unpredictable. Whether it's the weather, or my body, something might go wrong. I remember when I ran my first NYC marathon, about 16 miles into it, I was having weird pain in the top of the knuckle of my big toe (wasn't wearing brand new shoes or anything). Never had any type of pain while I trained and never had that pain again. Totally weird and random. Sorry I don't have any specific tips for you, other than shrug it off and get ready for the next one. If you are really concerned, you can see a physical therapist or a trainer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-17 04:56:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Blue crabs might be more work but the meat is sweeter/flavorful. Don't even need the old bay.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Yongnuo flashes</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-10 07:03:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi. I have a nikon sb700 and I'd like to get a second flash that I can use in manual mode and also that I can use as a slave to my sb700. I'm looking at the Yongnuo flashes but I'm having a hard time figuring out which flashes will work. Is it enough that the flash will support TTL or does it have to support Nikon's CLS. Thanks and apologies for my ignorance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-10 07:21:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's the lawyer for? Wgn hasn't used his photo. They are asking for permission to use his photo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-28 02:20:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I run early in the morning and wear a reflective vest. It's pretty cheap and but effective. It's a Nathan tricolor vest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-19 07:09:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is it weird they don't use Dungeness crab in that picture? They look like blue crab from the east coast</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-29 20:23:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's supposed to. I have an old cookbook that says microwaving the bowl of mixed pasta for a little bit to make sure the eggs are cooked. I've never tried it, so I can't comment on how it changes the dish</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dust spots, are they something that happens to everyone or am I doing something wrong?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-02 03:45:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi I have a D7000 and do not change the lens often (maybe a few times a year). When I do change my lens, I'm usually at home and try to be quick about it to reduce time the body is open. However, I still get dust spots. Can dust creep into the body when the lens is attached or does the dust indicate that the environment I change lens in is not good (i.e. dusty). Also, I bought a giotto blower to try and remove the dust spots. After blowing the rocket multiple times, I don't think it had any impact (e.g., I don't think the dust moved at all). Is there something special technique? Thanks for the help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-02 06:41:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the help. My main concern was I was doing something wrong with my camera, but it seems like dust is just a normal issue. I'll keep blasting away with the giotta and look at the cleaning kits. Happy new year!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-22 06:26:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm planning a trip to see the Northern Lights and am looking for a lens that is faster than my 18-200 VRII. I have been looking at the Nikon 17-55mm f/2.8 and was wondering if anyone had any thoughts or experiences with this lens. FWIW, I will be using a D7000 with the lens.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-22 16:22:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>thanks for the suggestion. the reviews I see of it seem pretty good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-09 08:08:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it's more than acceptable to put on a suit and tie, stand in front of a background (neutral color wall, brick wall, or outside) and have a friend take a picture from the shoulders up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-09 16:47:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I disagree. I understand that this isn't your Facebook profile but I don't think your Linkedin profile needs to have a professional headshot. Also, you don't need studio lighting to take a decent portrait. If you need absolute control of the light, then sure, studio it is. But, I don't think you need that type of picture for Linkedin.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-09 19:47:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fair point - I agree with the idea that the resulting picture will not look like a professional headshot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Do I need studded tires?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 04:54:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi. I'm coming to Fairbanks at the end of February and I'm going to rent a car. It seems that most of the rental places offer cars with all season tires and do not offer cars with studded tires. Is this ok? I'm not planning on doing anything crazy but I'd like to drive up to Murphy Dome or Chena Hot Springs. Is it dangerous to drive around on all season tires if I'm going outside of Fairbanks? Thanks for your help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 16:01:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for your advice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-25 07:00:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is the tenderloin experiencing gentrification?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-14 03:49:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Denali is worth a trip. They plowed up to mile 12.5.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-15 18:41:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Totally agree, Chena hot springs is worth a visit. A few suggestions - bring your own towel (they charge $5), bring quarters for the locker, bring water/drink b/c they want an arm and a leg for this out of the vending machine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-21 15:15:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not sure this is right. I moved from NYC to SF and never saw/heard comparisons of sf to NYC (or the reverse). However, after I moved here, I started seeing comparisons or debates of sf vs NYC. I like my life here, it's different from NYC but that's ok to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Anyone make a quilt from their old race shirts?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-07 05:07:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have way too many tshirts from various races over the years. Some are old and ratty but have sentimental value. I've been thinking of having them made into a quilt. Anyone have any experiences doing this and can you recommend a company. Thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Great set of pictures of fans at Wrestlemania XXX.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-12 21:22:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-12 21:22:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't know cosplay was a big thing at Wrestlemania.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-12 23:35:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I assumed he was going for Andre.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-12 23:56:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not my photos (I follow him on Flickr).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-27 07:23:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like the Rebel Within from Craftsman and Wolves in San Francisco. Here's someone's recipe mimicking the muffin. http://www.followmefoodie.com/2013/08/the-rebel-within-egg-baked-inside-a-bacon-cheese-muffin-recipe/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-02 07:17:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a shaved head. If I don't wear a hat, the sweat just flows down my head and I find myself constantly wiping the sweat from my eyes. However, when I wear a cap, I have no problems. The hat is soaked and dropping by the end of my run but I didn't sleep d the run wiping sweat from my eyes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-04 03:18:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I always chuckle at the "The City" tshirts in sf. I'm not sure why they claim that title</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-17 16:38:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I saw the Winogrand exhibit at SFMOMA about a year ago and enjoyed looking at his pictures. However, I was wondering, what makes them moving or great. I'm not knocking his work or street photography. I just don't know what I'm looking for or if I'm missing something. Is it the idea that he's captured such a candid moment or is it something about composition, lighting, etc. (Sorry for having an untrained eye/being uncultured)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Anyone bothered by 500px's terms of service?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-06 00:47:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>After spending some time on this subreddit, I decided to check out 500px's terms of service. I noticed the following language:  gt;Please read this section carefully before posting, uploading, or otherwise submitting any Content to the site. By submitting content to the site you are granting 500px a worldwide, Non exclusive license to use the content and are representing and warranting to 500px That the content is owned or duly licensed by you, and that 500px is free to publish, Distribute and use the content as hereinafter provided for without obtaining permission Or license from any third party. Now, I'm not a professional and I'd probably be flattered if they wanted to use one of my pictures, but it seems odd to be giving them the license to publish, distribute and use our content. Maybe that's language so they can actually display our photos? Am I overthinking this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-09 06:08:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>What intersection is this? Great shot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Has anyone ever damaged a sensor by cleaning it?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-12 20:28:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've got some dust on my sensor and the rocket blower isn't getting it off. I've been thinking about trying one of the sensor cleaning swabs but I'm nervous about doing it myself. Everything I see online makes it seem pretty easy, but there is part of me that thinks I shouldn't do it myself. The worst thing that could happen is I damage the sensor, right? But how common is that? Have any of you damaged the sensor by trying to clean it with the swabs? Thanks in advance!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-13 01:36:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks. I imagine it to be "anal-clenching." I think I'm going to bite the bullet and try it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-13 01:36:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>did you have any streaking from the oil that you couldn't get off?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-13 01:46:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I watched the stopper review and it looks interesting. One thing that worries me is the amount of force it looks like he's using to press the gel to the sensor and to remove it. I'm guessing you haven't had any problems. Any way to tell when you're pressing too hard?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-13 23:48:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>what'd you do to blowout the background? And is she on a pier or something?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Experiences running Yosemite on older equipment?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-19 19:44:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm running a mid 2009 Macbook Pro (8GB of Ram) and I'm thinking about upgrading to Yosemite. I haven't noticed too many slow downs or problems on Mavericks so I'm hopeful that the upgrade to Yosemite will also be painless. Anyone running Yosemite on older Macs want to share their experience. I'm just looking to avoid a repeat of installing iOS 4 on my iPhone 3G and basically making it unusable. Sorry if this has already been asked. I didn't see it when I scrolled through</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-29 14:51:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Toy story 3. In particular, the scene on the conveyor belt when they all accept their fate and hold hands ready to meet their maker together.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-04 05:17:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Try walking down the stairs backwards</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-05 05:55:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I L L</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-16 16:29:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Check out Russian gulch state park in Mendocino. It's about three hours and the coastal cliffs are epic scenery. Also, get some wine tasting or visit a brewery on the way up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-18 15:33:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Squeegee guys on public transport?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-02 00:54:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree that that the main library and grand central are the big draws but I think tourists should go to Times Square if they haven't been there before. Also the Empire State Building and Rockefeller plaza are worth visiting as a tourist (the tree may still be up). These are all touristy things but OP is a tourist. The people watching in the touristy areas is pretty good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-02 02:06:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could he have IBD? My pal has had IBD for a few years now. We used to feed him natures variety instinct limited ingredient and that was great for him. But they changed the formula so we switched foods. He's now eating wellness's limited ingredient food and he's ok with that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-30 16:23:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi Maisie. Have you ever busted out the crip walk on set? http://imgur.com/gallery/TXUrzF8</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-04 15:19:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you know why he is licking? My guy has been licking my pillow, the couch , his bed, my arms... He's also an older guy (13). Is it the dementia?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-06 15:14:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nintendo world in NYC.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Wrestlemania Pre-Show is 2 hours?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-26 05:18:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>How is the pre-show 2 hours long? Other than the tag title match, what else are they going to do to entertain the audience? They can't really expect fans to get there at 2pm, can they?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-25 23:14:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I N I</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-18 06:12:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was in Tokyo and Kyoto for 10 days and I got over 300 street tags. Now I'm back in the states and I average about 1 a day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-18 15:54:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Filling up my queue was one of the biggest problems I had. I wanted to get as many as possible, so I was constantly clearing out my queue. It became kindof a hassle. I guess if you live there and regularly collect 10+ a day, you probably don't get as obsessive as I did.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-02 06:32:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Imagine getting those street passes!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-12 06:59:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>My N3DS will last about 4 hours of play before the Red LED comes on. If device is sleeping (lid closed) and Wireless is still on, it will last about 3 days before the red LED comes on. Do you see much better performance?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-22 17:07:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do the diagram numbers line up with the pictures? Picture #2 looks more the diagram labeled #6.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-24 00:08:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>The instructions are in Japanese right? Did you find that to be a problem?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 18:40:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you know why the vibration reduction affects the image if there is no vibration to reduce? Seems like the system would be seeing zero delta and adjusting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Question about nintendozones</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-31 08:25:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does anyone know if the nintendozones (e.g., Home Depot, McDonalds, other ATTWifi spots) have to configure their access points to provide street passes or is it automatic due to the ATTwifi? I stopped by several locations listed on ATT's webpage (https://www.att.com/maps/wifi.html) and I didn't get any street passes. I, however, did verify that I could see an attwifi access point. Anyone have information about this? It's so frustrating to bounce around from location to location and not receive any street passes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A prized possession - The Maxx</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-03 21:56:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 01:56:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have the Isz - but didn't make the photo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 01:57:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a McFarlane toy from the 90s. I don't have too many recent figures. I had him sitting on my dresser (along with a 90s Beta Ray Bill) that I thought I'd share.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Rocky the Leprechaun in San Francisco</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-01 06:43:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>One year anniversary of my N3DS XL</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-13 17:36:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I bought the N3DS XL on launch day last year and it's been a trust companion on my daily commute to work. I thought it would be interesting to look at some of the stats over the last year. StreetPass Tags 1336 Plaza Population 1502 Puzzle Swap 1536/1597 Steps Taken 1,534,240 Titles Played 39 Animal Crossing New Leaf - 184 hours Looking forward to my next year!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-13 18:31:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is my first 3ds so all stats are new to the device.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-13 19:06:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I live in a city and walk at least 2 miles each day as part of my commute to work. I also walk a lot at work from meeting to meeting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Recent addition to my collection - Venom</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-14 05:10:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-14 08:31:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-14 08:31:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>:)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-14 18:29:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's nice to have the N3DS with me, but I'd trade it for a short commute</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-15 14:43:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>What about all the drivers on their phone? You can blame pedestrians at some level but driving aggressively surely won't help reduce the number of pedestrians getting hit by a car. I think everyone needs to pay more attention to their surroundings</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-15 15:03:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I L L How is the street passing on campus Sorry for not adding to the discussion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Black Series Captain Phasma - "I'll find Skywalker"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-20 18:09:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm really digging Miifoto.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-04 05:02:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-05 06:37:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>3ds please. Thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-06 03:54:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks a lot. I took B0JLCCH33BSTS0W</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-21 20:45:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi. This is probably a super noob question but what's the difference between the Sawyer Squeeze filter vs a pump based one. Is there a benefit to the pump based systems? I'm guessing there has to be some type of benefit b/c I don't see how to rationalize the purchase of the pump based system which is more money and takes up more space than the squeeze system. Thanks in advance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-04 17:06:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry to bother you, but I'm confused. I thought OP wanted to have a clear shot of a runner and then have the background blurring to give the sense of motion (panning). Doesn't the fast shutter freeze everything? I guess the background blur will be bokeh? Thanks for the help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-11 23:20:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry if this is obvious, but why do you recommend renting a car if there are a lot of road closures? I'm guessing you need a car to get out into the country to see the lights better but some roads (not major roads) are closed?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-20 07:03:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you know who is opening?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-26 00:01:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kevin smith went until at least 10. He realized he had a 10 pm show and was like "oh shit". It was a good session</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-27 05:15:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is the colossus juggernaut a custom?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-04 05:26:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>A link between worlds please</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-04 05:32:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Next gen fish ai</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-08 05:00:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>What dcpi are you using for the men wave?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-08 05:32:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Steak</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-18 05:43:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where would you go for a good steak? Are there classic steak houses in sf? Thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-18 16:12:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-27 14:48:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Has anyone seen this line in the wild?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-04 14:45:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>From the official Nintendo page - http://www.nintendo.com/games/detail/super-mario-maker-for-nintendo-3ds *Not all levels created in Super Mario Maker? for the Wii U? console are compatible with this release. Wireless Internet access required in order to access the Wii U version's courses. For more info, go to support.nintendo.com. **This game does not include an online-upload feature. Game in 2D.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-04 15:04:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>How are you enjoying Sf comic con?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-07 16:24:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure how unique this is but I love it. http://geekdesignz.com/product/mario-bros-3-iphone-6-case/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-11 04:52:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love the Instagram.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-12 14:50:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can imagine you yelling "clap push! You're the next contestant on the price is right! Come on down"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-13 06:49:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Darth_oblivious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-15 20:46:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cool. I'm always looking for feedback.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-24 07:04:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Comment!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-01 04:03:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>How poseable is his waist? Mine will twist with pressure but will not hold that pose. It'll spring back. Also my left arm makes a horrible clicking noise when rotated.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-02 07:37:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good luck to all. But mostly for me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-02 20:42:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-06 05:17:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Empire State Building. Yes you have to pay some money but the view is worth it. https://flic.kr/p/9tV8h7 Or le Parker meridian hotel.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-08 07:13:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>did you say waffles?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-15 06:49:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks again</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-31 15:14:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lols</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-01 04:27:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>How about a local library?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 16:52:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which hub did you buy? The confit you're describing is exactly what I'm looking for. I'll be moving from 2009 MVP so I imagine I'll be enjoying the new tb mbp as much as you are.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-12 15:24:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>129</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 16:24:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you enjoy your time at UIUC? What was your favorite bar? I -L - L</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-31 04:16:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's your instagram.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Third party replacement batteries for MacBook Pro 2009?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-26 17:56:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anyone have experience with a third party replacement batteries? The battery in my MacBook Pro is swollen and needs replacing. Apple wants $100 or so to replace the battery. It's hard for me to justify that price for a laptop that is already 7 years old. I've seen third part batteries on amazon and see mixed reviews. Mostly they say the battery life drops after a few months but others never mention that. I hoping that some of you have tried them and can share your experience. Thanks for the help</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-03 15:20:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same thing here. It originally said they would arrive on 3/3 and now it's 3/6.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-04 07:08:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good luck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-17 07:27:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>356</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-21 07:28:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which joints did you buy? I'm in the same boat - broke the shoulder joint and wrist joint within hours of opening. Did you have to paint them?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-21 14:30:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Marvel legends cyclops up on HTS</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-30 14:14:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-18 14:26:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>The writer loses all credibility when she describes a Chicago dog as having a sesame seed bun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 04:58:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cool shot. What is your lighting like? How many light sources do you have? My guess is Light source + diffuser behind Juggernaught with reflector behind iron fist? But, that doesn't seem right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 14:16:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the setup.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-27 14:58:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have ko amazing yamaguchi spider-man. The quality of the joints was really poor. The wrist and shoulder both broke within hours of opening it. However I bought a bag of replacement joints and swapped out all the joints I could and it is now a great figure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 04:59:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not sure. If you search eBay for revoltech joints you'll see sellers with bags of x joints. They seem to be real - have clicking noise that the ko joints did not have and haven't broken yet - but who knows.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-15 04:25:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hash house harriers? Did you see a running group tracking the trail? I some in soma too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-16 01:49:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry, I must have missed this. I bought revoltech replacement joints. do the Figma joints fit for a revoltech figure?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-17 15:28:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd like to play splatoon 2. I'm horrible at fps type games so I never want to buy them but really want to try it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-03 07:25:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>What did you get? Which con was this at?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-04 03:04:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>FWIW, I bought a blind bag of Bandai/Tamashii Nations figures (5 figures for $100) at SDCC and the overall value was over the $100. They, however, advertised it as a $250 value. In their defense, it would have probably been $250 of value if some of the figures weren't "on sale" on their website. Although I didn't really know many of the figures (Pegasus Kouga anyone?), I'm ok with the purchase since the articulation is pretty good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-10 19:35:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you the length of the legs? Also, how fast is the team? I'm not fast and I'd hate to hold you guys back</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 14:55:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>They are called Shen Jian Bao. http://www.seriouseats.com/recipes/2015/04/sheng-jian-bao-pan-fried-pork-soup-dumplings-recipe.html</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 18:35:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not sure that is right. I think you pan fry first.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 05:07:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where did you get this made?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 06:51:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's pretty cool that you made it yourself. Sorry for all the questions, but how do you make this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 17:45:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you in Sf?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 13:32:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cool fog/smoke. What did you use for it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 02:39:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>What was your light source?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 06:35:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>What #8217;s the photo for? LinkedIn or is your firm asking for the headshot?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 07:11:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cochran #8217;s?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 15:05:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Micronaughts?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 14:53:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could you get away with riding Caltrain without a ticket? Yes. Should you? No. You wouldn #8217;t steal food from a restaurant or skip out on a paying your doctor because the likelihood of getting caught is low, would you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 06:45:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>He said it. Tasty hand pulled noodles on doyer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 18:01:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks. My major concern is not knowing the cat is there. The low numbers of fatal attacks is somewhat comforting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My first build. Kamiki Burning Gundam (Plavsky Particle Clear version). Didn #8217;t know what to expect but this guy is cool!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 01:51:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 06:47:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks. I used photoshop on my iPad. I #8217;m not very good with it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 15:36:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you think a bear bell would help joggers too?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 15:45:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought you couldn #8217;t take Dungeness crab from the bay.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 15:47:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Heidi #8217;s pies in San Mateo had them on sat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 15:50:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you paint some of the parts?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[TOTM]. Respect My Authoritah! Sorcerer Supremes</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 20:26:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 02:41:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! I don't have a great collection so when I can contribute to the TOTM, I feel like I should</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 06:52:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s from kidrobot. Grand wizard cartman from the stick of truth series.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sony PlayStation offices getting hyped for spider-man!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 23:32:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[image] PlayStation offices are getting pumped for the release Spider-Man</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 23:57:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 01:14:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s awesome. I was wondering if it was lit up at night. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 01:39:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope. Nor cal. Bay Area</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>PlayStation offices getting pumped for the Spider-Man release!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 01:42:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:34:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>What book?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:38:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>nice. I wasn't aware that there was a tie in to a book</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:11:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Was this a repost? I searched and didn #8217;t find it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:40:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah. I #8217;m also accused of reposting but I didn #8217;t see it when I searched. Oh well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:08:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wonder if I saw you taking the picture. I saw a guy walk across parking lot to get to the spot I took it. I think he was FaceTiming or making a video with some narration. Maybe a olive color shirt?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>