<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject2947</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-05-28 01:22:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>You must add Bad Pun Raccoon!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-05-28 07:44:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>My favorite book on how to apply makeup is "Makeup Makeovers" by Robert Jones. This book is AMAZING. It shows you exactly where to place makeup to look fresh and glowing no matter what brand you buy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-05-28 08:05:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of my favorite and most unique online stores I know, ModCloth, ships internationally. They have a great selection, really unique pieces, and styles range from trendy to retro, and sometimes feature vintage pieces as well. They also sell shoes, accessories, and have a great and easy return policy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-05-30 10:21:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>She WAS freaking out and trying to contain herself. I figured I'd skip that part to save everyone having to read the lame extra panels. She was absolutely confused by the concept of pleasurable sex or sex for a reason other than making kids</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-06-06 18:05:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Something dignified, like reginald</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-06-09 01:20:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Flip phone?!?! What is this, 2003?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-06-13 12:19:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>let me introduce you to the world of lasik</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-06-17 11:35:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://www.zappos.com/french-sole-sloop-black-suede</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-06-17 11:37:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://www.aldoshoes.com/ca-eng/women/shoes/high-heels/66556845-arnoldoa/96</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-06-17 11:40:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://www.gap.com/browse/product.do?pid=768638042 amp;desktopSiteActive=true</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-06-28 04:55:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you would rather not use a walkthrough, take this advice for the interrogations: - if the character ISN'T making wierd faces, s/he is telling the TRUTH - If s/he IS making weird faces, making odd gestures, fidgeting, gulping, etc. go ahead and accuse them by choosing LIE. - Once you have accused them of lying, you will find out what kind of proof they want, and you can look through your collected evidence to catch them in their lie. - If you don't have the proof they are asking about, back out of the accusation by pressing the O button and DOUBT them instead</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-21 00:27:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got chills and teary when the protection spells went up it was haunting and ominous in the most beautiful way</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-21 00:40:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I also had really different feelings about the way the movie portrayed it. The book felt a bit cheesy, but Daniel Radcliffe did a nice job of being fatherly but not overly dramatic when telling his son about "the bravest wizard" he ever met. I thought the aging of the characters was really well done, seeing as they're only 37 (36 in Ginny's case)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-21 00:42:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I liked how those Death Eaters jumped ship too, seems very consistent with Voldy's first disapprarance</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-22 11:05:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Went back for multiple degrees, quite the bookworm, love research, consider myself quite brainy! Better be... Ravenclaw!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-23 04:11:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's been a while since I read them (must do that again when I get a chance) but wasn't Voldemort looking for the Philosophers stone to grant him eternal life? Perhaps Voldemort assumed this was the resurrection stone, and one of the hallows to be sought. In this same vein, I wonder when Dumbledore was tipped off that this might be what Voldemort was trying to do. When Dumbledore had the cloak at the beginning and gave it to Harry, I think it's quite plausible Dumbledore already knew what it was and figured that since no one else suspected, it was in as good of hands as any with Harry while under his care at Hogwarts. Hidden in plain sight so to speak.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-23 04:50:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>this! i think the invisibility cloak was meant to be there the entire time, not as a deus ex machina for Harry to be able to do whatever the hell he wants and not be seen. I feel much more confident that she meant for it to be there so that when we get to the part where we learn about the Hallows we go "holy. crap. can it be??? He's had it this ENTIRE TIME?! *mind blown* GENIUS!!!" *read read read* edit: to add mind blown</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-23 09:34:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>you ought to x-post to r/firefly for the karma!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-23 11:11:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Part 1 here: http://i.imgur.com/H7nxR.jpg Opened this new one in store and same problem</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-23 11:13:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Part one here: http://i.imgur.com/49mfO.jpg Opened the second one in-store, same problem!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-23 11:28:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I see what you did there</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-23 13:18:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love Fringe! Great interplay of characters, and though not a sci-fi western, very sci fi. The first season is rather slow, i don't feel it gets good until halfway through the season, but at least the entire first season is on hulu, for free. Second season is amazing. Also, LOST. Both very cult-y, deep shows.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just wanted to say...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-23 13:27:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I LOVE all the customized icons in this sub, especially the vote icons! Jayne's hat? Blue gloves? So shiny. I didn't get the gloves at first because I haven't downvoted anything here, but when I stopped to think about why there were gloves, it was like holy cow, genius! That's all. Keep flying, Browncoats.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-23 13:57:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fringe season 1 is on regular hulu if you want to give that a shot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-23 21:19:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought the other one with the locket was tom riddle. I thought the purple-cloaked witch could be trelawney, but there're no glasses.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-23 21:23:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>She looks like a good witch, so i figured trelawney, but she's got no glasses.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-23 21:23:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I saw in another thread that the one back to back with kreacher was regulus, but couldn't it be tom?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-23 23:39:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-23 23:53:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree with that it should be a french-pronounced name luh-STRON-zh However, maybe they just didn't do the french pronunciation. Americans would likely bastardize the pronunciation too. However, did you notice that jim dale did bellatrix's voice with a french accent? I always figured she was british and married a frenchman, so it bothered me greatly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-23 23:58:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>She needs to write this properly. With chapter summaries and study questions and everything</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-24 00:02:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, i flipped through, no disc 5!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-24 00:07:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>The first thing that really got me was when the teahcers were putting up the protection spells. As i said in another thread "ominous and haunting in the most beautiful way". it was just like, ohhhh this is the beginning of the end</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Firefly art at comic-con from Fillion's twitter feed</TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-24 00:31:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>DAE think sf4 ken looks like he-man?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-24 00:53:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-24 06:45:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Check these out: http://www.modcloth.com/Modcloth/Womens/Dresses/-Jewel-Be-Mine-Dress http://www.modcloth.com/Modcloth/Womens/Dresses/-Scalloped-Sea-Dress this is a link to many dresses at the site, all with ruffles http://www.modcloth.com/store/ModCloth/Womens/Dresses/Ruffle</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-24 10:31:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've always felt that Early was intuitive, but nothing more, other than psychotic. rationalizing rape is pretty good place to draw the line of sanity. I think the mind readings River hears are what is weighing heavy on the person's mind. She hears Simon's regrets about abandoning his career, Jayne's concerns about them finding out about how he sold out River and Simon, and Mal and Inara's unspoken (but true) feelings for each other. specifically, Shepherd says, ["I don't give half a hump if you're innocent or not. So where does that put you?"](http://www.fireflywiki.org/Firefly/ShepherdBook) The Shepherd was not an Operative. IMO, the comment Shepherd made was more likely in reference to his past, which can be found in The Shepherd's Tale. if you want spoilers, message me =P edit: removed spoilers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-24 12:47:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>[how about this](http://www.amazon.com/MaxStudio-YOKE-TRIM-DRESS/dp/B004H3HBK8/ref=pd_sbs_a_2) ? [or this](http://www.amazon.com/Maxandcleo-Womens-Ruffle-Front-Dress/dp/B004LZ5V3G/ref=sr_1_132?s=apparel amp;ie=UTF8 amp;qid=1311503501 amp;sr=1-132), [another](http://www1.bloomingdales.com/catalog/product/index.ognc?ID=536056 amp;cm_mmc=Froogle-_-n-_-n-_-n), [pretty](http://www.dillards.com/product/Jessica-Simpson-RuffleTrim-Tiered-Dress_301_-1_301_502659647)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-24 22:33:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>he can slap'a my bass anytime</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-25 00:31:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>awesome, she's so cute! i can so see them working together doing something firefly related.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-25 00:46:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>you have a very nice face!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-25 03:34:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fucking eloquent as fuck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-25 04:43:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think this too. Plus, it's not as visible a piece of magic, unless Lily was changing teacups into rats on her front lawn. Not to mention you would think that Lily's family would be somewhat exempt from the wizard secrecy, seeing as they would have to know about her being a witch, whereas Harry kept doing magic in front of muggles.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What do the characters looks like in your head? Here's how my Ginny looks</TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-25 11:59:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-25 12:01:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or closer that least. Thats Kaya Scodelario</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-25 22:47:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love socks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Prevent things from falling into the gap between your seat and center console in your car!! Use promocode REDDIT for free shipping</TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-26 05:21:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-26 05:22:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just in case you hadn't seen this on your front page, is device fills the gap next to the car seat. They saw traffic from reddit increase and decided to give a promo  gt;Yo! Jeff and Marc here from Drop Stop Saw the traffic to the site. Thanks for the post and the love. To reward, any Reddit folks who see this post and wanna order...just type in REDDIT on promo code, hit apply, and we'll give free shipping and handling on the whole order. You'll see it appear right there in the cart before you purchase anything. Did this for another Reddit post a few days ago. Thanks again! Happy to answer any questions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-26 05:37:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ohh emma stone is a very interesting ginny!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>DYR this show? It came out on dvd recently!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-26 08:22:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-26 08:24:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I saw this at target and HAD to buy it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-28 08:53:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>excellent use of freddie! upboat from me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-28 08:54:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>this bot is awesome.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-28 09:18:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>rita skater</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>For ramen, or pho! Why didn't i think of this?!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-29 02:12:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-29 05:09:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ginny is actually not shy. IIRC, by her 4th or 5th year she's transformed into a mischievious, clever, daring, provocative, and amazing woman. If you think about it, in the books she's described as being far more desirable than Hermione, dating lots of boys (most older, if i'm not mistaken) and breaking their hearts because they were boring or controlling. Like all the other boys, Harry was captivated, and rightly so, not just because she is beautiful, but because she's fun and has a great personality.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-29 10:10:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>When they say they want experience, they mean experience as a nurse. If she really wants l amp;d, she will have to put in time as med/surg first. Here you will hone your general assessment and time management skills, and that's what they're really looking for. I've heard of ONE nurse who got into their specialty straight out of school (out of hundreds) Once she has those two years under her belt, she can move on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-30 13:22:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love how the responses are mostly in line with the character of their respective houses</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A(nother?) link between Ron and the patronus of Hermione</TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-31 07:15:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-31 07:21:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Was at the Monterey Bay Aquarium and saw this at the sea otter exhibit!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-31 09:56:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pottermore by J.K. Rowling Can you find The Magical Quill? Day 1 clue How many breeds of owl are featured on the Eeylops Owl Emporium sign? Multiply this number by 49.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-31 20:38:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mine changed too! Yayayayayayayayaay</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This firefox add on can check every 30sec for changes to website. after installation, highlight the text in the center banner of Pottermore. It sings "ch-ch-changes" when a change has been detected.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-31 20:49:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-31 21:03:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://addons.mozilla.org/en-Us/firefox/addon/check4change/ This one check every 30 secs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-08-01 04:33:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love zappos.com . Great styles, ridiculous return policy (365 days) with free shipping both ways. I looked up [black men's oxfords](http://www.zappos.com/men-oxfords/CK_XARC31wHAAQLiAgMBGAI.zso?s=goliveRecentSalesStyle/desc/#!/men-black-oxfords/CK_XARC31wFCAQPAAQLiAgQBGAII.zso?s=goliveRecentSalesStyle/desc/) for you on zappos. With this policy don't be afraid to try on things. Now how much you should spend depends on how long you want these to last and how much you have in your budget. A nice pair of black oxfords should last a long time but you will pay more obviously. Cole haan has a line of shoes with nike Air in them, which should make them very comfy. Frye is a great brand for younger people, with nice styles. You should go for something classic, so no wingtips, no pointed toe, not patent shiny, nothing too detailed, unless you really are into that. Aldo is a nice brand too, but they sometimes get a little too club-y with their styles.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-08-01 04:36:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is possuble to set your twitter to alert your smartphone when someone tweets</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-08-01 09:26:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I forget where I read it, probably from a j.k. rowling interview, but you must be magical to make potions as well. i think it had something to do with infusing the elements of the potion with magic as they are being added and brewed. i'll look for the reference</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-08-01 10:28:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Found on Leaky Cauldron  gt;here is Jo's answer to that question from An Evening with Harry, Carrie and Garp, August, 2006: QUOTE Unknown (1): Can Muggles brew potions if they follow the exact instructions and they have all of the ingredients? J.K. Rowling: Well, I'd have to say no, because there is always... there are magical component in the potion, not just the ingredients. So, at some point they will have to use a wand.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>DAY 2 POTTERMORE click the link and let it load, then click around the screen and scroll for the picture of the quill in the set of pics on the left</TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-08-01 11:13:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-08-01 11:15:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>DAY 2 POTTERMORE click the link and let it load, then click around the screen and scroll for the picture of the quill in the set of pics on the left http://quill.pottermore.com/588</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-08-01 11:39:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://quill.pottermore.com/588 DAY 2 POTTERMORE click the link and let it load, then click around the screen and scroll for the picture of the quill in the set of pics on the left</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-08-01 11:52:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>i'm not a sir, but that's okay. i think they (they being the others that haven't gotten in yet) probably would frown upon that. wait for the email, it may take awhile. mine took 20 mins. if it's not there in an hour, reg again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-08-02 11:37:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>My **shot in the dark**: in what chapter does the whomping willow destroy the nimbus 2000? Multiply this number by 35.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-08-02 11:45:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh and it will probably direct you [here](http://www.wbshop.com/Harry-Potter/hp,default,sc.html)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-08-02 12:06:27</DATE>
    <TEXT> #160;Day 3 clue #160; In the Gryffindor versus Slytherin Quidditch match, in Harry's third year, how many points is Gryffindor leading by before Harry catches the Golden Snitch? #160; Multiply this number by 35.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Day 4 registration</TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-08-03 16:31:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Day 5 registration</TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-08-04 19:33:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-08-04 19:57:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>[our power level!](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SiMHTK15Pik amp;feature=youtube_gdata_player)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-08-05 21:57:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>How about making people go bald?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-08-06 06:12:55</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;found this in the bathroom of a pub and she decided to put it on her finger?? she's definitely cursed! to St. Mungo's immediately!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-08-10 19:42:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Got mine, registered first day, 29 yo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-08-21 11:42:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have tried this, no luck here, got in on day 1, submitted my email early</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-08-24 11:15:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nurse here (RN-BSN), been working in a hospital in California for 2 years now, right out of school. I'm going nto be supportive about your choice by being realistic. Going to nursing school will take your full time commitment, especially if you're going to do it right and get your BSN. You sound fairly young, so if you're sure about this, get your BSN. As you mentioned you were a communications/marketing major, so even if you only want an ADN, I'm assuming you have to get all of your pre-requisites out of the way: chem, bio, anatomy, physiology, microbiology, sociology, statistics, psych, nutrition, etc. You may have taken care of the communications and english requirements, but the others will take at least a year, more if you want to work part-time concurrently. Then you have to get into a nursing school. I dont know what the environment is like in the NY/NJ area, but here, all nursing programs are highly competitive and impacted, meaning you have to be at the top of your game, or very lucky (ADN schools here sometimes admit based on a lottery). Most require good grades plus volunteer/paid health care experience, fluency in another language, and good scores on a nursing entrance exam. Make sure any school you consider is regionally accredited. Nursing school is rough. If you do well in your pre-reqs, you may still falter in nursing school, but the reality is, a license is a license, no matter what your grade point average was. Some of the best students i've met still only managed Bs and Cs in nursing school. You will easily spend 10+ hours a week just on a couple nursing classes writing care plans and doing homework, not to mention going to clinicals at the butt crack of dawn, or perhaps leaving at 10 pm. In my class of 48 students, 9 dropped out, 2 flunked out, and we had 2 divorces and many strained relationships amongst the remaining. I will say the NCLEX was not that bad as far as licensing exams go. But I took review classes and studied for a month for 8 hours a day. Once you get your license, be prepared to clean up a lot of poop, deal with disgruntled coworkers, and become frustrated with the state of health care. Especially if you want to be an acute or sub acute care nurse in a hospital, which it sounds like you do, if there were a lot of nurses around for your friend. California is the only state that currently mandates nursinig ratios, which means you may have to care for (so I've heard) up to 8 patients at a time. And while it has its moments, a lot of it feels thankless and frustrating. If this doesn't sound good to you, you will need a MSN degree to go straight into a supervisory or managerial poition. However, if you skip getting acute experience, your nurses will probably not respect you. I love being a nurse, but this job is not fun or for the faint of heart. It is HARD WORK and while it is worth it, it is also very very stressful throughout the process. Also check out r/nursing for more info.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-08-25 08:04:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Signed up day one, just got in, only 5 chapters are available for me though, when do i get sorted?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Badgers eat snakes for breakfast!! O__o</TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-08-30 02:52:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-09-01 07:08:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>She would EXPERIENCE more if she read the books. Or at least listened to the audiobooks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-09-01 08:48:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's about as embarassing as going to the doc/gyno. They are professionals and it's their business, they do not view it sexually. It's odd at first, but your waxist should try to make you feel at ease. The best advice i can give you is to go someplace that specializes in skin care and waxing services (they will do spa services, massage, facials, waxing, etc), rather than a place that does nails (nail salon/ hair salon/ waxing). In places that offer both, i've noticed the best waxes will be by someone that only does wax/facials and doesn't do nails; don't let the manicurists touch your foof</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-09-02 11:07:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I frequent modcloth quite a bit, and if you wait long enough it will probably come back into stock. You can sign up now for an email notification for it when it does</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-09-04 08:34:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Makeup Makeovers](http://www.barnesandnoble.com/s/Robert-Jones-makeup?store=ALLPRODUCTS amp;keyword=Robert+Jones+makeup) by Robert Jones is fantastic and shows you basics about the types of makeup, formulations of makeup, tools, and application. It shows you how to mask imperfections and exactly where to place your makeup. Best makeup book i've ever come across, and it's even in ebook format</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-09-04 09:09:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Makeup Makeovers](http://www.barnesandnoble.com/s/Robert-Jones-makeup?store=ALLPRODUCTS amp;keyword=Robert+Jones+makeup) by Robert Jones is fantastic and shows you basics about the types of makeup, formulations of makeup, tools, and application. It shows you how to mask imperfections and exactly where to place your makeup. Best makeup book i've ever come across</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>More foreshadowing fun with JKR</TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-09-04 09:31:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hope this hasn't been discussed yet, but reading CoS again, when Harry uses floo powder to accidentally transport into Borgin and Burkes, Harry notices a cursed opal necklace which is likely the one Draco uses in HBP to try and curse Dumbledore. Instead, Katie is cursed and sent to St Mungo's. DANG YOU JKR AND YOUR GENIUS!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-09-05 15:59:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>What kind of bitch would Umbridge be?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-09-05 17:45:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tom is a good looking guy, but he looks a little derpy in the bottom pic</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Show your fashionable 'Puff pride</TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-09-05 20:05:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-09-06 05:18:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, is [this ring](http://www.modcloth.com/Modcloth/Womens/Accessories/Rings/-Wind-Your-Way-Ring) more your style?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-09-06 17:50:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Was it really so simple? Yes it took planning on her part, but what i really marvel at is she didn't come back to this bit until 4 books later. I think it's admirable that on some level she expects us to remember and tie these things back, not just take them at face value.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-09-08 06:16:58</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;shutupandtakemy**galleons** FTFY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-10-17 04:29:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>What i think is really interesting about this information is that it means desmond and subject 16 must be very very closely related if both their bloodlines converge in a way such that they both have memories of altair and ezio</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-10-26 21:09:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>more of tristan? yes please: [1](http://imgur.com/yJvzJ,qc0vH) [2](http://imgur.com/yJvzJ,qc0vH#1) [3](http://imgur.com/B7RHn) holy moly...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-10-26 21:09:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>MOAR!! [1](http://imgur.com/yJvzJ,qc0vH) [2](http://imgur.com/yJvzJ,qc0vH#1) [3](http://imgur.com/B7RHn)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-10-26 21:17:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>MOAR! [1](http://imgur.com/yJvzJ,qc0vH) [2](http://imgur.com/yJvzJ,qc0vH#1) [3](http://imgur.com/B7RHn)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-10-26 21:19:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>MOAR!! [1](http://imgur.com/yJvzJ,qc0vH) [2](http://imgur.com/yJvzJ,qc0vH#1) [3](http://imgur.com/B7RHn)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-10-27 07:32:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Found stuff. Pm me your email i'll try to send to you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-10-27 07:34:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Edit: here's an excerpt, 'cause i'm legit. Description of the condition Falls incidence in nursing care facilities are reported to be about three times that in the community, equating to rates of 1.5 falls per bed per year (Luukinen 1994; Rubenstein 1994) or 1.4 falls per person per year (Nurmi 2002). In hospital settings, the presence of newly acquired risk factors for falls (e.g. hip fracture, stroke) and unfamiliar surroundings may increase falls risk. In stroke rehabilitation wards, between 25% and 46% of patients have been reported to fall at least once during their admission (Dromerick 1994; Forster 1995). An incidence of 6.2 falls per person per year in psychogeriatric wards and 3.4 falls per person per year in geriatric rehabilitation wards have been reported (Nyberg 1997).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-10-27 08:15:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>that's pomeranian with a haircut</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-10-27 20:02:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, theyre quite loud. IIRC they were originally bred from larger dogs, so they have big dog personality in a little body, and in my experience can be temperamental and yippy. Very loyal through</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Saw this and my first thought was: the templars are making their move! - Vatican suggests establishment of "global public authority" and a " central world bank" (x-post from uk reuters)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-10-27 20:17:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Real Ezio climbing - amazing Norwegian climber can do 6 pull ups with one finger</TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-10-27 20:27:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-10-28 18:38:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want second panel as background image</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-10-31 03:48:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>You married this guy?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-11-02 06:52:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know, right? "that goes for everyone" is not enough of a prompt. I know she won before but how did she get this gig? Does she sell a lot if dresses or something?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hope looked mad the entire show</TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-11-02 06:59:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wonder if training with a different pro has made Hope bitter about what her dwts experience could have been. She looked angry the entire show!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I don't think Hope should still be in the competition over David, but Nancy's screw up should have sent her home!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-11-03 02:36:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think David has shown a lot of growth this season, and while I still think Nancy is the best dancer between David, Hope, and her, Nancy should have been sent home for her screw up, much like Chynna. Hope is an awful uncoordinated dancer, and while I like her, I would never have voted for her. Nancy is a much better dancer, and David has been getting progressively better as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-11-03 08:35:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I vote for AC2 also! If he's ever been to Italy, or wanted to, he'll get a kick out of the amazing scenery and fairly accurate depictions of landmarks in that game-- the story is pretty good too!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-11-03 09:07:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Homeless appearing? Not very glamorous, but they'd fit in the city... Probably ignored even. Wasn't Desmond's family pretty nomadic?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-11-03 09:40:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nobody has enough staff or wants to pay to train brand new nurses. I get that you think you have all these hours of training and youre fresh and eager, but believe me, it's a different world when you actually get out there. I was there just 2 years ago. Also, there are TONS of new nurses all competing for jobs that require experience. I'd say a third of us got hospital jobs in the area we were schooled, but the others moved or went to SNFs or home health.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-11-03 09:46:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is a shortage of EXPERIENCED nurses and too many NEW nurses trying to break in. There is also a shortage of nurse educators not enough funding for nurse educators-- because why teach when you can make more practicing in a facility? No one wants to spend the money to train a new nurse because the investment is not good enough to them to take the chance and train a new graduate who is a bigger liability than the experienced traveling nurse whom they don't have to provide benefits to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-11-03 09:56:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>[CPR shields on keychains](http://www.buyemp.com/product/11229859.html)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-11-03 10:31:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi i'm finishing a Masters in nursing education and thought I'd put in my $0.02. From what i gather, seeing as this your teacher's first online class, she has no clue how to run an online class and nobody showed her how. Assignments and expectations should be VERY clear, with specific dates and a REASONABLE time to do the assignments in. If she expected discussions, she should have said that outright in the syllabus. The assignments should also reflect information that can be found in your learning materials, or else based on concepts within your learning materials. Assignments must be graded in a consistently timely manner. If you meet again with the dean, you should bring [this article on evaluating online teaching](http://info.sreb.org/programs/EdTech/pubs/PDF/Essential_Principles.pdf) and maybe [this article on standards and guidelines](http://academic.regis.edu/ghodne/OnlineAssessment/Online_Guidelines.pdf) Know objectively where she stands based on these guidelines as compared to her emails, her assignments, and especially her syllabus, and that should help make it painfully clear where her shortcomings are. And not to be a jerk, but the blame can't be put solely on her. If she'd been PROPERLY trained to teach an online course, you wouldnt have this problem. I feel some schools think they can get away with online courses because they present the illusion of being less work, when in reality, it's a LOT more work for both the student and teacher, you just get to do all that work on your own time with no commute.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-11-03 20:55:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I totally agree, hope should have gone long ago, but for some reason they stay on. Maks is a great dancer but even "sex on a stick" can't fix hope's epic awkwardness. I try not to judge people based in who they appear to be, but rather how good of a dancer they are. I was just as shocked that chynna and kristin went home as i am that NG gets to stay when she flubbed everything that night, and DA was good. This is all despite the fact that NG is actually the best dancer of the three, when she's not messing up. She appears to have actually learned the basic steps. I wonder if Tristan has anything to do with it. I must admit i think he's adorable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-11-03 21:00:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, thats just petty and evil. This teacher sounds truly awful, but the thing is you cant go to the dean and appeal to his emotions. "look, she made this girl cry" isn't as compelling as "these are the standards for an online class and she isn't meeting them"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-11-03 21:18:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah sort of an odd thing. I mean it's funny, no one notices ezio running around in his super nice robes with huge weapons dangling from his belt. I suppose shawn's clothing blends better into the modern world in terms of flexibility, as i feel a full suit can be kind of conspicuous. But as for the hood, i guess it doesnt get any better than the one desmond has now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-11-03 21:19:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahh, i started with AC2, so i don't know much of his backstory.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-11-04 01:03:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks i'll check those out!! I actually got into the series after going on a trip to Italy ;p I wanted to reminisce but i got so into the game i bought brotherhood also. Now i have revelations pre ordered as well!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-11-07 02:41:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree on those brands and would like to add Naya, Earthies, and Fitzwell. However Sofft is my ultimate favorite comfort heel brand. They use an awesome mix of comfort and good looks. Thicker heeled and wedge heeled shoes will feel more stable and more comfortable Also, if you want height, [platforms with thicker heels](http://zappos.com/product/7820871/color/303764) can be comfortable, while still being cute. If you notice, the heel height is 3 inches, but the platform us 3/4 inches, so the actual heel raise is actually only 2 1/4 inches. However platform wedges tend to look overwhelming on me, and can get way [too high and young looking](http://zappos.com/product/7884396/color/3) so i stay away from those. If you wear wide, look for wide high heels. Sofft is quite good at this. Additionally, avoid overly pointy toed shoes. Go for a more almond or rounded toe. As others have mentioned, stay away from things with skinny straps and most peep toes. There are brands that do peep toes right, but if you are looking for function over form, skip the peep toe. Leather is the key as it stretches over time, but stay away from patent (shiny) leather which is stiffer and less yielding to squished toes. If really desperate, try looking for REAL dancing shoes. Same rules apply but the toe box for dancing shoes tends to be bigger with more coverage on the sides which helps avoid pinching and bunions. The downside here is your options will be much more limited. Just be sure they have "street" soles, as opposed to suede sole which can't really be worn outside of the ballroom. Edit: chnaged "heel" to "toe" in the tirade on pointy toed shoes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-11-11 12:10:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Eurail pass is awesome, but they're only for sale to non-european union members ie. you'll have to buy one before you get there</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-11-11 12:30:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>My brother said the same thing when i told him i finished AC2 and was working on AC:B. i've only played these two, but i didn't find the gameplay repetitive. As someone who's seen many of the towns in italy where AC2 takes place, the worlds are ridiculously immersive, accurate, and gorgeous. There are more and new characters and the story keeps developing and makes you care what happens next-- i was compelled to try to get 100% to get the whole story. I think AC2 is stronger than ACB storywise, but the missions in ACB are more varied</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-12-02 13:51:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Instead of "why should we hire you" i got "why are you a good fit" and "why do you want to work with us". It helps to know what the characteristics of the unit are. Also, character questions like, "describe a time you were in conflict with a coworker-- how did you handle it?" and "describe a time when you demonstrated teamwork". They may also ask situational questions like, you observe such and such a thing, how would you handle this? For these questions, i'm fairly certain theyre more interested in hearing your thought processes and are checking your critical thinking skills moreso than if you know the right answer. Especially since you are new, this is pretty important, as you will probably not have all the right answers right away. I also got what do you see yourself doing in 5 years and 10 years.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-12-20 03:33:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was there in September. Rome is a blast! It sounds like you want to make this trip really memorable for your gf. If so, trust me on this: BRING A DECENT SIZED PADLOCK that uses keys. I remember walking across the bridges crossing the Tiber and noticing padlocks that had been locked all over the bridge with couples' names on them. Pro tip: get the padlock engraved with your names and once you've locked the padlock securely, toss the keys in the river. If you like ice cream, you must visit Caffe Giolitti. Second best gelato I had the entire trip. Best was in Siena. The Sistine Chapel is amazing. Pictures of it do not do it justice, and even if you are not religious, knowing the time it took, how long it has been there, and the talent that went into it should be enough for anyone to appreciate. Go early, be prepared to wait, and be aware that the line starts way outside the Basilica. I also really enjoyed the Piazza Navona and the Pantheon, and Trevi fountain was really nice to see at night - much less crowded. Obviously, Ancient Rome is not to be missed, the Colosseum and Forum are super cool. My best advice for food is to follow your guidebook and avoid the touristy spots as best you can.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-12-20 20:35:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>upvote for "yo dawg". not really worth my money though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-12-21 02:40:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I will always be your constant"?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-12-21 02:58:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>PRO TIP: get an [ID tag engraved](http://solutions.3m.com/wps/portal/3M/en_US/3M-Littmann/stethoscope/stethoscope-catalog/catalog/~/3M-Littmann-Stethoscope-Identification-Tags-2171-Gray-5-each/case?N=4294871053+5142935 amp;Nr=AND%28hrcy_id%3AGSTJ4V8N97gs_C7QGLCF9G8_1JTK302GS0_GPD0K8BC31gv%29 amp;rt=d) for her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-12-31 20:37:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Essie mochaccino: warm greige (gray/beige) with sparkle. Available in us drugstores Opi for sephora leotard optional: light brownish pink</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-12-31 22:03:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have black hair and brown eyes and i use the same benefit brow zings kit in dark, and it is perfect. The pigmented wax allows a place for the powder to stick to. I tend to use the wax to brush in my eyebrow, the way i might with a pencil, and then brush in the powder. It's the only thing i like for my brows now, it's that or nothing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-12-31 22:10:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>The too faced naked eye palette is really beautiful too, with cooler less gold tones. Another really great palette! It's much more versatile than the natural eye palette with a lot less glitter and too faced eyeshadows are some of the best delivering easiest to blend shadows i've come across.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-01-01 07:15:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>You remind me of a more exotic audrey tautou! So pretty!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>JJ Abrhams connection: "LOST" numbers in ep 6955 mHz</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-01-05 09:08:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-01-07 09:26:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>The bottle of liquor in the LSD cartoon episode that Belly drinks was the same brand that appeared significantly in Lost! They are alive and well!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-01-07 12:16:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Forever a-parasitic fungus</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-01-08 09:52:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Point taken! Can't help it though, i love both shows! Finally got caught up this week and ready for next week!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>After finally catching up with the show, i have some thoughts and theories! Are there any you'd like to share before the premiere? (Spoilers if you're not caught up!)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-01-08 11:24:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>* I see that there are two popular theories about the new yellow/amber-verse: the amberverse is a third universe; and the amberverse is the existing blue/red-verse rewritten. I'm tending toward the former, that the amberverse is a third universe that was created when Peter got into the machine. This is my guess since the machine had the ability to destroy and create universes. We already saw the result of destroying a universe, and this is the result of creating a universe. Also, the visual cues of blue red and yellow as the primary colors make me believe this is a separate universe. * I'm dying to see how (if?) Olivia will act as the "fail-safe" . I guess I also just want to see Peter and Olivia back together because I'm a sucker for love stories. * Speaking of love stories - i am concerned that Peter and Olivia just cant have their happy ending! I can't remember who said it, but someone said that the best love stories are tragic, or something to that effect. * i'm so impressed with the story telling this season. While i don't always see the point of the MOTW/COTW, it was very plain that the themes in these episodes have mirrored the characters' emotional journeys. One night in october was amazing, easily one of the strongest episodes of the series and a great episode to emphasize the importance of choices and of not being a victim of your circumstances. * i was really confused by the lcd tv and toy plane at peter's new house on campus. I just dont think those are likely to have been provided when walter might have moved in two years ago, and even if they gave him a new tv, did walter buy his peter a toy plane and bring it with him to the college? I guess he could have, since there were other toys of Peter's there, but i had thought that was the toy elizabeth had bought red peter, as seen in subject 13. * does anyone else feel this season is very it's-a-wonderful-life-ish atm? All the characters are so pathetic without Peter: Walter must live at his lab because he never got over his agoraphobia; Olivia can't seem to move on emotionally; and Astrid is easily irritated and seems unfulfilled. However since Peter created the bridge, they have begun to make progress. Phew. Glad to get that off my chest. What do you think? Gah, can't wait for the next ep guys!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Nude tones with sparkle base water marble [PC FA Cell]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-01-23 23:16:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-01-23 23:19:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Base: Sephora by OPI -Keep me on my mistletoes Marble1: sephora by OPI - leotard optional Marble 2: sephora by OPI - dear diary</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-02-06 06:50:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>In season one, Peter mentions thay it is easier to lie when the lie is closest to the truth. He gave the example that he might use the name Peter Knight on a con. Clearly a chess reference if it helps. This could be an interesting clue if it leads somewhere.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-02-11 09:24:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love that mani, especially the nude color, thanks for posting the brand and name!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-02-19 13:20:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is an observer in every episode. If you check out fringepedia, they catalogue all the observers, clues to the following episode, all the glyphs, and other trivia for each episode. They've always been there. http://fringepedia.net/wiki/Fringepedia</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-02-29 20:19:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have to agree, i can't wait for jaleel white. I can imagine him being quite dashing! I don't know if i care to see him dress up as a nerd as some celebs have for other dances. Would it feel cliche or awesomely nostalgic?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-02-29 20:27:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Add diced celery, a little minced red onion, cashews, a little chopped apple, and curry powder to the chicken and mayo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-08 11:01:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nurse here... Everything looks awesome and if you deelop you're natural talent and work hard you cn go far! My two cents, in addition to swelling and redness, it might be useful to think about what a bruise and wound look like as they get older too. For example, older bruises start to turn yellow and green, and untreated infected wounds can start turning green and black and ooze yellow pus. Infected wounds my also have a yellow stringy layer on top, or a crusty dry black layer. Maybe try googling "gangrene", or "eschar"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-08 11:07:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Benefit dandelion and hervana are really light pretty pinks that will look more natural on a paler face. I love sugrbomb but i have more light/medium skin that tans and can pull off coralista and orgasm no problem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-08 11:23:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree, some contouring and highlighting would go a long way!! You have AMAZING cheekbones!! Maybe a little benefit hoola to contour, it's a matte bronzer (just make sure you go really easy with the provided brush, or use a different one all together), and whatever highlighter you like. I'm admittedly a benefit girl, so i like the pearl one, but the nars highlighters are pretty too and very good quality. Robert jones has a series of books that show exactly where to put what products for contouring and highlighting! Really great with photos, diagrams, and before and after photos and also available in e book format. I would also invest in a concealer for use under your eyes, it will make your eyes pop that much more. I really like the dior three color eyeshadow and lancome 5 color eyeshdow palettes if you really want to treat yourself, and smashbox or urban decay eyeshadow primers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-16 15:55:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was lucky enough to snag this too! I'd say it's more purple than pink. Such an awesome color, and i think it covered it two coats.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Nude discoball nails!! So sparkly, yet still surprisingly unassuming! (PC, CCW, cell)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-16 21:51:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-16 21:56:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Many layers for this: Base Zoya - avery (creamy nude) Butter london - hen party (irridescent nude/purple) China glaze - fairy dust (tiny multi reflective glitter? I don't even know, i just love it) Revlon - stunning (clear with tiny silver glitter and larger multi reflective hex glitter)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My own St Patty's inspired green and gold gradient mani featuring CG HG Agro! (CCW, FA, cell)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-16 22:00:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-16 22:11:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>As mentioned i used Base One layer: China Glaze (Hunger Games) - Agro Plus! Tips: OPI for sephora (christmas 2011) - keep me on my mistletoes Gradient: essie (luxeffects) - as gold as it gets I can't seem to get a good hold of the gradients. I don't like the tips, but i wanted a stronger gold at the end than i seem to get without the tips. However the tips got so goopy they started smooshing everywhere. I also would like to do gradient w/o a sponge, as you can see i just did this in subsequent layers. Please - CCW!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Anyone else really impressed with the new line of Revlon colors?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-16 22:26:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Once i got ino the world of OPI i sort of abandoned my Revlon polishes deeming them inferior colorwise. I was used to the formula and actually liked how it's a bit thin, because then less bubbles and less cracks under topcoat. But lately i've seeing some amazing colors - whimsical, stunning, scandalous, and sparkling, just to name a few. I'm thinking i should spend more time in their aisle at the local ulta rather than keep myself confined to the OPI, essie, CG, butter london section...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-17 05:39:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>For me the zoya avery went on really thick, and after so many layers, a few days later it was getting cracks in it. This was my first try with a zoya, but if i were to do this again, i'd either go straight to hen party, or skip hen party. I just really liked how hen party gave it some extra depth with its irridescence.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Searched and didn't see this yet: BellaSugar tutorial on how to make your own magnetic polish! Has anyone tried this before?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-18 07:42:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-18 20:22:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fast track is my fave, but i am really into nude shades. I also like riveting and harvest moon, as well as the matte Stone cold. Dress me up is also an awesome neutral. I like luxe and lush, but i think it's too much like shine of the times which is more wearable</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-20 07:52:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>have her check out the pinup style wiggle and swing dresses on [Unique Vintage](http://www.unique-vintage.com/). They have longer lengths and lots of different and interesting styles</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-20 08:24:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I LOVE Ramen Dojo, but my hands down favorite ramen is at Izakaya Sozai in SF. Pork broth + spicy miso = heaven Also, Santa ramen (and ramen parlor) are the same guys as ramen dojo, though dojo is the tastiest choice of these three by far.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-20 15:41:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Victorias secret sells a convertible low back bra (the "gorgeous" model iirc), but the piece that makes it low back is just a wide strap extension with the right number of hooks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Experiment # 1: essie "a cut above" and revlon "sparkling": true dupe?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-22 04:39:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Experiment #2: OPI "DS coronation" vs OPI "bling on the snowflakes" + china glaze "fairy dust"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-22 05:03:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-22 05:09:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Base: Sephora by OPI Dear Diary Essie - A Cut Above on thumb, middle and pinky fingers Revlon - Sparkling on index and ring fingers The essie shade is more saturated with the larger hex glitter, and this is even evident from looking at the polishes within their bottles. Essie's formula is thicker too, which I think helps with application. However, at 4-5 dollars less, Sparkling isn't a bad dupe, you'll just have to apply more coats, or more apply carefully (try to pick up more of the larger glitter). Edited for formatting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-22 05:16:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>OPI - DS Coronation on Thumb, middle, and pinky, Sephora by OPI - Bling on the Snowflakes PLUS China Glaze - fairy dust on index and ring fingers The DS coronation is one of the prismatic colors, and has a lot of depth. This is three coats, and is really smooth and almost grayer. The layered polishes are close, but don't have the same depth of the true prismatic polish, although I think i could achieve the same effect with more coats of fairy dust and a slightly darker base, maybe even a light gray instead of silver. More investigation needed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-22 10:36:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have you looked at [benefit brow zings](http://www.benefitcosmetics.com/product/view/brow-zings?ext_id=psad_Ggl__Mobile amp;siteID=NvvL0PcAZqY-O2PCi8naJmjSUkVGxYQXAw)?? It is a compact with colored wax and brow powder, two brushes and tweezers. It comes in a light shade and looks natural. The hard angled brush is perfect with the wax and helps to shape them too. The powder matches well, and is far easier and more forgiving than a pencil</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-23 03:39:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have my polishes grouped by color, more or less. All my nudes, neutrals, grays, glitters, and topcoats, are in one box, and then I have another box arranged by color.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-23 17:58:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I dont have wheels, but seriously considering now.... Inside my boxes theyre arranged by similar color, so my lighter nudes are together, my light grays are together, my black tones are together, etc. The box of colors is easier. I'll post pics later</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-23 20:27:58</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;the spirit of Panem already in our society. FTFY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-24 01:33:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>cast a spell looks more like fast lane with a darker base rather than green, but maybe it's my screen. spectacle almost looks like gold and blue microglitter. Count me in for those plus immortal. i can't tell if glitter goblin is awesome or something i've already got =\</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-24 08:21:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>RN here - probably because of its anti-inflammatory properties, it reduced the swelling in your sinuses and opened them up a bit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-27 21:12:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would consider getting lots of nude and neutral tones: beige, tan, sand, pinks, light brown, light bronzes and golds, warm gray, subtle topcoats, mattes. And then, go crazy!!! Just because you are limiting your colors doesn't mean you have to limit your designs. I think some of the classiest and age appropriate designs are interesting combinations of nudes and neutrals.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Nude tone mani with silvery pearl gradient [PC, CCW, Cell]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-28 02:25:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-28 02:30:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably my most favorite mani yet, subtle but not boring! Base coat, Essie "Mamba", then Essie "Pure Pearlfection" gradient, plus shiny top coat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-31 22:59:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>My mom likes to have fresh avocado scooped out into a bowl with cream and sugar. She also is fond of avocado ice cream.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-04-02 10:48:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Prime example of nurses "eating their young". Why do we do this to each other? It's no wonder we get burnt out so easily-- such little support.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-04-04 10:12:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>[hamburger helper](http://www.thecoupondiaries.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/06/HamburgerHelperL11.jpg) is basically american style dinner in a box: pasta, plus seasonings/sauce. just boil the noodles and add hamburger, or more accurately, ground beef. there are lots of different flavors, like "three cheese", "cheeseburger", "cheesy enchilada", "stroganoff", and "lasanga". They also have "chicken helper". Edited for completeness</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-04-04 10:35:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>you're right. *technically* LVNs cannot do certain assessments, and therefore should not suggest orders, but you're right, in the real world sometimes we have LVNs take an assignment, which means they better be advocating for their patients.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-04-06 10:46:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Modcloth](http://www.modcloth.com/shop/party-dresses) and Unique Vintage (http://www.unique-vintage.com/occasion-bridesmaid-dresses-c-225_169.html) are good websites to check out. I ordered my bridesmaids dresses from unique vintage and i am a frequent shopper of modcloth. Both very reliable with gorgeous dresses and some run in extended sizes, especially unique vintage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-04-12 11:32:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just home cook here. My go to dishes are all braised-- you really can't go wrong. First a basic braised short rib- sear the short ribs on all sides, cover with liquid (french onion soup, mushroom or beef stock, and/or red wine do nicely), bring to a boil, then let simmer for at least 2 hours. 3 would be better, longer would be best. Adding pepper and a bay leaf are good ideas if you have them, and you can add veggies and potatoes and turn it into a stew, but just the beef is pretty delicious. Second is my version of filipino chicken adobo: sear chicken thighs skin side down (skinless works too), add roughly chopped 1-2 tomatoes and half-1 onion to cook down for a bit, add liquid to cover, 1 part vinegar to 2 parts soy sauce and another 2 parts water to cover. Add a bay leaf and then lots of pepper to taste, bring to a boil then simmer down for 30-60 mins. I like to serve this with rice, and i like mine dry, but lots of my family enjoys the liquid as a sauce with the rice. I also make badass mashed potatoes. Peel, chop, and boil potatoes. When all pieces are soft all the way through, drain and return to heat. Add lots of butter while you mash. Alternatively you can use a ricer, but i tend not to. Once mashed to an even, smooth consistency and youve incorporated 1-2 sticks of butter in (depending on the amout of potato) add cream or half and half to get a consistency you like. Salt and pepper to taste. I also second the carbonara. Easy and impresive. Also pesto! Basil in the processor, then a little garlic, a little parmesean, some pinenuts, and salt to taste. Gradually add olive oil to the cosistency you like. Don't cook it, no cream, add it to the pasta. Spread it on bread too! Practice dishes you like. Eventually it becomes second nature and you can make it up as you go</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-04-12 11:46:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>This dessert was a BIG hit at thanksgiving and christmas: Put a scoop of good vanilla ice cream into a small dish/bowl (ice cream sized, yes?) and then pour 1-2 teaspoons (or tablespoons!) Bailey's Irish Cream over top. It shouldn't be so easy to be that delicious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Copperplate nails!! Ccw, pc!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-04-20 19:48:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-04-20 19:54:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>2 coats CG: hunger games - harvest moon 2 coats sephora by opi - traffic stopper copper It looks like hammered copper from far away!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-04-20 20:11:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really like this color too! I have light/medium asian skin and it's what I call one of my "perfect nudes"-- it mimics the pink tones in my skin perfectly! One of my other perfect nudes is dior's beige safari which mimics the lightness of my skin. I'm trying to find a cheaper similar color. I'm also trying to find a perfect nude for the medium tones in my skin. Nice doggie! Is he a rat terrier? My dog looks like him!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-04-27 09:08:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I lived in PR for two years. It will be hot and humid and hurricane season starts around july/august IIRC. There is a lot of history on the island. Old san juan is cool, el morro (an old fortress) is there. Get breakfast at La bombonera-- it has the tastiest mallorca (bread rolls) and a super old espresso machine. It can be very touristy but I think this area is worth it. Ponce is very nice too and has an awesome museum. El yunque is the national rainforest and really beautiful. It also has caves that were featured in batman forever. The satelite dish at the arecibo observatory is kind of neat too. It was featured in goldeneye. The beaches are awesome. Amazing fine white sand, though there is also a beach (i forget where now) with black sand. The water is clear and beautiful and warm. I don't actually remember there being a lot of seafood in PR. You will probably eat more starchy things like rice and beans and plantains and deep fried empanadas there. Btw, the empanadas are amazing. Things are actually relatively expensive there because everything is imported. I was personally terrified of driving there. Lanes are super small and the drivers are fearless. I'm not sure how efficient the metro is because it wasn't complete yet when i was living there, but i remember that at the time, buses were highly inefficient. You can get across the island in something like 3 hours (with traffic) so you can do a lot in a day. Though english and spanish are the national languages, if you're planning on straying from the beaten path you'll need to bone up on your spanish.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Downton theme on Dancing with the Stars. The dance itself wasn't amazing, but I still went "squee!" when it started</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-02 01:22:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-03 18:04:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This is the interview where they say that Altair is not related to Ezio](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=46FRp7dIn80 amp;feature=youtube_gdata_player). Interesting interview if you haven't seen it. TLDW: Desmond is descended from many different unrelated assassins' bloodlines. It explains that although Desmond is descended from Altair and Ezio, the two assassins are not related AT ALL. Desmond is the convergence of many bloodlines, which is why he is the one in the Animus, and not Desmond's daddy (for example). Likewise, Connor must be an ancestor of Desmond, but also not descended from Altair or Ezio. I'm betting he must have had major contact with a Piece of Eden, there's no reason to follow him otherwise.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-06 06:22:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, neither did i until i bought the soundtrack. Atrocious. It should never have had lyrics put to it, and if the lyrics came first, shame on that songwriter.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-08 21:04:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you are totally right to honor the memory while still making your wedding a celebration. Maybe you can just leave a space in the wedding where he would be. For example, while the wedding party is walking, you can leave him a space where he would walk, and leave a space at the altar where we would have stood. Keep his spot open at the wedding party's dinner table, maybe even keep the place setting? He can still be there in spirit, without taking the focus off your happy day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-08 21:40:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wear a skirt and top with a similar shape as your dress. If it's strapless, find a similar top so you can replicate the feeling. For the skirt, find something with a similar fabric, length and especially the similar weight so you can feel the movement of the skirt. Dance stores have heavy practice skirts and you might even try wearing more than one if it isn't heavy or wide enough. Also! You may want to consider wearing the actual shoes you will be dancing in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-11 11:52:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>ironic morals are MORONIC!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-11 21:13:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are lots of gluten free pasta options, and rice is gluten free. Just make sure the liquid for boiling is gluten free--for example if you cook the rice in chicken stock</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-11 21:19:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dat reflection!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-12 09:44:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>from the article:  gt;nearly every psychopathic adult was deeply antisocial as a child [... but] almost 50 percent of children who scored high on measures of antisocial qualities did not go on to become psychopathic adults and  gt;physiology isn't destiny just because a child is genetically pre-disposed, s/he is not necessarily going to end up a product of her/his genetics. this reminds me of an episode of [fringe where a man became a serial killer or a brilliant professor depending on the kind intervention of one person](http://fringepedia.net/wiki/One_Night_In_October). it's a simplified argument, but shouldn't people be allowed to make their choices before we condemn them? that said, this kid sounds psychotic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-16 08:41:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>* no appetizers or * JUST an appetizer * eat half the meal and toss the rest * salads w/dressings on the side! * don't eat the bread and butter at the beginning of the meal. just check how the things are prepared, obviously something grilled (usually) has less calories than the same item fried.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-16 12:06:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>you could have the ushers use pretty bells, or a gong. if you haven't sent the invites, you could include a small map or explanation of the plan, or else include something in the program (if you end up using one). if that's the case they will lead themselves-- in my past experience people like being in the know and feeling smart ;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-24 06:29:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm 9 years out, and I would absolutely make the same choice. I am an asian female and never felt discriminated against. I think it's safe to say if you come you will definitely find your niche. Honestly, your experience will depend on YOU. if you aim to get out and meet people of different races, you will, and you will make great friends. if people of a certain race decide not to be friends with you based on yours, you probably don't care to be their friend anyway. i think Cal students are probably the most open minded students there are. they study hard and party hard. it all depends on what you want to do. if you want to study 25/8, you'll find people to do that with you. if you want to party like it's 1999, they're out there, but you better believe at the end of the day, they take care of their business too. Many of the programs at Cal are THE BEST in the nation, inclusive of the "ivy leagues". i believe students are the most well rounded and that's partially because of the core curriculum for the college of letters and science and the quality of students-- people want to be there, want to learn, want to get the most of their college experience. the campus is relatively small, but there is a lot of area around the campus that will feel like home too, like the city of berkeley itself, the bart (metro) into the City (SF), and oakland.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-24 07:36:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I work in CA where we have a surplus of new grads. while you're NOT required to do med-surg first, at most places they are the positions available because the nurses that have seniority want those specialty positions and then med-surg opens up. of the 38 classmates i graduated with, i think only one got her NICU position right off the bat. and i might be remembering that wrong. the public health department i wanted to start out with TOLD ME i should do med-surg first then come back to them in a year. so, there you go. i guess it depends on what state you want to work in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-24 19:35:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>This turns it into a [strata](http://www.google.com/search?q=strata+recipe amp;ie=UTF-8 amp;oe=UTF-8 amp;hl=en amp;client=safari). Bread + frittata mixture (before cooking) = strata</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-25 08:48:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>if she doesn't already have a great stethoscope, [this stethoscope](http://www.allheart.com/2163-65.html) is pretty badass. you can laser engrave her name and new title on the tubing and also put initials on the head. i have the same one, and it's amazing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My cakeday submission: my smiling dog!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-27 00:32:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-06-01 22:09:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's like an awesome erupting mini volcano complete with lava! And pus!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-06-04 03:03:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>This ought to be in the sidebar, don't you think?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-06-08 04:14:00</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I had interviewed there just the other day for a floor nurse position but I turned it down because I really want to go into wound care. the original position she applied for is standard floor nurse. they called her back for a new interview in a wound care nurse position.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-06-08 04:38:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>lean cuisines and steamer bag veggies!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-06-08 08:19:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesus! Gotta save this thread... I second the vote on no mambo #5!! I didnt even realize how much i hate those songs until i saw them all here. Thank you thank you for this reminder!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>As an MT, how do you feel about your clients falling asleep?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-06-08 09:37:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I checked to see if this has been asked before: I've had massage done regularly for the past two years or so, ranging from trigger point to swedish, and I'm wondering if it's okay if I fall asleep on the table. I would ask my therapists but I confess I'm embarassed about it. Is it considered bad etiquette? Is it confirmation that your client is relaxed? I love massage and I love my therapists and I don't want to offend them!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-06-08 21:17:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ooh i don't talk, but i try to enjoy my breathing and muscles and things. I find myself trying to keep awake out of politeness, but i wasn't sure it was necessary to keep awake, hence my question. Okay, how about snoring? Is that awkward or similarly ok? Also, when all my body juices get going, often times my nose starts running. Is that normal, and do you want to know or would you rather we ignore it until we flip over? I've had MTs tell me to just let it run all over...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-06-09 07:29:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for mentioning this, i never realized it was considered annoying to "help". From my POV it's my own self consciousness wanting to be thoughtful, sort of how i won't let my fianc #233; carry me piggyback because i'm kind of a big girl with big limbs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-06-09 13:11:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Da Vinci Code. I should have loved it, but for some reason just could not get into it. Also, Interview with the Vampire</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-06-10 03:36:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Having been in a similar but not identical situation to the movie Unfaithful =)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-06-10 04:52:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Be gentle: [yanni (live at the acropolis) - within attraction](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EqcR6ud-MCo amp;hd=1) [another (newer version) with different soloist](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mIsi1yxNQvg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-06-10 05:16:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I also love sandwiches. ONE of my favorites is from a place in the SF Bay Area called Bake Sale Betty. They serve the absolute best chicken sandwich EVER. [Imagine a pieces of perfectly seasoned, still juicy, crunchy fried chicken breast, jalapeno red onion cabbage slaw (vinaigrette base) between a fresh french roll.](http://www.yelp.com/biz_photos/PkLfjhJ_XExjwARO1RkQIw?select=-Wcx-_Eyqau6IRKtB9rBvA#-Wcx-_Eyqau6IRKtB9rBvA) ugh i want one now!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-06-10 05:33:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Favorites: * Benefit erase paste * Benefit Hoola * Benefit Sugarbomb * NARS orgasm blush * Urban Decay 24/7 eyeliner (persuasion) * Stila Stay All Day Waterproof Liquid Eyeliner Pen * Smashbox photo finish lid primer * Tarte light camera lashes! Least favorite: * Dior Diorshow mascara * anything philosophy * anything Clinique skin care</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-06-10 08:52:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I use hoola as a contour. for me it builds pretty nicely, and it's matte, so it does a pretty good job.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-06-10 09:01:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I tend to mix and match whatever doesn't make me break out. philosophy just smelled awful to me. i use [peter thomas roth (the blue scrubby one)](http://peterthomasroth.com/p-105-botanical-buffing-beads.aspx) as a cleansing exfoliant. if i want to be rougher, i use [lush's ocean salt](http://www.lushusa.com/Ocean-Salt/9999902128,en_US,pd.html?start=1 amp;cgid=cleansers), if i want something milder, i use [fresh's soy face cleanser](http://www.fresh.com/skincare/skincare-soy/soy-face-cleanser-150ml). i also like peter thomas roth's [ultimate creme in a tube](http://peterthomasroth.com/p-212-ultimate-crme-in-a-tube.aspx) or [oil free moisturizer](http://peterthomasroth.com/p-69-oil-free-moisturizer.aspx) depending on how dry my face feels anything with salicylic acid makes me break out, so i don't use anything with that in it. instead i just exfoliate a lot and use moisturizer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-06-10 09:20:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a nurse: That nurses are inferior and subordinate to doctors. This is inaccurate; nurses have a different scope of practice and a different kind of expertise and training than a doctor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-06-10 09:39:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>very generally, nurses are trained to understand what's wrong with your health and intervene to improve your health. we make our own "nursing diagnoses" based on your health deficiencies and our actions are supposed to remedy those deficiencies. this includes physical ailments, obviously, but we are also trained to provide emotional support and assess social situations of the client/patient and make recommendations based on all the things we observe. our clients may be a patient in a hospital, or an entire community, and the key is that we observe, make assessments, and then try to act in such a way to improve the situation. we are trained to be observers, and our assessments can drive the decisions your doctor makes. again, it's not a question of superiority, it's a collaboration where each party has their own sets of information to manage and different (though complimentary) goals in care.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-06-12 22:55:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>yes there is. upvote. =p</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-06-12 23:41:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>isn't this the guy whose trainer is currently the trainer on Extreme Makeover: Weight Loss Edition? EDIT: [YEAH it is...](http://www.reshapethenation.com/results)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-06-13 00:56:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>She can bear children, she'll just probably have to have them cut out when they're ready.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-06-15 10:22:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here's his original post: http://www.reddit.com/r/loseit/comments/v2tmh/lost_92_pounds_from_268lb_to_176lb/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-06-15 21:07:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like a thumb to me. Wishful thinking, OP?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-06-19 21:26:26</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; "I am not a dog... I do not get rewarded with a cookie." I will hang this on my wall</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-07-08 07:05:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got to know my school preceptor pretty well, so i ended up getting her a sephora gift card; she's younger than me, and loves makeup. When my preceptee moved on, she got me a small coach zip pouch, and i really liked it. I got her a review book ;p Essentially, it depends on what your preceptor is into, same as a gift for anyone else. It doesn't necessarily need to be nurse themed. Relaxation stuff is nice too though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-07-08 07:22:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any other Firefly fans reminded of the Shindig episode with the Armani double line look?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-08-10 08:41:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>What about a new sub, /r/newnurse for students and new grads or those getting into the profession? I would be interested in r/nursing being more scholarly, like more research info, updated EBP, new drugs, discussion on the profession, conferences and professional meetings. I often find myself checking in here to find posts on what it's like to be a nurse, or wanting to know if nursing is the right profession, and i would check in a lot more often if this sub had useful information.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-03 06:27:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I use these [sugar facial hair removal strips](http://www.amazon.com/gp/aw/d/B001ET701I). They're really easy to use, you wash the area where you're removing hair (so it grabs the hair and not the oil on yor face), warm the strips up between your palms or behind your knee for a couple minutes, peel the strips apart, apply to the hairy area, brace yourself and pull! It stings but it's not horrible, and it's probably a lot less work than trying to use wax yourself. After a while, the hairs grow less.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-09 08:12:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bronzers can be used for contouring, but you wouldn't use a bronzer with shimmer as a contour color. I use [benefit hoola bronzer](http://m.sephora.com/product/productDetail.jsp?productId=P290636) as a contour color. It can be layered for more saturation and is matte.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-09 08:47:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think he means Gus' original pollos hermanos partner, the one Hector killed in the pool. In a side note, did anyone else think he was Gus' life partner as well as drug partner?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-10 20:44:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually think the cancer is still in remission. We already know he makes it to 52. What i think has changed is Walter's reaction to this news. Previously, he was angry that he'd made such terrible choices for seemingly no reason as he now would have much longer to live. He is terrified of the inevitable consequences of these decisions. Now though, he's come to terms with those choices; he's accepted who and what he is, and there are no apologies. I feel the towel dispenser is to remind him and us that he is not who he was when he started cooking. Cancer or not, he has to know the fallout is coming, and from a moral perspective, i think he feels the cancer would be too easy a way out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-10 21:25:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Amazon streaming video</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-10 21:35:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like the reason there's not speculation about Gale is because it was fairly obvious with Gale. With Gus I didn't have an inkling until they show the episode of Gus' history with the cartel.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-10 21:45:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes! I really thought some shit was going to go down, and then NOTHING. Actually I'm still waiting for that fallout. That will be a good episode.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-11 05:34:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hmm, I guess i really did breeze through the episodes too quickly. I suspect i needed to mull it over in my head much longer rather than waiting a couple minutes before the next episode starts to really appreciate the episodes. Sometimes I wonder if I do the writers a disservice by watching all the episodes in huge chunks instead of one a week because of this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-11 07:57:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oops!! Noted, thanks ^__^'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-11 09:16:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Luckily with a FREAKIN YEAR between now and 5.9, i can rewatch the series and let the episodes have more time in my brain! Thanks for the insight!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-13 03:19:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you do this often?? Is this a thing? I played with someone last night that did this!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-20 18:07:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Loved him in kick-ass!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-21 17:30:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I keep threatening my fianc #233; that i'm going to dress as sexy walt with a bald cap, goatee, green shirt, glasses, and white hotpants as briefs. He was not amused</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-23 22:16:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you may [relate to this](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QSGOFnyr3OU amp;feature=youtube_gdata_player)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My most recent project: chunky doggie sweater!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-24 10:10:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-24 10:19:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was done freehand in 2-3 hours on size 13 needles circular needles using wool ease thick and quick. Bonus ribbed neck and hem. It was knit all in one piece, switching to knitting flat at the "armholes" and then continuing in the round. You can't see it from this side, but the other side has a long strand of yarn running next to the armhole where i refused to have to cast on again. Does anyone have tips on how to go from flat to in round more elgantly?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-24 16:51:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why don't you just pick up stitches at the end to add the ear flaps? They can be knit flat after the fact and then you don't have to worry about casting on again. It looks like the original pattern has 80 stitches in round; you just have to put markers in the right place (use yarn there so you can take it out after) work up from the brim as the pattern states, then go back for the ear flaps which would be worked down. Edited for clarity</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-27 02:53:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which is on PSN!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-10-30 03:21:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's [subreddit californiaelection](http://reddit.com/r/californiaelection) for that already</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-10-30 08:03:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh i like this game! 1  #8226; [urban decay 24/7 glide on eye pencil in perversion](http://m.sephora.com/product/productDetail.jsp?productId=P133707). Ultra black eyeliner pencil that i use in my waterline. 2  #8226; [benefit brow zings eyebrow kit in dark] (http://m.sephora.com/product/productDetail.jsp?productId=P1274) awesome for definition and framing, comes with tinted brow wax and matching powder. 3  #8226; [benefit hoola](http://m.sephora.com/hoola-P290636). Great as a matte bronzer. 4  #8226; [benefit sugarbomb](http://m.sephora.com/sugarbomb-P252916). Natural but buildable blush for a dewy look. 5  #8226; [tarte lights camera lashes mascara]( http://m.sephora.com/lights-camera-lashes-P111902). Defining and lengthening, doesn't flake or clump. 6  #8226; [buxom lip polish in dolly](http://m.sephora.com/buxom-lips-P174213). The perfect compliment--subtle but pretty. 7  #8226; [laura mercier secret concealer](http://m.sephora.com/secret-concealer-P109935). Amazing and creamy for undereye areas. 8  #8226; [urban decay de-slick mattifying powder](http://m.sephora.com/de-slick-mattifying-powder-P210592) a nice powder to keep shine at bay. 9  #8226; [make up for ever HD invisible cover foundation](http://m.sephora.com/hd-invisible-cover-foundation-P217905). I found a perfect match and it looks natural and feels weightless. 10  #8226; [make up for ever HD microperfecting primer](http://m.sephora.com/hd-microperfecting-primer-P217906). The blue one to even out my yellow undertones. Thats 10! Bah i dont have room for eyeshadow. Ah well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-10-30 08:23:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is it [this one](http://m.youtube.com/#/watch?v=BwZDnt_QSOA amp;desktop_uri=%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DBwZDnt_QSOA)? It's all i could get on a google search.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-10-30 15:33:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>You may have issues renting a car since you are under 25 and not yet 21. Some require that you are at least 21 and will charge a fee if you're not yet 25. Just do your research.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-10-30 15:42:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Benefit brow zings in dark!](http://m.sephora.com/product/productDetail.jsp?productId=P1274) it's a tinted wax and powder kit. Really black brows can look harsh, i'm asian too, and this kit is perfect.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-10-31 07:32:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>From [this link](http://unionsquareicerink.com/plan-your-visit/) it looks like the skating rink at union square will be open EDITED to add that [The Lion King](http://events.sfgate.com/san_francisco_ca/events/show/250369565-the-lion-king) will be at the Orpheum Theater</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-10 21:07:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aww you're adorable! Like a doctored josh hutcherson</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-10 21:12:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>The [relevant commercial](http://m.youtube.com/#/watch?v=aiCq1ZMOa-w amp;desktop_uri=%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DaiCq1ZMOa-w)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-12 07:03:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I LOVE your succulent inspiration. However, IMHO (emphasis on opinion), i prefer a monochromatic scheme for the dresses, just not with whichever color green your bridal party wants. What i DO think would look really good is if you chose the color you like from your succulents color scheme, [for example, pistachio](http://www.davidsbridal.com/Browse_Bridal-Party-Bridesmaids-Shop-By-Color? amp;colorName=Pistachio) then have each bridesmaid choose a different cut of dress that suits their style. Each girl gets to be more individual, but they are all the same color. Their bouquets, their jewelry, hair accessories, and maybe their shoes would contain the OTHER colors from the succulent palette. Then your other decorations can contain all the colors of the palette again. I think this gives a more cohesive look than rainbow dresses or monochromatic (but any shade or hue) Here's [another article to check out](http://www.bellethemagazine.com/2012/01/secrets-of-successful-mismatched.html?m=1) about mismatched bridesmaids</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-19 22:03:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Those are amazing, and so practical!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-19 22:21:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seconding a lot of sentiments here. California's winter weather is great! If you do California, consider visiting both southern and northern CA, as they are very different, even though they're about 7 hours away by car (depending on how fast you drive). If you get to SoCal, Las Vegas is, i think, 4 more hours by car and will be pleasant (weather-wise). I'm from NorCal, and in general it has a lot of beautiful scenery and nature available to you, and the San Francisco Bay Area specifically has some things to see as well. Yosemite is beautiful, SF has fun things to look at and AMAZING food. If you like to eat, the Yelp website/app will be your best friend. The Monterey Bay Aquarium is 2 hours from SF by car and not to be missed. Carmel and Half Moon Bay are very pretty. Napa and Sonoma are also very accessible by car if you want to do wine tours. There are lots of hiking trails and parks near SF as well. Edited to add: oops, scratch the wine tours, they are 21+. Sorry. The area is still very pretty though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-19 22:44:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're able to get to a sephora, try the Make Up For Ever HD foundation and the green color correcting primer. Make sure you have someone match your skintone for you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-22 09:37:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Erase paste was my go to concealer until i asked someone at sephora what might be better. She recommended [laura mercier secret concealer](http://m.sephora.com/secret-concealer-P109935). It's creamier than erase paste but in the same tone and looks way more natural with no cakiness. She also applied [boscia eye depuffing](http://m.sephora.com/super-cool-de-puffing-eye-balm-P309105) stuff that felt amazing. That has been my undereye routine since. You don't want to use concealers that will dry out that area and when it comes to undereye concealer, less is more. As soon as there is too much, it will get cakey on you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-23 06:52:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nerd blackface.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-04 21:07:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awww man, cannot unsee!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-04 22:07:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or doing a flamenco!  #161;Ol #233;!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-10 06:15:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like to think her cortexiphan powers helped her pull all that off. How could she know he would be the one coming through the door and the bullet would be able to hit him? She may have subconsciously used her powers to hit that guy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-26 22:09:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>To piggy back onto the file system, a document safe for things like your passport, social security card, and birth certificate if you are now holding onto them. You don't want to have to go back to your mom for these things every time you get a new job, for example. You might also store electronic copies of these things. Also, get in the habit of keeping hard and soft copies of your health record. Diagnostic tests, immunizations, medications etc. It may not seem important now, but good records may be very helpful later on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-01-09 21:13:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only ones better are the flushable ones!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-01-10 18:35:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hugh Laurie</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-01-29 23:41:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I use this in color #3 for my under eye circles. It's not drying and feels creamy and light, instead of sticky and thick. I apply it with a tiny brush, directly to the circles and blend upward</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-01-29 23:44:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I use this sometimes too. Less is more with erase paste. I use the small benefit concealer brush and apply to my circles and blend up using a half patting, half brushing motion. Sometimes i do the kim kardashian concealer technique with erase paste too, using a bigger foundation brush Ninja edit: typos</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-01 20:08:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/popping</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-01 20:30:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exhibit A</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-15 20:41:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you post to r/canada too? Edited: thought the sub was inactive, there's a lot of content</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-22 23:37:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think we should make this a thing. A treat for us too, new sexy silky things for him rather than tattered old boxers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-03-02 03:32:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did this exact same thing when i first started knitting in the round. I used a circular needle and instead of knitting on the outside of my project, i ended up knitting on the inside. This resulted in what looks like purl stitches from the outside, but was knit stitches when i made them. I think this happened when i put my work down and started up again-- i didnt realize i'd flipped my knitting inside out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-03-08 18:47:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also ask if there's a separate education leave. We have to keep up our licenses!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-03-14 20:59:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think gray and a nice green would look great and that perfect palette website others have mentioned has a few examples of that color palette. This website (http://design-seeds.com/index.php/search) is also great for searching color palettes. Gray and green are much more man-friendly than pink but can still be beautiful. If you really NEED pink you can have it be an accent color-- just touches in bouquets, napkins, shoes/jewelry. I think it's awesome that he has an opinion, so I would err on the side of working with him than outright choosing colors he dislikes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-03-15 20:06:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi i'm a nurse and I had a tonsilectomy a while back. This by no means makes me an expert, but while many of these ideas are great, i have to recommend really warching the acidity and spiciness of the liquids your wife consumes while she's healing. Acidic fruits and drinks including gatorade could irritate your wife's stomach and esophagus, and part of the reason for the hernia was probably GERD anyway, right? No coffee, no caffeinated drinks, NO SODA. Avoid tomato, avoid acidic and spicy. Dairy can make one produce more sputum which might induce coughing, so be careful with those. I would say stick to mildly flavorful broths for some time. She'll just have to bite the bullet. Even after the initial healing period, she should cut down on the acid and spicy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-03-29 19:09:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a novice cook new to dough and the concepts of gluten formation, can you please elaborate?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-04-08 08:01:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lasik eye surgery</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-04-24 02:39:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Their pizza is DELICIOUS. My favorite combo is pepperoni, sausage, and mushroom. Are they honoring the fundraiser with take out orders as well?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-04-30 18:27:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree with you, i think a better choice would have been to take on bell's vocal inflections and speech mannerisms than a full on impersonation. Maybe something similar to peter in season 5.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-05 01:10:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Harry Shum Jr is just on another level when it comes to hip hop style dancing. I really think they need to find a way to showcase Jacob's dancing strengths other than doing crazy spins every other episode.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-09 07:29:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Speaking as a nurse, i think this is really important. As one can see from just this thread, there is a lot of misinformation as to what this kind of donation entails.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-10 06:51:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll third Benziger!! The biodynamic method seems really cool, and the winery tour is amazing. I really liked hearing about their alternatives to pesticides, and the wine is very tasty. It's also family owned, and the land itself is very pretty.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-10 06:54:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just remembered, the tasting is included with the tour which i think was 20 or 30 bucks-- totally worth it. You get to taste 5 i think. Edit: they also have a self guided tour through a section of the biodynamic garden, but the paid tour is really engaging and interesting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-13 10:52:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>An apron or pajamas!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-17 08:49:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Petrichor -- (the scent of rain on dry earth)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-20 08:27:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>EXACTLY.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-28 09:44:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Moreover, those were the [earrings she wore in italy](http://imgur.com/KRbddpm) when she was flirting with the two men at the caf #233; before Don picked her up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-31 07:29:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is no point in working a position below your license seeing as you want experience in a nurse position. Not to mention many hospitals will not hire you in a position lower than your training because it is a liability. I've told my students this when they graduated and started looking: this is your first nursing job-- what are you willing to compromise? Location? Pay? Specialty? Because in my observations, as a new grad from California, you will have to give up something if you stay. What is your ultimate goal in nursing? Do you envision yourself in a hospital? Case management? Nurse manager? Teaching? You have to take these things into consideration when looking. Also, keep an open mind. I am a Bay Area grad and I was EXTREMELY lucky that my first job was acute care in a hospital doing 8 hour days. Many of my classmates were not so lucky. Some very close friends did the same thing as you, earning more certifications, since it took nine months to find a job-- and that was in a SNF. So it all comes back to what are you willing to compromise on and what are your goals? I think if you approach the question from that angle, you will have a better idea of what to do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-31 09:01:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here we go! have you considered: public health, home health, education, case management, diabetes education, school nursing, in home private care, Or SNFs? Public health alone has so many different areas to practice in-- communicable disease management, HIV management, foster care visits, mother/baby visits, homeless clinics, immunization clinics, disaster planning, special needs case management, transition planning, genetic disability management, men's health, women's health... If you don't like the hospital, don't practice there. I recently made a switch out of hospital nursing and couldn't be happier. Don't become trapped by your pre-conceived notions of what nursing is. Especially since you have your BSN, there are lots of oppprtunities for you. You don't necessarily need more skills, you just have to explore your interests and apply your skills accordingly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-31 09:52:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, it's tough here right now. One of my current coworkers used to practice at a hospital on an Indian reservation. Several classmates moved out of state (hawaii, texas, washington, colorado etc) and one even joined the military. How is your resume? Did you participate in extracurriculars or student nurse organizations? If you are interested in a certain specialty, consider joining their professional organization. Many have discounts for students and new grads. Consider volunteering for community health fairs or vaccination clinics.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-31 18:16:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Since you said you are leaning more towards patient education, i would check your hospital's home visiting office and see if there are any patient education positions. Alternatively you can check with the outpatient clinics; some hospitals offer free classes theough these clinics to assist patients with outpatient condition management. Also it wouldnt hurt to get an MSN in nursing education. The curriculum at the school i graduated from was slanted slightly more towards nurse education, but only by two or three classes. As for your PHN certificate, check with your state if you can still get a certificate. Also check with your okd school; if your BSN program had a public health component, you have probably already completed all the requirements for certification.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-31 19:01:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>As i understand, you have to teach below your degree. So if you want to teach BSN students, you must have a Masters. If you want to teach MSN you must have a PhD/DNP</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-01 08:56:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>They can't technically strike until their contracts are up, which is at midnight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-01 08:56:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anyone going from concord to oakland city center?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-16 04:19:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did this last month. Not to to say your or my family is clueless or anything, but you should be REALLY explicit about what info you want back. If you want a number, use a little number sign (#) next to the line to clue people in. If it's important to know the number of kids, then include a line and # for that too. I went as far as to write the family name with the number of expected guests if I knew it because ultimately this is a tool for YOU to use and it needs to be legible to be useful. I even added text about including an email address on it which (surprise) only a third of my guests wrote in. Trust me on this. Don't make them guess what info you want.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-20 03:22:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>brussels sprout chips!!! AMAZING. toast the individual leaves in an oven with olive oil, serve with lemon juice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-21 02:59:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>At the work potluck this past week, i brought something really simple, but absolutely delicious and so monumentally successful, i've been asked to bring it for every potluck: Berry fruit salad with "dressing" All kinds of berries: blueberries, raspberries, blackberries (i don't use strawberries anymore because the big chain doesnt sell yummy ones) plus Grapes, peaches, pineapple. I cut them up into bite side pieces, and mix to distribute (be gentle with the raspberries!) But HERE is what makes this amazing: the dressing made of : Cream cheese (whipped-- i used the larger tub) Honey Vanilla greek yogurt (i used a single serve of chobani) Start with the cream cheese and beat it so it's smooth. Add in the yogurt and beat again until smooth. Then add honey to taste. Alternatively you can sub the yogurt and honey for marshmallow fluff. And that's it. It's amazing and easy, and is a real crowd pleaser. Tastes like fruit with cheesecake! Best thing to do is keep them separate and let people self serve so those who don't wish to mess up their diet don't have to eat it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-21 21:36:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>The short answer is that the excess blood sugar actually danages your body's blood vessels, which leads to athersclerosis (hardening of veins) and consequences of this are restricted blood flow which, then leads to heart disease, numbness in the feet and hands, eye disease (which can result in blindness) and poor healing (your veins carry the blood which contains nutrients and building blocks to repair tissues).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-08-01 08:15:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some things to think about: How many people does each place hold? How does this compare to how many you are planning have? Does the area seem nice for photos? What is the parking situation like at each place? Do they want insurance for alcohol? How late can you be there? Do they allow loud music? Is there a dancefloor? Does the site have "preferred vendors" or can you use whomever you want? Is there a kitchen? How are the bathrooms? How is the dancefloor? Will they take care of garbage? Do they have a sound system?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-08-11 22:12:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Every picture of Heath Ledger is a picture of a young Heath Ledger :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-09 02:46:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>But there also aren't commercials, so the time that could be used on commercials is instead used on an awesome opening theme. I don't mind.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-15 12:18:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>So a new nurse but no longer a student right? I would say let them shadow you a day or two so they can get a feel for the unit. Have resources ready, like phone numbers of the various depatments. Check and see how comfortable they are with certain things. Ask them to tell you up front things they want practice on/ don't have experience with so you can supervise or assist as necessary, and push for your orientee to have those experiences. Have the unit orientation things ready, so you are in control and have a plan. Offer unit /hospital specific protocols (ones that are different from what is accepted as general practice). After the first couple days, shadow them a day or two make sure theyre okay, or start them out with a partial assignment and work up to a full load over a week or two, then let them go, but act as a resource nurse for yor orientee. They have their license but will need practice acting by themself. I've had a several preceptees and orientees. You can PM me if you want more ideas.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-02 08:20:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>yes!! vanilla ice cream with some bailey's poured over top is really tasty</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-20 04:40:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love to see Ghostwriter again</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-22 09:43:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Had my tonsils out 4 years ago. Brace yourself because even though the procedure was absolutely worth it, the recovery SUCKS. Some tips to get you through to the other side: Make sure you know what pain meds work for you. ex: i was prescribed tylenol with codeine, but opiates make me terribly nauseated. You do not want to throw up post-tonsilectomy. All i was able to take was extra strength tylenol, but luckily that was enough. You probably dont want to take ibuprofen as it may make you bleed more. The fourth day post op for me was probably the worst. I'm not sure if thats how long it took for the anesthesia to wear off completely, but I've heard consistently that day four is the worst. Prepare yourself. Once you get past day 7 or 8 it's ok, but you have to go through day 4 first. Keep hydrated (water only, see below) and keep your throat/mouth moist. You may want to get a stock of face masks to humidify the air around your mouth. Food: NO DAIRY, it promotes saliva production and causes you to swallow and cough which hurts. AVOID ALL ACIDIC FOODS AND DRINKS. They sting/burn badly. This includes but is not limited to: tomato anything, fruits/fruit juice, gatorade, jello. Salty soups are awesome, top ramen was my best friend when i got my tonsils out. Mashed potatoes are a good bet, i'm on the fence about pudding because it's dairy and so sweet. Crackers are good if you let them turn to mush in your mouth before you swallow. Ice packs feel great on your neck/throat. Consider getting a wedge pillow. I couldnt sleep laying down. You will probably want to take a full week to recover. After that you can eat fairly normally, but still be careful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-24 08:37:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>She encrypted it before they got to Providence, there's no way it could be linked to his lanyard. Ward wouldn't go for that. He's evil, not an amnesiac. Anyway, she probably doesn't want to let on to Ward that there was a tracker in the lanyards. He doesn't actually know because Koenig covered up the tablet as Ward was walking in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Episode 19 SPOILERS] I wonder what Skye thinks about _____</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-25 02:27:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>...Ward's feelings for her. When Skye discovered Ward was Hydra, i feel like she had a freak out, but Ward's training kicked in and she said to herself, "what would Ward do?" and she went into spy mode. She probably feels sad and angry and incredulous, but ultimately betrayed and ready to give him a taste of his own medicine. She had to go with Ward because she didn't feel she had many options; she wouldn't be able to fight Ward (well, she could but she knows that wouldn't end well for her), and (in her mind) letting on what she knows would almost surely get her killed. Later on the plane, I believe she assumes that Ward has taken her solely for decrypting the hard drive, while I think viewers are meant to see that Ward is actually trying to protect her. I wonder if she knows that Ward actually has feelings for her; after all, the Ward she knows isn't exactly a touchy-feely, hand-holding type of guy, and knowing what she knows now, she probably thinks he's buttering her up as part of the spy game. I think this could make for some interesting confrontations down the line and I can't wait to see how it plays out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-25 07:25:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I totally agree and I think you're right, Ward is every bit as lethal as he is talked about being. He really ISN'T a good man. I actually think this makes it easier for Skye to act the way she is: Ward is brutal and ruthless, so it enables her to be ruthless too. The thing is, Ward doesn't know it's an act.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-25 07:41:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope she doesn't. So many S.H.I.E.L.D agents have died to protect her, I think she'd feel bad if she did. Not that she'd approve of anything he's done, but it must be that much more painful for her. And it's her S.O.!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-25 14:48:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>We may not know for sure he told Lorelei, but he DID tell Garrett.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-25 15:52:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why do they have to be exclusive? The influence Garrett has over Ward in his situation with Skye does seem a lot like his past behavior with his real family, which seems to have actually set a precedent. This presents Ward with an opportunity to right his past wrongs and get over the bad feelings he had of that past situation. The only thing I don't like about this is it sets Ward up for redemption, and he's just so good as a bad guy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-30 10:16:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>She was trying for HER sake though, to feel better about herself after her conversation with Francine. Betty's current concept of womanliness includes motherhood, and Francine is now challenging this concept when she tells Betty about her office work. I think Betty was determined to prove her worth as a woman out of a sense of self preservation, not out of any genuine desire to connect with her son.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-03 19:51:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is your honeymoon booked? Or at least, someplace to stay immediately post reception? You will probably not want to drive around that evening. Also, you may want someplace near your venue to get ready beforehand, and have your bridesmaids/bridal party all stay with you the night before so you know where everyone is the day of. What about guest accomodations? Is that what "2 hotel blocks reserved" is? Shoes?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-06 11:06:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Freddie had a seizure because he was drunk</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-12 08:25:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wonder if part of the resulting effects of the procedure (psychosis etc) are related to the alien origin of the serum. Maybe it's possible that because Coulson knew about the alien origin of GH-325 (he was the director of that program, after all) has been protective. I feel like any test subjects of the GH-325 might not necessarily be privy to the fact that the serum is alien. Along these lines, perhaps Skye is also of alien origin and thus it wouldn't affect her. I don't believe Garrett knows about the alien origin of the GH-325</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-15 16:30:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>What about Coulson standing in front of the wall with his "mysterious drawings" Either way, it should wait until most people have seen the finale. Some people have mentioned it hasn't aired in Europe yet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-17 20:10:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just make sure they are recognized and have all the necessary accreditations in order. Your instructors should be required to have PhD degrees. Out of curiosity, by acute care NP, do you mean a clinical nurse specialist in a hospital setting?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-17 20:14:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nursing school can be rough. You'll probably be glad it happened this way in the end.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-20 21:31:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you planning to post these in r/wedding or r/weddingplanning? I'm sure the wedditors would appreciate this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-22 07:08:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also, faxes (even electronic faxes) still require a phone line, which can't get "hacked" or intercepted (at least until it prints out on the other end) which makes them good for documents that need to remain confidential</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-23 18:23:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nurses are not doctors. We have complementary but different skills from doctors. A good doctor is no replacement for a good nurse. Doctors are trained to diagnose illnesses and nurses are trained to diagnose people. That said, it's very common for even doctors not to really understand what nurses are capable of, especially ones that have never worked in an American hospital. I think your grandma's comment is somewhat generational but also cultural. My family is from the philippines and all the nurses in the family are very well respected as intelligent autonomous practitioners. I also live in California where nurses make a LOT of money starting as compared to other starting positions-- partially because the union is fairly strong but also because nurses are expected to take on a lot of responsibility in the hospital. In the US we are taught that we have the authority to advocate for our patients and we can participate in making decisions about our patients care. It may not be that way in other places.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-23 21:34:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-23 21:35:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is that supposed to mean?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-23 22:29:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not about inferiority, it's about priorities, and whole body care. Why is managing a patient's needs inferior to figuring out whats wrong with them? I see them as attacking a problem from two different angles not that one is somehow better or more effective than the other. It's a partnership-- not like batman and robin, but like the x-men. But anyway, i think we are arguing the same thing. What is it about what I said that made you think I believe doctors are superior to nurses? In reality that is the furthest from the truth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-24 01:22:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can understand why there is a misunderstanding, but i was actually being very literal with my meaning of "doctors diagnose illness and nurses diagnose people". As you know, "nursing diagnoses" don't decsribe the disease process as much as they describe the effects of a condition on a patient.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-24 01:30:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree, there was probably a much better way of making that point; sorry to trouble you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-27 09:18:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>The clothing designs especially remind of Prince. I mean, check this out: http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/File:Prince_PurpleRain_single.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-30 10:59:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you also have the latex allergy?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-01 16:36:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just found these using google, but hardware and home stores should have options: http://m.homedepot.com/p/15-1-2-in-Medium-Galvanized-Eyelet-Lantern-DS-20954-B/204355905/ http://m.homedepot.com/p/Home-Decorators-Collection-22-in-H-Adeline-Black-Lantern-1201220210/203721536/ http://www.ikea.com/us/en/catalog/categories/departments/decoration/20491/ http://www.amazon.com/gp/aw/d/B00D9E3EDE/ref=mp_s_a_1_28?qid=1401633261 amp;sr=8-28 amp;pi=AC_SX110_SY165_QL70 It just depends what you're willing to pay to get them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-18 04:48:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone else mentioned "The Care and Keeping of You". When I was a bookseller i recommended that book all the time. Another nice thing for travel and home is a package of baby wipes or flushable wipes for keeping messes at bay. Something else i havent seen mentioned here yet is a handheld spray that attaches to the toilet or a bidet seat to help keep fresh and clean. Something like this: http://m.homedepot.com/s/Bidet?searchtype=text</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-20 07:26:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>RN checking in. FWIW, one of the things that is being addressed now is the discovery that the efficacy of the (current) acellular Tdap vaccine (which is different from DTap) wanes after 3-5 years. As you can imagine, this, in addition to higher numbers of personal belief exemptions (PBEs) has contributed in the resurgence of pertussis' incidence. Part of the issue in my mind, is when the Tdap vax went from the whole cell version to the acellular formulation (which is what has been administered since 1997), they didn't know that this vaccine wouldn't confer the same level of immunity. The recommendation for the whole cell vax was to get 1 lifetime vaccination, and i think part of the reason for this was because of the side effects. The acellular vax doesn't have the same really nasty side effects, but apparently needs to be given more often. Additionally, the new recommendation is that pregnant women receive a Tdap booster in the third trimester of EACH pregnancy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-20 07:35:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you are absolutely correct that the schedule for the acellular vax needs to be re-examined, but i do think this combined with the higher numbers of PBEs is more detrimental than any one thing by itself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-20 23:25:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Again, I definitely think there is a link between the acellular vaccine and increased incidence. But to add to that calamity, in my county there actually has been a higher percentage of PBEs in 2014 as compared to 2000 when looking at the kindergarten blue cards: http://www.acphd.org/media/350431/local%20trends%20preventable%20diseases.pdf</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-23 06:16:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you wanted to get them a physical item, i would say to choose something off the registry. Maybe you can find the same item at a local department store. If you want to give them an experience, for example movie/dinner/museum gift cards, i think it would be okay to go off registry. Otherwise, there are lots of cute inexpensive gift ideas on the internet. Here are some examples: http://www.moneycrashers.com/unique-wedding-gift-ideas-cheap-budget/ http://www.buzzfeed.com/melissaharrison/nexpensive-wedding-gift-ideas?s=mobile http://www.brokegirlsguide.com/everywhere/article/diy-and-budget-friendly-wedding-gifts-youd-actually-want-to-get http://www.rd.com/slideshows/homemade-wedding-gifts/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-27 16:19:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Obligatory: http://i.imgur.com/HiQT9nt.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-02 04:09:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got really tired of acute care as well. I became a public health nurse. Chances are if she has a BSN from CA, she completed the requirments for a public health certificate. Has she considered teaching or alternative practice areas? Home health, case management, public health nursing? How about going back for another degree? Clinical nurse specialists have a different scope of practice. What about getting into health care admin, management, nursing informatics? The nice thing about having a BSN is there are a lot of opportunities outside of patient care. Edit to expand-- in public health alone there are lots of different options,: field nursing (home visits, WIC, lead), communicable disease (TB investigation, outbreak investigation), case management. And i almost forgot about School Nursing! Also, lots of private companies and vendors need nursing experitse to function.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-02 20:37:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not necessarily. I know some have mentioned a masters in case management, but that's not strictly required; case in point, me! I didnt have case management experience, and my masters is not in case management. Many of the nurses i work with did not have prior case management experience either, though i don't doubt it would be beneficial.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-06 05:30:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really like this book: http://m.barnesandnoble.com/s/cookwise?keyword=cookwise Alton Brown actually features her every once in awhile.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-07 05:58:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>God yes, this. It's gotten so bad that when I had a traditional waltz with my groom people actually told me later they were surprised that it was so lovely! Apparently they were expecting us to do some hip hop or silly choreographed thing as our FIRST DANCE. I'm all for fun dancing but come on. Edit: grammar</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-07 23:37:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Buffy is actually a nickname for Elizabeth which according to wikipedia means "oath of God". http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Elizabeth_(given_name) So there you go.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-08 08:02:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used wedpics, which is available on both android and ios platforms. It was really neat- you invite people to upload photos, or they can take them directly from the app. There was also an option for creating an on-the-fly slide show from the desktop website, which worked amazingly well when we used a laptop on wifi that was connected to a projector. All we needed was a backdrop and boom! real time photo booth. Plus, the app has facebook integration for easy uploads, and the host automatically has access to all the photos that are taken. The only thing is no instant photo print outs, but i feel like the facebook integration made up for that. I promise i don't work for them, i just had an amazing experience</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Small dog just had surgery, seemed in pain, gave her meds. Now she's really sluggish. Is this still safe?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-09 07:34:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi, my 1-2 yo (not exactly sure, she was a rescue) F 7.5 lbs chihuahua just had a tooth extraction (as in today). She was picked up around 3 pm. She seemed in pain or sad so around 830 pm I gave her a dose of 0.2 ml of buprenorphine oral solution to her cheek pouch (opposite the site of extraction) via pre-filled syringe. It was prescribed as 0.2 ml 2-4 times x day. 2 hours later her pupils are sluggish (i used the light from my phone) and didn't get very small and her respirations are 14-18. I'm an RN, but I've never given a dog narcotics, so I'm just a little scared. Even now she's making whimper noises, and in surgery, they said that had to turn up her anesthesia because when they went to the tooth they could tell she was in pain. Is this still safe? At what point should I think I've given too much?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-09 16:28:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, I think what was really getting me is definitely the dysphoria. She is normally very affectionate and playful and only stays upset a short while, though I can see why she was so distraught. Is 0.2ml a normal dose or might they have been influenced by her initial pain reaction at the start of surgery? She was also prescribed rimadyl 6.25 mg every 12 hours and i am considering only giving that. Will that be sufficient?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-09 16:28:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you, this is reassuring.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-09 21:29:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks again this was very helpful and reassuring.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-10 07:57:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here is the order i would go with: budget  gt; essentials  gt; guest list / venue  gt; food  gt; photography  gt; everything else. The raionale is you definitely start with your budget. You do not want to go into debt because of your wedding. You don't have to be precise, but at least get used to a ball park figure. $1k? $5k? $10k? $20k? Pretty much everything else will depend on what you are willing to spend. I see a lot of people starting with the guest list. Yes, the guest list is important, but can you afford a party for X number of guests? When the budget is established, I would start thinking about what are your priorities in the wedding. Does your wedding need to occur at a certain day or season? Do you have a particular venue in mind, or do you want as much friends and family as you can have there? Do you feel your money is better spent on food or photos? Your dress or decorations? Even if money is no object, think about what kinds of things that are MUST HAVES at your wedding. Once you get your budget THEN you can start thinking about who and how many people you want to invite and what kind of venue. I think these have to be done somewhat simulataneously because it's hard to choose a venue without havig an idea of how many guests, and likewise, if you're dead set on a particular venue, it will likely limit your guest list. Priotitize the essential guests you want there. Definitely start collecting names, addresses, emails of those essential guests. Also, the availabilty of a venue could dictate your wedding date! I think budget, essentials, and then venue / guest list are the way to go if you're just starting out. Good luck! And keep us updated! Edited for clarity</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-10 08:09:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like "sappy" is subjective. What are examples of sappy music you don't want? Do you want examples of modern music that is played currently?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-10 16:16:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>What about "What a wonderful world" by louis armstrong? The Israel Kamakawiwo'ole version is really nice too. Here are some other hopefully not sappy songs: Unforgettable - nat king cole In my life - beatles Just the way you are - billy joel Actually a quick search got me to this page: http://www.wedj.com/dj-photo-video.nsf/motherson.html It's a pretty good mix i think. Good luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-16 08:43:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me and hubby BOTH vote for #1</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-17 06:49:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your dress DEMANDS an updo. Something like this could be really beautiful with an updo http://www.modcloth.com/shop/hairaccessories/Adorned-in-Dreams-Headband? Or like this http://i.imgur.com/NBS2Vmt.jpg http://i.imgur.com/NoxGUu3.jpg Or this http://i.imgur.com/2HK83w4.jpg Or this http://i.imgur.com/aThZ6zM.jpg Or this http://i.imgur.com/zZrf75W.jpg Or this http://i.imgur.com/cJddaoc.jpg Basically a bun with a pretty clip. But maybe just one clip, and a smooth bun or textured bun, not a lot of things dangling. Crystal clip in a feather motif or feathers themselves. Are you wearing a veil? And if so, what kind?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-20 08:55:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Try 9am. 1030 means a 3 hour wait still.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-28 08:31:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>On the moon, having the most epic PvP of my life! I'm totally inexperienced in FPS and PvP and I was doing SO well. Just wish i knew what my score was before it went down.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-29 00:51:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think this question could be even more specific and then you can see if differnt classes specifically have gun preferneces. It could reflect playstyle, or at the very least, maybe find underpowered weapons more accurately. For example, "When playing as ____ in PvP/strike which do you use primarily?" As a titan, when playing PvP i preferred the shotgun, but in strike I used the sniper rifle, because trying to melee the Devil Walker/Sepiks Prime didn't seem efficient.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This rocher (quenelle) technique</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-02 09:05:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-09 17:52:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>This video of Miles Fisher's cover of Talking Heads' "This Must Be the Place". He looks SO MUCH like Christian Bale in American Psycho! http://vimeo.com/m/5690855 Edit: grammar</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-14 09:50:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm with you on this. One of the "consequences" of the catch up episodes was so much great character development. I was exposed to the NA anime before the manga and was shocked at how little time was spent with the characters before the inner senshi team was complete. I really loved the Naru-Nephrite storyline, too. I hope they make reference to it. It would also be really nice to see an expanded version of Earth and Beryl's motives.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-09 05:45:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>A lot of the skills she mentions are actually more like tasks, or micro skills in nursing. Have her consider the more global implications of her skills: time management, appropriate prioritization, delegation, individualizing patient care, culturally competent and age appropriate care, HIPAA compliance, application of evidence based practice, etc etc. Focus on those kinds of skills rather than tasks. Same with the retail experience, think about customer service, high pressure / fast paced environments, observing chain of command, providing service tailored to a customer's needs. Look at the "big picture" skills. Also, if it's good, include her GPA, plus any honors or awards, professional associations--ANA? AWHONN? If not suggest she consider joining and then she can write it off on her taxes. There are often discounts for students and those newly graduated. As a final note, I know very few nurses who got jobs in their desired specialty straight out of nursing school. I don't know where you live, but if this doesnt work out for L amp;D, consider suggesting that she apply to med/surg too and then transfer once she's no longer an RN I.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-20 23:25:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Champagne-- but not spelled this way. Also sisters named Maybelline and Loreal. Also Princes, Kings, and Sirs-- as in King James.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-21 00:02:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'vr also seen twins: Heaven and Nevaeh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-22 10:54:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Check the schools' NCLEX pass rates! After that, maybe evaluate what your plans for the future are. If management, teaching, advanced practice, or community/public health are at all appealing to you, you should probably go for the BSN. Otherwise, as other have mentioned, some facilities are moving towards only employing BSNs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 17:12:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I make the sauce and pasta come together for a carbonara I make sure my (room temp) eggs and (room temp) cheese are well mixed, then I temper the egg-cheese mix with a little with hot pasta water and stir well, before adding the just-finished-cooking (hot) pasta. The pasta cooks the egg mix, no extra heat. If it's too sticky I add more pasta water to get the "creamy" consistency, but no cream added. I believe this is a more traditional method, but please someone comment if this isnt't the case.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 18:01:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you'd missed the blue it would have been "mailed" to you and the postmaster would have it listed under "lost items"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-01 02:57:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fellow titan here. I'm level 26. I'm not great at fps so take my advice for what it's worth. In pvp, destiny tracker says you've played less than 20 games, so this could be part of the problem. To get better at pvp, I feel like you really need to know the maps well, so it sounds lame, but you just gotta practice the maps over and over. It also helps to know the differences in games modes. For example, you can revive in skirmish for points which is not the case in the other modes. As for technique: let me reiterate-- i'm not great at fps, and absolute garbage with guns that don't allow me to track easily. That said, most autorifles and pulse rifles are out of the question for me. I tend to stick with hand cannons or scout rifle and my secondary is the shotgun. Actually scratch that. If it's a slow playing mode or has fewer players (skirmish for example), i use the fusion rifle. In short play to your strengths. I have a tendency to combine attacks, using the shotgun and then the punch right after when up close tends to be pretty powerful, especially as a titan, but you have to be realistic about punching, you're generally not going to win in a punching match against a higher level character since they will have more skills. Figure out what skills you like as a titan and buff those in the skill tree and with your gear. Set your skills to optimize your style of play. The best combination for you may not necessarily be the skills that are further along in the tree. Do you enjoy punching? There are a couple skills that enhance the storm fist. Put on gear that makes you punch faster. Do you find yourself using the pulse grenade a lot? Use the skill that extends the pulse and wear gear that shortens the grenade cooldown. Which brings up another point: level doesnt affect your attack or defense in pvp, so keep gear (even old gear) that has buffs to the skills you're good at and the guns you like and wear them for pvp.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-05 10:10:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love this idea! A couple extra suggestions: you must be level 30, you should have to dismantle an exotic of the type of gun you want to build, AND dismantle legendaries with the attributes you want to add in addition to dismantling a lot of guns for parts. I think this would help cut down on exploiting the system.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-06 23:32:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>The key is it's k-d SPREAD, not ratio. As long as you're killing more than you die, you'll get there. In other words, when you finish a match your k:d (ratio) must always be higher than 1. Actually, if assists count too it's even easier. It was a relief because I was ready to round up a 6 person fireteam of friends and ask them to just let me kill them over and over again in rumble.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-11 02:31:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not in partucular, but the portion of the Thorn bounty he's asking about requires you to kill guardians specifically with void damage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-14 23:10:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the line is, "Now I know why you thought it'd hurt". Edited: verified the line.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-28 19:32:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://www.lekueusa.com/Food-Steamers-cat4.html I have a steamer case that i use at work to cook quick fresh lunches. You may want to check these out. Awesome for work situations, it's covered so it contains messes, and cooks really quickly. I usually do fish and veggies, but i've also cooked chicken and sausages in them. You can get away with thicker cuts too, provided they have enough surface area. For a steak i might butterfly or just cut into two pieces. You can put a little oil or herbs in the water for extra flavor, so marinated foods would probably be okay too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-22 10:41:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>You could serve spicy baby octopi like the ones you get at korean bbq!! http://www.koreanbapsang.com/2012/08/jjukkumi-gui-spicy-grilled-baby-octopus.html And then you play Hydra, which is like Mafia or Werewolf, only with Hydra instead of Mafia, and the doctor is actually Simmons and the cop is Romanov because of her interrogation skills. Ward could be vigilante. http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mafia_%28party_game%29 You could also makes cookies with Hydra and SHIELD icing logos. You could have those pinwheel sandwiches and arrange them to look like a centipede. Alternatively, sushi topped with salmon arranged to look like a centipede. Your bar and/or food area could be labeled TAHITI. Then you decorate with island stuff. You could make a photo booth of Tahiti and then create a prop for ones head that looks like your brain is being operated on Edited to remove a suggestion you already thought of but I couldn't see because mobile.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-05 11:15:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>OMG yes. I wore dance shoes at my wedding and they were great. Specifically i got this pair of Capezio ballroom shoes: https://www.amazon.com/dp/B006LXZP2S/ref=cm_sw_r_awd_7.LQub0WCAYKN and then i added swarovski crystals: http://i.imgur.com/M25ln3G.jpg http://i.imgur.com/XYv1ii6.jpg They were fabulous, confortable, danceable, and easy to put on and take off because of the dancer's clasp. Dancing shoes generally have a larger toebox so added comfort there, plus they are generally made to be more flexible. Latin shoes tend to have leather soles whereas traditional ballroom shoes have the suede soles. Mine had suede bottoms and my feet felt great all night! I did, however wear them outside, which is generally a no-no if you're going to bring them back on the dancefloor, but i figure i can brush them later on down the road if i ever want to do real dancing in them again. You should also be able to find them in a wider selection of sizes, widths, and heel heights if that's important to you. A friend also got dancing shoes from this awesome company HeyLady: https://www.shopheylady.com/shoes.php They are comfy and very wedding-styled, and I was likely going to buy from them, but once I got it in my head I was going to customize my shoes I didn't look back. Edit: i was actually inspired by Hey Lady's styles "Straptease" and "Knotty Girl" Edited again to add: unless a company specifically states otherwise, you should probably order your street shoe size.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-05 20:21:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>It took 2 months after work and parts of weekends to do, but that's pretty hard to quantify in actual hours. Also I just realized the shoes I bought were on sale when I got them, maybe $20-30 less. It was not less expensive overall because I overbought crystals, but it was definitely worth my effort. Those photos really don't show how sparkly they really looked. I should also point out I had a convertible dress so my shoes were visible for the entire reception. It will not matter as much if no one will see your shoes. I fully support dancing shoes, I just wouldn't recommend the crystals part to someone who didn't have the time or patience. I did try the Hey Ladys and they were gorgeous, super comfy, great if you need arch support and cushioning. Definitely the Tesla of wedding shoes if you get the analogy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-21 20:39:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>The kind where the United States has already had 141 cases in the first two months of the year, whereas there were 644 for all of 2014 and less than 200 in 2013: http://www.cdc.gov/measles/cases-outbreaks.html</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-21 20:46:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>People don't always die from the measles, but that's the best case scenario, and more likely what would be the case with a healthy adult. The danger is when a young child or immune compromised person gets it and ends up with encephalitis (brain inflammation that can lead to lifetime neuromuscular impairment) or pneumonia which is dangerous in and of itself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-21 20:51:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even if you were serious (I hope you're not because anecdotally having the measles REALLY SUCKS), if you're American and in school, unless your parents exempted you from the vaccination, you've likely already been immunized.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-21 21:05:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you saying we should let people get diseases that could lead to lifetime debilitation because they won't die from it? This is an easily preventable disease and the reason there are not more deaths is because we have the means to treat and prevent it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-04 18:15:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>You must shave or wax. It's an ingown hair!! The best kind, that encapsulates itself for easy retrieval.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-24 00:09:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pilot's "Magic" always makes me think of the movie Happy Gilmore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-02 23:11:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Check with the celebrants if they even WANT games. Especially at a food place it can get unweildy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-05 22:05:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used the www.wedpics.com website and app. It allows you to take pics from the app, upload pics to the app and create a real time slideshow using the uploaded photos. It has facebook connectivity, and you can print from the app too. It was really great because everyone could add their own photos to the app so we caught the moments the photographer might have missed. Also, we could have easily turned it into a photobooth if we'd had a proper "booth" but it worked fine showing all the newest photos as they were being shot. It looks like they've also added video capabilities as well. That could be a really cool way to do a guestbook! Edit: it's also free!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-06 07:07:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I apologize if the following feels like thought vomit. The song that bookends this episode really caught my attention. The song is "Is That All There Is" by Peggy Lee: http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Is_That_All_There_Is%3F. Per the wikipedia article, the lyrics are "written from the point of view of a person who is disillusioned with events in life that are supposedly unique experiences. The singer tells of witnessing her family's house on fire when she was a little girl, seeing the circus, and falling in love for the first time. After each recital she expresses her disappointment in the experience. She suggests that we "break out the booze and have a ball  #8212; if that's all there is", instead of worrying about life. She explains that she'll never kill herself either because she knows that death will be a disappointment as well. " Here are the full lyrics: http://www.lyricsmode.com/lyrics/p/peggy_lee/is_that_all_there_is.html I guess you can draw a parallel with Don's rather extraordinary lifestyle and how's he keeps returning to old habits and takes all his expeiences for granted. He is never satisfied with how his life is and thus his actions are a string of poor decisions meant to bring immediate pleasure raher than sustain him in the long term. Someone mentioned it elsewhere in this thread, but I think Diana the waitress is representative of all the women in his life that he's cared about but can't make sense of. He is swept up in the moment but the fall out is always disappointing: "I just work here" "I just want to sit here". I think Don wants to believe there is more to life. I think Don feels bad for how things with Rachel ended, and he feels bad about how his life has gone, and maybe her death will be the wakeup call he needs to turn things around for good. Then again, Don has followed this pattern before and just gone back to his old habits. I think this sentiment is also parallel to Ken and Peggy's story arcs this episode. Peggy is trying to make up for what she feels has been lost time and Ken talks about leaving the business and writing his book. But in the end, Peggy wants to get back to business and dismisses the connection she made with Stevie on their date, and after entertaining the thought of completing his book, he signs with Dow as their head of advertising. However, I think the song is hopeful too; the last line of the chorus seems to flip it all around: if these things are all there is to life, we should just drink our cares away, IF that's all there is. I guess the song is meant to remind us that it's not so unusual that Don is up to his old tricks following his separation from Megan, but the fact that Rachel's death is weighing so heavily on him hopefully means the turnaround will stick this time. Edited to fix some formatting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-07 07:44:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's questions the statement at least. It's not outright saying "that's all there is". I admit it's flippant about it but it doesnt totally dismiss it. Maybe it's just me wanting Don to have his epiphany and follow through.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-27 17:37:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is a really great documentary streaming on Netflix right now called Fed Up: http://dvd.netflix.com/Movie/Fed-Up/70299287 It goes more in depth about why sugar is so toxic, the corporations that control how sugar is marketed, and how hard it really is to avoid sugar even when trying to eat healthy. Such a great insightful movie.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-29 02:36:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Peaches, Ginger-lemon, and Fizzy cola!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[SPOILERS S02E20] Raina's manipulations and visions</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-07 06:39:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Raina's vision wasn't of SHIELD jets raining down fire. She saw Jiaying betraying her people by killing Gonzales and purposefully starting a war with SHIELD. While I agree that Raina is manipulative and deceitful, I thought she was finally seeing her gift (and everything that comes with it) as something amazing and purposeful, and I think her desire to keep the Inhumans safe was genuine in spite of her desire to lead them. She knew she couldn't tell Jiaying, Cal, or Skye. Her only recourse was to try and get Gordon on her side. So she was forced to lie about her vision to try and manipulate the situation before it played out the way she'd seen in her vision. Without having seen the promo, my prediction is that Raina will try to convince Skye that Jiaying killed Gonzales unprovoked, and possibly help it come to light that Jiaying was prepared to kill Coulson if he'd come to Afterlife instead of Gonzales. This will lead Skye to abandon the Inhumans for SHIELD. Conveniently, this still provides the catalyst for Raina taking leadership over the Inhumans. Extra twist theory: Is it possible Raina's known this would happen since last episode when she was questioning Jiaying's leadership?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-07 18:57:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree, I don't think it will be so easy. Skye had been searching for her parents, but she actually found pretty decent replacements in May and Coulson. Skye told Jiaying that Coulson was an especially good man to her, a father figure if you will, with SHIELD completing her make-shift family. However, Skye seemed really invested in the fact that her family was back together, and she wasn't sure SHIELD was really her home thus creating the conflict. I think after Hyde reveals himself again, and Skye learns the real circumstances around Gonzales death she'll be more likely to come back to SHIELD. If we want to get a little meta about it, it was interesting how the episode reinforced the connections Skye has with these people, how everyone said Coulson was too close, and even May seemed a bit hurt that Skye's allegiance seems to have shifted, "I hope your mom is everything you hoped" or whatever suggesting she has maternal feelings towards Skye. I think thats the reason I see that as the main conflict in the next episode.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-07 19:12:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes I think it's pretty futile for her to have tried to intervene, but there's no way for Raina to know that. My real point is that she wasn't trying to meet with SHIELD for the sole purpose of wanting to act as a leader; I think she wanted to avoid Jiaying getting into the mix at all since her vision was of Jiaying killing Gonzales and declaring war on SHIELD. I think Raina now sees Afterlife as her home and would see Jiaying's actions as a bad strategy for protecting the Inhumans.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[SPOILERS for AoU and AC] Pleasantly surprised with continuity regarding Stark inventions and best intentions</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-08 09:06:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really appreciate how between Agent Carter and Age of Ultron, a precedent is established regarding Starks and their inventions. In Agent Carter, we find that many of Howard's most dangerous inventions came about from ideas that were originally meant to help. One of the more notable inventions was Midnight Oil. Howard originally formulated it so soldiers could stay up and keep fighting, but it instead product had the unintended and deadly effect of causing recipients to rage and kill those around them. Likewise in AoU when Tony Stark is developing Ultron, his purpose was to program AI that could serve as world protector. As we know from the movie, this isnt how things go; Ultron doesn't abide by the Three Laws or else it has a warped understanding of how to protect humans. While you can't really blame Tony for wanting to create something like this so he doesn't have to fight anymore, this is a pretty severe oversight on Tony's part. Especially given that this is not Ultron's origin in the comics, I thought this was a really clever way to tie in the two series, provide some forshadowing, and set up a plausible backstory.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-08 16:39:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha thanks. I mean, Asimov made up the rules, but they are pretty sound, and the laws have permeated our thinking about robots, though maybe Asimov doesn't exist in the MCU. Have you seen the Disney Big Hero 6 movie? Baymax followed thise rules too. RoboCop was also programmed with a similar set of rules.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-08 16:46:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think of them more like twins! One good and one evil.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-13 21:06:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe rethink the garlic? Garlic has a way of reminding you that garlic was a part of the meal. Unless you're both aware of how it affects the both of you and are into it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-13 21:25:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, real talk: personally it makes me gassy. It's hard to feel sexy when one is gassy. If it's that small an amount anyway, maybe salt and pepper will be sufficient?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-13 21:28:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very true! But I see that line of thinking by Ultron as an oversight by Stark in not instilling that kind of value on human life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-02 20:25:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I tried to check the website but it's down (probably due to RHoD). Is there a mix of savory and sweet snacks? Is there an option to choose just savory or just sweet? If not is that a consideration for the future?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-13 01:57:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>My $0.02: Shailene is a bit trashy. Reminds me of the actress and this infomercial fitness trainer, and when I see that name i want to pronounce it "shuh-LEEN". Shalyn reads to me with a short -a- like "SHALL-in" (shallot or Jimmy Fallon) or "shall-IN". I think the "ae" conveys the long A sound that you're looking for without using Ys</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-02 06:36:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>What about a perk called "Big Damn Heroes" where close proximity to another teammate increases damage for a short time?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-02 11:54:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is really cool!! Your design got me all psyched for other possibilities. I found this for additional reference: http://www.imfdb.org/wiki/Firefly Vera looks to be a shotgun, and the Lassiter could be a sidearm!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-19 02:21:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>V is for Vera</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-20 07:32:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>If they don't reveal Elliot's inspiration for the plan, this will be my head canon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-03 13:50:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi, nurse here-- I didn't really see anything regarding your pregnancy and birth concerns posted, so I hope you see this. In my line of work, I have encountered many children who were born HIV positive, but who were eventually cleared of the virus after 4 months of age. With consistent medication administration and consistent pre-natal care, mom's viral load during prenancy and birth can be undetectable. Once born the child will have medications as well. The hospital would check for viral loads at 2 weeks, 1 month, and then 4 months. Barring other modes of infection, if the viral load of the child is undetectable twice by the end of that four months, the child is declared completely HIV negative and they wouldn't even recommend continued follow up with the infectious diesease specialist. In short, it is completely within your power to have a child that does not grow up HIV+. Also, FWIW, I'm sorry you've had to grow up so quick-- keeping up with medications and going to appointments can be exhausting, physically and mentally. The fact that you are concerned and committed to living with HIV is admirable and is really a testament to your resiliency and maturity. Just as I have seen babies who were cleared, I do encounter those who are in denial and are inconsistent with treatment, so I believe you are ahead of the game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-14 03:08:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Piggybacking on this great comment to emphasize the need to expand on kitchen hygeine and food safety! Some examples: - don't store raw and cooked on the same plate - don't touch raw food and then touch cooked food with the same utensil - temperatures/appearance for doneness of meats and eggs - don't store hot leftovers immediately on the fridge-- it should come to room temp first - max length of time to hang on to leftovers (maybe include within each recipe?) - how to tell if something is spoiled - how to care for a cutting board with awareness of cross contamination - how to clean prep surfaces before and after cooking - how to store different types of groceries - don't put oils down the sink - don't throw a hot dish/pan immediately in cold water - what to use to clean gunk off pans</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-16 09:56:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>- margherita pizza - grilled cheese sandwiches - macaroni and cheese - roasted cauliflower - eggplant parmesean - chicken katsu - veggie lasagna - veggie skewers (zucchini, mushroom, okra, tomato?) - tempura veggies - fried tofu (tofu fries are awesome) - dim sum style dumplings/ potstickers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-16 10:31:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is way better timing for that kind of gesture to one's parents!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-16 10:40:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're not being bridezilla. If ever there were a time to assert your authority it's now. At some point you have to act as if you are one of the heads of your new family-- because you are. Don't relinquish that control when it's something you feel strongly about because it will set the tone for your marriage and create unreal and unmanageable expectations down the line.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-20 08:31:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think this is particularly weird. I paid for my dress too. However like the others have pointed out, this incident highlights the need to a conversation about money once you are married. If his expectation is that you were going to take care of it because it "had nothing to do with him" and this was wasn't your expectation, you can be sure this will just be the first of many discussions you will have with money. Just as a heads up, as wedding gifts you may receive checks made out to "Mr. and Mrs. So-and-so". Because of the "and" in there in you will only be able to deposit the check to a joint account. At least, this is what we encountered when we took our checks to the bank. Also, I think it's fine if you split the household expenses and have separate bank accounts, as long as you two are on the same page regarding your money and you still understand you must act as single functional unit once you are married.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-03 11:44:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>It does come with a refill! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-05 00:07:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Korean standard for customer service is actually to follow you around the store in case you need anything. It's uncomfortable to us, but that may be how they were trained to help in that store.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-11 12:21:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Apple, brie, and cooked bacon, maybe add caramelized onion. Marshmallow, graham pieces, and chocolate. Pulled pork, sweet potato fries, and pickled onions. Sloppy joe fillings Diced skillet potatoes, cheese, breakfast sausage. Seasoned cooked ground beef and potatoes. You could also experiement with different types of dough to make pies/empanadas.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-02 04:15:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>TABITHA NOOOOOOO</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-20 21:21:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi Daniel!! I'm a big fan from your Gen X-Cops days! Great to see you and Steven Fung working together again! My question: With your extensive work in Asian markets, as an Asian-Am actor what is your perception of the differences (if any) in appealing to an American market? Do you find being American has helped? Thanks!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-21 23:09:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dessert sandwiches!! Nutella, chocolate, peanut butter, honey, fruit preserves, marshmallow, sliced fruit (apple, banana, strawberries, pear), fruit compote, whipped cream! Put out slices of challah or kings hawaiian.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-29 23:10:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Side question to Germans of reddit: is the word 'stormtrooper' used in German translations of the movies? More general follow up: what do you think of the movies' usage of 'stormtrooper'-- does the usage diminish or belittle its historical meaning/significance or does it simply serve to elucidate the brutality of the empire?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-01 09:38:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>We did this for our wedding! Each table got one cake which was one of two different flavors of our favorite cakes from our favorite bakery. They were plainly decorated but also uniformly decorated. We actually had something like 25 cakes, one at each table, and it served double duty as our centerpieces. So we saved money on cake to cover our amount of guests, but also saved on having to do centerpieces! It was a big hit!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-08 02:04:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe it hasn't been mentioned yet seeing as it's also a Broadway show but Hedwig would be incredulous if she weren't included in this list. Hedwig and the Angry Inch trailer: http://youtu.be/4p9mPhGo1j0</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-08 09:35:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>~ folks roamed the earth, like big rolling kegs, they had two sets of arms, they had two sets of legs, they had two faces peering out of one giant head so they could watch all around them as they talked while they read, and they never knew nothing of love-- it was before the Origin of Love So good... time to put the soundtrack on a loop again!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-09 09:14:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is he into creamy or pureed textures? Maybe start with cream of mushroom, cream of broccoli (really finely chopped broccoli!), or cream of carrot soups so for a smooth, fatty, richness mixed with veg. Or what about split pea, or bean soups? Or even just plain pureed veggie soups? Potato leek, roasted pepper, butternut squash? Would he enjoy french onion with a giant crouton and cheese on top? Does he like hummus with chips and or pita? Would he enjoy baked or fried "chips" of other root vegetables?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-09 09:25:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have you considered swapping his pasta for a more nutritious version? I've seen corn pasta and quinoa pasta but my favorite is brown rice pasta. I think it has the closest texture to regular white pasta. Maybe try pasta with a mushroom sauce? You can saute onions and mushrooms (cut as small as they need to be) in some butter, reserve the veg then make a butter roux with whats in the pan after removing the mushrooms and onions, add a little white wine/stock, stir until it thickens and alcohol (if added) is cooked off, add back in the mushrooms/onion, maybe add a little cream, then toss the noodles back in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-12 20:04:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you in the US? http://www.thingsremembered.com/category/top-gifts-him/4824.uts?int=TopGiftsHim Sometimes you see this store in malls too. It specializes in engravable keepsakes and they have all kinds of things from knives to cufflinks to glass bottles, to watches. My hubby had pocketwatches engraved for our groomsmen. Not sure about turn around times, but I'm betting you can get a rush job.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-26 04:34:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Colorful flood lighting! Your venue is seriously amazing, flood lighting in different colors to match the mood of your wedding and reception is really all you need.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 05:06:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>In an interview on Talking Dead after this episode, Cudlitz says that Abraham is not in love with Rosita, but he has a deep love for Rosita. I feel like he was struggling to try and let Rosita down gently, but Abraham doesn't seem to do anything gently.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-10 22:45:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it's a really intriguing theory, i can't imagine why you'd get downvoted because it totally fits with the idea of cooperation and playing as a fireteam. Adding to the theory: the icon for the 3oC is shaped like a card. Will attempt to test this with a fireteam when i get home.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-14 05:26:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I found this using google: http://www.ensotea.com/ Now all you need is hot milk. You could even do the milk in the microwave. Otherwise, get matcha tea powder (not a flavored one/tea mix) at a tea shop (Teavana, David's Tea etc) and prepare it like it says. Generally, 1 teaspoon of matcha makes 8oz, so if your cup is larger, you will obviously need to use more. If you do get a matcha tea mix, you may need to use as much as a tablespoon. Just follow the directions. The standard Starbucks recipe uses a simple syrup, but you can use sugar at home. If you want something that will dissolve more easily, just use honey. What I have at work to make matcha tea lattes is matcha powder, honey, milk, a hot water kettle, and a small electric whisk. A google search for "small electric whisk" should find some really affordable options and she can use this to whisk the tea AND the milk if sh wants a little froth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-14 06:25:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>+2 more if you count karen and david</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-15 04:04:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll allow it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-16 16:14:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm going to guess you're white, because if you weren't you'd realize why it's a big deal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-16 16:42:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well now we both know that's not true. But saying "we're all the same" when the reality is that there is horrible racism and a lack of equally represented culturally sensitive role models is belittling the problem. Also, yes the show isn't about race, but this thread and the article are, and that's why we're talking about it here. Edit to add: I don't know who downvoted you, but i upvoted you because we need this kind of discussion to understand why there are issues. Anyway, the fact that you have no problem relating is great. The problem happens when you assume that tolerance is the lived experience of every other person, because it's not. Saying we should look beyond race because everyone is equal is effectively shushing the people who KNOW racism exists and is a problem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-16 18:28:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you're missing my point. Yes, we are all equal, obviously. And thankfully, that's how people are portrayed on the show. But coversely, you can't treat people equally until you acknowledge that they aren't treated equally. So you said, "people don't reserve the right to not be offended by the opinions of others." And that's fine, but are you then saying that my opinion is also invalid? I thought that's what this thread is about. Discussing race. I'm not offended by his comments, just pointing out that racism exists and it exists in hollywood and Chloe Bennet has experienced it, and that's why she's pointing it out. If you deny a problem, you can't address it. It not about controlling people, it's about informing and providing perspective.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-19 17:10:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you still taking suggestions? This is dead easy and tastes amazing. http://www.seriouseats.com/recipes/2009/08/jacques-pepin-crusty-chicken-with-mushrooms-white-wine-sauce-recipe.html</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-20 18:25:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I collect ticket stubs for transit and attractions, as well the maps of museums i've visited. I also take a business card from restaurants that we've eaten at and take a photo of the restaurant's front.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-26 01:18:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not a comics reader yet, so that seems oddly specific to me; is there some precedent for the use of "Underoos" as a nickname?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-05 04:31:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Another filipino checking in. I think your mom is too, judging from her text. I can definitely speak a bit to the filipino immigrant experience versus the first gen mindset. Pease bear in mind, this is my opinion from just reading your post and just things coming off the top of my head. Our fellow redditors definitely nailed down what it means to be independent in america. But, i think they missed your mom's question-- WHY does independence = adulthood in america. My perception of "adulthood" in the perspective of someone from the PI is about being able to provide and basically, being able to have a family-- not in the abilty to make babies, but in the ability to ensure survival for your offspring. This translates to money, and saving, and in their perspective, schooling. So spending that money = not saving which takes away your money and ability to provide. Not making money or otherwise doing things that do not get you more money mean you are inhubiting your own success. In America, adulthood is about the freedom to make choices and forging out to see how one can make their mark. Consider the historical inception of the United States and the "American Dream" and the kind of values that re-inforces-- for example, independence, being able to do what you want and winning (or failing), breaking away from the "norm". Similarly, you could make the argument that Americans value youth and exploration over wisdom and tradition which is why getting out into the world and making mistakes while young is perceived as desireable compared to doing the same-old-thing. Maybe you've heard American parents say that "kids should be allowed to make choices and fail". The "eastern" counterpart might be "why mess around with the bullshit? do what we know works". Don't forget that if they made it out here, they very likely made a lot of sacrifices to get here. So why take the risk when they (in their mind) know how to you can succeed. Yikes, that was a lot longer than I intended. Hopefully this provides some perspective. FWIW, it sounds like your mom is trying to understand your thinking. Maybe she can be persuaded that the ideal American life is different from in the Philippines, and thatdifference is the whole reason she came here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-12 21:36:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also orange juice and peanut butter. There's a reason we can't keep them in the fridge on the renal unit. Source: passed the nclex in 75 questions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-26 08:42:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've completed as much of the game as has been released so far. I think my very best tip is to take it slow and be strategic when possible. But when that's not possible these are my best general strategies: - always look for opportunities to make more than 3 pop. - When you have special gems (stripes, burst, prisms, painters) don't use them right away, try to save them. - always try to combine the special gems, especially gems of different abilities. Two prisms clears the board, a stripe or burst and a painter will turn all the gems the same color as the painter into a stripe or burst. - when you have a special power, check to make sure there aren't any 4 pops and then use the special power right away.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-26 19:10:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Depending on your preference, run Gift of Light for a chance at an orb with melee kills, or Unbreakable for continuous melee recharge, and max your strength bonuses.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-29 05:27:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Charli Raye Charli Zelda Charli Belle Charli Faye Charli Samus Charli Peach Charli Ariel Charli Jasmine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-14 22:19:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Case management! I do this and for better or worse I work behind a computer and on the phone with specialty care clinics and families to support access to treatments they might not be able to otherwise because of insurance limitations. I have other friends who do case management in the inpatient setting which involves discharge planning and some utilization review. Also, there are case management opportunities in home health, hospice, outpatient care etc. I know you already mentioned public health but there are very diverse roles in public health besides field nursing. Nurses are used in the immunization unit, communicable disease unit, TB investigation, and foster care. These positions could be in an office but will also require some patient contact. There are also specialized programs within public health which will have unique oppotunities for program development with specific demographic and geographic communities as well as diagnosis based programs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-16 06:07:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Evan Rose Evan Mary Those are about as girly as names get!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-10 03:17:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Another no for synestheisa. For those that know the reference it is too clinical sounding and is also a really long name. My vote is for Vannity Cosmetics. Not such an off spelling that you dont know how to say it, still very much your name.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-10 03:37:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds very much like Cantina, which I can imagine some people mistaking it for. As others have pointed out, canty can also be mistaken for a not-so-nice english word. If you are looking for music names here are some: Cadence Harmony Melodie Aria Lyric Coda</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-17 03:06:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg YES. although i thought he was more like a Reinhardt with a Bastion bird</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-17 04:31:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually LOLed when Griff mentions the general store is "Helpington's"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-18 18:03:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have no idea on either points, i just thought it sounded funny.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-18 18:21:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>For anyone (like me) that didn't get the reference and doesn't want to look it up: the "con system" in the Everquest videogame allows you to see the relative level/power of a particular foe or encounter compared to the player's own. This allows the player to determine if the encounter is worth their time. Basic example: seeing a "gray" enemy means they're very low level which in the game would essentially yield 0 experience points and is therefore not worth the player's time; a "green" enemy is one that should be "just right" and might be tough but the player should be able to defeat them. alternatively, a "red" enemy would indicate that the enemy's level is so far above the player's that engaging combat would mean certain death. Griffin mentions that con-ing Roswell shows "red with skulls" (or something) indicating that Roswell is 1- a VERY powerful being and thus 2- not someone our heroes are going to engage combat with. Roswell would handily handle our boys just like those ruffians.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-21 03:18:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>EXCEPT BEING WIDOW AND REALIZING YOU HAVE TO PUSH THE DAMN THING YOURSELF.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-21 09:51:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>To piggyback, here is an article on how to knead a very wet pizza dough: http://slice.seriouseats.com/archives/2011/03/pizza-protips-how-to-work-with-very-wet-dough.html</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-23 10:57:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is exactly what i was thinking! Roswell's bird immediately reminded me of Bastion, but Roswell's physical description was much closer to Reinhardt. I like to think a Reinhardt type is also more likely to look ultra imposing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-01 04:15:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I attempted to transcribe what Griffin says about Tres Horny Boys' objectives for this arc: 1. Recover the temporal chalice and get it out of town. 2. Figure out what caused the bubble to pop up around town--discover the mystery of the bubble. 3. Figure out what is destroying the town and figure out how to stop it. Griffin says the most important objective is the third objective but figuring out the bubble and what is destroying the town will help with getting the chalice. I think it's really interesting that Griffin made getting the chalice OUT OF TOWN a priority, as though just getting their hands on it is not enough. Maybe the chalice would possibly disappear like the diamonds disappeared from Magnus' pack if they didn't quite figure out how to get the chalice out of town. I'm really curious to see what happens when they try actually leaving the bubble, because they haven't tried yet. Please forgive my phone formatting! Edit - went apostraphes crazy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-01 04:37:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really want to keep track of the timeline! 11:05 - Griffin has mentioned this in both episodes now, which makes me think something happens at this time, we just haven't heard what it is yet. 11:10 - a couple banadana ruffians come flying out of the Davy Lamp when Ren blasts them out. 11:30 - earthquake o'clock. Shortly thereafter, Roswell goes to Helpington's and Cassidy escapes the jail cell and heads for the quarry. 11:45 - the bank fire 12:00 - destruction of town and death of the heroes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-01 05:09:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Paloma's hint: Imminent destruction comes from below. Before you can learn how to stop it, first you must figure out what you must stop. Turn your eyes to the quarry-- you're not ready to face what awaits you there, but you must know its face.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-02 02:26:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>But the worms they fought were before they got into the time cannon. If you go back to ep 41, they go through woven gultch, then encounter the worms, then get into the time cannon and then Avi blasted into the white space. So if Refuge is stuck in a time loop in the past, where did these worms come from? Why so small now? Are they just babies of the worms under refuge? I also think it's worth noting that Refuge isnt just under a dome-- one of Griffin's initial descriptions of the bubble is that it's speherical. It stands to reason that the bubble extends under the town, likely under the quarry, and i'm betting under the Elder's house.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-06 22:49:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think this happened to me. I had to download it while on wifi to listen with iTunes because it took too much memory to stream it on the fly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-09 06:50:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>My god, it's almost the exact color of the sky!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-13 02:21:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is APS - adult protective services. Also, if the 22 year old can't take care of himself there is a chance he is conserved under the parents in which case the parents are still responsible for him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-14 17:47:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm going to say Yael (a female name of hebrew origin), Emerich, and Osha (like the Game of Thrones character).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-14 18:13:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm into this. However, my change to this theory is that the Giant Purple Worm isn't attacking the town, so much as it's attacking Tres Horny Boys, and each time noon strikes, Tres Horny Boys are in the vicinity of the bank/elder's house which happens to be directly under the Large Hatch where the party has seen the Giant Purple Worm. Tres Horny Boys can see outside he bubble, so likely the GPW can see in too. If this is the case, are they looking THROUGH time? I then think the worm breaking the magic of the bubble is probably what annihilates the town. EDIT: i listened to the ep again and now i'm realizing there are three bubbles in the big room, one inside the opening to the Large Hatch that the GPW breaks through, one in the ceiling, and one around another "airlock"-type door. I still wonder if those bubbles keep time isolated or if they are just a barrier within the time of Refuge.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-15 01:03:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>But they did attack the worms, which I think he was pretty certain they WOULD do. I feel like Griffin knows them well enough to have been able to guess that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-19 16:04:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>IBS is not the same as IBD (ulcerative colitis and Crohn's) does this work for that too? All the articles listed under the article you posted are for IBS.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-22 09:01:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes i agree! In the loop where they encounter the furry bugs in the cart the first time, the earthquake makes Magnus sees smoke which is actually the bugs, and Griffin describes their numbers in the order of billions. Is that many enough to eat the purple worm? Also, there is a barrier covering a hole in the ceiling that allows light through the top of the shaft. Maybe the barrier is there for the benefit of the furry bugs since they don't like light.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-28 18:59:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was thinking rowdy boyz</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-29 04:01:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did anyone else catch when Magnus and Merle were interrogating Cassidy and she says that she and the dead miners found a worm nest that had been cut in half by the bubble? Griffin says, "and then the ma--that that big worm, that big nasty worm woke up and it killed my friends..." What was he going to say there? "And then the Mom"? A few people have speculated that the small purple worms Tres Horny Boys fought at the beginning of the adventure are babies, does this confirm that the giant one is the mama worm?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-11 18:18:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Goddamn it Justin, fucking brilliant play! Garyl was incredible, but Taako's seemingly selfish turn with the gems turning into an attempt to bind Roswell to himself was pure genius-- totally in character in every way. I wonder how long he was waiting to pull that out. Maybe thats why he was so eager to get his hands on diamonds.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-15 04:47:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pricier: Bluetooth enabled sous vide immersion circulator Good kitchen knife Kitchen aid mixer Coffee/espresso machine Big nameled cast iron pot Toaster oven More reasonable: Hot water kettle Vacuum/airtight storage containers Set of mixing bowls Bakeware/stoneware Funnels/ sieves Digital scale Good tongs Servingware (carafes, pitchers, platters, serving utensils, trays) Pasta machine/ pasta attachment(s) for kitchen aid Ethnic-y cooking things you wouldn't know how to get otherwise CONGRATULATIONS!! Edit: thought of more! Cookbooks you really want but are too expensive to justify getting yourself Non-stick pans Deep fryer</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-24 09:24:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>In my head the director is styled after Meryl Streep a-la Devil Wears Prada-- stern and not-to-be-fucked-with. I think you captured that feeling well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-30 03:21:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>How about a really really tender shepherd's pie-- all pieces should be small and swallowable or falling apart. Likewise, stews and braises. All cut down small enough where the bits are tasty but still manageable. Asian noodle soup- just leave out any veg. There're lots if options- ramen, udon, pho-- you can cut the noodles down if you need to. Asian rice porridge- jook, congee, arroz caldo Soft eggs can be fairly manageable and very nutritious. Macaroni and cheese, cooled down, maybe mushier than you might normally prepare it. Pasta and meat sauce-- again ground meat. Also gnocchi cut small and cooked to mush - maybe with pesto?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-30 03:34:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the only reason I'm sure it's not a relic. I'm pretty sure the grand relics are not in the book. ... Or maybe they are. I don't think theyve ever checked to see if the relics are in the book!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-31 04:19:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I get the point you're trying to make-- that the umbra staff isn't a relic. If it wasn't clear, i don't think it's a relic either, but Leon identified the umbra staff, and it didn't come from the machine. So, per the canon, we know that objects that are not only in the machine can be described by the book. Hence, based solely on what we know to be true about the book, it is possible that the relics are in the book. Is this likely? I don't think so, but I don't think we can automatically rule out that the relics AREN'T in the book. And THB haven't asked if they are.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-07 05:20:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I always figured it was due to Magnus' animal handing proficiency.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-10 06:16:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Perfect discussion for The "The Adventure Zone" Zone!! We should suggest that they record that in preparation for paternity leave.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-10 06:56:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really love this podcast. They're not as... PC as The McElroys, to put it mildly, but the players REALLY know the game. Their DM, Sark, is amazingly quick and great at being dynamic and adapting to his players' choices. I think another of his strengths is making failed rolls entertaining and not showing any mercy when bad rolls happen. This results in failed rolls actually adding to the narrative rather than inhibiting play. After listening you can compare Sark's storylines to Griffin's storylines and although I think Griffin is the superior storyteller, Sark is the better DM. Sorry I'll answer the question now. I really love any episodes with Gerry Duggan in it. So the El-Ryan episodes and the Sir Richard of Glinnishmore episodes are my favorites. Gerry has a great way of playing where he tries to stay true to his character and it really pays off. The longest narrative thread with a Gerry character starts at episode 19, but it's hard to know what's going on without listening to the first few episodes. I agree though, the first few are hard to get through. I think it gets easier around ep 9? I will also say, try as I might, I couldn't listen after Sark left around episode 74/75.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-19 08:54:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the British generally call desserts "pudding" whereas Americans use "pudding" specifically to describe dessert with custard-like or creamy consistency.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-25 18:59:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some elderly folks put tennis balls over the feet of their walkers (assistive walking devices) to allow the walkers to slide better. This can make it easier for the person to use.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-20 23:34:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe this is nitpicky, but why feta, rather than cotija?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 08:04:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>tools might be easier to choose than specific types of makeup: - lighted vanity mirror - set of nicer makeup brushes - makeup bag/organizer - an empty palette (to put individual pans of makeup in)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-01 07:18:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>YMMV, but if you're in relatively good health: double dose of multivitamins and 3L (~120oz) of water per day. You can sub 2L of water with your favorite electrolyte beverage but you should still drink 1L of just water. Also, LOTS of sleep.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-08 04:56:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>if you're in the US, you can call 1-800-273-8255 for help or just someone to talk to. edit: outside the US you can check here for other countries' suicide lifelines: http://www.suicide.org/international-suicide-hotlines.html</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-15 19:44:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really loved Nerd Poker!! Did you stop around ep 75? Me too. Regarding The Adventure Zone, each episode is about an hour. Though some may go a little over, they generally stick to an hour. Another great one is the Glass Cannon Podcast. They actually play Pathfinder, but the game is similar enough to D amp;D that you'll understand what is going on. The guys that record GCP are entertaining and really into the game mechanics if that's your thing. Also about 1 hour per episode, again with a few exceptions here and there. It's what I listen to when I've run out of The Adventure Zone episodes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-20 01:18:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>But if there is a medical concern, and you are over 18, you possibly are protected under HIPAA, and she still can't disclose to your family without your permission.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-20 08:12:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>my family's version has lychee and whipped sweetened cream cheese.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-29 20:30:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://loveheylady.com/collections/shoes This company has 3-4 wedge styles. Their shoes have memory foam, supportive arches, and roomy toeboxes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-31 03:15:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>They do have arch support, if you look closely at the photos your can see the molded arch supports in each shoe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-01 23:57:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the next steps right now have mostly been covered. First know your budget. Next try to settle on a date and or venue. Sometimes these three things will affect each other. For example, you may want a venue that is only available a certain weekend, or you may find that you want a specific date so this will automatically rule out certain venues. Alternatively, some venues are cheaper on Sundays or weekdays. You may want a destination wedding which can also help limit the number of guests. You don't need to set your wedding invite list in stone, but it is also a good idea to talk about who you both want there. You may need to rebudget or cut down your list. After that I think it's important that you and your fiance sit down and prioritize your other needs and wants for your wedding so you both know where each of you is able to compromise if it comes down to it. Catering, photography, alcohol, flowers, other decorations, dress, hotel accommodations, bridal party needs, rehearsal dinner, honeymoon, DJ... the list goes on and on. As others have said, you can find all kinds of lists about what you'll need but you should know between the two of you what you think is necessary to have or not have and what you want to splurge or skimp on. As an example, hubby and I splurged on delicious catering and didn't bother with flowers because the church where we had our ceremony was incredibly ornate. We bought a smaller cake for each guest table which also doubled as the centerpiece.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-04 15:24:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>My eureka moment came when I realized EVERYTHING that touches my face makes a difference. I change my pillow case at least once every two weeks, usually once a week. I never put anything on my face without washing my hands and if I accidentally touch something that isn't going on my face while I'm doing my routine I wash again. I use a different towels to dry my face and body after showering. My face towel also dries my hands if I have to wash them before or during my routine. I try to clean all spatulas at the end of my routine by rinsing then swiping clean with alcohol so they're ready to go when I need them again. About every two months, or when I remember, I also give the bottles and tubs for my products a good swipe with alcohol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-07 04:49:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>A bit off topic, but that "Berkeley" school you thought was in California is actually Berklee College of Music in Boston which makes perfect sense as a college choice for Maya. https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Berklee_College_of_Music</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-10 05:19:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love organza!! gorgeous dress, but more importantly, you can tell you feel gorgeous in it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-16 04:23:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>not OP but top to bottom, then left to right: strawberry cheesecake rum raisin uji hojicha (roasted tea) red bean (adzuki bean) sandwich sakura (cherry blossom) green tea melon mascarpone purple yam (ube) shinsu apple strawberry green tea edit: did some more research, I was so intrigued!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-16 19:02:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>nope, purple yam for the top right. filipinos call it ube. the bottom left is red bean sandwich. i did more research.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-17 22:05:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Natalie/Natalia Nyssa Neena Nia Nanette Noemi Noelle/Noel Norah (alternate spelling?) Nidia</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 00:20:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is completely personal preference, but I like Norah. Maybe because the 'h' is a visual cue to give the 'a' sound at the end a little more length? I have no anecdotes and don't highly associate the name with anyone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-28 02:06:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know you're asking for opinions, but far more important than ours is your partner's. If she doesn't want you to go and SHE would be resentful, I think you've got your answer. If you still want my opinion: if she's okay with it, you can make an emergency plan and just stick to it. I think it also matters how complicated this pregnancy has been and if there are any signs that the birth could be complicated. If I were her and my pregnancy was complicated or the doctor let me know that there were ANY signs the baby could be early I would prefer my partner not make plans to travel, even if it's closeby. In this scenario you will want to be there to support her and reassure her so she can focus on the baby, not on where you may be.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 04:51:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>In general they are ranks that may denote levels of experience and in some organizations they can be used to designate the types of tasks a nurse can perform, or roles they can take on. For example, in my organization, RN I's are brand new nurses and we don't hire them. RN IIs tend to have at least 6 months experience and can handle routine nursing tasks and activities. RN IIIs are in a senior position and have recognized increased clinical expertise and also handle some supervisory tasks. However, RN IIIs do not handle managerial tasks-- that would be an RN IV.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 22:34:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>or just "Lil' Deputy"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-04 04:33:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>no one's suggested "We're having fun" ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-05 03:14:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>it looks absolutely ETHEREAL on you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-05 18:43:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are the sleeves actually part of the dress and you slipped them off? As they look in the center photo, it seems like they're slightly bunchy; I can imagine a nosy aunt or someone walking up to you and trying to put the straps back on your shoulders they way they look in this photo. I think with more tailoring it would definitely work. If you decide to go strapless, I like the belt from the third photo, but if you do go with the straps, I would consider the thinner belt from the first photo. Something about the straps plus the belt makes the dress look "bandy" for lack of a better word (maybe because the lace motif isn't carried through the rest of the dress), and I think with a softer off the shoulder look, a more delicate belt is more suiting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-09 06:51:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Amaryllis Camellia Poppy Tansy Jasmine Azalea Willow Hazel</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-11 12:43:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was working on the Disneyland measles outbreaks from a couple years ago, and without giving away identifying info, we found that some of the folks that were identified as our local "source" cases picked up the disease while traveling and being exposed to people who clearly had the disease and were likely unvaccinated. In some of these cases, the patients had clear documentation of vaccination. Their symptoms tended to stray from the "classic" presentation and the disease course was overall milder than one would otherwise predict. So, there was some evidence that the vaccine had provided some protection. As mentioned above, in general, sometimes immunity wanes over time (why we need boosters), and sometimes the vaccine just doesn't "take" for one reason or another. I'm another one of those that needed to get the Hep B series twice for example. If you take the measles example again, measles is extremely infectious but the vaccine has a relatively high effectiveness--95%. But just by sheer numbers, if you think about it, we should be hearing about far more cases of measles each year. If there are 300,000,000 in the US (there are actually more) and we assume hypothetically that ALL are vaccinated, we could still consider at least 15 million (5% of 300 million) people could get measles if exposed to an infection, and yet they didn't, actual prevalence was obviously FAR lower. This has to do with herd immunity as well quick action by public health departments in conjunction with community physicians. If you're concerned about you and your kids' vaccination status, you could always just ask for their antibody titers from your MD. This takes a blood test. Admittedly I don't know what that costs, but it could provide some peace of mind when you have the knowledge that your kids' herd immunity is potentially compromised.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-13 17:14:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>a paper shredder</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-16 21:33:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>bring your pillow, bring a pillowcase for that pillow, chuck the pillowcase after? still thinking about this myself!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 03:58:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Noelle Donata K__ Noelle Donia/Dania/Donya K__ Noelle Dolly K__ Noelle Donella K__ Noelle Donnelly/Donna-Lee/Donna-Leigh K__(or similar variation?) --could lead to a cute nn: "DL"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-25 02:31:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>You really have to be sure your steeping time and temperature are correct for the type of tea you are using. Some teas can steep in hotter water than others, and some teas can steep for longer before getting bitter. If you want a more prominent tea taste, you want to steep a higher concentration of leaves for the same amount of water rather than steeping for longer. In other words, if you wanted to double the strength of the tea taste, you would double the amount of tea rather than doubling the amount of time the tea steeps in the water.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-26 12:00:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>OP said it's feta</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-09 19:51:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>is it lab or labs? edit to address the below reply: do both subreddits also work?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-13 20:28:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>just send him a youtube video of stages of labor or more specifically "early labor" and then if he doesn't change his mind, be very worried. you must not be very far along? or are you are very very mobile right now? edit: found you a couple: https://youtu.be/-Rc6QwFpKMU https://youtu.be/pqhcy2MWaNc also just noticed you're due in may. i've been super mobile up until now (due in two weeks), so maybe that's partially why he's so optimistic as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-13 21:30:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>yes!! i got a kick out of this too! in related news, how are you planning to carry this thing? i've been checking breast pump bags on amazon; it seems like slim pickings for this model, and i'm not into the bag spectra offers. given its closed system it's probably not so crucial if it's stored or transported on its side (didn't see any reference to this in the manual) but i don't want to take any chances.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-13 22:25:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>nice, thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-13 23:30:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>i'll check them out!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-13 23:31:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>i've got a twig and berries coming too! i've also considered a longchamp bag just to throw everything in. maybe i'll take this into closer consideration.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-14 06:31:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is so interesting! I can't believe I missed out on participating. I think it would be so neat to see the difference in sensations as compared to when movement was first felt. As in "women who said they first felt movement in weeks 14-19 most often said it felt like popping". I remember thinking movement felt different between weeks 14-19 than it did weeks 20-25 and then changed even more as the pregnancy progressed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 16:48:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree with the above comments and will add that if you are so inclined, check out Erik Erikson's stages of child psychological development: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Erikson%27s_stages_of_psychosocial_development This first stage during infancy is trust vs mistrust where the child learns about the world. To reiterate, you cannot spoil an infant. Crying is a last resort for a baby if they cannot self soothe, and it's their way of communicating a need to mom and dad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-23 02:33:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I bought a pair of dancing shoes on Amazon (https://smile.amazon.com/dp/B006LXZYH4/ref=cm_sw_r_cp_awdb_qoY0yb4HA801C) because i wanted a wider toe box and straps that were easy to put on and take off; a whole lot of flat back Swarovski hot-fix crystals that already had glue on the back (http://www.crystals2love.com/swarovski-hot-fix-rhinestones/); and a special tool from the local Jo Anns (something like this: http://www.joann.com/darice-crystal-crafter-heat-applicator-wand/1434695.html#q=heat%2Btool amp;start=10). I bedazzled the entire shoe with great results for far less than I would have spent for designer "bedazzled look" shoes. EDIT: here's the finished product after ~1 month: https://imgur.com/a/7nVwm</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-23 04:01:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>added link to photos above, i think</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-23 06:10:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aww thanks! I'm just glad i had a dress that allowed me to show them off. I wouldn't have gone to all the trouble if my dress had been long.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-23 06:12:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's what my husband said too. It was really fun but pretty time intensive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-01 02:53:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I suggest making the name discussion more objective: instead of actual names, see if you can agree on a set of criteria that either "rules in" or "rules out" a name. For example, no gender ambiguous names, must have a cool nickname, not more than 3 syllables, doesn't start with the letter P, no names from the top 10 of last year's census, bonus points for referencing a famous writer, etc. Once you have your criteria you can begin working together to find names that fit all the criteria, rather than you each having your set of favorite names and fighting over which ones you individually like.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-09 20:21:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aldrin Nikola Edison</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 04:03:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>"American Hero John Garrett" :( RIP</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 05:12:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ooo, that makes it a lot easier to believe they could bring a real Tripp and a real Ward (and a real Hope?) out of the framework without then being LMDs. Is this where they're going with it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-28 00:29:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey I'm a voice from the other side, I have PCOS and terrible insulin resistance and I gave birth to a healthy baby boy just about a month ago. FWIW, I'm also an RN. I was consulting with the reproductive endocrinologist in addition to my OB and was basically told "lose weight or you won't have a baby" (much more nicely than that, but I'm paraphrasing). I lost 25 pounds by heavily limiting my carb intake-- pretty much the only carbs I had came from fruits, non-starchy veg, and the occasional milk tea or cheese. I kept up this diet until my glucose test around 28 weeks, and they told me the same thing they've told you. 6 meals, 45 carbs for breakfast, lunch and dinner, and 30 for snacks. I was so confused and honestly pretty indignant-- I was thinking, "I know my body and my body hates carbs!! I lost 25 lbs doing this, what the hell do you know??" It wasn't until an actual certified diabetic educator explained to me that gestational diabetes isn't like regular diabetes that I finally understood. When we're pregnant our placenta starts doing crazy things and makes our insulin resistance worse. Okay so-- our babies are subject to whatever is going on in our bodies, right? They are not advising you to eat carbs for YOU, they are advising you to eat carbs FOR YOUR BABY. Baby needs a STEADY level of carbs to grow properly and if we instead subject baby to large swings in blood sugar levels or deprive baby of carbs, as baby doesn't make their own insulin, and won't have your body to keep a good blood sugar level, at birth baby won't be able to compensate, leading to dangerously low blood sugar levels. It's also worth nothing that 45g of carbs is not a lot of carbs. It's a cup of oatmeal without sugar, or a slice of whole grain bread. It only sounds like a lot because you've cut them out completely. Keep jn mind too, the quality of carbs matter-- some carbs will make your blood level sugar spike, and others are released much more slowly in your system. For myself, my goal for pregnancy was not to gain any net weight. I started obese, lost the 25 lbs mentioned above, and by the time I delivered I had gained the 25 lbs back. Within a week of delivering, the weight dropped off again, it was staggering. I am breastfeeding, but I think it also like to think a lot of that weight really was baby, placenta, and amniotic fluid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-28 18:37:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh no, that sounds super stressful. I'm really sorry. My baby is my first so I can't imagine how much added worry you have with your older child. Believe me though I know how you feel about eating because I got VERY depressed and anxious regarding eating as well. I hated my body and I hated eating and I stopped eating anything for pleasure. It became woefully clear just how much of an emotional crutch food is for me. I decided I needed extra support and began seeing a therapist. Not saying you need to do the same thing but I mention it more to validate your feelings that managing GD and DM is really difficult and multidimensional and there's much more to it than just diet modification. You've already made a lot of changes and seen results. This is an obstacle but it's doable and you know it is because you've already done it! Another diet modification is just an extra little step forward in the AMAZING progress you've already made. But, it doesn't mean that it doesn't SUCK. You can do this!! Feel free to PM me if you want a little extra support. I'm pulling for you mama!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 06:45:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>awesome, your ring AND mani are gorgeous</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 21:01:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like that's how they spelled it in the captions/subtitles. Or maybe it's more mandela effect.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-02 15:19:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought this was the important point because doesn't it constitute entrapment if Chuck was setting Jimmy up to destroy the copy rather than the original?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-07 18:57:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I havent't worked ICU myself but I did adult med surg. I have also been the preceptor for two students and mentored plenty of new staff. Obviously the end goal is 2 patients without assistance, but I don't think starting you off with two patients with minimal assistance is the way to go. Maybe this is your preceptor's first time doing this, but precepting a new nurse should be harder for her, not easier. She is responsible for you AND your assignment, and it's her role to make sure you are gaining confidence and completing your assignment. Is she aware you are a new grad and not transferring from another unit? Did you have a few days to just shadow your preceptor so you could get a feel for the rhythm of the unit? Maybe you will feel better with a more structured orientation. If I were you I would check with your preceptor and make sure you both have clear expectations: what skills and duties does she expect you to know and perform, and by when? Plan this out week by week. Is your preceptor available to assist or is she just watching you do everything and critiquing you? She should be on hand to help out if you feel like you're floundering, and you shouldn't feel bad asking for help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-10 03:32:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>LO is 6 weeks too! The lactation nurse pointed out LO's tongue tie right away and mentioned that clipping it might help his latch and ability to be more efficient with breastfeeding. Three weeks later I'm so glad we had it clipped. He is so much better with breastfeeding and it was easy and relatively painless. The LC's advice for a sleepy baby was to burp and switch back and forth between breasts when LO falls asleep to keep him engaged. Sounds normal though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-10 03:34:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have you tried gripe water? It can help settle their stomach.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-10 04:45:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>well there we go, done feeling sorry for her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-10 04:56:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>yea, not i guess</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-13 08:03:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>After reading your previous post I want to know if your mother's behavior has changed and that is the reason you want to wish her happy mother's day. If her behavior hasn't changed then HELL NO, do not call her for Mother's Day, do not send a card. Mother's Day is for showing your appreciation for everything your mother has done for you. You decided she is not looking out for your best interest and I don't know why you would show her gratitude when this is the case.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-14 12:59:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Approaching 7 weeks! I was depressed and anxious for most of my third trimester and breastfeeding was the thing I decided would be the redeeming element for my early motherhood experience. I had a horrible time breastfeeding those first two weeks. Milk didn't feel like it came in until day 3 or 4 and I cried and cried with worry because I wanted so badly for breastfeeding to work. As many have said, fed is best, so at the suggestion of a pediatrician we did supplemental formula feeds to make sure LO got back up to birthweight. The lactation consultants advised to me pump and express after every feed to encourage more milk production but my nipples were cracked, bleeding and horribly sore. I ended up doing nipple shields with an SNS of my breastmilk plus supplemental formula feeds that my husband would give via the bottle. My baby took forever to feed and had horrible colic so I kept getting caught in the middle of pumping to try and feed LO again. All the while I was beating myself up for not having enough milk and having to "resort" to formula. Per the LC i started fenugreek capsules and ate oatmeal and had milk producing tea everyday. During the third week my lactation consultant thought we should revisit the issue of my baby's tongue-tie which was noticed at his birth but we didn't move to correct until this appointment. We went to the ENT to have his frenulum clipped (relatively painless) and went home feeling hopeful this would result in a turn around. I think it took a couple days for the tongue clipping wound to heal and it took another little while for baby to notice the new freedom of movement of his tongue. The night after the tongue clipping I got mastitis which was awful and its own mini adventure. Meanwhile, I still had to use the nipple shield to allow my nipples to heal, but luckily my healing coincided with his healing tongue. By the time we were both ready to try without the shields LO was sucking much more efficiently and the difference was like night and day. At this time we were still supplementing with formula to allow extra time so I could keep pumping. By week 5 I was still having to retrain LO's latch but I had stopped pumping except once or twice in lieu of feeding on demand, about every 1.5-2.5 hours. However, my nipples were finally healing, my milk production was decent and LO was finally latching and gaining weight faster than previous. I'm now, at 7 weeks out, mostly breastfeeding. The lactation consultants discharged us from their service. DH still does 1-2 formula feeds depending on if he needs "topping off" or just to cover a feed so I can rest. I pump once after he's had his morning feed to see if I can up my production more and still take fenugreek and oatmeal. His latch is good, my nipples are 95% healed, and breastfeeding is (finally) a pleasure. Sorry for the wall of text. I feel accomplished that baby and I both stuck with it. However, if I'd been more accepting of formula I could have saved us both a lot of tears and heartache. TL;DR: Had a bad time breastfeeding at first, needed formula. Corrected tongue-tie resulted in better latch and feeding efficiency. Still using formula to keep baby satiated. Fed is best, but if you are determined to breastfeed, it IS possible to go back! Let me know if you have any questions!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-14 19:18:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>here's a link to get you started: http://m.shop.nordstrom.com/sr?contextualcategoryid=60165729 amp;origin=keywordsearch amp;keyword=blue+lace amp;top=24 What about the dress does your mom like? The blue lace? The boatneck? The see through part at the top? The shape (maybe drop waist fit and flare?)? The sleeves? The length? You may have more luck looking for the features that she likes rather than the specific dress. It's possible that dress could be designer and super exclusive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-14 21:08:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>That first dress is stunning!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-17 07:25:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is Yo-Yo pregnant? Maybe it's my new-mom brain, but it seemed like when they had the camera focused on Mack and Yo-Yo holding hands, the camera wasn't centered on their hands, but on Yo-Yo's stomach. This plus their conversation about how Mack was hoping to share a future with Yo-Yo makes me think Yo-Yo is pregnant.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-17 20:30:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Misread the title as "name is pudding". I think PUDDING is a great name for her!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-20 03:49:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>If anyone wants to revisit the original: https://youtu.be/SUtziaZlDeE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-04 05:59:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Take screen shots and send them to yourself!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ROLL CALL!! Let's discuss which characters will be back next year [SPOILERS FOR SEASON 4]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 20:04:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>With many characters graduating, it feels like we don't have a ton of characters left who are up and coming. Let's establish what year are they so we can see how long they will potentially have left on the show. Bonus points if you can identify what Degrassi stereotype they will fill. Returning students: Lola Frankie Shay Hunter Yael Baaz Vijay Esme??? Saad Abra In related discussion: Degrassi used to be really good about introducing new characters by bringing in background extras and turning them into main cast like (Darcy, Chauntay, Marisol) and introducing younger sibs as freshmen (Danny, Alli, Claire, Maya) Do we have any freshmen? Maybe Abra?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 22:28:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>For some reason I thought Rasha was a senior because she was prom queen, but if she didn't graduate that would likely make her a senior next season too. Jack would be amazing! I wonder if they would go in that direction because it seems like they've taken a lot of stories away from the teachers and introducing Jack would definitely mean Principal Simpson would have to be featured, like when a couple Peter stories required Hatzilakos.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 22:29:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really like Abra too. She seems sassy. I wonder if she'll be more like Goldi or more like Alli in terms of her stories.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 19:10:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>genius!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 00:45:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hold on, the Firefly poster and the print of Wash with dinos in the background-- those were edited in, right? Or am I gonna have to track down and watch this again?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 01:06:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chuck made Jimmy subjectively a good guy. (I think) we love Saul because he's charismatic, not because he's a good guy. Jimmy isn't a good guy either, but the contrast with Chuck helps.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 01:09:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>HA amazing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 03:07:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>out of curiosity, MEE-kuh or MY-kuh?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 03:24:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hero is the name of a female character in Much Ado About Nothing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 21:54:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I totally agree, he's like an RPG-style "lawful good" character to the extreme.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-23 23:21:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just want to chime in. If the deficits are not very severe, it is possible that with the early intervention and lots of practice at home, your little one can catch back up in milestones and be quite normal if not high-functioning. I've seen children "graduate" from these programs so you have nothing to lose by being referred.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-27 09:15:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>my big two: Cosleeping -- he's in bed with me and we both sleep better for it) screen time --this video regularly saves my sanity https://youtube.com/watch?v=wLFjYVN3dIo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-27 15:26:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>hmmm looks like witenry's work.... ah yep!! his instagram is full of his art http://instagram.com/witenry</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-04 03:34:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>West Coast USA - Vee-oh-LET-uh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-04 18:01:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Digital Love - Daft Punk That guitar solo just soars</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-21 09:16:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>aww makes me nostalgic for dinklebot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 22:37:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm intrigued!! What would be in a dessert poutine? Is it bread or cookies instead of potatoes and sweet cheese or cream instead of curds? I'm assuming the gravy gets swapped for chocolate or fruit sauce?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 01:54:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>personally i'll bet on forged :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-30 00:29:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>What would he think about "Elisse" with a double S? It may satisfy his need for cool  amp; unique without being too out there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-03 00:04:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>not even a savory british scone has the same texture of an american biscuit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-04 09:16:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>have you checked out the "glass cannon podcast"? it may help to balance out your need for game mechanics. i listen to TAZ for the story and the boys, and glass cannon for really tight game mechanics (those boys are fun too though). hb</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-05 13:00:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>the shots themselves were fine, but my baby also got a fever that night-- around 102. had to use tylenol around the clock for the entire next day and some of the following day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 08:21:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's also Saint-14!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 22:41:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had gestational diabetes. I won't lie, it sucked and I hated checking my blood and watching my diet-- I wanted the fairytale pregnancy where I was allowed to eat anything and indulge in weird cravings. Alas it was not to be. I followed the diet very closely, told myself it was all about baby, and gave birth to a perfect, healthy, 6 lbs boy. The good news is, about 8 weeks later when I did the follow up test, the diabetes was completely gone. I actually lost weight during the pregnancy (my own, not baby's) and coming out the other side, I'm the healthiest I've been in a long time. Good luck and hang in there!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-15 07:14:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>no one tells you about that GODDAMN FOURTH TRIMESTER. thanks everyone for leaving out the worst part that we might be super surprised when it hits.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 12:55:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great work! Are you also going to add the PS exclusive gear?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 21:53:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure where you currently get glasses but I used to go to a higher end optometrist who sells glasses that come in different sizes to accommodate my wider face. My glasses used to always press on my temples until I started ordering larger frames. Don't want to dissuade you from Lasik though, it is one of the best things I've ever done.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-20 11:15:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg yes WINDIS saved my baby's gassy tummy before he learned how to help burp himself and fart</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-26 00:53:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>36! I started with TNG and in between seasons I watched junior high and degrassi high. Teen Nick showed at least one of the degrassi high movies which was also great. Stopped subscribing to cable tv so I missed out starting when Imogen, Dallas and Cam joined the cast. Not sure how but I was watching again with eclaire #8217;s miscarriage and then stuck with it until new class. Went back and watched previous seasons to figure out more about the characters I missed. glad it #8217;s back on a format I have easy access to!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 23:26:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>my good knitting friend likes to say that nothing is a mistake, it #8217;s just a  #8220;design feature #8221;.  #128516; there are plenty of patterns that will require you to twist your stitches! you #8217;ve just got a leg up on those now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-06 21:43:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes I #8217;m on board with this. Everyone goes to the good place eventually. Some just take longer to get there. So technically, the fact that the top 1% go to the good place after they die isn #8217;t incorrect, those are just the ones that start there. Everyone else has to work for it by reflecting on what they did wrong when they were alive and then correct this. We are now seeing that Tahani is starting to regret how she lived but in this run through Chidi hasn #8217;t accepted it. Makes me wonder what it #8217;s going to take for Jason to realize how he lived was not the most beneficial for himself or those around him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 05:58:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Paris is the name of the prince in Romeo and Juliet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 06:19:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually like India, Oslo, and York. NMS but still fairly useable. I will add to your list of unuseables: Guantanamo Miami Portland - would the nn be Porty? Porto? Anchorage Helsinki Prague Belgium Shibuya PyeongChang My observation is that Asian place names arent great as western names. Fun fact: in the Philippines it #8217;s relatively common to name a daughter Luzviminda after three main Islands, Luzon, Visayas, and Mindanao</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 04:08:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oreo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 18:53:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jason would need to have a set of his Jianyu monk robes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 19:15:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha or maybe a Blake Bortles jersey!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 23:42:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Little guy and i were hanging out on my bed when all of a sudden i notice brown streaks #8212; baby has pooped in the bed. Time to wash the sheets, again. Later, i put him in his play enclosure so I could use the restroom. When I got back I opened the door and sat at the door and motioned for him to crawl to me, and he absolutely refused. He just cried and cried and cried even though the distance was only a couple feet. I almost feel like he would have crawled if I #8217;d been further away, but seeing how close I was, he got increasingly frustrated that I wouldn #8217;t just pick him up. Little goofer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-16 19:33:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>reduces sweat and chafing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 19:07:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>My milk came in very slowly at the beginning and I had a downtime where my cracked nipples were healing and he was learning how to latch after getting his tongue tie clipped. There are supplements you can take, like fenugreek, that will help boost production. If you can, feed on demand or at least every 1.5 hours to make sure your breasts get tons of stimulation. Drink LOTS of water. The extra fluid to produce milk has to come from somewhere, so aim for 3L a day. It #8217;s really hard but you can do it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 05:22:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>are you fatal chemist or fat alchemist?  #129300;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 05:57:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>[wut](http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-C4I67cpex00/UdI4gGUW8iI/AAAAAAAAQVE/urcxTp28rXc/s312/fma.gif)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 02:17:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yona Iva Dawn Renee Dagny Roxane</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 05:46:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn #8217;t enjoy Clint as GM but I thought the Irene/Kardala character was really great and had a lot of potential.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-22 21:40:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, he sounds like the guy from The Wire.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-22 22:28:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have one too. Like it for extended RF, crunch zones, narrowness, and the rigid LATCH mechanism. Fairly easy to install and adjust. It #8217;s also really cute. Downsides are that it #8217;s really heavy, and the fabric is not super breathable and it #8217;s expensive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 07:18:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Breastmilk production works on a positive feedback loop so the more you feed, the more milk you will produce. Feed on demand and empty your breasts as much and as often as possible. Make sure to keep yourself well hydrated. I drank around three liters a day to start. Your body will prioritize self over breastmilk, so if you #8217;re dehydrated you won #8217;t make as much milk.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 07:24:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does power pumping work for you? Power pump at least three days in a row and drink lots of water.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 11:35:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Glass Cannon Podcast has great production quality, amazing role-playing, a good story, and an engaging cast (players and characters). They play Pathfinder, which was originally a D amp;D offshoot, but is now its own game. They #8217;re so good the company that makes Pathfinder made them an official podcast of the game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 20:39:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I promise I #8217;m not trying to be snarky, but what is the full name of Moxie? Or do you mean like one of those random nn that is not at all related to the full name?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 20:58:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Moxie - useable but nms. I feel like this sets up a self fulfilling prophecy of a really tough girl. Actually I think in the 80 #8217;s there was actually a fashion doll a la Barbie named Moxie. Coriander - not useable because of the food association. It #8217;s unfortunate because that aside, the combination of sounds is pretty pleasing to me. I would however definitely use this name for a pet, nn Cory/Cori Karmendi - totally useable. Someone #8217;s already pointed out the makeup artist named Carmindy. Nayda - useable but nms. Although I feel like they #8217;d have a lot of folks mistaking their name for Nadya. Stevia - not useable, again because of the food association. Another name I would use for a pet though. January - useable but nms. The actress has definitely made this name acceptable, so these days it wouldn #8217;t be seen as weird. Cassiopeia - useable, probably the only one I would consider personally using. Darling - Useable but nms. I #8217;m almost certain people from the country my parents are from use this regularly as a name. L.S, Y.Z - not useable as a full name. I love L.S. as a nn though especially since it sounds like Ellis. This reminds me of how when I was mich younger I thought it would be cool to name my kids Kasey Charles (KC) and Katie Teresa (KT) so their nn mimicked their first names. Caliber - I guess so but nms. You could approach it as meaning a  #8220;standard #8221; but it might get associated with guns. Von - useable. Cage - not useable. Too easy to associate with jail/prison Quade - useable but nms Axon - useable. I #8217;m into the science-y names I guess. edit: missed Ranger - useable but nms, only because Hunter is a thing. but I think Hunter is falling out of style because of the violent associations. I suppose Ranger doesnt evoke the same kind of thing though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 00:23:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>TALL-ya or ta-LEE-uh?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 11:34:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most recently, Ron Cephas Jones (William) was in Mr. Robot as Leslie Romero, one of the fsociety members. I think he was also in Luke Cage but I don #8217;t remember the character #8217;s name.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 15:02:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can #8217;t speak much to medications while breastfeeding, but I did benefit from therapy while I was pregnant for anxiety. If you can get it, start therapy. With regards to feeding, whether formula or breastmilk, FED IS BEST!! From personal experience, a lot of pain comes from a bad latch. Initial discomfort is one thing, but cracked nipples could mean something is going on. If you really want to keep going, make an appointment with the lactation nurse and/or contact your local La Leche League chapter. They may be able to diagnose problems with baby #8217;s latch if it #8217;s hurting that bad. My baby had terrible problems latching due to tongue and lip ties. Is it possible your baby has that too? It #8217;s a relatively common problem that can be fixed pretty easily and makes a huge difference in the quality of baby #8217;s feeding. edited to add: through my own breastfeeding journey, i #8217;ve learned that a poor latch can lead to pain, low supply, long feeding times, and more clogged ducts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 23:01:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Been binge watching This Is Us. I think they purposely try to make each episode tear inducing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 15:00:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Going to piggyback here. We won #8217;t advance the profession if we can #8217;t justify our profession and research is how we do that. Without the theoretical component, you don #8217;t have the framework with which to understand how to study the actual practice of nursing. If you #8217;re in an acute care setting or outpatient day clinic, of course none of the theoretical material is going to apply. Of course all of the theory feels like rehash of thing you already know, because that #8217;s the point. To teach and do research on these concepts you #8217;d have to be able to name and manipulate these ideas. As soon as you step outside of direct care and want to do case management, public health, education, research, policy making, or management you need a higher degree. You can #8217;t have ADNs do these activities, In my area of practice the upper management is doing their damndest to phase out nurses in lieu of cheaper, non-licensed personnel because they think the work they do is equivalent. It #8217;s also because there is a nursing shortage because we don #8217;t have anyone to teach. There #8217;s no one to teach because not enough nurses with advanced degrees go into education. The introduction of the ADN was to fill a need for nursing skill, but as a profession we really shot ourselves in the foot because it #8217;s become harder to push nurses into higher education where the REAL nursing shortage is. If we can #8217;t build and maintain a professional knowledge base nursing as a profession will deteriorate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 13:50:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was never going to use this name, but I feel totally bad for Aarons who will forever be A-A-Ron because of Key and Peele: https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=Dd7FixvoKBw#</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 01:18:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to think that #8217;s because all the memories she has of him are childhood (childish?) memories where he is this idealized figure rather than a  #8220;real #8221; fleshed out person. Her memories don #8217;t go beyond a certain point and so she #8217;s unable to imagine him being anything than just there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 22:05:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought this season was great. I would place this after DDs1, JJs1, the first half of LC, and DDs2. As has happened with the other Netflix Marvel shows I think part of the issue people have with JJs2 is the drastic plot shift between the two halves of the season. Particularly in this season, to me there was also a drastic shift in tone and even genre of the season which I think threw a lot of people off. JJ is primarily a psychological detective noir where the background happens to be that powered people are around. This theme was pretty consistent throughout the first half of JJs2 with the IGH investigation. Once the mother was revealed the show turned into a family drama where the background happens to be that powered people are around. I think the tone change was so drastic it threw people off. I think the overall themes of the season are family, rebirth and reform. Hogarth #8217;s arc over the entire season brought her to her lowest place, where her business partners are turning on her, where her body could fail her, to the point where she would rather believe in strangers and false healers than her trusted associates. For better or worse, she realizes she can only trust herself and like a phoenix she  #8220;burns it all down #8221; to start her own company, fearless in the face of her disease. She even appears in an all white outfit as a visual signal that this change has taken place. Trish finally gained the powers she wanted so bad. After realizing what she really wants in life is not the great husband or the great job, she brought herself to the brink of death so she could do what Jessica seems not to want to do and fight crime. She was reborn, for better or worse, after literally  #8220;losing 2 of her 9 lives #8221;. Nice reference btw writers. Malcolm #8217;s rebirth was less dramatic but still significant. After months (years?) of poor treatment by Jessica, Malcolm finally realizes his self worth. He gets himself some new threads and a new haircut and aligns himself with a successful, professional PI firm. I #8217;m not sure what to think of Oscar. He was a reform felon, trying to rebuild his life with his family. Yet he committed crimes to help Jessica and her friends with all the fake IDs. I guess it was to repay the debt of Jessica saving his son, but for someone who didn #8217;t even want police in the building it seems uncharacteristic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 09:44:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>case management public health</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 23:14:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wallis is probably in reference to the American socialite who married into British royalty. She became the Aunt of the current queen. If I heard the name I would assume male, but if I read the name first I would guess female.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 05:37:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>could not unsee Toby</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 22:20:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I definitely think you should invest in a bidet seat or at the vey least a hand shower/sprayer. They #8217;re super easy to install, waaaaaay easier to use, and work better than the peri-bottle especially for your backside. It #8217;s life changing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 22:21:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>start this before you give birth!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 03:34:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ones i hadn #8217;t seen yet #8212; boy: Alder, Flint, Glenn, girl: Daisy, Dahlia, Ana #239;s,</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 23:14:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like the name and I like how it sounds with his brother #8217;s name. The ONLY criticism is he will be August born in May.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 20:27:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to be the woman that people see and go,  #8220;she just had a BABY?! #8221; Mama, you are my goal!! Great job!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 01:58:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>omg  #128161;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 02:02:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>but how do you keep them from rubbing it in their eyes? :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 02:15:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Scully speaks to me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 02:04:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>omg i want to be you! i had a baby 14 months ago and i actually got gestational diabetes week 28. I kept a very strict diet and honestly, while I was pregnant was probably the most physically healthy I #8217;ve been in my adult life. I actually didnt gain any net weight during my pregnancy because I was losing as much of my own weight as i was gaining in baby weight. My mental health was really bad though and between the stress of having an infant, PPD and going back to work, i gained back almost everything I lost. You are such an inspiration. Our numbers and stories are so similar, you give me a lot of hope.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 03:47:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>are you using one of those dish soaps that is supposed to be good for hands? i #8217;ve noticed the smell lingers with those. alternatively, is your sponge or rag mildewy? sometimes that can impart a flavor or smell.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 02:31:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>omg thank you, i know what i #8217;m doing this weekend</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Some musings on the group #8217;s voice work as of Episode 12. Praise and criticisms.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 18:10:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>12 episodes in, here are my initial thoughts and opinions on the group #8217;s voice work, uncoupled from their actual character choices or role playing ability: Troy: Solid as always. I was pleasantly surprised by his portrayal of Gevalask Nor, which sounded like Troy #8217;s standard creepy guy with a more charming affect. Very effective! Matthew: Whether you love or hate his Umlo, I thought it was refreshing that Matthew uses the Umlo voice with a female character and otherwise plays it straight. Contrast this with... Grant: I really want to love this character but I can #8217;t get over the put-on voice Grant uses for her. In these more recent episodes it feels as if he #8217;s toned it down significantly, but it still comes off as a guy thinking of what a  #8220;sexy woman #8221; sounds like. My personal opinion is a more neutral affect but higher voice would be more effective. Ellinor: I have to admit, her old woman voice caught me off guard and I thought it was too forced until I realized she just slightly tweaks a lot of her natural timbre to create the voice for Mac. I think it #8217;s interesting the way Ellinor and consequently Mac significantly alter their voice to reflect her needs at the time i.e. Mac is overly sweet when in negotiations, but when captaining the ship is much more assertive. Joe: I like his android voice, but find it interesting he defaults to a pseudo-British voice when there are instances of American androids. Hal and Data immediately come to mind. It makes me wonder if his idea of an android being cold but courteous translates into British, which is funny for me to think about. Skid: Half of the reason behind this post is because I wanted to praise Matthew and the other half is to discuss Dr. Friss #8217; voice. I love all the work that Skid so obviously put into this voice and I think the added made up slang are super interesting. However, I feel there have been times his accent was bordering on Jar-Jar. I think he #8217;s smoothed it out since the start of the podcast and it sounds much more natural, and actually closer to Jared Harris from The Expanse, Skid #8217;s inspiration. I really like this voice so I hope Dr. Friss doesn #8217;t die soon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 20:11:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>because of Umlo? sorry I was trying to be careful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 20:21:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I apologize! i don #8217;t think i #8217;ve spoiled anything but i #8217;m caught up so i may be too far removed to notice. mods? u/syndactl, i can #8217;t change the title, but i #8217;ve tagged it just in case, can you please make any additional edits?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 22:56:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I #8217;m OP, not the guy you replied to. I don #8217;t have a problem with Grant playing a hot female alien. I just don #8217;t see why that automatically makes you sound like Jessica Rabbit. I mean, given that Barron is a dwarf with a Texas accent in the GCP, Meisyun #8217;s voice just seems a little... obvious? on the nose? Trust me though I #8217;m a fan of the podcast, and again, it #8217;s just my opinion and this is all just meant to illicit discussion. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 00:00:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea, I #8217;m a woman also. Not offended regarding Meisyun, but I think I must be hearing the same thing you are.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 21:23:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>OHHH yes i did hear that. I thought to myself, what #8217;s going on, these guys are more professional than to eat while on mic. That makes a lot more sense knowing it was actually a sound effect.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 06:45:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>That Smitten Kitchen recipe is the one I use too. Chewy and chocolatey, but not overly sweet. Every time I #8217;ve made them I #8217;ve done double batches and it disappears quickly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 18:03:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>A #8217;Goblin O #8217;Bugbear L #8217;Elf M #8217;Dwarf N #8217;Gnome</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 07:09:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>A</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 05:29:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, though to be fair, if I knew dad was Sean (Shawn) first, my eyes would roll less hard. maybe just an eye raise.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 05:33:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Apple</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 06:24:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>full disclosure: i #8217;ve eaten these but i #8217;ve never made them, i #8217;m just a fan who likes to appreciate all y #8217;all #8217;s creativity 1- goat cheese, fig, and honey- creamy, slightly salty, but sweet. like if cheesecake were part of the base but not actually mixed in as chunks, plus fig jam and honey swirled in. had this in seville spain 2- creme caramel almond crunch - if you #8217;ve seen the movie  #8220;up #8221;, it features an ice cream shop based in the suburbs of san francisco and it #8217;s real and has delicious ice cream. swirls of buttery creme caramel and crunchy almond toffee in a vanilla base. 3- pistachio. i had the most delicious, rich, flavorful pistachio gelato in sienna italy. the pistachio flavor was so pronounced and yet the gelato was only slightly green. i can imagine it had to have pistachio butter as part of the base, aside from maybe oils? these are the flavors i want all the other flavors to taste like.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 03:02:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>sometimes I see 3D embellishments and they look completely unwearable, but THIS is AMAZING and i would wear them in a heartbeat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 17:11:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>they have yongmudo which is decidedly not showy and probably the closest you #8217;ll get to bjj without being in bjj. edit: http://www.yongmudo.org/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 00:34:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>also not OP but in addition to the Eminem song I thought it was a portmonteau of stalker-fan</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 19:25:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>looks like you got your answer, but there is a website [Worn on TV](https://wornontv.net/) that archives outfits from TV and shows you where to get them. edit: so nothing from legion is listed there after all. :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 17:37:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>the classic,  #8220;a couple things are gonna happen... #8221; barron #8217;s one-liners all fairaza #8217;s (actually, anyone #8217;s)  #8220;hello, my friends #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 20:51:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh neat, did you train at Cal? When i was active in UCMAP many many years ago it was the Hapkido club. They changed the name a couple times from Hapkido to Hankido to Yongmudo. Part of what you saw was probably tournament style Yongmudo that was developed in the past ten years to provide a scoring structure where there are 4 rounds: kicking and hand strikes a-la tkd; a throwing round like judo; a grappling round; and a free for all round. They do have demo techniques they like to show off on Cal day for the sake of attracting new students, but the majority of techniques are not meant for tournaments or demonstration. The majority of instruction when I was there focused in teaching students to be safe and also introduce them to the various techniques. There are entire weeks on the schedule each devoted to escape techniques, or how to defend multiple attackers, but also throwing, and grappling in addition to strikes. Of course, all of the training must be in the context of being safe, so yes, partners are compliant when you are still on your way to learning techniques. The higher up you go the instructors and other students will adjust to your skill accordingly. Not that the black belts hurt each other, but they are much more rigorous with each other than with the lower ranks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If you lost your iPhone in Golden Gate Park</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 02:49:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you lost your iPhone at the Japanese Tea Garden it is at the front entrance lost and found. edited to add: this was around 17:45 August 4, 2018</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If you lost your iPhone at the Japanese Tea Garden August 4, 2018</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 03:13:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[FOUND] iPhone found in the Japanese Tea Garden August 4, 2018</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 03:24:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 07:39:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>dang, good to know :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 21:44:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sean Kai Claude</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 19:46:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>also on mobile and one of the boxes ended up on a second line for me, ie not next to its filter. If you do implement a drop down, it would be great if there were still an option to search without selecting a type of finish.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 23:34:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, because Cal is a school</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 00:43:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Follow up question: If for example, you trip or are surprised by something, is there a sign language version of swearing when you #8217;re surprised? Super follow up question: When sign language users are medically confused, have dementia, or have mental illnesses, is sign language communication affected in a similar way speech can be? I #8217;m wondering about things like  #8220;word salad #8221; or  #8220;clanging #8221;.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 06:06:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve mentioned this before in another post but Aaron is out. Key and Peele #8217;s famous sketch means Aaron always reads as Ay-Ay-Ron to me now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 01:39:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, that #8217;s really the question I want answered but I thought it might get more exposure here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When sign language users are medically confused, have dementia, or have mental illnesses, is sign language communication affected in a similar way speech can be? I #8217;m wondering about things like  #8220;word salad #8221; or  #8220;clanging #8221;.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:00:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Additionally, in hearing people, things like a stroke can effect your ability to communicate ie is there a difference in manifestation of Broca #8217;s or Wernicke #8217;s aphasia. Is this phenomenon even observed in people who speak with sign language? Follow up: what is the sign language version of muttering under one #8217;s breath? Do sign language users  #8220;talk to themselves #8221; with their hands?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:58:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>So interesting! I figured clanging would still occur, but I was trying to think what that would look like, so thank you for your input. I was assuming it could either be words that look the same on paper that might get signed, but signing words that use similar movements makes much more sense. If you could elaborate more on people who are deaf having auditory hallucinations I would love to know more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 06:24:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for your input! So are you saying that auditory hallucinations might be interpreted by a deaf person as immediately foreign? Might it be easier to identify or diagnose schizophrenia in that instance?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 06:25:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, I #8217;ll check that out, thank you for your contributions!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 06:32:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! That article looks like a good place to start. Do you have any experience with what these manifestations of aphasia physically look like when signed?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>